Chapter 1606 - You Shouldn’t Have Tried to Play Dirty In Front of Me

This distance!

The audience felt their hearts jump. The stalagmites scattered around the cave weren’t arranged densely together. Most of the time, the distance between them was too far to cover in a single jump. Du Ming had chosen two relatively close stalagmites, but it seemed a bit sketchy. Was he going to make it?

Moon Luring Frost fell from the air. It didn’t seem like he would make it. The Samsara fans had already started crying out in alarm. Then, they saw Moon Luring Frost take a step in the air. His foot landed on the stalagmite, and with a push, he was able to bring his entire body over onto it.

Applause!

Even though it had just been a normal jump, that final step made it seem like he had just barely made it. The fans couldn’t help but cheer out of joy.

With a new view of his surroundings, Du Ming quickly looked around, but Boundless Sea was nowhere to be seen. In the meantime, the viewers also took a look, paying attention to any nearby stalagmites. Apart from going back the way he came, it didn’t seem like there was any other stalagmite he could jump to. Moon Luring Frost could take a step in the air, but he couldn’t take two steps, could he?

The normal players could tell that this time, there was no way he could jump to any other stalagmite. However, Du Ming didn’t seem to have noticed. Moon Luring Frost turned and went for a stalagmite that was clearly too far away.

This time, not only did their hearts jump along with Moon Luring Frost’s jump, the crowd went straight for cries of alarm. There was no way he would reach it. He would land in front of it, and his view would then be blocked. Moon Luring Frost faced the stalagmite squarely, showing his determination…

But in the game, jumping power was a number. Determination wouldn’t change anything!

Then, they noticed that although Moon Luring Frost was facing the stalagmite, he was jumping slightly off center.

This is?

The audience able to immediately figure out Du Ming’s goal using their omniscient view of the map. There was a stalactite hanging down from the ceiling. He wanted to jump off this stalactite to make a second jump, which would make it possible for him to reach the intended stalagmite.

That was exactly what happened. Moon Luring Frost went for the stalactite first. He pushed off of it and then jumped gently onto the new stalagmite.

After seeing this jump, the audience immediately started paying attention to the stalactites, realizing that there were actually a lot of them that he could use. This sort of jump might be a bit tricky for normal players to successfully perform, but there was no way a pro player would make a mistake at something as fundamental as this.

With a new view of his surroundings, Du Ming once again looked around, but he still didn’t see Boundless Sea. However, the audience knew that if continued searching, he would find Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea in the next try if he was lucky. By choosing the stalagmite where Boundless Sea was hiding behind, he would end up positioned right above Boundless Sea. Everyone was eager to see this ambush happen, particularly when the one being ambushed was the master of playing dirty.

Du Ming was looking for where to go next. All of the Samsara fans were filled with hope. At this point, the Happy fans were starting to question Fang Rui’s inaction. How was he supposed to win if he just sat there doing nothing?

Du Ming finally picked a stalagmite. The crowd immediately started clapping excitedly.

Not only was Du Ming playing amazing today, his luck was out of this world. There had been four stalagmites that he could have jumped to, and he happened to pick the one that Boundless Sea was hiding at. If that wasn’t luck, what was it?

Jump!

Moon Luring Frost jumped off a stalactite and then landed gently onto his destination. From start to finish, no sound had been made. He could already see Boundless Sea crouching behind the stalagmite.

As if afraid to startle Fang Rui, the stadium suddenly went silent. The Samsara fans seemed to have put themselves in Du Ming’s situation. Du Ming had to be carefully and quietly make his move.

Coming!

Moon Luring Frost stepped off the top of the stalagmite and suddenly dropped down. His sword descended, leaving an arc of pale blue light.

As for Boundless Sea? Everyone quickly looked towards him.

Boundless Sea had moved the moment Moon Luring Frost had taken the step. Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea suddenly got up and stepped away calmly, dodging Moon Luring Frost’s attack.

Boundless Sea slowly turned his head to look at the sword light flashing in front of him.

Du Ming was alarmed.

He didn’t think he had made any noise. He also didn’t see Boundless Sea look up. How had Fang Rui known that he had attacked?

Du Ming’s attack had missed, and now, Fang Rui could take advantage of it to launch an attack of his own. Qi Masters were a powerful mid-ranged class. They were quite threatening at close-range, but not in comparison to the other three Fighter classes. By pulling away, he would be able to effortlessly take advantage of the opening, and there was nowhere for Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost to run to. Boundless Sea had already started gathering qi, ready to attack.

I have to act before I land!

Even though he had no idea how Fang Rui had noticed him, it wasn’t the time to ponder over it. His ambush had failed, and he needed to quickly do something before he got caught by Fang Rui’s counterattack.

He didn’t have many options though. All he could do was try to make it harder for Fang Rui.

As a result, Moon Luring Frost gently twisted his body. His movements needed to be very minute so that it looked natural. He also needed to do it before he landed on the ground.

Du Ming wanted to push off the stalagmite so that he could attack first.

But Moon Luring Frost had only just moved a tiny bit, when Boundless Sea pushed out his palms.

Dragon Wave!

The wave of qi was filled with killing intent. This skill could be controlled after it was shot out. Du Ming could no longer bother with making his movements subtle. Moon Luring Frost straightened his body in a panic and jumped off of the stalagmite!

His gaze was locked onto Boundless Sea. However, Du Ming discovered that he had no way to attack him. All the attacks that he could make were sealed off completely by Dragon Wave.

Everything had been within Fang Rui’s expectations. Could he dodge this Dragon Wave?

Moon Luring Frost didn’t have any place he could jump off of anymore. If he wanted to dodge while in the air, he could only rely on a skill. He saw the Dragon Wave roaring towards Moon Luring Frost. He had to act immediately.

Falling Light Blade!

Sword light flashed. Moon Luring Frost dropped straight down. The Dragon Wave wouldn’t be able to keep up with Falling Light Blade.

But Boundless Sea could…

Noticing that Du Ming had his attention on Dragon Wave, Fang Rui had Boundless Sea rush forward. Dragon Wave? He had abandoned control over it. Boundless Sea gathered a new wave of qi. Not waiting for Moon Luring Frost’s Falling Light Blade to land, he threw the qi at him. Du Ming finally had no options left.

Flash Burst!

Boundless Sea struck Moon Luring Frost with his palm. The Falling Light Blade was interrupted. Qi violently blossomed, sending Moon Luring Frost flying back. Du Ming lost control of his character, and the previous Dragon Wave hit him as well!

Fang Rui had chained these two skills to perform a pincer attack from the front and the back.

The damage dealt by Flash Burst couldn’t be underestimated. Dragon Wave’s effect was annoying. The target hit by it would have decreased attack speed and attack power for a period of time.

Moon Luring Frost flew back to where he came from towards that stalagmite. Boundless Sea didn’t give chase. Instead, he began gathering qi again.

What was coming next?

Sky Piercing Strike!

Boundless Sea pushed out with his two palms. The gathered qi swallowed the airborne Moon Luring Frost. Du Ming couldn’t attend to what was behind or what was in front. The Sky Piercing Strike made Moon Luring Frost crash even harder into the stalagmite.

The force of the impact was quite heavy. Bits of sand broke off from the stalagmite and fell.

Du Ming was stunned. He realized how Fang Rui had noticed him. It turned out that his silent jumping would still give off signs. The stalagmite seemed sturdy, but whenever he landed, bits of sand would shake off from it, which Fang Rui had unexpectedly noticed.

Fang Rui wasn’t nearly as bored as he appeared. He had been very focused. Otherwise, how could he have noticed such a tiny detail? The shaking that he had produced from landing couldn’t compare to when he crashed into the stalagmite due to the Dragon Wave. The bits of sand that fell off would be much smaller, yet Fang Rui had still noticed them.

“Your biggest mistake is playing dirty in front of me.”

A message jumped out in the chat. His words were quite domineering, but when you thought about it more carefully, all of that loftiness seemed to disappear. Wasn’t he basically saying that I’m dirtier than you are?

There was no such thing as appearing imposing when playing dirty, yet Fang Rui had made it sound that way.

Fang Rui… was indeed very dirty!

Chapter 1607 - Everything Hitting

“Yup, you’re dirtier than me,” Du Ming unexpectedly replied back to Fang Rui immediately. He seemed quite eager and quite happy to acknowledge it.

“Fuck! You can’t lose, even if it’s in being dirty!” Lu Boyuan jumped out of his seat. He had been feeling rather unhappy because of his defeat in the group arena. Just when he was feeling particularly sad, he saw Du Ming admitting that he couldn’t compare to his opponent and couldn’t bear it. As for what was being compared, that wasn’t the point.

“Um… well…” Fang Minghua coughed.

“From the way Tang Rou plays, I don’t think she’s very appreciative of people who play dirty,” Jiang Botao said.

“Fang Rui hit him right where it hurts!” Fang Minghua said.

“That’s why he immediately made things clear,” Jiang Botao said.

“If that’s all he’s concerned about, how is he going to win?” Lu Boyuan was very dissatisfied with how Du Ming was letting his emotions affect the match, especially in one as crucial as the finals.

“Don’t worry,” Jiang Botao patted Lu Bouyan’s back, “He’s very focused right now. Even if he’s thinking of Tang Rou, all that will be on his mind is to play his very best. Have trust in him!”

Lu Boyuan still wanted to say something, but when he saw a new development happening on stage, he was able to restrain himself.

After Du Ming replied back to Fang Rui, he immediately counterattacked. There was no dirtiness, only righteousness. He turned to face Boundless Sea, Downwind Sword Slash!

Sword light flew out. Moon Luring Frost had just crashed into a wall after getting hit by Dragon Wave. His entire body was shaking, making it very difficult for him to attack accurately. Even so, Du Ming let out an attack. The Downwind Sword Slash collided with Boundless Sea’s qi.

Blade Masters dealt physical damage, while Qi Masters qi dealt magic damage. Physical against magical. It was much harder to calculate which one had higher priority. Boundless Sea had fired a Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow, a Qi Master Awakening skill. Its might didn’t need to be said. On the other hand, Downwind Sword Slash was a Blade Master skill with very high priority. When the two skills collided, there was no interaction between them. The Downwind Sword Slash moved right past the qi, striking Boundless Sea. The Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow continued its journey forward, hitting Moon Luring Frost.

Hit!

Moon Luring Frost was hit again. Fang Rui had accounted for how far Moon Luring Frost would bounce back after crashing into the stalagmite. His attack had been extremely precise.

However, Fang Rui hadn’t thought that Du Ming would send out an attack of his own in these circumstances. It was a Downwind Sword Slash, too. Unfortunately, Du Ming was just a bit too slow.

Because Moon Luring Frost had been hit by Dragon Wave. His attack speed and attack power had been reduced. As a result, despite beautifully executing the Downwind Sword Slash, it wasn’t as powerful nor as fast as it should have been.

Even so, it wouldn’t be easy for Boundless Sea to dodge it. The execution from Du Ming had been too on point. Fang Rui wouldn’t be able to avoid it unless he used a skill. As a result, instead of dodging, he blocked!

Fang Rui was able to respond in time due to the attack’s slowed speed. Boundless Sea pushed out with his palms. Qi gathered in front of him and then quickly enlarged, forming a Qi Wave Shield.

Pai!

Qi Wave Shield wasn’t a material object. However, when the Downwind Sword Slash hit it, the collision still made a sound. The immaterial Qi Wave Shield was like a material object, and it shattered just like one.

He had blocked it, but Fang Rui still felt a bit of lingering fear from the attack. The Downwind Sword Slash had been slowed because of the Dragon Wave, which gave him enough time to form a Qi Wave Shield. The Downwind Sword Slash had been less powerful as well, which made it just weak enough for his Qi Wave Shield to resist it. If the Downwind Sword Slash had been faster or stronger, Boundless Sea would have taken a huge blow.

Although Boundless Sea was able to block the attack, because he had to deal with it, he wasn’t able to continue his combo on Moon Luring Frost. As a result, one Moon Luring Frost recovered from the strike from Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow, he used Triple Slash to close in onto Boundless Sea.

Qi Masters had close-ranged capabilities, but close combat wasn’t their specialty. Against a Blade Master, who specialized at close combat, most Qi Masters would choose to run away.

But Fang Rui was a dirty Qi Master. He seemed to be the type of person who would avoid these sorts of disadvantaged situations, yet he made a surprising move.

Spiral Qi Kill!

Boundless Sea didn’t retreat. He stood his ground and let out a Spiral Qi Kill!

The spiralling qi instantly enveloped a large area in front of Boundless Sea. Du Ming didn’t go into it. He just happened to be on his third slash of his Triple Slash, so he changed directions and slid past the Spiral Qi Kill. Without pause, he slashed with his sword, using the fastest Blade Master attack possible, the Level 75 skill, Meteor Form!

But this time, before the Meteor Form arrived, it lost its radiance. Moon Luring Frost’s right hand was caught by Boundless Sea’s left hand.

Empty Handed Blade Block!

It wasn’t a Qi Master skill. This was the skill Fang Rui had chosen to put on his weapon.

Every player would take advantage of the extra skill that they had. Because not only was it another tool, it was an unknown to the opponent. When used correctly, its first usage in a fight would always shine. Ye Xiu was able to take advantage of this principle almost limitlessly because of his unspecialized character and his special weapon. He could use a total of 12 different skills for the first time…

Other classes were different. Everyone only had one opportunity, and because the range of possibilities was much smaller compared to an unspecialized, the opponent could sometimes guess what it was. It wasn’t the case today though. Su Mucheng’s Electronic Eye and Lu Boyuan’s Cloud Grasping Fist had been used to great effect on their first use. Su Mucheng had used Electronic Eye to finish off Jiang Botao effortlessly. Lu Boyuan had used Cloud Grasping Fist to successfully close in on Dancing Rain, giving himself the upper hand at the start. Unfortunately, he wasn’t able to convert that advantage into a win.

Now, Fang Rui had chosen Empty-Handed Blade Block, and it too was put to great effect. Fang Rui had predicted that Du Ming would easily dodge his Spiral Qi Kill and had used the Empty-Handed Blade Block in advance, which was how he had been able to block Meteor Form, the Blade Master’s fastest attack.

It was a dismantle skill. Block and then throw. Even if it was only level one, this basic structure would always exist. Boundless Sea blocked the attack and then hit Moon Luring Frost’s stomach.

If this skill was used aggressively enough, the throw would send the opponent flying back. However, Boundless Sea had punched very softly. Moon Luring Frost didn’t move an inch after taking the punch. However, Du Ming’s expression had already changed. Fang Rui had given up on the explosiveness of the throw to minimize the throw effect, so he could follow up with his own class’s offensive moves.

Du Ming had no way of dodging because with the “throw”, Boundless Sea’s hand was already touching his stomach. The difference between Qi Masters and other classes when they attacked was that Qi Masters didn’t need to make any arm or wrist movements to produce a force. Their attacks relied mainly on qi, which flowed from their inner body. Since his hand was already on Moon Luring Frost, he could immediately attack. The qi quickly traveled from his body to his hands far faster than Moon Luring Frost could swing his arms!

Pulse Break: Break Intelligence!

Break Intelligence lowered the opponent’s Intelligence stat, which reduced the opponent’s magic attack power and magic resistance. Qi Masters dealt magic damage. Thus, the purpose of this skill was to drastically lower Moon Luring Frost’s weak magic resistance even further so he could maximize his DPS towards him.

Once the Pulse Break went into effect, the real offense began. It started with a gentle Cloud Pushing Palm, followed by a Spiral Qi Rush. The combo was a very standard one. Not a bit of dirtiness could be seen. For the final blow, he ended with Qigong Blast!

After a standard combo, he finished perfectly with a Level 75 skill. Fang Rui didn’t do anything new with his comboing. He ended it with a reliable Qigong Blast, pouring qi into Moon Luring Frost. The light armor worn by Moon Luring Frost trembled from the violent qi. As his body flew back, blood spurt out from Moon Luring Frost’s mouth.

“Admit it, you can’t beat me not just in dirtiness!” Fang Rui taunted arrogantly. His attacks had been extremely efficient. Apart from the Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow that missed, all of his other attacks had landed on Moon Luring Frost. All of it had taken place within one or two exchanges, yet Moon Luring Frost had already lost 54% of his health. He only had 34% remaining.

As for his Boundless Sea?

Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea hadn’t lost any health. He was at a perfect 100% health.

The entire stadium was dead silent.

That shameless and despicable bastard, who just sat there behind a stalagmite in the beginning, was somehow dominating Du Ming, who was playing incredible today? Du Ming had shown that he was in amazing form during his match against Su Mucheng. No… even in this match, that Downwind Sword Slash showed how well he was playing. Even so, Fang Rui was completely overwhelming him.

Moon Luring Frost climbed onto his feet after getting blown back by the Qigong Blast and immediately counterattacked. A trace of blood still hung from his mouth due to the damage from the qi.

Isn’t he being too impatient?

Has he lost his cool?

It was hard not to think these thoughts seeing Du Ming’s impatience. However, Fang Rui felt a shiver down his spine. He knew best that Du Ming immediately counterattacking was the biggest threat to him right now.

This bastard! He really is playing well today. Fang Rui couldn’t help but admit it.

Chapter 1608 - Too Honest

The comboing onto Moon Luring Frost used up many of the skills Boundless Sea had available. During a combo, both sides needed to pay attention to which skills were used. The side performing the combo wanted to leave as few openings as possible for his opponent to take advantage of. The side being comboed wanted to look for opportunities to break out of the combo.

Fang Rui didn’t get so carried away that he would leave any huge holes for himself after finishing his combo. However, because he had chained together so many skills, he didn’t have many skills left to use and his options were rather limited. If Du Ming counterattacked immediately, Fang Rui would be in greater danger.

Fang Rui clearly felt this danger.

Such a fast counterattack couldn’t have been out of impulse. Du Ming had calmly calculated when exactly his counterattack would be most effective.

Du Ming was playing like he was on fire.

Boundless Sea had appeared righteous and grand just a moment ago. Within the next second, he became the reincarnation of vulgarity. He was rolling all over the ground, fleeing, and hiding, all to run away from Du Ming’s counterattack.

“Du Ming is playing extremely well today,” Ye Xiu once again brought up this point.

“But he’s too honest,” Ye Xiu sighed.

“So?” Chen Guo didn’t understand.

“He lacks variation and finesse,” Ye Xiu explained.

“Finesse as in… playing dirty?” Chen Guo asked.

“You could say that!” Ye Xiu thought about it carefully for a moment before nodding his head.

Du Ming knew the importance of making the first move and counterattacked immediately. But no matter how threatening he may be, Fang Rui had instantly seen through him. If he had mixed it up a bit, he would have made things much more difficult for Fang Rui. Playing dirty required one to pay particular attention towards controlling the pace of a match. The master of playing dirty, Fang Rui, was an expert in this area. Du Ming’s counterattack was too straightforward and honest. Even though he had the initiative, the more time went on, the more feeble he seemed.

Blade Master skills had cooldowns too. Every attempt Du Ming made to land the first blow was making his available skill pool smaller and smaller. On the other hand, Fang Rui was only focused on running away. Boundless Sea occasionally took damage, but he always avoided any critical blows. His skills were gradually coming off cooldown. However, Boundless Sea continued doing whatever he could to run away. There didn’t seem to be any indication that he was planning on counterattacking, and it was making Chen Guo extremely worried.

“Why isn’t he attacking back?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

“Because Du Ming is asking the same question,” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was confused at first, but she figured it out after some thinking. Fang Rui was doing what Du Ming had been lacking previously. He was mixing it up by making Du Ming second-guess himself. It was a way of controlling the tempo. Du Ming felt like Fang Rui was going to start attacking back, but he wasn’t seeing any signs of a counterattack. As a result, Du Ming had no idea what Fang Rui was planning on doing.

It was making him uncertain on what he should be doing. Should he continue attacking? Should he slow down the tempo? Should he let out an opening to bait his opponent?

His heart was wavering, and all of this could be seen from the way his character was moving!

An opening!

An obvious opening appeared in Moon Luring Frost’s offense. Normal players might not have noticed it, but the spectating pro players immediately saw it. But Fang Rui didn’t do anything.

Fang Rui still didn’t act. Boundless Sea was still rolling all over the place.

What is he thinking!! Even the pro players were starting to get restless. As for Du Ming? He had immediately noticed the opening and panicked. In a fluster, he started thinking of how he could bring things back. However, Fang Rui didn’t act on it.

Did he not see it? No way? What is he thinking?

In any case, I really got lucky that he missed the mistake I made. I have to focus. Du Ming thought to himself. Spiral Qi Kill! Whirling qi suddenly appeared in front of Moon Luring Frost.

Fuck!

The reaction from the pro players were even more intense than the normal players. After all, most of the audience hadn’t noticed Du Ming’s mistake, so they didn’t understand how sudden the Spiral Qi Kill was.

It was as if Du Ming had fallen off a cliff and was climbing back up, but during this time, Fang Rui just stood there, not doing anything. Then, as soon as Du Ming climbed up, narrowly escaping death, Fang Rui ran over and pushed him off.

How dirty! How despicable!

“I can’t even watch!” Thunderclap’s Dai Yanqi cried out. Many of the younger pro players nodded their heads in agreement. They were all too inexperienced to deal with Fang Rui’s dirtiness.

The spiralling qi surged. Du Ming had been completely caught off guard, but there was still time to dodge it!

Du Ming’s condition today was godly. He had somehow reacted in time to this surprise attack. Moon Luring Frost stepped to the side, narrowly dodging the Spiral Qi Kill. Just when he was about to counterattack, he suddenly hesitated.

Why does this feel like deja vu? The last time he counterattacked after narrowly dodging a Spiral Qi Kill, hadn’t Fang Rui caught him with an Empty Handed Blade Block?

Some of the more astute and experienced pro players noticed Du Ming’s hesitation and had the same sentiment as Ye Xiu: “He’s too honest…”

Fang Rui had numerous skills that he could have used to attack, but he had specifically chosen to use “Spiral Qi Kill”. His aim was to bring up an unpleasant memory for Du Ming and make him feel a sense of deja vu.

Advance or retreat. The decision needed to be made fast. On the other hand, hesitation was exactly what Fang Rui wanted. The hesitation had only been an instant, but Fang Rui had been waiting for that instant!

Spiral Qi Rush!

It was an attack similar to Spiral Qi Kill. The difference was that Spiral Qi Rush carried the user forward as well, closing the gap created from Moon Luring Frost dodging the Spiral Qi Kill. Du Ming shouldn’t have been hit by it, but he hesitated when he couldn’t hesitate…

Hit!

The spiralling qi wasn’t a quiet one. The moment Moon Luring Frost was hit, ear-piercing screeches sounded from the qi tearing through his light armor. The dirty Qi Master immediately looked bright and radiant again. Skill after skill followed. Wave after wave of qi struck Moon Luring Frost from close and from afar. The qi danced like a dragon, swallowing Moon Luring Frost’s life.

Du Ming refused to give up!

It wasn’t the last round yet. He hadn’t come across the person he wanted to come across. How could he lose here?

Immortal Guides the Way!

Suddenly, Moon Luring Frost swung his sword, splitting apart the roaring qi towards Boundless Sea’s chest. Empty Handed Blade Block? Let’s see it! Du Ming was completely ready for Boundless Sea’s Empty Handed Blade Block. But to his surprise, Boundless Sea’s two arms didn’t rise up. Boundless Sea stuck his chest forward and took a step towards him, prepared to take the blow.

Fuck!

Du Ming cursed. He had been completely focused on the Empty Handed Blade Block, but what came was Reinforced Iron Bones…

I guess that’s it…

Immortal Guide the Way’s knockback had no effect against a Super Armored target. Boundless Sea’s qi wrecked havoc, destroying the last bit of Moon Luring Frost’s health.

Happy’s Fang Rui, won!

Chapter 1609 - Directly Ignored

Fang Rui had obtained an outstanding win. Boundless Sea still had 77% health left. Du Ming left the stage downcast, but he received much applause from the crowd nonetheless. Even though he had lost quite badly, his win against Su Mucheng had been beautiful. His fans wouldn’t be so easy to forget his brilliant performance.

Even so, Du Ming was dejected. After all, apart from winning, he had brought his personal feelings into the match. When he returned to his seat and he received comfort from his teammates, he couldn’t help but glance towards Happy’s seats first.

“There’s no saving him.”

“Might as well sell him to Happy.”

“Haha, I was thinking, when we sell him to Happy, we should do it as a trade for Tang Rou. Wouldn’t that be hilarious?”

It was the finals, and Samsara was behind, but Samsara’s players could still joke around. It had to be said that the team had cultivated a healthy environment of trust and confidence. No matter what situation they were in, they always kept calm. Whether they were in the lead or falling behind, it was all a part of competing. They would face it with a hopeful outlook that they would win in the end.

“It’s my turn.”

Sun Xiang got up. He had a long history with Happy and with Ye Xiu. Two group arenas had passed in the finals. He hadn’t fought against Ye Xiu in either of them, which made his fights somewhat less storied. Right now, he was Samsara’s last player in the group arena. He would need to beat practically two challengers from Happy to win. It wasn’t looking too good for him.

However, Samsara’s fans seemed to be confident in this newly-joined member of theirs as they cheered excitedly for him. Brimming with confidence, Sun Xiang walked towards the stage and waved towards the crowd.

Group arena, deciding round. He would need to beat two opponents to win.

Sun Xiang was clear what situation he was in. Before he entered his player booth, he couldn’t help but look towards Happy’s side, at Tang Rou.

The meaning behind his gaze at Tang Rou was completely different from Du Ming’s. Du Ming had been looking forward to playing with her. On the other hand, Sun Xiang was picking a fight, telling her “I’ll be waiting”. He wasn’t a stranger to Tang Rou’s fiery fighting spirit. Tang Rou was a rookie though, while Sun Xiang was a top God. Challenging a rookie to a fight seemed rather illogical. However, his challenge had another layer of depth to it. He was completely ignoring the 77% health Fang Rui.

Fang Rui was an All-Star player. He was the master of playing dirty. Just in terms of status, he was far more suitable target for Sun Xiang to challenge. However, Sun Xiang was completely ignoring him. In Sun Xiang’s eyes, Fang Rui’s defeat was a foregone conclusion.

The Samsara fans suddenly cheered and clapped even harder.

Everyone on Happy was looking at one another. Their teammate was being disrespected, but when they remembered that the one being disrespected was Fang Rui, who had no idea what was going on, it all seemed rather funny.

“I wish I could tell him,” Su Mucheng said.

“How terrible. Let’s all give him a moment of silence,” Ye Xiu said.

“I kind of don’t want to play in today’s group arena.” These words were quite rare coming from Tang Rou, who longed for a good fight.

“Yeah, that’s what we hope every match,” An Wenyi said. Tang Rou was usually placed as Happy’s last player in the group arena. Her not playing meant that Happy would have at least a 2 point lead. It was an outcome that Happy always hoped for. An Wenyi was saying the truth.

“I always hope that boss can 1v5,” Steamed Bun really worshipped Ye Xiu like he was a god. Even Ye Xiu embarrassed at times.

“Let’s watch Fang Rui play,” Ye Xiu hastily brought the subject back to the match.

The two sides loaded into the map, and the match soon began.

“Surrender!” Fang Rui started trash talking Sun Xiang. Unfortunately, poor Fang Rui didn’t know that to Sun Xiang, he was already a dead man.

“Haha.” Sun Xiang clearly had no interest in talking to a dead man. One Autumn Leaf rushed forward towards the center of the map. And to no surprise, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea was nowhere to be seen.

“Where are you hiding this time?” Sun Xiang asked in the chat.

“In a place where you’re not expecting,” Fang Rui replied.

“Is that so?” Sun Xiang said. One Autumn Leaf looked as if he were taking a casual stroll as he enjoyed his surroundings. He didn’t seem to be in a hurry to find Boundless Sea.

Soon, One Autumn Leaf arrived at a stalagmite. The viewers suddenly felt a sense of deja vu. Before they could recall where the deja vu was coming from, they saw One Autumn Leaf jump, once, twice, thrice, four times.

Four jumps, and One Autumn Leaf stood at the top of a stalagmite.

Everyone suddenly remembered. Wasn’t this what Du Ming did? Was Sun Xiang planning on reenacting the previous fight.

“What’s the meaning of this? Doing the exact same thing? Is he trying to show that he’s better than his teammate?” Chen Guo said disdainfully. Her dislike for Sun Xiang made her even want to fight for justice for Samsara’s players.

“We’ll see,” Ye Xiu didn’t make any hasty conclusions.

Chen Guo curled her lips and continued to watch the map.

One Autumn Leaf took the same route as Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost last round. His jumping was smooth. It seemed like all of Samsara had done practice in this area.

One Autumn Leaf…

Chen Guo always found the name particularly eye-catching. One Autumn Leaf was a character she loved to death. Who knew how many times she had cheered for him. Cheering for him also meant cheering for the player though. The owner of One Autumn Leaf had changed, but it was hard for fans to part with their feelings for the character. Every loyal fan was used to seeing their familiar player and familiar character together on stage. A change in player or character was always painful for them.

One Autumn Leaf had switched owners, and the new owner was particularly irksome, who was also their opponent. It was unbearably uncomfortable for Chen Guo.

She couldn’t say anything about it though because she knew that whatever she felt about One Autumn Leaf couldn’t compare to what Ye Xiu felt.

In the finals of the Challenger League last year against Excellent Era, Ye Xiu had personally fought against One Autumn Leaf. Chen Guo felt her heart go sour just thinking about it. She had even cried a little bit in private. She dreamed of getting One Autumn Leaf over to Happy, so that Ye Xiu would be reunited with him. Even if Ye Xiu wouldn’t be playing him anymore, even if Tang Rou was the one using him, One Autumn Leaf wouldn’t be their opponent at least.

However, One Autumn Leaf ended up going along with the annoying Sun Xiang to Samsara. And once again, One Autumn Leaf had become an obstacle in their path to the finishing line.

One Autumn Leaf!

Chen Guo sword a silent vow. One day, she would definitely bring him over to Happy. Even if they wouldn’t use him, even if he would just remain there as a memory, she really didn’t want to see One Autumn Leaf as their enemy anymore, especially as an enemy to Ye Xiu. But whenever she thought of this point, she felt scared because she knew about Happy’s financial circumstances clearly. Even if Happy was able to gather enough money to buy a top-tier character, it wouldn’t be so easy. Sun Xiang was a young player, and he had integrated himself successfully into Samsara. This champion team wasn’t going to give up an important asset on their team so easily.

Taking back One Autumn Leaf was perhaps a thought for the future. As the team’s boss, Chen Guo had the patience and determination to wait until that day. But Ye Xiu? How much time did he have left as a pro player? Would there be a day where she could see him fight alongside One Autumn Leaf again?

Chen Guo knew that these hopes were small. All she could hope was for them to encounter One Autumn Leaf less often.

At least they didn’t meet each other in the group arena, last round and this round. Chen Guo could only console herself in this way.

One Autumn Leaf jumped nimbly from one stalagmite to another, searching below him. But this time, Fang Rui didn’t copy what he did last time. Boundless Sea didn’t crouch behind a stalagmite, waiting quietly for his opponent to come. Instead, he was constantly switching between hiding places. Even though he had yet to see his opponent, he was playing very cautiously as if his opponent was right beside him.

There was no way Happy’s players could use the stalagmites as cover as well as Samsara’s players, who had practiced with this map. However, the dirty Fang Rui was doing everything to the utmost of his abilities. The broadcast had quite the experience by now, paying close attention to Boundless Sea’s movements. The broadcast zoomed out and looked around from different angles to show the audience how difficult it was to notice Boundless Sea’s movements.

However, this difficulty was constructed on the basis that he was on the same level as his opponent. Sun Xiang was jumping between stalagmites like Du Ming had done previously, but it didn’t seem like Fang Rui had noticed. Boundless Sea continued to scurry stealthily across the ground, but Sun Xiang had finally located him from above.

One Autumn Leaf immediately changed directions towards Boundless Sea. At this moment, One Autumn Leaf was moving towards an area where Moon Luring Frost hadn’t gone to before.

By jumping, One Autumn Leaf moved faster than Boundless Sea. Whenever Fang Rui reached a stalagmite, he would always crouch there for a bit.

Finally, One Autumn Leaf reached him. With a jump, he landed onto a stalagmite behind Boundless Sea.

What?

Fang Rui immediately noticed an abnormality. He realized that something had happened, but he didn’t look above him. Instead, he stuck his head out from behind the stalagmite to look around.

Chapter 1610 - You Wanted Me To See This?

Sun Xiang let out a smile, but this time, no one could see it. One Autumn Leaf didn’t make any unusual movements. He simply leapt downwards.

Everything so far had been going the same as Du Ming’s fight against Fang Rui. The differences began after One Autumn Leaf jumped down.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

One Autumn Leaf crashed down like a meteor. By borrowing the force of gravity alongside Dragon Breaks the Ranks, his fall speed was many times faster than when Moon Luring Frost dropped down!

Such a powerful force was naturally very noticeable, but Fang Rui still didn’t lift his head to look up. Boundless Sea’s movements weren’t as unhurried as before though. He rushed forward, not to pull away, but to circle around the stalagmite.

Boundless Sea circled behind the stalagmite. The fierce One Autumn Leaf seemed to suddenly freeze at this moment. Then, One Autumn Leaf pushed off the stalagmite, placing his spear, Evil Annihilation, horizontally in front of him. It seemed like he planned on changing directions before he touched the ground. However, it seemed like his timing was a bit off. In the end, One Autumn Leaf touched the ground and turned around, but he didn’t make a large enough turn. His body was bent over, and the momentum from Dragon Breaks the Ranks completely vanished. It almost looked like he was plowing the fields.

“Hahaha,” Chen Guo didn’t hold back her laughter, “You wanted me to see this?”

“Well…” Ye Xiu didn’t know what to say.

From Sun Xiang’s actions, if Fang Rui had done the same exact thing as he did last round, no matter how he mixed it up, the Dragon Breaks the Ranks from Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf would be able to deal with it. His extremely technical right-angle turn in midair was truly quite brilliant. It wasn’t something that just anyone could do, and as a result, that made it difficult for the opponent to predict.

Sun Xiang had fully utilized the information that he obtained from his teammate’s fight against Fang Rui. He wasn’t like what Chen Guo thought, using the same exact method to show his teammate that he was better than him. He was using the same method so that he could replicate Fang Rui’s response to it. Since he would know what Fang Rui would do, he could come up with a way to counter it. It was a perfect example of a group arena team strategy, taking advantage of the knowledge gained from previous rounds.

Unfortunately, Fang Rui did something completely different than what he did last round. Boundless Sea circled directly behind the stalagmite. No matter how brilliant his turn was, it was impossible for One Autumn Leaf to circle around the stalagmite so quickly.

Sun Xiang had been caught off guard by it. The surprise made him react slightly too slow, and he ended up faltering on the extremely technical turn in midair. It was why One Autumn Leaf looked like he was a farmer plowing the field right now.

Since he failed to execute the move perfectly, there was a small opening. Boundless Sea circled back and shot out a blast of qi.

Sky Piercing Strike!

The qi flew rapidly, but it missed!

One Autumn Leaf seemed to know that Boundless Sea had attacked from behind him. He jumped up, leaping over the Sky Piercing Strike. Then, he twisted around in midair. Battle magic was already gathering around his spear, Evil Annihilation!

Crash down! Shattering the Lands!

Magic descended and then spread outwards. The surface of the earth swelled and then burst!

The magic condensed and exploded, sending dirt flying violently into the air. Fang Rui knew that the situation wasn’t good and didn’t dare contend against it. Boundless Sea immediately ran away. Sun Xiang had completely put a stop to Fang Rui’s sneak attack. In this instant, Chen Guo hated to admit it, but… she seemed to see a shadow of the former Battle God.

Brandishing his spear, One Autumn Leaf chased after Boundless Sea. As Boundless Sea ran, he would turn his head back to check behind him. He looked like he was in a panic. Soon, he reached another stalagmite and immediately hid behind it.

Sun Xiang didn’t hesitate. One Autumn Leaf rushed towards the stalagmite at a diagonal. The moment you circled around behind a stalagmite, there would be a slight opening. This opening was too small though, and to most people, it wasn’t enough time to respond to a potential sneak attack. However, Sun Xiang had the confidence that he could.

One step!

There was no one behind the stalagmite. Boundless Sea had plans on making a sneak attack. After using the stalagmite to block Sun Xiang’s vision, he continued to scurry away.

Sun Xiang sneered. One Autumn Leaf continued to give chase. However, so far, there hadn’t been any opportunities for One Autumn Leaf to create any Neutral Chasers. As a result, he didn’t have much of an advantage in movement speed, and the two maintained the same distance between each other. Sun Xiang wasn’t in a hurry though. He just needed to keep close enough to Boundless Sea.

He might not catch up, but what about after his Dragon Breaks the Ranks went off cooldown?

Everyone realized it. The broadcast put a special countdown, showing the cooldown on Dragon Breaks the Ranks as if it was Boundless Sea’s death timer.

Chen Guo couldn’t laugh.

Last round, Fang Rui had looked dominant against Du Ming. This round, Sun Xiang was chasing him around as if he were a stray dog.

Is there nothing he can do? Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu understood her intent and answered: “Don’t worry. Fang Rui is still in control.”

“In control?” Chen Guo looked at Boundless Sea. It looked more like he had completely lost control.

“If that’s what Sun Xiang is thinking too, then that’d be great,” Ye Xiu sighed.

“What’s that supposed to mean!” Chen Guo replied.

“Haha…” Ye Xiu pretended like he didn’t know.

“Okay! Dragon Breaks the Ranks is about to be off cooldown!” Pan Lin shouted, “3, 2, 1!!”

Pan Lin soon swallowed his words because Sun Xiang didn’t do like he had imagined, immediately using Dragon Breaks the Ranks once it came off cooldown.

Sun Xiang wasn’t in a hurry. He could see that Fang Rui wasn’t in a panic. Fang Rui was still running away because he hadn’t found any opportunities to counterattack. If he hastily made a move, he might actually be giving Sun Xiang an opening to attack him. A single Dragon Breaks the Ranks wouldn’t be enough to fully close the distance between the two of them.

Sun Xiang had completely ignored Fang Rui and provoked Tang Rou, but that didn’t mean he was underestimating his opponent. From the start, he had used all the knowledge that he had to gain the upper hand. This was more than enough to show that he had respect for his opponent.

Sun Xiang wasn’t as young and naive as when he was captain on Team Conquering Clouds, nor was he as arrogant as when he was on Team Excellent Era. He had matured, using the appropriate behavior to face a match.

Are they just going to keep running until the end?

Seeing that neither side was doing anything apart from running, the viewers couldn’t help but be puzzled. The finals was a grand stage to be on. It couldn’t just end up being a contest of who was better at controlling their stamina, could it? That would be too boring.

Even though that was what most people were thinking, there really didn’t seem to be anything apart from stamina consumption that would change the situation. The broadcast showed the stamina bars on the two characters, which was extremely rare to see in a pro match.

“It seems like Boundless Sea will last longer?” Pan Lin said.

“I doubt either side will have any problems controlling their stamina properly. However, there’s an inherent disparity between their classes. Even though One Autumn Leaf has a bit more stamina, Qi Masters consume stamina slower. It’s probably designed that way to show how the circulation of qi allows Qi Masters to more efficiently utilize their energy!” Li Yibo said.

“No one really cares usually though, no?” Pan Lin said.

“But right now… it’s very important,” Li Yibo refuted.

“To think he would take advantage of such a small detail, no wonder he’s Fang Rui…” Pan Lin said.

“Yes.”

“So he’ll have a bit more stamina to use, which he can use to run a bit faster and move farther away from Sun Xiang. And after that?” Pan Lin said.

“After that he can use it to find an opportunity to counterattack…” Li Yibo struggled to explain. Pan Lin felt that it was a pretty unlikely justification as well. Such precise calculations, requiring perfect execution over a long period of time, all so he could get a bit farther away from his opponent. That didn’t seem very logical.

Some words weren’t meant to be said out loud, but in their hearts, they were thinking the same thing: I’ve already taken off my pants, and you want me to see this?

Once the race was over, it would just start again. This sort of development was too boring to watch. Pan Lin and Li Yibo had no way to hype things up. Stopping people from dozing off was the best they could do.

“One Autumn Leaf is out of stamina,” Pan Lin said listlessly.

“Yeah,” Li Yibo replied listlessly.

“Fang Rui should know, right?”

“He should know!”

“Do you think Sun Xiang has any ideas?” Pan Lin said.

“If he had any ideas, wouldn’t he have used them by now?” Li Yibo answered.

“True…”

“He’s out.”

“Yup.”

“So now…”

“Dragon Breaks the Ranks, fuck!!!” Pan Lin shouted. He couldn’t help but curse, and he hadn’t noticed it all. He was completely astonished. He hadn’t expected it at all. To think Sun Xiang would choose to use Dragon Breaks the Ranks once his stamina ran out.

It was truly surprising. Fang Rui must not have expected it either. That arrogant Sun Xiang was exceptionally calm. It was truly surprising.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

One Autumn Leaf rushed forward, and this skill’s speed was far faster than a sprint. But there was a bit of distance between them. Dragon Breaks the Ranks would take some time to close the distance, and that was where the issue lay. But who would expect a Dragon Breaks the Ranks at this moment? A slight hesitation may result in Fang Rui not being able to react in time.

But Fang Rui didn’t hesitate. He had unexpectedly thought of the Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

Boundless Sea moved horizontally, successfully dodging the Dragon Breaks the Ranks. Then, he responded with a Spiral Qi Rush. However, One Autumn Leaf didn’t immediately stop after Dragon Breaks the Ranks missed, like Fang Rui had expected. One Autumn Leaf continued right past him. As a result, the two seemed to swap places. One Autumn Leaf wasn’t able to close the distance, but Fang Rui wasn’t able to get his counterattack. However, Qi Masters were experts at mid-range. The skills that he had in mind couldn’t be used because of the distance they were at, but he had many others skills he could use.

Qi Blade!

The attack was inherently difficult to see. With Fang Rui’s sneaky methods, people who weren’t paying close enough attention probably didn’t even think Boundless Sea did anything.

The Qi Blade flew out. Boundless Sea’s palms continued to gather qi for the next skill. One Autumn Leaf had turned around, brandishing his spear, but he couldn’t make any attacks because of the distance. Suddenly, his body flickered. A trace of magic was all that remained in his original position. One Autumn Leaf had disappeared.

Teleport! The skill that One Autumn Leaf put on his weapon today was Teleport.

The first time using a bonus skill on a weapon would always be a surprise, but Teleport was a very common Mage skill that people chose. Even when it was spread to all classes, Teleport was the most commonly chosen skill. No other superclass had a skill that was so beloved by everyone.

Even if the Teleport distance was rather small at level one, it was an extremely versatile skill that could be used to escape or to attack.

Was Fang Rui caught off guard by this sudden change?

Chapter 1611 - Unable to Play Dirty

The sudden Teleport surprised quite a few of the viewers. But to a pro player, Teleportat was pretty much considered a required skill for Mages. Thinking about it more closely though, since One Autumn Leaf had Teleport, he could have easily combined it with the burst of speed that Dragon Breaks the Ranks provided and chased Fang Rui down. It didn’t seem at all necessary to save it and use it at the last second. So did that mean he didn’t use it just to as a set-up, a set-up where Fang Rui mistook his skill build to not have Teleport, and thus lure him to let his guard down against it?

A normal player would not have given a second thought after observing this move. But to a pro player, there was often a deeper layer to things.

A competition of endurance?

From the start, this was only in the eyes of the average viewer. None of the pro players considered it to be that simple. It would be looking down on them if you expected a pro player to make a basic blunder like this.

Up until they saw this Teleport!

This skill has lost its element of surprise because too many players added it on their weapons. However, in this situation, it had gained a brand new element of surprise. Many spectators felt a whole new level of respect for Sun Xiang.

Everyone who had played against Sun Xiang, and even those who once called him teammate, clearly felt changes from him. Had he been enlightened during his time at Excellent Era? Had he learned during his time at Samsara? Perhaps both? Whatever it may be, this new generation player did his utmost to continually move towards perfection.

Nice Teleport!

The spectators all praised to themselves. Because Teleport could only be level one, One Autumn Leaf could only move so far with it. But this Teleport finally put One Autumn Leaf directly beside Boundless Sea.

Sky Strike!

One Autumn Leaf used the fastest skill in the Battle Mage’s arsenal. Evil Annihilation was thrust out the exact same moment that his body appeared.

Roll!

Boundless Sea rolled sideways.

“He dodged it!” Pan Lin cried out in shock. The pro players also all felt that it was odd. Such an unexpected Teleport and such an unexpected attack. Yet Fang Rui managed to react to it?

“The fact that he could react proves he was still prepared!” The statement came from Ruan Yongbin, the Cleric player from Wind Howl, Fang Rui’s former teammate. He clearly had a good understanding of Fang Rui.

“We gotta give it to the king of dirty plays. He always expects his opponent to have the worst intentions eh?” Misty Rain’s Li Hua said.

This didn’t sound much like praise, but it was spot on.

Everyone watching felt like if they put themselves in Fang Rui’s shoes, they would have let their guard down against Teleport after seeing Sun Xiang’s plays. However, Fang Rui himself was still on guard against it, and that could only be because of his personality and playstyle.

Sky Strike missed, but Sun Xiang didn’t look like he was going to be discouraged this easily. At least he had an opportunity right now and was in close range; One Autumn Leaf unleashed another attack straight away.

Draconic Crusher!

Evil Annihilation, which was swung up from the Sky Strike, crashed down and unleashed a Draconic Crusher.

This skill had a knockdown effect and had extremely high priority. It was not possible to answer it with another skill. Boundless Sea had no time to get up after dodging the Sky Strike, and had to quickly roll again.

The magical energies of Draconic Crusher bombarded the ground and immediately smashed out a small crater in the ground. Evil Annihilation shot up once again, not giving Fang Rui any time to catch his breath. Dragon Tooth!

Boundless Sea used the momentum from the roll to take a sideways step. He barely managed to dodge and at the same time, slapped out a palm.

Cloud Pushing Palm!

A low level Qi Master skill. This tiny window was nowhere enough for Boundless Sea to even think about using a strong skill with cast time. He could only use a quick, weak skill to try to disrupt his opponent’s relentless attacks. Cloud Pushing Palm had low damage but also had a knock-back effect. This was a natural skill choice for Boundless Sea in his current predicament, who needed to create some space for himself.

Circle Swing!

He didn’t expect One Autumn Leaf to not dodge and instead directly use this skill. The grab effect of Circle Swing would send him crashing into the ground. Even though Boundless Sea’s Cloud Pushing Palm would still land and send One Autumn Leaf backwards, it was still unfavorable for him.

Helpless, Fang Rui could only abandon his attack. Boundless Sea flipped backwards to dodge again. But he didn’t expect Boundless Sea to not respond to his input. When Fang Rui suddenly realised why, Evil Annihilation had already pierced his chest, and flicked him skyward.

“What happened?”

The normal players saw it as a whiffed dodge, resulting in him being hit. But in the pro players’ eyes, not dodging this attack was inexcusable. Something unexpected must have occurred to cause it.

“Boundless Sea ran out of stamina!!” Someone realized it and yelled it out, no one knew who.

Everyone started. Then their minds were blown. They realised that the answer to their speculation over Sun Xian’s intentions were far simpler than they thought.

Sun Xiang was not trying to set up for a successful Teleport earlier. His main ploy was to whittle away Fang Rui’s stamina.

Because of Fang Rui’s playstyle!

A dirty playstyle meant the player will never seek direct confrontation with his opponent. He would use all sorts of tricks to gain a slight advantage by avoiding bad positions and moving into good ones, meaning a lot of movement would be used. Sprints, rolls, jumps, these common movements are all stamina-hungry. The vast majority would never feel that their stamina limited their movements, except for when they sprinted without a break. These movements were seldom used so frequently that they caught up to stamina recovery.

Fang Rui’s dirty playstyle would use these movements far more frequently than a normal player. Even so, his stamina had never limited his play. Stamina recovery was very quick, and it was usually more than enough to handle Fang Rui’s pace of play.

But in today’s match, Sun Xiang and Fang Rui participated in a chase that wore down his stamina. Battle Mages had slightly more stamina, but Qi Masters spent slightly less. In the end, it was One Autumn Leaf who ran out first. Thus, Sun Xiang launched his attacks at that moment. Dragon Breaks the Ranks and Teleportation were used in succession to let him get within melee range. Even though he didn’t hit Boundless Sea, he managed to seize the initiative.

Thus began the close combat attacks. Fang Rui dodged continuously, naturally using the dirty playstyle that he was so used to. After consecutive rolls and sprints, he managed to wear down all of One Autumn Leaf’s stamina, while not having much left himself. As the Circle Swing came, Fang Rui had Boundless Sea forcefully cancel Cloud Pushing Palm.

A forced cancel was an action that expended stamina. Here, it finally depleted Boundless Sea’s stamina. The next roll that was meant to dodge Circle Swing had not been executed because he was out of stamina.

Stamina!

Stamina, which seemed to never run out in a real battle, was depleted by this intense pursuit. The high paced battle that followed meant that his stamina could no longer sustain Fang Rui’s dirty playstyle.

If you were to say before that what everyone felt in Sun Xiang was a sense of growth, you could say that now that what everyone felt in Sun Xiang was a sense of formidability.

He was no longer the kind to rely purely on superior technique and skill to overwhelm his opponent. He had started observing and analyzing his opponents. Fang Rui’s dirty playstyle had brought years of misery and headaches to many pro players. But today, Sun Xiang actually found a way to completely suppress him.

Even though stamina recovered quickly, Fang Rui’s dirty playstyle also expended it quickly. When his stamina bar was near zero, the recovery really wasn’t enough. Sun Xiang just needed to maintain a tight offensive to make Fang Rui constantly feel his stamina deficiency.

Slam!

Boundless Sea crashed into the ground after being swung around by Circle Swing. In these few moments, the pro players have already finished analysing Fang Rui’s predicament. The players who used to be on the receiving end of his dirty playstyle were getting a healthy dose of schadenfreude right now. When the dirty playing Fang Rui couldn’t play dirty, then what would he do? Everyone was about to find out.

Tyrant’s Destruction!

One Autumn Leaf once again swept Evil Annihilation at Boundless Sea, who was currently flat on the ground. Boundless Sea rolled to dodge. Again, he used what little stamina had recovered in the last few moments.

Dragon Tooth!

Another attack followed closely. If it was the regular Fang Rui, he would roll once to dodge, and roll again to end up on One Autumn Leaf’s flank. But right now, he couldn’t even roll consecutively. Boundless Sea’s stamina bar flashed repeatedly as if someone installed a red blinker light under it.

Chapter 1612 - One Second Sandbag

Sky Strike!

Dragon Tooth followed by Sky Strike, a plain and simple Battle Mage combo. Sun Xiang didn't do anything fancy after sealing shut Fang Rui's dirty methods. He used this ordinary but very effective combo to knock Boundless Sea into the air.

Seeing Boundless Sea launched tumbling into the air, Fang Rui's heart turned ice-cold.

Stamina...

He had indeed overlooked this aspect. His playstyle was quite stamina-heavy, but over his six years of pro play, stamina had never been an issue for him. If you had no mana, you couldn't do anything. If you had no health, you would be dead. If you had no stamina, you just had to wait a bit for it to recover.

It had always been this way.

So it couldn't be said that Fang Rui had been careless. He had never thought that stamina would ever be an issue. However, in today's match, he hadn't been paying attention, while his opponent had. The issue of stamina now limited what he could do.　　

Sun Xiang...

Fang Rui never had any rivalries with Sun Xiang. In Season 7, Sun Xiang had just been a rookie. In Season 8, he had joined Excellent Era midseason and then was relegated alongside them. In Season 9, he had been in the Challenger League. Sun Xiang had never been a player that Fang Rui had particularly cared about. To Fang Rui, Sun Xiang was just another player competing in the pro scene.

Up until this season. Fang Rui's professional career suddenly took a huge turn, and Sun Xiang brought One Autumn Leaf with him to Samsara. Because of the complicated relationship between Happy, Excellent Era, Ye Xiu, One Autumn Leaf, and so on, Sun Xiang became a rather special existence to Happy.　　

Apart from him, the rest of Happy had played in the Challenger League. At that time, Su Mucheng had been Happy's enemy as well, but her relationship with Sun Xiang had always been quite unpleasant. Fang Rui quickly got along with the team. As a result, there was no way he would have a good impression of Sun Xiang. What's more, the two had fought 1v1 in the regular season, and at that time, he had lost to Sun Xiang.

Their next encounter was today in the finals. Happy had lost the first game. If they lost the second game, their run would be over.

Fang Rui beat Du Ming, and he knew that his next opponent would be Sun Xiang. He didn't care who his opponent was. He would beat him. Happy still had a player left, but that didn't weaken his resolve. If he won, Happy would go into the team competition with a two point lead. As the away team, this two point lead would be very precious. Fang Rui had performed rather mediocre throughout the playoffs, and he really wanted to be useful to Happy. Starting from the previous round against Du Ming, he had been determined to win Happy this two point lead.

But right now, Sun Xiang was suppressing him, using such an ordinary combo to send Boundless Sea spinning into the air.　

What am I doing?

Fang Rui was angry, not at Sun Xiang, but himself.　　

Stamina had never been a problem for him before, so he had never considered that it could ever be one. Fang Rui was furious at himself for being so careless.

But I haven't lost yet.

He may be out of stamina, but stamina recovered quickly. It didn't matter if he was taking damage. As long as he didn't do anything that required stamina, it would continue to recover.

Fang Rui stared closely at Boundless Sea's stamina bar.

His health was dropping, but he couldn't care about that right now. What he needed was stamina, only stamina!

His stamina was recovering bit by bit. Fang Rui felt like it was recovering at a snail's pace. In the past, he had never felt like he had to wait so long for his stamina to recover.

How much stamina do I need?

Fang Rui was calculating in his mind, when Boundless Sea suddenly dropped down.

He stopped the combo?

Everyone was astonished. One Autumn Leaf's comboing had been perfect. He could have easily continued it. Why did he suddenly stop?

A mistake? The people who thought that felt surprised because it would be a very low-level mistake.

Boundless Sea fell towards the ground. Out of reflex, Fang Rui did a Quick Recover, but just when he was about to act, he stopped himself.　　

So that's it!

Fang Rui instantly figured out what Sun Xiang's motive was. Sun Xiang had intentionally broke off his combo because he wanted to keep him at zero stamina. Juggling Boundless Sea in the air wouldn't be enough to kill him. During this time, Boundless Sea would recover stamina, which would let Fang Rui respond and counterattack.

As soon as Boundless Sea's stamina recovered just a little bit, Sun Xiang intentionally stopped his combo to give Fang Rui an opening to react and use up what little stamina he had.

Boundless Sea crashed to the ground.

Quick Recover?

Usually, that was the right call, but if Boundless Sea used Quick Recover to get up, One Autumn Leaf would certainly be ready for him. Fang Rui's usual methods required stamina, and he would quickly exhaust what stamina he had left. Once his stamina was gone, he would once again be in a passive state. Then, once his stamina recovered a bit, Sun Xiang would give out another opening, so he would use up his stamina. The cycle would just repeat endlessly until he died.

I can't let that happen. I have to recover enough stamina before I act, even if it means I take more damage!

Bang!

Fang Rui didn't Quick Recover, and Boundless Sea fell straight to the ground.　

Sun Xiang immediately grasped Fang Rui's intentions. He couldn't force Fang Rui into action. If Fang Rui insisted on trading his health for stamina, then he could only oblige and deal as much damage to him as possible.

Tyrant's Destruction!

Evil Annihilation swept towards Boundless Sea.

The people who had figured out both side's goals thought that what came next would be a one-sided beatdown. The Happy fans couldn't help bear to watch.

But Evil Annihilation missed. Boundless Sea suddenly rolled, dodging the Tyrant's Destruction.

He was using what little stamina he had left? What is he thinking?

What is he thinking?

The people who thought they understood were now completely puzzled again.　

If Fang Rui hadn't noticed Sun Xiang's goal, then he would have Quick Recovered before. If he had noticed, then he shouldn't be using his stamina, instead trading his health for it.

And where was he rolling to? What is he trying to do?

No one understood. Sun Xiang didn't either. He had already been ready to treat Boundless Sea like a wooden stump, a sandbag. He was planning on using everything he had to deal as much damage as possible within a short period of time. But Fang Rui unexpectedly moved. Boundless Sea rolled away to dodge One Autumn Leaf's Tyrant's Destruction.

What's the meaning of this?

Sun Xiang didn't understand either. But since Fang Rui made a move, he should force him to use up his stamina and pull him into a cycle of death.

Then...

Then what?　　

Sun Xiang suddenly blanked. He discovered a problem. After the Tyrant's Destruction, any other attack he made seemed awkward. It seemed as if no skill he chose would be able to perfectly accomplish his goal.

Sun Xiang figured it out. After seeing the ending lag from One Autumn Leaf using Tyrant's Destruction, the pro players also figured it out.

Fang Rui, that bastard was too dirty!

Everyone thought that his only choice was to trade his health for stamina. Sure, so he pretended like that was his plan. Boundless Sea crashed into the ground like a sandbag. However, this sandbag wasn't an obedient one. Sun Xiang was determined to give this sandbag a fierce beating, but when he attacked, the sandbag suddenly dodged.

When attacking a defenseless sandbag, what mattered was dealing as much damage as possible. There was no need for defense or for combos. But Fang Rui wasn't a defenseless sandbag, which meant that you needed to make adjustments depending on the situation. Attacking Fang Rui and attacking a sandbag were two entirely different things.

Fang Rui had Boundless Sea pretend to be a sandbag. For a second, he displayed his dirtiness. Sun Xiang saw that his target was a sandbag, but in the next instant, his target became a dirty Fang Rui. Attacking Fang Rui required a completely different mindset than attacking a sandbag. Sun Xiang needed to make the switch, but he wasn't ready for it. The fluidness of his offense instantly vanished.

Fang Rui was waiting for this moment, and it was more than enough for him to turn things around. Even if Boundless Sea didn't have enough stamina, what he needed to do next was to use attacks that didn't require stamina.

Spiral Qi Kill!

He had narrowly escaped from a crisis. Recover stamina? That wasn't the goal. Fang Rui only had one goal: to win! Whether he had stamina or not, he needed to win!

Chapter 1613 - Forever Dirty

Air and qi whirled together and blasted towards One Autumn Leaf.

Sun Xiang realized that he had been wrong. He had thought too little of Fang Rui. Whether it was thinking of him as a sandbag or attempting to force Boundless Sea to use mana, he had completely overlooked the possibility that Fang Rui could counterattack.

After his Tyrant’s Destruction was dodged, he lost control of the tempo. Immediately switching to a defensive stance would be his best option, but he had forgotten that Fang Rui could be an offensive threat. Boundless Sea didn’t have any stamina, but that didn’t mean his skills were all on cooldown.

Spiral Qi Kill!

Not a single bit of qi was wasted. All of it struck One Autumn Leaf’s chest. The powerful twisting force of the qi warped One Autumn Leaf’s leather armor.

Team Happy’s characters couldn’t compare to characters on other teams, especially those on top teams. Even Lord Grim was no exception. It was mainly his transforming weapon and unspecialized that made things troublesome. In terms of actual stats, Lord Grim had no class advancement bonuses or armor proficiencies. His stats didn’t come close to the stats on other pro characters.

Happy only had two characters that could compete with characters on other top teams.

One of them was Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain. When the level cap was raised to Level 75, Excellent Era hadn’t given Dancing Rain their full support. However, after transferring to Happy, that gap was quickly mended. For one, the leader of Happy’s R&D team, Guan Rongfei, had come from Excellent Era, so he was already very familiar with Dancing Rain. In addition, while Happy’s low-end material reserves couldn’t compare to other top guilds, they had accumulated quite a lot of high-end materials during Ye Xiu’s time playing in the game.

Dancing Rain’s equipment was upgraded from Level 70 to Level 75, and most of the materials were Level 75 materials. Everyone had started the race for these materials at the same time. During this race, not only did Happy not fall behind, due to Ye Xiu’s participation in the race, Happy had a significant lead over the other guilds.

Dancing Rain’s strength quickly caught up to the other top characters. As for Happy’s other strong character, that would be Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea.

Boundless Sea had been Glory’s number one Qi Master. Even if the character had been in the low-tier Team Seaside, the team had poured in all of their resources to maintain this title of number one. In Season 9, Zhao Yang announced his retirement. For Team Seaside, maintaining this number one title became their team’s burden. As a result, the team gave up on Boundless Sea and sold it to Happy.

Boundless Sea had been number one when the level cap had been 70. Once the level cap was raised to 75, he had the same advantage as Dancing Rain. Happy didn’t lose to any of the powerhouse clubs in Level 75 materials. Although Guan Rongfei had never touched Boundless Sea’s equipment before, a Qi Master had been a main part of Excellent Era’s force for many years. Thus, Guan Rongfei was no stranger to this class. Boundless Sea just wasn’t as convenient for him to upgrade as Dancing Rain.

Boundless Sea’s equipment was soon upgraded to Level 75, and the character kept the title of Glory’s number one Qi Master. The only problem was that his new owner was Fang Rui, who had switched classes from Thief to Qi Master. This new dirty Qi Master playstyle was very unconventional. For a time, neither Qi Master players nor Fang Rui fans liked it. Boundless Sea falling out from the All-Star roster was unrelated to its stats.

Boundless Sea was not weak, not even close. This was another big reason for why Fang Rui was very concerned with his performance in the playoffs.

He was Happy’s highest-paid player, and he possessed one of Happy’s strongest characters. But his performance in the playoffs was only so-so. He felt like he wasn’t living up to his pay or his character.

I have to win!

Fang Rui’s desire to win had never been stronger.

The powerful Boundless Sea fired an enormous blast of qi towards One Autumn Leaf, towards the Battle God. At its peak, the Battle God had stood at the top of Glory, overlooking everyone else.

Go!

The whirling qi scattered. One Autumn Leaf’s leather armor looked as if it was about to warp. The hair on his head rippled from the intense winds.

Spiral Qi Kill. Depending on how the qi was used, the attack would have different effects. If the qi rotated clockwise, it would send the target flying. If the qi rotate counterclockwise, it would suck in the target.

The spiralling qi was whirling counterclockwise. Fang Rui didn’t want to send One Autumn Leaf flying away, because he wanted to win! Boundless Sea had enough stamina now, but he didn’t need it. He just needed to get close and attack with all his might, pouring out as much qi as possible into One Autumn Leaf.

The spinning force from Spiral Qi Kill locked One Autumn Leaf into place. As soon as it dispersed, Boundless Sea fired out another blast of qi with his other hand.

Flash Burst!

Another powerful attack. The qi violently surged around One Autumn Leaf as if it were trying to rip him apart.

Taking advantage of the fact that One Autumn Leaf was stunned, Boundless Sea retracted his other hand and pointed with his two fingers, gathering qi around them.

Pulse Break: Break Intelligence!

Battle Mages were considered Mages. Their Strength stat was higher than other Mages, but their Intelligence wasn’t low either. Due to their Leather Armor Proficiency, their equipment would usually have bonus Strength and Intelligence.

Battle Mages had high Intelligence, and the Battle God One Autumn Leaf would be on an even higher level. Facing the killing power of another top character, Boundless Sea, One Autumn Leaf’s Intelligence decreased the damage from the qi attack by a considerable degree. After all, qi attacks were considered magic attacks.

However, Fang Rui seized this opportunity to use Pulse Break, lowering One Autumn Leaf’s Intelligence by a large amount, which in turn, would lower One Autumn Leaf’s magic resistance.

Boom boom boom!

Explosions one after the other.

Fang Rui was planning on using all of his Qi Master’s instant qi attacks. Right now, he didn’t care about cycling through his skills. Qi continued to flood into One Autumn Leaf’s body and explode. The shockwaves produced were more powerful than what any other class could create. This dirty Qi Master wasn’t holding anything back, attacking with a reckless violence.

Because I’m going to win!

Spiral Qi Rush!

The roaring qi carried along Boundless Sea, pushing One Autumn Leaf forward. After this Spiral Qi Rush, he would have to gather qi for his other skills. It was time for the finishing move.

Qigong Blast!

The finishing move was the Qi Master’s strongest attack, the Level 70 Qigong Blast. Even with the addition of the Level 75 Pulse Break, Qi Masters didn’t have a stronger attack.

The Qigong Blast struck One Autumn Leaf, knocking him back.

The qi exploded as One Autumn Leaf slid back. The series of qi attacks seemed to erupt all at once. Blood blossomed from One Autumn Leaf like a crimson flower, blooming and withering in an instant.

55%

The system showed how much health One Autumn Leaf had after this combo. He had lost nearly half his health.

Fierce and aggressive!

The crowd could feel their blood racing as they watched Boundless Sea’s wave of attacks. It was almost hard to believe that this was being done by that dirty Fang Rui. But after the wave passed, it was hard not to be worried. He had used all of his instant-cast skills. Although the combo had been immensely satisfying, it would likely be very difficult for him to hold off One Autumn Leaf’s counterattack with his other skills that had cast times.

They quickly discovered that they had been too worried. They unexpectedly forgot that the player who performed this crazy combo was Fang Rui, that dirty Fang Rui.

Boundless Sea had recovered quite a bit of stamina during that combo. The dirty Fang Rui was back!

Roll, climb…

When Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf counterattacked, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea began playing dirty again, sneaking around and scurrying about like a Thief.

Dodging, not running.

Fang Rui patiently kited around Sun Xiang. Whenever there was an opening, he would harass him using fast low-level skills.

Qi Bullet!

The cast time was extremely fast. It was practically no different from an instant-cast. The Qi Bullet went straight for the eyes, blocking Sun Xiang’s view. Fang Rui had used this trick who knew how many times. It didn’t create any particularly good opportunities, but Fang Rui never got tired of it.

Countercurrent!

A knock-up skill used when his back was turned away. One Autumn Leaf narrowly walked right into it.

Qi Blade!

When you lost sight of Boundless Sea’s hands, you didn’t need to think about where he was hiding them. Nine times out of ten, what came next would be a Qi Blade. But you also had to be careful, sometimes when he hid his palms, what came out wouldn’t be a Qi Blade, but a Cloud Pushing Palm. Sun Xiang had fallen for it many times and was hit by the Cloud Pushing Palm. The damage wasn’t much, but he would be sent flying back.

Endless tricks and endless hidden attacks.

It was annoying, frustrating, and nauseating.

Many players in the pro player group felt triggered recalling these unpleasant memories. It had happened when Fang Rui was a Thief, and when he was a Qi Master. Times had changed, but Fang Rui’s dirtiness never would. Even if he seemed heroic and flashy, in the next moment, he would be dirty again. He never disappointed.

Sun Xiang was a young player, one who had been extremely arrogant. This sort of player was the easiest to tilt. But today, he had held back his emotions. After Boundless Sea knocked him down to 55% health, he told himself not to think about Tang Rou’s battle. Right now, beating Fang Rui and keeping one point for Samsara was much more urgent. Winning the next round might not even happen at this rate. He needed to give everything he had to win the current one.

Keep calm and search for an opening!

Sun Xiang sucked in a deep breath. He calmed himself down and carefully contended with Fang Rui.

However, constantly telling himself to stay calm was also a form of distraction. Seeing the careful One Autumn Leaf, Fang Rui seemed to see victory waving her hands at him.

People who played cautiously would always be thinking more things. However, Sun Xiang wasn’t that type of player. Even if he knew that it wasn’t his strong point, even if he was purposefully telling himself to be careful, Sun Xiang was Sun Xiang. He wasn’t Zhang Xinjie. It was a crucial moment, and Sun Xiang wasn’t doing what he was best at. In Fang Rui’s eyes, it wasn’t wise. In contrast, it was easier to find an opening against this type of Sun Xiang.

Fang Rui kept making feints, releasing smoke, sending himself messages, all to make Sun Xiang think and decide until those thoughts and decision became hesitation…

Sun Xiang lost his resolve, his drive. He himself didn’t realize it. He thought that he was calmly and effectively dealing with Fang Rui’s dirtiness. However, the pro players watching could tell that Sun Xiang had fallen into Fang Rui’s pace. Fang Rui was leading him by the nose.

He was waiting for Fang Rui to let out an opening, but he didn’t know that Fang Rui was gifting him the opening. This gift definitely wasn’t candy either, but poison wrapped in sugar.

I’m coming!

Sun Xiang’s eyes lit up. He had been patiently waiting for this opening for a long time. Finally, it was time to harvest the fruits of his labour.

Charge!

One Autumn Leaf charged towards that lie of an opening.

“Let’s get ready for the team competition…” Samsara’s Jiang Botao sighed.

Victory had been decided.

Group arena, Happy 5-3.

Chapter 1614 - Historic Team Competition

“We won! 5 to 3!!!” Chen Guo was excited. Although the match wasn’t over yet, they had a 2 point lead going into the team competition. It was an incredible result, especially since this was Samsara’s home stadium. Samsara had clearly practiced with the map, Dripstone Cave, and put it to good use, yet Happy had still been able to win 5 to 3. It was definitely worthy of being happy about.

Everyone knew the importance of this two point lead. The fans in the away team seats started cheering loudly, while the home stadium Samsara fans were disappointed. Today’s group arena had been vexing. Their captain, Zhou Zekai, lost in the first round, putting everyone in low spirits. Jiang Botao was able to bring things back, but Lu Boyuan lost disastrously. Du Ming’s exceptional playing made them overjoyed, but their spirits were immediately dampened by the dirty Fang Rui.

Then, Samsara only had Sun Xiang left. Their hopes of winning the group arena were rather low at this point, but Sun Xiang’s confidence made them think again. But the result…

Everyone had been hopeful, but in the end, Sun Xiang wasn’t able to beat even a single opponent. Samsara’s fans weren’t at all pleased with Sun Xiang’s performance. When the group arena ended and the players came down from the stage, there were even boos towards Sun Xiang from the crowd.

Sun Xiang lowered his head, silent and embarrassed. His teammates sympathized with him though because his loss hadn’t been as bad Lu Boyuan’s. In contrast, Sun Xiang had his glimmering moments. Unfortunately, Fang Rui wiped it all away.

Fang Rui…

He had essentially done a 1v2, successfully earning Happy a two point lead. It was a result worthy of him being the highest paid player and having their strongest character. Fang Rui was satisfied, and the booing towards Sun Xiang was just heaven to his ears. Fang Rui wasn’t polite. He grinned as he waved his hands towards the crowd as if they were cheering for him.

Samsara’s fans weren’t happy with Sun Xiang, but they weren’t going to just let the opposing team laugh at them. The look on Fang Rui’s face made them stop booing towards Sun Xiang. Then, they started sending their boos towards Fang Rui. The players on Samsara, including Sun Xiang, couldn’t help but look towards Fang Rui. Their gazes were filled with gratitude. Nice job pulling that aggro!

But Fang Rui didn’t care about that. When he returned to his team, he was in high spirits.

“What do you think? Just say it! How’d I do!” Fang Rui asked Ye Xiu.

“Good job, good job,” Ye Xiu clapped his hands in praise.

“I appreciate your honesty!” Fang Rui said. The gloom that he had been holding in throughout the playoffs was finally let out today. Fang Rui felt like he was playing great, his Golden Right Hand was on fire. He couldn’t wait for the team competition to begin. He couldn’t help but look towards Samsara, but they noticed him and immediately looked at him with hostility.

“Where’s that cup of water? Hand it over to him to cool off,” Ye Xiu called out.

Fang Rui had asked Su Mucheng for the water when he went to the stage. After Su Mucheng got back, she really did get him a cup of water. After Fang Rui got it, it seemed that he had forgotten about what he had asked for because he immediately gulped it down in one go.

“The water’s still hot!” Fang Rui yelled, “Have you guys heard the story ‘Warm Wine, the Killing of Hua Xiong*?’”

“We’ve heard of it. Let’s talk about the match,” Ye Xiu quickly replied.

“Okay okay, the match,” Fang Rui calmed himself down. He didn’t let the joy get to his head. He was the master of playing dirty, an expert at switching up the pace, no?

The two teams didn’t return to their prep rooms. They stayed at their seats, discussing the upcoming team competition.

A while later, the referee called for the two teams. The lineup for the team competition had been decided beforehand, which the large screen in the stadium displayed for the audience to see.

Team Happy: Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi, Steamed Bun.

Team Samsara: Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, Sun Xiang, Lu Boyuan, Fang Minghua, Du Ming.

There were some small adjustments to the lineup compared to their first game.

On Happy’s side, Tang Rou wasn’t playing in the team competition. Qiao Yifan took her place. On Samsara’s side, their Assassin Wu Qi was on the bench, while Du Ming was the sixth player.

Every player hoped to be a part of the participating lineup especially on a grand stage like the finals. Du Ming’s position in Samsara wasn’t as stable as a core player’s. Being able to play in the team competition in the finals was a rare opportunity.

Even so, Du Ming couldn’t help but hope for a bit more, but after seeing that Happy’s lineup didn’t include Tang Rou, his hopes were immediately extinguished.

How unlucky!

Du Ming really wanted to let out a sigh, but he suddenly noticed that his teammates were looking at him and hastily swallowed his sigh.

It’s just not right!

It was a rare opportunity for him to play, but he was still a bit sad about it.

Du Ming thought to himself as he collected his emotions. With his head held high, he marched forward, the first one to head towards the stage.

“How unfortunate, Tang Rou isn’t playing,” Behind him, Jiang Botao and Fang Minghua stood close to each other, whispering.

“Yeah, we miscalculated,” Fang Minghua said.

“But then again, Du Ming’s playing really well today,” Jiang Botao said.

“Like I said, the power of love,” Fang Minghua said.

“But his love’s not even on stage!” Jiang Botao retorted.

“But his love’s watching him off stage!” Fang Minghua said.

“If we knew, we should have put someone else as the sixth player,” Jiang Botao said.

“We can make adjustments during the match!” Fang Minghua said.

Soon afterwards, the players on the two teams lined up at the center of the stage, giving their pre-match greetings to each other.

Zhou Zekai wasn’t a talkative person. He pretty much just smiled to the players on Happy as a greeting. The first to say something from Samsara was their vice-captain, Jiang Botao.

“You guys played amazing in the group arena,” Jiang Botao shook Ye Xiu’s hands.

“You’re about to see something even more amazing,” Ye Xiu smiled.

“I hope you won’t be as scary,” Jiang Botao said.

“You scared?” Ye Xiu said.

“A bit, but I still have to play even if I’m afraid!” Jiang Botao replied.

“Why force yourself?” Ye Xiu grinned.

“You two… are you done chatting?” Su Mucheng couldn’t help but interrupt them. The pre-match greeting was just a formality. Usually, the two teams would line up and then shake hands, starting from the captain. But instead, Ye Xiu had just gotten to Samsara’s second player, Jiang Botao, and the two were chatting up a storm. The two of them were holding up the line. The others behind them were looking at each other.

“Ha, Sis Su, don’t be anxious,” Jiang Botao could chat with anyone. After letting go of Ye Xiu, he immediately started making small talk with Su Mucheng.

Every match had its formalities. No one really cared what happened during them. Soon, the two sides finished their greetings, and under directions from the referee, each side went to their respective player booths.

Cheers erupted from the crowd.

Although Samsara had lost in the group arena, the outcome of this match depended on the team competition. It was very common to see a team win a team competition by more than two points. As a result, neither Team Samsara nor their fans were too worried.

Who cares if we’re losing by two points? As long as we gain it back in the team competition, it’s fine. If we gain the points back, we win today’s match and the finals. We’ll be the champion’s! It’ll be the start of a new reign!

A historic moment could happen today, giving Samsara’s players and their fans endless motivation. It allowed them to keep calm despite being behind.

As for Happy, they were facing a match that they could not lose. Even if they had a two point lead from the group arena, it wasn’t enough. They had to win the team competition, so they could get another chance for a third game tie-breaker. If not, their journey this season would be over. No one on Happy wanted to see this outcome.

“Good luck!” The players on the two teams gave each other one last round of encouragement before heading into their player booths.

The referee looked at the time.

For this potentially historic match, everything needed to be handled perfectly.

Time was ticking. At 21:25, the referee announced the start of the team competition!

The map and characters loaded. The loading bar seemed to be carrying killing intent, a battle between the two sides.

Lord Grim finished loading.

Cloud Piercer finished loading.

Dancing Rain finished loading.

Empty Waves finished loading.

…

At the end, the map finished loading, and the team competition was officially underway.

The map was Selkie City Warehouse.

The map was a city map, but because of the enormous size of the warehouse, the map had a large indoor area. As a result, it didn’t feel like there were many layers to this map compared to maps in the wilderness. There were all sorts of commodities piled up inside the warehouse, creating a maze. Some of these commodities could be used in battle too. Teams that weren’t familiar with the map would probably have a hard time utilizing it well.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo introduced the map to the audience, while the two teams spawned at the east and west side of the map.

This map was an actual part of a city in the Heavenly Domain. The Selkie City Warehouse was asymmetric. There were areas that could be utilized on both the east and west sides of the map. However, as the away team, Happy needed some time to observe the map. On the other hand, Samsara immediately set out as soon as they spawned. Instead of heading straight for the center, Samsara moved in the southwest direction.

At the top of the warehouse in the southwest area, there was a tall chimney, which was the highest point in the map.

Samsara was heading towards it. However, the chimney was actually closer to Happy’s spawn point, and it was quite conspicuous too. Happy quickly noticed it.

Chapter 1615 - High Ground

“High ground?”

“Obvious!”

The communication going on in Happy’s chat was short and concise.

Su Mucheng had asked about the high ground. It was common knowledge that Launchers with the high ground could more easily provide support to the team. The height of the chimny was neither too high nor too low. It was the perfect height for a Launcher. If a Launcher player saw this high ground and didn’t have any thoughts about it, then the player wasn’t suited to be a Launcher.

But Ye Xiu quickly replied back with an “Obvious”.

The chimney was easy to notice. Samsara knew what Happy’s team composition looked like. Samsara had also chosen this map, so how could not know what the chimney meant for Happy. Since they knew, why would they choose this map if it gave their opponent an advantage? It was unlikely. This obvious advantage was more likely to be bait.

“Closer,” Fang Rui quickly typed.

He judged that they were closer to the chimney than Samsara was. Happy could take advantage of this fact. If Samsara had left the chimney there as bait, then they must have a method to deal with a Launcher holding the high ground. What was that method?

“Check,” Ye Xiu ordered. Happy set out. Their destination was the high ground.

A total of five words had been said, but it was enough for them to get the message across. Even the average viewer could understand Happy’s intentions from these five words: the high ground is bait, so don’t rush over. Instead, check how Samsara plans on dealing with it and then search for an opening.

The team advanced. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim moved faster than the others, leaving the team behind. He planned on scouting ahead by himself.

Happy had the advantage in distance, and Ye Xiu had left the team to operate on his own. With Ye Xiu’s experience, even if he wasn’t too familiar with this map, he would likely find the key to this map soon. However, the viewers, who could see everything, saw Ye Xiu’s movements and started lighting candles for him.

Because Samsara had also split up to get there as fast as possible. It wasn’t just one person either, but three.

Zhou Zekai, Cloud Piercer.

Sun Xiang, One Autumn Leaf.

Jiang Botao, Empty Waves.

The three characters were in a triangular formation. After setting out from their spawn point, the other two were left behind. Lu Boyuan’s Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was left behind to protect Fang Minghua’s Cleric, Laughing Song.

Happy didn’t rush towards this obvious high point rashly. However, their caution approach was within Samsara’s calculations. They had predicted that Happy would send someone to scout ahead, so they sent out their trio as a counter. Was Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim going to be killed in one go, just like this?

The broadcast showed a bird’s eye view of the map. Four blinking lights were quickly moving towards the chimney.

Ye Xiu was holding nothing back though, using whatever movement skills he had on him. As a result, even though Samsara had left their healer behind to rush over, their speed couldn’t compare to Lord Grim’s. Samsara had started off farther away too, so Ye Xiu would definitely arrive first. The question was how long he would stay around.

The blinking indicators grew nearer and nearer towards the storeroom with the chimney on top.

Selkie City Warehouse was composed of numerous large, medium, and small storerooms. This storeroom was a small one. It was no more than three meters tall. Even so, it wasn’t a height that a character could make in a single jump. However, this height wasn’t a problem for Ye Xiu. Rotor Wings and his umbrella’s ninjato form could easily overcome three meters. Lord Grim had transformed his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella into its ninjato form. After two jumps, Lord Grim climbed onto the roof of the storeroom. The chimney was already in sight. It looked to be around 15 meters tall. Along with the storeroom’s height itself, it was approaching 20 meters. It was indeed a very suitable location for a Launcher.

With a distance and movement speed advantage, it was impossible for Samsara to have arrived there before him. Lord Grim rushed straight for the chimney. Along the way, he looked around to check his surroundings.

Storerooms everywhere. Selkie City Warehouse consisted of storerooms of different sizes and heights. The storeroom to the left of him was a small one, about 7 meters tall. The storeroom to the right was connected to the one he was on, and was 5 meters tall as well.

7 meters on the left, 5 meters on the right. There were numerous places where the enemies could situate themselves to force the Launcher down.

That would have been the case in the past.

After the level cap raise to 75, Launchers had a new skill, Mounted Gun, which Su Mucheng had employed effectively in today’s group arena. When this skill was activated, the Launcher wouldn’t need to worry about knockback from attacks. During the duration of the skill, she would be able to provide even stronger support for Happy. Of course, it would also be at the sacrifice of her health. Whether or not the exchange was worth it depended on the situation. Ye Xiu didn’t think that Samsara’s method of dealing with the chimney would be so unreliable. It was true that Zhou Zekai would be the one dealing with this high ground, but banking everything on him would be too naive. Samsara hadn’t won two championships through blind trust.

What else could there be?

In the blink of an eye, Lord Grim reached beneath the chimney, which had stairs that could be climbed. Ye Xiu had Lord Grim climb up to the top. When he looked around, he noticed that the view was indeed extremely good. If the two teams fought here and Su Mucheng was positioned on top of the chimney, she would have a very easy time helping the team. It might even be impossible for Zhou Zekai’s Sharpshooter to obstruct her.

If before, Ye Xiu had felt like it depended on the circumstances, then now, after getting an understanding of how effective this high ground was, Ye Xiu felt like having support from up here would improve Happy’s chances of winning a fight enormously.

In that case, where was Samsara’s confidence coming from? Was there some sort of dead angle, or could it be…

Ye Xiu looked down towards the bottom of the chimney.

The chimney was emitting any smoke, but if there was a way to get it operating, then the Launcher at the top of the chimney probably wouldn’t be able to see through the dense smoke.

Was Samsara confident in their control over the high ground because of the chimney itself?

Lord Grim crouched and jumped down into the chimney. A height of 12 meters was enough to induce fall damage. However, Lord Grim’s umbrella was still in its ninjato form. After dropping down for a bit, he swung his ninjato to safely land into a pile of garbage. He looked around. Then, his eyes lit up. He struggled out of the garbage and into the storeroom. He had come out from a huge furnace. Scattered all around the storeroom was a bunch of discarded junk. It seemed like this place was for burning trash.

Ye Xiu quickly found power switch. After pulling on it, the furnace began to burn, and the conveyor belt started up, sending trash into the furnace.

As expected.

Ye Xiu was certain now. Because the chimney was still operational, it couldn’t be used as a high ground.

“There’s smoke!”

The efficiency of the furnace was astonishing. It had only just been turned on, but the chimney was already letting out smoke. Both teams noticed the smoke.

“It turns out the chimney can be used,” Pan Lin said.

“It’s a good thing Ye Xiu found it ahead of time,” Li Yibo said.

“The two sides haven’t come across each other yet, but it looks like a battle of wits has already begun,” Pan Lin said.

“But it looks like Samsara has thought farther ahead!” Li Yibo looked at the info he had and smiled.

“Oh?” Pan Lin asked.

“Look at the entrance to this storeroom,” Li Yibo reminded Pan Lin, while also reminding the audience.

The storeroom entrance.

The broadcast gave a close up of the entrance. However, only a portion of the audience members could see it. The other portion couldn’t rely on the screen to understand the peculiarities behind the entrance. This was because everyone was seated in different locations, so they saw it from different angles. The entrance to the storeroom was facing to the east, so the audience members on the east side saw it clearly, but the audience members on the west were at a loss. Fortunately, the projection technology in the stadium could change depending on the situation. Previously, the projection only showed the area surrounding Lord Grim, but now it extended to the entire storeroom, allowing everyone to see Lord Grim’s movements inside the storeroom.

After being able to see the entrance clearly, the audience members quickly caught on to what Li Yibo meant.

This storeroom only had one entrance, facing to the east, which Samsara was coming from. If Lord Grim wanted to leave the storeroom, he only had one exit to choose from. But Samsara’s trio was getting closer and closer to this entrance. They could stop Lord Grim from coming out. The smoke coming from the chimney was a signal to them to rush in.

But they didn’t see Lord Grim.

After Ye Xiu looked around the storeroom, he had noticed that the entrance was facing east and immediately realized the problem. Thus, he didn’t go towards the entrance and instead turned off the furnace.

Then, he tried to go into the furnace, but ended up losing health!

The furnace’s temperature was too high, dealing damage to him. Going back the way he came through the chimney wouldn’t work.

There were piles of garbage scattered everywhere around him. Ye Xiu found a random one to hide in, while typing out: “Fight for the high ground!”

Chapter 1616 - Storeroom

High ground? Fight for the high ground?

The audience was puzzled.

Ye Xiu had turned off the furnace, and his Lord Grim was guarding it. However, Samsara had three people, while Ye Xiu was alone. He probably wasn’t enough to hold down this place, no?

But the people with this opinion soon realized something. They had an omniscient spectator view, so they could see that Samsara had three players there. On the other hand, Ye Xiu never exited the room, so he had no idea what Samsara’s arrangements were. As a result, his order to fight for the high ground was actually a good decision. The furnace was in his grasp right now. Even if he discovered that three people had come and he couldn’t defend the furnace, it wouldn’t be too late for him to tell Su Mucheng to give up on the high ground.

Happy’s other four players were approaching. After receiving Ye Xiu’s message, Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain immediately sped up. She left the team behind and rushed towards the storeroom.

The storeroom entrance.

Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, and Sun Xiang had surrounded the entrance, but they didn’t see any enemies.

Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer was standing farther back because he was long-ranged. As a result, he could see the top of the chimney. He quickly noticed that the smoke was gradually getting sparser.

“Turned off.” He typed in the team chat.

The others immediately understood that the furnace had been turned off.

Turned off. That meant the high ground could be taken. However, Samsara didn’t go for it.

“Enter!” Jiang Botao said.

Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf led the way. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves followed next, and then Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer. The three didn’t split up, and headed into the storeroom together.

One to the left, one to the right!

One Autumn Leaf and Empty Waves moved orderly and nimbly. They were clearly very familiar with the interior of the storeroom. The two split up and immediately searched the piles of garbage in the back, but they didn’t find anyone.

‘Forward!” Jiang Botao messaged again.

The three of them split up again, each taking their own path. All of them moved slowly and quietly, pressing forward together. Step by step, they grew closer to the furnace. When they reached about halfway to the furnace, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer suddenly stepped on a pile of trash near him and jumped twice to get on top. He looked around and immediately noticed the hiding Lord Grim.

Boom boom boom!

But Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was the first to flash. He had been looking in that direction, waiting for a target to come into sight.

Zhou Zekai reacted extremely fast though. Cloud Piercer immediately rolled backwards, disappearing from Lord Grim’s view. Anti-Tank Missiles rained down, exploding the trash pile that Cloud Piercer had been on. The trash consisted of a bunch of worn-out rubbish. The missiles sent the rubbish flying into the air, which then pitter-pattered down like rain.

Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer rolled backwards to dodge the attack. Then, he rolled forward twice, leaning on the pile of trash. His pristine windbreaker lay crumpled on the dirty trash. To the fans, it made their hearts ache.

Bang bang bang bang!

Cloud Piercer took out his two guns and pointed them towards Lord Grim, firing at him. But Lord Grim was no longer there. The bullets splattered against the trash.

The exchange of gunfire had attracted Sun Xiang’s and Jiang Botao’s attention. When Zhou Zekai fired back, he also gave out Lord Grim’s coordinates. Sun Xiang and Jiang Botao made their own choices on what to do with the information. They continued to go deeper into the storeroom to block off Lord Grim’s escape path.

“Gone!” Zhou Zekai saw his target disappear and messaged again. The two received the message and put up their guard. Where would Lord Grim come out from?

Some of the viewers couldn’t see and started getting anxious. The projections were already showing the storeroom as translucent. Turning the trash piles inside translucent would only make things more confusing. This had been tested before.

As a result, some members of the audience couldn’t see Lord Grim’s hiding spot. Since they couldn’t see, they could only rely on the big screen and then compare it to the projections. When they made the comparison, they only became more anxious! Lord Grim was crouching at a spot, while Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf was getting closer, one step at a time. At this rate, he was going to get ambushed!

Just when One Autumn Leaf was two steps away, he suddenly stopped. On the other side, Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves suddenly sped up and rushed out.

Their eyes met.

Bang bang!

Gunshots. In the end, thanks to Ye Xiu’s fast reactions, he was able to get off two shots as soon as he saw Empty Waves.

But One Autumn Leaf’s Evil Annihilation shot out at the same time.

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart!

The spear pierced through the trash with ease.

Ye Xiu was saved by his good instincts. The moment he fired two shots at Empty Waves, Lord Grim also rolled back in case there was a possible counterattack from the other side. It was a defensive habit of his, and it let him dodge the attack. Seeing the familiar spear narrowly miss him, Ye Xiu thanked the gods for his luck. He hadn’t noticed anyone near him.

Cloud Piercer, Empty Waves, One Autumn Leaf.

There were three people. Was there a fourth? Maybe even a fifth? If there was a fifth, then Samsara didn’t have a healer. A healer couldn’t have gotten here so quickly. If there was five, then they had gone all out on the aggression. There should be no reason to take such a risk just for this high ground. Just these three players alone showed their aggressiveness. If he had been the one making the calls, he would have only sent two people to go past the team, while leaving two to protect the healer. In that case…

“Storeroom three people, intercept healer!” Ye Xiu quickly gave out an order.

Deciphering these five words would require a bit of thinking.

Intercept the healer, sure, but go where to intercept him? Ye Xiu had provided information that there were three people in the storeroom. Happy was closer to the storeroom than Samsara, but three people had already reached there. Why? Because they had left the healer behind. Thus, the healer was behind them, en-route to the storeroom from the spawn point. There was one healer and another one protecting him. Who was the one protecting him?

“Cloud One Empty,” Ye Xiu quickly typed.

Cloud – Cloud Piercer, One – One Autumn Leaf, Empty – Empty Waves.

The information was thorough and clear. It was either Lu Boyuan or Du Ming protecting the healer. In any case, Happy’s healer was completely safe. He wouldn’t be under attack any time soon, and he could be left behind on his own.

As a result, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea and Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash sped up. Previously, it had only been Dancing Rain that had gone ahead. Now, she had reached the storeroom. Even though Ye Xiu had told her to get to the high ground, with three of Samsara’s players inside, having the high ground wouldn’t be much help. The high ground was rather far away, if she wanted to intercept Samsara’s healer. As a result, Su Mucheng gave up on it. She used the recoil from her cannon to leap onto a nearby three meter high storeroom before heading towards that storeroom entrance.

This was a moment where players needed to decide on their own what was the right call according to the situation. Ye Xiu had just given the order. However, it was likely that it wasn’t suitable anymore because of a change in circumstances. The other players needed to decide for themselves whether it was the right choice and act accordingly.

Inside the storeroom, Ye Xiu was facing against three of Samsara’s figureheads. There was naturally no way he could face them head on. By a fluke, he had dodged One Autumn Leaf’s Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart. He sent out information to Happy, while throwing a grenade at the corner of a trash pile.

Sun Xiang’s vision was blocked by the trash, so he didn’t know a grenade had been thrown. The Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart had unexpectedly missed. He immediately had One Autumn Leaf rush out. But even though he couldn’t see it, Jiang Botao could.

“Dodge!”

Warning, grenade, One Autumn Leaf’s right foot, all of them came out at the same time.

Boom!

The grenade exploded the moment Sun Xiang saw Jiang Botao’s warning. How could there be any time for him to dodge? One Autumn Leaf was thrown back. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves rushed forward, but Lord Grim had already hidden himself behind another trash pile.

Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves specialized in Wave Slashes, but he had learned Wave Formations too. He stopped and swung his shortsword, Divine Chains, to gather magic. But just when he swung his sword, Lord Grim suddenly popped out again. Ye Xiu had predicted that Jiang Botao would set down a wave formation, so he came out to interrupt it.

Jiang Botao smirked.

You predicted what I would do, but I predicted that you would predict what I would do.

Divine Chains chopped downwards!

It wasn’t a Wave Formation, but a Ghost Slash.

The emblematic purple light of the ghost god crackled as it passed through the air. This slash wasn’t towards Lord Grim, but rather to the right a bit, towards the pile of trash that he was hiding behind.

Ye Xiu saw that the attack would miss, but he didn’t capitalize on it. Lord Grim immediately jumped back. The Ghost Slash fell and sliced through the pile of trash. The pile of trash instantly crumbled. If Ye Xiu hadn’t jumped back, the trash would have swallowed him.

“Tricky!” Lord Grim turned around to run. Ye Xiu didn’t forget to leave a bit of trash talk for Jiang Botao.

One reason was to taunt at Jiang Botao, the other was to notify his teammates that he could handle the current situation. If not, he wouldn’t have taunted Jiang Botao and asked for help instead.

He turned around and ran away again. Ye Xiu tried his best to keep Lord Grim as low as possible. This slimy crawling and rolling gave the audience a sense of deja vu. This was clearly how Fang Rui moved!

“What can’t this guy do!” Zhang Jiale couldn’t help but sigh from the spectator stands. He had known Ye Xiu for nine years, and he knew that his title as the Glory Textbook wasn’t just for show. Ye Xiu had innovated many of the playstyles and techniques used in Glory, but not everything. For example, Zhang Jiale’s Hundred Blossoms Style, or Fang Rui’s dirty playstyle, those were all their own original creations.

These became their symbolic playstyles, but that didn’t mean that they were the only ones who could do them. People could learn. But Ye Xiu used to be a Battle Mage, not a Spitfire or a Thief, yet he seemed to have grasped these playstyles too. Then, he used his understanding of them to find their weaknesses. There was no one more annoying than him.

“They have three people, and they can’t deal with him. Fight my ass!” Huang Shaotian shouted. The pro players were getting worked up as if something had hit a nerve.

Chapter 1617 - 1v3

Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves stepped on the trash that he had just struck down with Ghost Slash in pursuit of Lord Grim. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf continued forward, hoping to pincer Lord Grim with Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves. At the same time, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer continued to head over from atop the trash piles. Despite having the higher ground, he couldn’t see any sign of Lord Grim. Ye Xiu had used Fang Rui’s shameless crouching position to move and prevent Zhou Zekai seeing him from above.

However, this map was still Samsara’s map. Though they might not be able to see Lord Grim, the three from Samsara had an idea of where he was heading from the direction he had run in. Jiang Botao on the left, Sun Xiang on the right, and Zhou Zekai above. Samsara wasn’t just doing a pincer from two sides, but closing in from three different directions.

Here!!Jiang Botao and Sun Xiang had the same thought as the two’s characters closed in at the same pace. Once they both got to the corner, they glanced over at Cloud Piercer above.

Great!

Cloud Piercer had managed to keep up with their pace as well, taking the high ground and surrounding Lord Grim from three sides.

Earth Wave Slash!

Tyrant’s Destruction!

One swung out from Empty Waves’ shortsword Divine Chain, while the other swept from One Autumn Leaf’s spear Evil Annihilation forwards. As soon as Empty Waves and One Autumn Leaf charged out from this corner, they were already using their attacks to defend themselves and guard against the possibility of Ye Xiu lying in wait to ambush them.

However, the two had over thought things. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim wasn’t there, waiting in ambush. Instead, he continued forward, crouched. That was when One Autumn Leaf’s Tyrant’s Destruction swept out, blocking his path. Turning around, he saw Empty Waves’ Earthquake Sword fly at him, sending trash flying. Above came the sound of Cloud Piercer landing on the trash heap.

Lord Grim jumped back!

After dodging the Earthquake Sword and twisting his body as he did so, Lord Grim attempted to climb up the trash heap behind him. However, Jiang Botao had been anticipating this. Empty Waves’ Divine Chain flicked up, and a Light Wave Sword cut off Lord Grim’s plan before he had a chance to enact it.

Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf was already approaching and saw Lord Grim rapidly form hand seals.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Sun Xiang immediately thought. One Autumn Leaf stopped his approach, quickly turning to look around.

No one was there!

He quickly turned back, but there was still no one there.

What on earth?

Sun Xiang was shocked, but then heard a noise from above.

Underground Tunneling Technique!

Ye Xiu had actually made Lord Grim use a different Ninja Technique, burrowing underground. Yet when he reappeared, he had surprising done so at the top of the trash heap. Zhou Zekai’s position hadn’t given him a good enough view to see Lord Grim so he didn’t know what the other was doing. Lord Grim erupted from the trash heap right in front of him, ninjato striking!

Luckily, while Zhou Zekai didn’t know Lord Grim’s exact position from above, Ye Xiu wasn’t certain of Cloud Piercer’s position either. His Underground Tunneling Technique had sent him right in front of Cloud Piercer, and a little ways away as well.

This gave Zhou Zekai enough time to react.

Cloud Piercer quickly jumped back, dodging Lord Grim’s imperfect strike. His dual revolvers glinted in the light, Shattered Frost and Wildfire, their mouths dark before gunfire sprung from them as one.

Bang bang bang…

Bullets flew. With only two steps between them, they were certain to hit.

Lord Grim was shot, but no blood appeared, his form suddenly dissolving like a broken shadow.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Whoosh!

A swift sound flickered past Cloud Piercer’s neck, drawing a splash of blood.

Cut Throat!

Lord Grim had used Shadow Clone Technique to dart behind Cloud Piercer, striking swift. Next, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella folded into two parts, turning into tonfas. With a grab, he caught Cloud Piercer and then threw him forward using Fling!

It had all happened in a split second. It was like Lord Grim had been pincered by Empty Waves and One Autumn Leaf the previous second, and in the next, he had appeared on top of the trash heap, darted behind Cloud Piercer and thrown him out, blood still dripping from his neck.

So fast!

There was no other word for it but fast. It was like lightning, and it felt like chopping up the word fast was the only way to really give it a description worthy of that speed.

If it didn’t reach that speed, how could it catch even Zhou Zekai?

Jiang Botao and Sun Xiang only just heard the noise above, about to investigate, when they saw Cloud Piercer thrown off. But it clearly wasn’t the time for greetings. The two didn’t need to think or discuss. They each took a path, one left, the other right, heading up the trash heap in pursuit.

But just as Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf’s head peeked out, he saw a grenade land in front of his eyes. There was no time to think. Sun Xiang subconsciously flicked his mouse, One Autumn Leaf’s spear stabbed forward right towards the grenade.

Boom!

In the rush, he wasn’t able to control the force of this stab very well, but the grenade still exploded and it counted as a parry. The explosive force didn’t throw him back, so One Autumn Leaf aimed to leap up again. But who would’ve thought that while the explosion didn’t affect One Autumn Leaf directly, it did blast away the trash he wanted to land on. With that foothold gone, turned into a pit by the grenade, One Autumn Leaf’s jump failed and his form plummeted again…

Sun Xiang over here just seemed a little silly, but Jiang Botao over there was the one in trouble. As soon as Empty Waves peeked out, he saw the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella descend down onto him, like a meteorite.

Star Fall!

An Exorcist skill, one Jiang Botao obviously knew the priority of. In that moment, he had given up in his heart. An airborne character didn’t have that much freedom. Jiang Botao hurriedly had Empty Waves Guard. Star Fall slammed him straight down, and he didn’t have any footholds in reach.

Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao and Sun Xiang, three of the Glory scene’s top ten players, had all been thrown off the trash pile by Ye Xiu in a 1v3.

Though it was only a few moments, though it was clear how Ye Xiu had taken advantage of the situation, this scene was etched into people’s minds.

The commentators Pan Lin and Li Yibo didn’t know how to comment on this scene. Ye Xiu’s thought process and methodology were simple, even a normal player in the same situation could think of such a tactic. However, the problem was that the opponents Ye Xiu was facing were Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao and Sun Xiang. Three top players. It was easier thought of than done.

Yet Ye Xiu had done it, so the entire venue went silent, and even the TV broadcast lacked the voices of the commentators.

Everyone watched, lost for words, as Lord Grim turned and left.

In the end, he didn’t dare face the three head on. However, this small victory was already miraculous.

Before, the other pros had all thought that a 1v3 was sure to get rid of Lord Grim. If they couldn’t, then that would just be plain embarrassing. But in this moment, they all fell silent, too. After putting themselves in Samsara’s shoes for moment, they all felt that, in that moment, Ye Xiu was unstoppable. The three on the field couldn’t stop him, they couldn’t stop either, and neither could anyone on this earth.

“Fuck…”

All these thoughts and words whirling around in their minds ended up expressed as one single short curse. It was a sigh, a shock, but more than that, it was admiration.

They couldn’t blame this on Samsara’s three not being up to par, they could only blame this on their opponent being too strong.

However, Samsara’s three didn’t plan on staying shocked and silent with the audience.

Cloud Piercer, who had been thrown off the trash heap with a Fling by Lord Grim, had been knocked down due to the grab’s effect. However, after being knocked down, he got back up as quickly as was possible.

Cloud Piercer’s movements were also stunningly swift. To most, it was almost like he had been knocked down onto a trampoline before being immediately thrown back onto his feet.

Fire!

He activated Rage Firing, but used it for Aerial Fire. The stronger recoil shot Cloud Piercer onto the trash heap, his body already twisting in midair. Zhou Zekai’s control of the attack’s recoil, his own jump, and whatnot was extremely precise. After leaping up with help from the recoil, he turned, landing right down onto the trash heap in front of him in one smooth motion.

Bang bang bang!

The gunshot sounds never stopped, and the bullets were already heading Lord Grim’s way.

Ye Xiu was shocked. He had never thought that it would Cloud Piercer to recover and pursue him first, what with the forced knockdown. Zhou Zekai’s reaction speed was far beyond his expectations, and he wasn’t far enough just yet for Lord Grim to take cover. This trash heap was nowhere near as reliable as solid ground, and moving along it would sometimes cause your foot to sink in. It was a plague on movement speed.

Rolling to avoid the hail of bullets, Ye Xiu managed to return two shots. The dodged bullets lodged themselves into the trash heap, splashing bits of trash everywhere and sending them dancing around Lord Grim.

Bang bang bang!

Clink clink clink!

Cloud Piercer never stopped firing, but amidst this, there was a strange noise.

Thwack!

Lord Grim’s shoulder was hit by a bullet, much to Ye Xiu’s disbelief. He was certain he had dodged out of the path of Zhou Zekai’s bullets…

The trash…

Ye Xiu quickly realized what was going on.

Zhou Zekai had actually used the trash that the bullets had thrown into the air, making his bullets collide with them to not only increase damage, but also to alter their paths slightly, making them unpredictable.

In this time, Lord Grim was hit thrice more. Twice by the flying trash and once by a bullet.

His movement was slowed and on the end of an attack like this, his rhythm was completely destroyed.

With no other choice, he opened up the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella…

Twack thwack thwack….

Like pouring rain, bullets and trash bombarded the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella’s shield form.

Ye Xiu couldn’t stay under the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella’s protection forever. With the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella’s current durability, it wouldn’t be able to last for too long under Cloud Piercer’s assault.

Opening the umbrella merely gave him a chance to catch his breath. In the next moment, the umbrella closed and gunfire erupted from the tip.

Gatling Gun.

A shoot out!

Chapter 1618 - Unbelievable Control

With just the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella’s rifle form, Lord Grim couldn’t hope to contend

Bullets swept across the ground, launching trash up into the air. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer moved to the side to dodge, but all he could see was trash flying around everywhere. The bullets chasing after him began colliding with the airborne trash as well, making it difficult for Zhou Zekai to figure out their trajectories.

He could only do what Ye Xiu did before: keep Cloud Piercer moving and try to get as far away as possible from the chaos.

The two fired at each other, getting hit by each other’s attacks. Blood, bullets, trash…

Everyone was dumbfounded. No one had expected to see another fierce confrontation between these two right after a brilliant match between these two in the group arena.

Gun Fu!

This was Zhou Zekai’s famed Gun Fu, but Ye Xiu wasn’t losing to him. The two were even.

The broadcast provided a slow-mo of the battle for everyone to enjoy. With the speed slowed down, the viewers could see how the bullets were bouncing off the trash, allowing them to realize that there was another layer to the fight.

“This is… Delivery Gun?” After watching the slow-mo, Pan Lin was able to see everything clearly, but he wasn’t certain what exactly he was seeing.

“This is…” Li Yibo’s voice was filled with uncertainty as well because he had never seen anything like this before.

Delivery Gun was a technique, where the gunner used the knockback from bullets to send the target to the desired location. Zhou Zekai had once used Delivery Gun to juggle a character to death in the air as part of an exhibition match. Even today, this play was still widely discussed.

Of course, an exhibition match was completely different from a competitive match. Zhou Zekai had never performed it in an official match. Oftentimes, Delivery Gun was used in the team competition to control where the target landed. By pairing it with the grabs from Lu Boyuan’s Grappler, it was a very powerful control tool.

When talking about Delivery Gun, it was impossible not to mention Ye Xiu because he was the one who had developed the technique. Although to many people, it sounded more like a legend than a fact. Most people couldn’t wrap their heads around how he could have developed Delivery Gun. From what they knew about him, he had always been a Battle Mage player. Nowadays, many of the Glory players didn’t know the history behind the technique. When they heard Delivery Gun, their first thought would be Zhou Zekai.

Li Yibo had come from an older generation. How could he have forgotten that Delivery Gun had been Ye Xiu’s innovation? He just wasn’t sure if what he was seeing could be considered as Delivery Gun. He couldn’t quite grasp it.

“This… I’m not sure if it’s Delivery Gun, but what I can say for certain is that anyone who can do what they’re doing has reached great heights with Delivery Gun!” Li Yibo finally concluded. His words sounded evasive, but his reasoning wasn’t without logic. To do what they were doing, their shots needed to be extremely precise, and precision was a fundamental part of Delivery Gun. However, in contrast to the traditional definition of Delivery Gun, the two were not fixed on specific target. The two were aiming to hit the pieces of trash flying around. Perhaps this was just a form of Delivery Gun.

Li Yibo had his own opinions on the matter, but he didn’t say them. He had been taught a lesson by Ye Xiu far too many times. Zhou Zekai had slapped his face numerous times today too. He didn’t dare say more than what he needed to say.

“But Ye Xiu can’t keep this up for long, no?” Pan Lin asked.

“It’s not that he can’t, but his character can’t,” Li Yibo said. The only reason Lord Grim could compete with Cloud Piercer in this firefight was because he was using Gatling Gun. However, Gatling Gun had a duration. It would eventually run out of bullets.

“Even if his character could keep this up, the circumstances won’t permit him to,” Li Yibo added. He saw that Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves and Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf had started moving. The two didn’t rush towards the garbage heap again. Instead, they circled around to the left and right of Ye Xiu’s retreat path. They knew that Lord Grim wouldn’t be able to keep this up forever. He would have to retreat sooner or later.

One to the left, the other to the right. The two dashed along the outside of the garbage heap. Ye Xiu couldn’t see them from up above, and the sound of gunfire covered their footsteps. The two quickly made their way behind Lord Grim and were now heading towards him. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer pressed harder. He had calculated that Lord Grim’s Gatling Gun would be over soon. There were only a few bullets left.

Ta!

The Gatling Gun suddenly stopped. Ye Xiu cancelled Gatling Gun ahead of time. His character jumped up and slashed out with his sword!

Sword Draw!

Sword light swept towards the ground, leaving a clear mark. A circular arc in the shape of a crescent moon was carved into the garbage heap.

Hua!

The piled up trash suddenly started sliding down like a rockslide. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves and Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf had rushed towards this area. The two of them saw Lord Grim jumping from the garbage heap. Just when they were about to throw an attack at him, the garbage heap next to them collapsed, showering them with trash.

The two struggled, but weren’t able to stop the incoming flood of trash. In an instant, they were swallowed by the garbage, and Lord Grim disappeared from their sights amidst this surging sea of trash.

“?”

“?”

Sun Xiang and Jiang Botao both put out question marks in the team chat. They had lost sight of their target, and their characters were currently struggling to free themselves from the collapsed garbage heap.

“?”

A third question mark soon followed. When Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer arrived, he didn’t see Lord grim. He looked around, but didn’t see anyone.

Bang bang bang bang.

Cloud Piercer immediately fired at the garbage heap that had collapsed, sending trash flying into the air. But he failed to dig out Lord Grim. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves and Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf finally freed themselves from the prison of garbage and climbed out.

It was a 3v1, yet they were losing?

They had chosen this map, yet their opponent was giving them this much trouble?

What was being injured wasn’t their health, but their pride. As soon as One Autumn Leaf climbed out, he immediately leapt into the air.

Shattering the Land!!

Sun Xiang vented, creating a huge explosion. Magic erupted, blasting the garbage heap apart. If Lord Grim was hiding underneath it, his cover would be blown away. But he wasn’t…

The Samsara fans sent their regards to their three generals. They had seen that the moment Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim toppled the garbage heap, he had run away with a Shadow Clone Technique.

With cover from the garbage heap, he was able to instantly vanish out of sight with the Shadow Clone Technique. Lord Grim’s real body had slipped away, going around Cloud Piercer and towards the exit.

Zhou Zekai, Sun Xiang, Jiang Botao.

Three famous names, three top 10 All-Stars, facing a single Ye Xiu, and all three of them had been duped. Ye Xiu hadn’t truly been fighting against them. He had been doing everything he could to run away, but it was still a 1v3. Being able to escape was a huge success on his part. None of the three had taken much damage, but in everyone’s eyes, they had been the losers. The more loyal the Samsara fan, the more deeply they felt this.

The three continued with the same pace. One Autumn Leaf’s Shattering the Lands had confirmed that Lord Grim was no longer hiding there. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer jumped onto the garbage heap up ahead to see if he could find any traces of Lord Grim. Jiang Botao and Sun Xiang then split up to the left and right, continuing their search.

They had the advantage.

No one needed to remind them. They were very clear about it. Even though they hadn’t succeeded yet, this was a fact that hadn’t changed yet. However, they were taking longer than they thought, so they needed to warn their other two teammates who hadn’t arrived yet.

“Be careful of snipes!” Jiang Botao warned.

“We’ve been careful,” Fang Minghua replied.

Fang Minghua and Lu Boyuan didn’t receive any other info from the team. All they got were those three question marks. They could tell that things weren’t going well on that side. According to their initial plan, no matter who it was on Happy, he or she would check the garbage disposal room. Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, and Sun Xiang should have been more than enough to deal with whoever that was. In this way, the other side would be forced either to rescue or trade for that person. They would first kill whoever was in the storeroom, and then go back and help Fang Minghua and Lu Boyuan. They felt that chances of success were quite high. Happy ended up only sending one person – Ye Xiu. However, after this much time, Ye Xiu still hadn’t been caught by their three players. This became Ye Xiu stalling the three of them, which spelled trouble for Fang Minghua and Lu Boyuan.

Thinking of this unfavorable possibility, Fang Minghua and Lu Boyuan had made adjustments long ago. They stopped going along the direct path that the other three went along, instead taking a roundabout route that couldn’t be seen from up on the chimney.

Su Mucheng didn’t go for the high ground, but by circling around, they were able to avoid Happy’s intercept.

“They circled around,” Fang Rui judged based on the time, so he didn’t continue searching.

“How’s it going there? If you’re still holding on, type 1,” Fang Rui messaged.

“11111111111,” Ye Xiu typed a line of 1s, showing that he was doing great.

“Wow, amazing! What are we even here for?” Fang Rui replied. He was actually very shocked. That was Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, and Sun Xiang! Ye Xiu was just by himself, but he was doing so well that he could type that many 1s? Even Ye Xiu’s teammates found it hard to believe how well he was pinning the enemies down.

Chapter 1619 - Once in a Blue Moon

Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, Sun Xiang.　　

These three top players were being held down by a single person. It was inconceivable, and it also meant a once in a blue moon opportunity.

You needed to be aggressive facing these kinds of opportunities. If you missed it, wouldn't that be a tragedy?

Fang Rui was thinking about the pros and cons, when he saw Su Mucheng type out in the chat: "Scatter!"

That's my line! Fang Rui saw that Su Mucheng had come to the same conclusion. He no longer hesitated.

Samsara didn't go along their original route, likely because Ye Xiu was holding down three of their players. Nevertheless, they would come across them at some point. No matter which route they took, their general direction would remain the same.

However, Samsara had many options available to them. Searching through all of them with just three people might take too long.

Narrowing down these options required intuition and courage. Samsara did not take the most direct route. That was a reality. What would they be thinking when making a choice? If they took a route that was too far, they would be too cut off from the others on the team. Both parties would have trouble helping each other. However, this choice would also prove the most troublesome for Happy. A simpler route wouldn't result in the team coming apart, but Happy would have a relatively easier time intercepting them.

Which choice was Samsara more likely to take? Answering this question required careful thinking. If Happy took the wrong turn, there would be no room for regret.

"Checking nearby!"

Fang Rui was still trying to figure out what Samsara might be thinking, when Su Mucheng made the choice. Then, he saw Dancing Rain climb onto the roof of a nearby storeroom and check their surroundings.

No one.

As expected, Lu Boyuan and Fang Minghua didn't choose an overly conspicuous route. But by moving along the rooftops, Dancing Rain would be able to see more than the others, while also being at a convenient high point if a fight broke out.

"Me left, you right," Fang Rui messaged. He went to the left, while Qiao Yifan went to the right. They started inspecting what simpler routes Samsara might have taken.

But soon afterwards, Fang Rui saw Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain moving along the edges of the storeroom near him and waving her hands at him.

Fang Ming understood her gesturing. She had already checked this area. Fang Rui could move farther to the left and expand their search area.

Fang Rui had Boundless Sea immediately make adjustments. He moved farther to the left before moving on.

We have to be fast!

All three of them had the same thought. Even though Ye Xiu had replied back confidently with numerous 1s, he was certainly under a lot of pressure. It wasn't like they could hope that Ye Xiu could kill the three on Samsara on his own. They needed to hurry and seize the opportunity that Ye Xiu had given them, so they could pull the carpet from under Samsara!

This was what it meant to be an ace player!

As Boundless Sea scouted ahead, Fang Rui felt deeply moved by Ye Xiu. It was true that he was the highest paid player on Happy, using their strongest character. However, if he were in Ye Xiu's position, he felt rather terrified thinking that he could stall those three on Samsara by himself. He didn't have any confidence that he could do it.

Ye Xiu was Happy's true ace player. There was never any doubt about that. Su Mucheng's firm decisions had touched Fang Rui as well. Although he had been thinking the same as Su Mucheng, Su Mucheng had been the one to make the call. This was a huge difference. This was a show of her confidence and her courage in taking risks. Fang Rui had lost to Su Mucheng in this aspect.

Sure enough, my fate is to be a supporting character!

Fang Rui sighed. Even though he didn't have any grand ambitions, every pro player longed to be the core of a team. Because of Fang Rui's playstyle, he was never suitable to be the symbol of a team, and he felt wronged by it. But through Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng, he realized that he wasn't suitable to be an ace player. His playstyle wasn't the only reason.

It's okay though, I'm used to it!

Fang Rui knew how to console himself and quickly discarded those thoughts. He had never cared much about it in the first place. He was just a bit sensitive after feeling unhappy about his performance in the playoffs.

After discarding those useless thoughts, Fang Rui's focus quickly returned back to the match. Boundless Sea continued to move forward. He was currently between two storerooms. The entrances of the storeroom weren't on this side, so it was a rather narrow path. The storeroom to the right of him was longer than the storeroom to the left. He soon reached the end of the left storeroom and arrived at the beginning of a new storeroom. He was at a T-shaped intersection. He looked ahead, but didn't see anyone, so the left then?

Fang Rui hesitated slightly, but he recalled the resolve that Su Mucheng had before and admonished himself.

To the left!

To the left it is!

Boundless Sea took a left turn at the T-intersection. He wasn't letting his emotions affect his decision. Fang Rui had estimated how fast their targets were moving. If they had continued forward, he should have seen them up ahead. However, they hadn't. Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan hadn't found anything either. If he continued heading to the left, he would have a higher chance of finding Fang Minghua and Lu Boyuan.

The path to the left was narrow. Only one person could fit through it at one time. As Boundless Sea ran along it, Fang Rui would look behind himself ever so often. During this process, Fang Rui inadvertently noticed that there was a window at a height of three meters, every few meters along the walls of the storeroom to his right.

This...

Fang Rui could sense that something wasn't right.　

These sort of details were difficult for away teams to notice ahead of time. By utilizing these windows, Samsara could check outside without needing to stand out in the open on top of the roof, making it much harder for Happy to find them.

Fang Rui looked around again. The storeroom behind him and to his left weren't as tall as the one on his right. The view from those windows were quite good. At the very least, they would be able to see Dancing Rain jumping across rooftops.

Then, what about his Boundless Sea? If Fang Minghua and Lu Boyuan were watching from those storerooms, they would have noticed his movements long ago!

Thinking of this, Boundless Sea sped up. As an expert at ambushes, Fang Rui was aware of how dangerous his location was. He was in a long and narrow path that could only fit one person. The walls to his left and right were too tall for him to jump over. If he were pincered, he would be in a very bad situation.

Not good!

Not good!!!　

Samsara had chosen this map. The loading screen gave some information on the map though. For example, the locations of the support zones. Fang Rui's current location was quite close to the support zone at the center. If he were in Samsara's shoes, he would probably...

Bang bang...　　

Two gunshots. Fang Rui's thoughts were interrupted. The crowd burst into cheers.

While Fang Rui was thinking about what his opponents would do, the viewers could see Lu Boyuan's and Fang Minghua's movements. They moved towards Fang Rui's area and then went into one of the storerooms. Then, they went to the windows. From these windows, they soon noticed Dancing Rain jumping across rooftops, looking for them.

The two couldn't see Fang Rui's Boundless Sea because he was blocked by a storeroom. However, the two seemed to somehow know that Boundless Sea was heading towards them. Fang Minghua's Laughing Song ran over to the support zone and switched with Du Ming's Moon Luring Frost. Samsara had five attackers on the field now.

Then, Fang Rui arrived at the T-intersection. While he was figuring out which direction to go towards, the Samsara fans gripped their seats in the suspense. They knew that Lu Boyuan and Du Ming were hiding to the left, waiting to ambush him. But what if Fang Rui didn't go left?

Fang Rui's Boundless Sea ended up going to the left. Their hopes were fulfilled...　　

Bang bang.

Two windows were broken. Lu Boyuan's Chaotic Cloudy Mountain and Du Ming's Moon Luring Frost each broke through a window and jumped down. Their ambush had begun. Samsara's fans had been waiting for this scene to happen. 　　

Fuck!

Fang Rui clenched his teeth. He wasn't surprised by the ambush. But his opponents had truly been cunning. When they saw that Fang Rui had been caught in their trap, they didn't immediately attack. Instead, they held their positions and waited. They hadn't waiting for Fang Rui to move, but for Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan to move. They were waiting for those two to move farther and farther away. As for Fang Rui? Until he was 100% sure that he was ambushed, he couldn't ask them for help. If it turned out that there was no ambush, a false alarm would destroy Su Mucheng's and Qiao Yifan's pace.

And now the ambush had come.

"XXX, XXX!"

Fang Rui had his coordinates already typed into the chat. When he saw Du Ming and Lu Boyuan arrive, pincering him from the front and the rear, he immediately pressed enter. 　　

In front was Lu Boyuan's Chaotic Cloudy Mountain.

Behind was Du Ming's Moon Luring Frost.

Fang Rui didn't hesitate. He immediately turned around and charged at Moon Luring Frost.　

The exit behind him was farther away than the exit in front, but in this narrow space, Blade Masters were easier to fight against than Grapplers. As a Grappler, all Lu Boyuan needed to do was activate Reinforced Iron Bones, walk over, and grab him. Fang Rui didn't think he had any chance of getting past him. On the other hand, Blade Masters had their movements restricted by the narrow space. Many of their skills couldn't be used. Fang Rui could take advantage of that!

Charge!

Boundless Sea sprinted towards Moon Luring Frost. His palms were already gathering qi, but as Moon Luring Frost fell, his hands grasped his sword, and his gaze directed at Boundless Sea!

Downwind Sword Slash!

A sharp sword light fell. Du Ming knew that this terrain was unfavorable for his class. He knew that Fang Rui would certainly choose to get past him. As soon as he broke the window and leapt out, he had started his attack. The sword light from the powerful Downwind Sword Slash filled the entire path. There was no escaping it.

Chapter 1620 - Trapped

The space between the two storerooms was so narrow that it could hardly be considered a path. It was more apt to describe it as a crack between two storerooms.

In this crack, there was only forward and backwards. There was no left or right.

Lu Boyuan’s Chaotic Cloudy Mountain blocked the rear, while Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost’s Downwind Sword Slash blocked the front. Under the shadow of the cold light, Boundless Sea didn’t seem like he had anywhere to run to. At least, that was what everyone thought.

The only one who disagreed was Fang Rui himself.

The fierce sword light was dazzling, but it didn’t steal away his calm. He had already decided that he would break through from Moon Luring Frost’s end. There was no room for hesitation.

Sword light flooded his vision, but he saw a tiny opening where there was no sword light. He didn’t know if he could make it through, but he didn’t have any other choice.

Charge!

Boundless Sea continued to sprint. The moment the sword light descended, he dove forward.

Fang Rui didn’t roll. Instead, he put himself parallel to the ground and borrowed the momentum from the dive to slide forward. Fang Rui had pressed Boundless Sea as low to the ground as possible. He couldn’t go any lower.

Can he dodge it?

Du Ming was confident in his attack. Even if Boundless Sea was laying flat, he didn’t think his attack would miss. But when the sword light came down, Du Ming suddenly discovered that he might be wrong!

His Downwind Sword Slash had a tiny opening. Was it because he hadn’t executed it perfectly enough?

Spiral Qi Kill!

Boundless Sea was still flat on the ground when he fired a blast of qi. Moon Luring Frost was still in the air. The spiralling qi struck his two legs.

Bang!

Moon Luring Frost was flung to the side. His head slammed into the wall.

The crawling Boundless Sea jumped up, his hand placed on Moon Luring Frost’s shoulder.

Grab, twist, throw!

Fling!

Moon Luring Frost shot towards Chaotic Cloudy Mountain like an artillery shell.

Du Ming was at a loss. He didn’t know how his Downwind Sword Slash had missed until he was thrown. As he flew through the air, he looked at the ground and noticed that the place where Boundless Sea had dove towards was very distinct. The ground there was sunken down (凹).

This was just a crack between two storerooms. No one was going to do any maintenance here. As a result, the ground was bumpy. In that instant, Fang Rui had noticed a depression in the ground in front of him. He saw it as a potential safe area and dove towards it.

The slightest difference determined life and death, and it was what allowed Boundless Sea to dodge the Downwind Sword Slash.

That’s the reason?

Du Ming had no choice but to accept it. He hadn’t noticed it. When he used Downwind Sword Slash, he hadn’t thought that the bumps (凹凸) would create holes in his attack.

Moon Luring Frost flew towards Chaotic Cloudy Mountain. Fang Rui had obviously planned for the two to collide.

But Chaotic Cloudy Mountain didn’t retreat.

His arms trembled, Reinforced Iron Bones!

Bang!

Moon Luring Frost crashed into Chaotic Cloudy Mountain. However, due to the Super Armor, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain didn’t budge. Moon Luring Frost fell to the ground, while Chaotic Cloudy Mountain jumped over him and continued forward.

Lu Boyuan’s reaction looked merciless, but the spectating pro players knew that wasn’t the case.

Since Moon Luring Frost wasn’t able to block Boundless Sea, a reversal had happened.

The crack was too narrow. Even if Samsara had two people, without a pincer, the two of them were no different than one person. Both were close-ranged classes. They couldn’t attack at the same time in this narrow path.

As for Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea? After breaking past Samsara’s pincer attack, he was no longer in danger. On the contrary, this narrow terrain was extremely favorable for his Qi Master. Qi Master attacks were AoE attacks. If he let out qi attacks in this alleyway, how was the other side going to dodge them?

Lu Boyuan had thought of this point, which is why he didn’t have time to slow down. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain activated Reinforced Iron Bones, knocking Moon Luring Frost away so he could immediately launch his attacks.

Sure enough, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea had started gathering qi, but Lu Boyuan’s extremely quick response had caught him off guard. The Moon Luring Frost that he had thrown at him unexpectedly wasn’t able to slow him down.

There was time for him to finish using the skill that he had been casting. However, Chaotic Cloudy Mountains had activated Reinforced Iron BOnes and now had Super Armor. His qi attacks would push him. All Lu Boyuan needed to do was tank the attack, and Chaotic Cloudy Mountains would close the distance with Boundless Sea. Then, he could use any grab skill he wanted, and Boundless Sea would be caught in a pincer again.

No matter how reluctant he might be, Fang Rui’s only choice was to give up on this attack!

Boundless Sea cancelled the skill. He activated Cloud Body and then turned and ran.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain stopped. He raised his two hands and grabbed the air.

Cloud Grasping Fist!

The skill that Lu Boyuan had chosen had truly been put to great effect today. In the group arena, he had caught Su Mucheng off guard with the sudden long-range grab, although he wasn’t able to fully take advantage of it. This time, in this narrow alleyway, Cloud Grasping Fist seemed to be very difficult to dodge. If Boundless Sea was grabbed, he would meet his end.

Fuck!

Fang Rui kept looking back as he ran away. When he saw the Cloud Grasping First from Chaotic Cloudy Mountain, he suddenly panicked.

Cloud Grasping Fist was a Qi Master skill, so Fang Rui was very familiar with it. But because he was familiar with the skill, he knew that dodging it in this terrain would be extremely difficult. Crouch? Roll? In this narrow passageway, none of those would work. The only area with enough space to dodge the Cloud Grasping Fist was above him. But there was only so much he could control while in the air, far from the control his opponent had with the skill.

But even so, what other choice did he have?

Boundless Sea stopped and turned around.

To dodge this Cloud Grasping Fist, he would need to time it perfectly and be extremely precise with his movements. Fang Rui didn’t think he would be able to do it while running and looking back.

By this time, Moon Luring Frost had gotten back up from the ground.

Fang Rui had no energy to spare for him. His gaze was fixed on Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s two hands.

Because Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was a Grappler, the equipment that he wore wouldn’t have the preferred stats for a Qi Master. His Cloud Grasping Fist would take longer to gather up the required qi. However Fang Rui wasn’t trying to predict when the attack would come. He was locked onto the movements of his hands.

It’s coming!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s ten fingers tightened. His two hands made a clear pulling motion. Fang Rui jumped into the air. But Lu Boyuan had predicted that Fang Rui would jump. His two hands shifted up slightly.

From the start of the move until it landed, Cloud Grasping Fist could be controlled by the player. This was one of the reasons for why it was so hard to dodge under these circumstances.

Boundless Sea pushed out with his palm, Cloud Pushing Palm!

Pa!

He hit the wall. Boundless Sea immediately dropped towards the ground. He curled into a ball and then laid himself flat to the ground…

Fang Rui was like a fish in the water. He had no reserves about how shameful it might look for him.

The jump had been a feint. He wanted Lu Boyuan to move up. Fang Rui’s true goal was the ground.

Boundless Sea hastily tried to make adjustments. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s two hands pressed down. But it was too late. The qi was only able to rustle the top of his hair. Apart from that, it wasn’t able to grasp onto Boundless Sea.

“Hahahaha!”

Fang Rui was overjoyed. His dodge had been shrewd and technical. He felt like he was a genius.

“I might only be a supporting character, but don’t think I’m easy pickings!” He boasted. Everyone was baffled. Where’d that come from?

Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost jumped onto the roof of a rather short storeroom. Even though it wasn’t a tall one, it wasn’t possible to get onto it with a normal jump. Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost jumped and then jumped again off the wall. He followed with a Rising Dragon Slash in order to get to the right height.

Colliding Stab!

Triple Slash!

Moon Luring Frost didn’t hold back and used his movement skills. Fang Rui had been delayed a bit in order to dodge the Cloud Grasping Fist. The increase in movement speed from Cloud Body wasn’t as explosive as his movement skills. By chaining these two skills, Moon Luring Frost was already in front of Boundless Sea. He stepped out and then twisted his body while in the air. He fell towards the ground, his blade descending. This time, he made sure to take note of the terrain. He wouldn’t let Fang Rui get through because of neglect on his part.

Falling Phoenix Slash!

Sword light descended. This time, Fang Rui had nowhere to run to. Helpless, Fang Rui could only have Boundless Sea put up a Qi Wave Shield to reduce the damage. Behind him, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was closing in. Moon Luring Frost’s sword had cut off his path forward. Despite a few complications, Fang Rui wasn’t able to escape from their pincer.

Suddenly, an enormous explosion sounded. Fireworks seemed to burst forth from the falling Moon Luring Frost. The flames engulfed him, and the resplendent sword light lost its luster.

“YES, SIS MU! PERFECT TIMING!! I LOVE YOU!!!”

Fang Rui was practically incoherent from his excitement. Just when it looked like his life was over, Dancing Rain arrived. Fang Rui almost wanted to cry out how perfect the timing was.

“Charge!” Su Mucheng didn’t have time to share his joy and reminded him.

Fang Rui put away the rollercoaster of emotions he had experienced. Boundless Sea ran for his life. Moon Luring Frost had been blasted out of the air. His Downwind Sword Slash had been interrupted, and his balance had been broken. Even so, Du Ming was able to get a sword slash out. Unfortunately, it had been too forced. Boundless Sea was able to dodge it with ease.

Not good!

From behind, Lu Boyuan had no choice but to re-examine their situation. It had originally been a 2v1. Through the terrain, the two thought they could easily take care of Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea. But they hadn’t expected him to be so slippery. To think he could find a way out from such a dire situation. Now, his backup had arrived. A Qi Master and a Launcher. He and Du Ming had practically no room to dodge their attacks. How were they supposed to fight against them?

This time, the ones trapped was Samsara.

Chapter 1621: Would it kill you to let me look cool for a bit?

"This match... Samsara's home game... it seems... it seems..." Pan Lin thought carefully about he should word things, but wasn't able to find the right words in the end. In reality, he didn't need to explain anything. Most of the viewers had the same feeling as him.

This was Samsara's home game. Samsara had chosen this map. They should be the ones taking advantage of the terrain. It was supposed to be their biggest weapon. But the result? What everyone saw was Ye Xiu taking advantage of the trash room to stall three of Samsara's players. On the other end, at this alleyway, Samsara's two players were supposed to pincer and trap Fang Rui, but in the blink of an eye, the situation was flipped.

How did everything turn out this way?

No one could think of an answer. Samsara hadn't underestimated their enemy. They had sent three players to the trash room to deal with one Ye Xiu, how could that be underestimating the enemy?

At the alleyway, when Chaotic Cloudy Mountain and Moon Luring Frost formed a pincer onto Boundless Sea, everyone thought that it was hopeless for Fang Rui. But Fang Rui had other ideas. He had danced around them, staying alive until Dancing Rain arrived.

This couldn't be considered a mistake from Samsara. Fang Rui was playing incredibly well. A great performance happened when you made outstanding plays in unordinary situations. Samsara's ambush had been set up meticulously. They had started by checking their surroundings through the windows. After noticing Dancing Rain's movements, they thought of this plan. Then, Fang Minghua's Laughing Song went to switch with Du Ming's Moon Luring Frost. When Fang Rui's Boundless Sea appeared, the two didn't act too hastily. They patiently waited for Fang Rui to go in deeper and for Su Mucheng to move farther away.

Every detail had been considered by Samsara. Every part of the plan had been executed well.

Even so, they had failed to trap Fang Rui and inflict heavy injuries onto him like they had liked. Now, they were the ones in a dangerous position.

"Retreat!"

Lu Boyuan said decisively.　　

Rushing forward was an option. However, the terrain wasn't favorable for them. Rushing through attacks from Fang Rui and Su Mucheng was too risky. Lu Boyuan hadn't forgotten that Happy didn't only have Fang Rui's Qi Master and Su Mucheng's Launcher. There was also the threat of Qiao Yifan's Phantom Demon Ghostblade. Maybe he was waiting at the exit at the front. If they successfully made their way out from the alleyway, they would instantly be enveloped by multiple ghost boundaries.

As a result, they could only retreat. They had to retreat.

Lu Boyuan didn't say anything. He had Chaotic Cloudy Mountain turn around and run, while paying attention to Moon Luring Frost's situation up ahead. Moon Luring Frost had been shot out of the air by Dancing Rain. As he fell, Boundless Sea flitted past him with his head turned back. From the looks of it, he planned on looting from a burning house. Lu Boyuan needed to make sure that Moon Luring Frost could run away, so that Du Ming wouldn't need to be rescued.

Sure enough, Boundless Sea stopped. He was a dirty Qi Master, who loved to be sneaky. But at this moment, he was making a huge show, gathering qi around his two palms. Lu Boyuan resisted the urge to charge at him because he knew that Boundless Sea was situated outside both his and Moon Luring Frost's attack range. That was why Boundless Sea was so fearless. That bastard, Fang Rui, was too infuriating. It was like he was purposefully trying to annoy them.

Dragon Wave!

Boundless Sea made his move. The gathered qi transformed into a dragon, which flew out towards his two enemies.　　

Moon Luring Frost had just landed on the ground. Du Ming saw the warning from Lu Boyuan and rolled back. By the time he got up, the Dragon Wave was roaring towards him.

Du Ming didn't even think. He immediately had Moon Luring Frost jump towards the wall and then jump again!

Unfortunately, Rising Dragon Slash had just been used and was still on cooldown. Du Ming had no way of using the same method to send Moon Luring Frost onto the rooftop. The double jump was just to avoid the attack for as long as he could. Dragon Wave could be controlled by the user. Du Ming didn't think he could actually dodge it fully. But with this jump, Fang Rui would need to focus on him so that he could aim his Dragon Wave properly. That would at least buy some time for Lu Boyuan.

The two players on Samsara hadn't forgotten to take care of each other. Lu Boyuan didn't have Chaotic Cloudy Mountain leave first. He made sure that Du Ming could also escape. As for Du Ming? He was using his character's position to help Lu Boyuan escape.

If Lu Boyuan didn't have Chaotic Cloudy Mountain run away, then he would be wasting Du Ming's kindness. There was no time to think about all that though. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain turned around and sprinted away.

Boom!

An explosion from behind him.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's footsteps didn't stop. He looked behind him and saw that Moon Luring Frost had been shot by Dancing Rain again.

Du Ming hadn't forgotten about Su Mucheng's presence. He had predicted that Dancing Rain's attacks wouldn't stop. But in this narrow alleyway, there really wasn't anywhere for him to run to. Du Ming had Moon Luring Frost swing his sword at the missile, but the explosion still hurt him.

Moon Luring Frost lost his balance again, with smoke coming off from him as he fell. Then, Boundless Sea's Dragon Wave swallowed him whole. Lu Boyuan felt terrible.

He wanted Chaotic Cloudy Mountain to turn back, so that he and Du Ming could fend them off together. But he knew very well that doing so would be unwise.

He was abandoning Du Ming, but this was because he had no other choice. Their goal was to win, and winning depended on the entire team. As long as one person stood at the end, they would be the winners.

For the win, to remain as the champions!

Lu Boyuan brainwashed himself, constantly repeating these words to himself. He didn't have Chaotic Cloudy Mountain turn his head back, instead using all his might to run away. He hated his decision, but he trusted that his decision was correct. He wasn't playing just for himself. He couldn't make decisions based on his own likes. Every one of them was carrying the burden of the dreams of the entire team and countless fans.

Ahead is the exit! Keep going!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain rushed out from the alleyway. Only then did he turn his head back.

Even though everything about Du Ming's situation pointed to disaster, Lu Boyuan still felt hope for him, hope that Du Ming could catch up to him.

But no...

Moon Luring Frost was far behind him. Fire and light flashed again and again. Endless qi mixed in with the explosions. Moon Luring Frost's sword light glinted tenaciously.

Again, Lu Boyuan resisted the urge to turn back.

But...

"You can do it!"　

Du Ming typed out in the team chat.　　

He was the one fighting. He was the one who was trying to escape, but Du Ming was the one encouraging him.

Lu Boyuan couldn't keep watching, afraid that he wouldn't be able to resist his urges any longer.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain turned around and immediately rushed towards the support zone.

Seeing Chaotic Cloudy Mountain leave, Du Ming felt at ease. Moon Luring Frost was hit by a blast again. Du Ming tried his best to stabilize the situation, but the attack disrupted his efforts. Moon Luring Frost tumbled to the ground.

How embarrassing!

Du Ming laughed bitterly.

He had been hoping to put on an outstanding performance, especially in this match against Happy. But it looks like this was it.

To the left was a wall. To the right was a wall. He couldn't use many of his skills. As for charging towards them in a straight line, as long as his opponents maintained a certain distance away from him, he posed no threat.

The two on Happy were too experienced. They were carefully taking advantage of the terrain.　

Qi Masters and Launchers didn't have a lot of strong CC abilities. As a result, the two didn't intend on pinning Moon Luring Frost down. The two were doing their utmost to deal as much damage to Moon Luring Frost. If it happened to work out, then they would also try to make it hard for Moon Luring Frost to move around.

I won't make it.

His health was dropping fast, and there was still quite a way to go before he could leave. Du Ming was already certain that he would die before he escaped.

I'll cheer up my teammate first. As for me, I'll just have to contribute as much as I can to our win!

Moon Luring Frost suddenly rolled backwards. Instead of moving to the exit, he went for Boundless Sea.　　

Fang Rui immediately had Boundless Sea retreat, while sending out a Cloud Pushing Palm.

Jump!

Moon Luring Frost got up and jumped, but soon, he heard the sound of a cannon shot.

Falling Light Blade!　

Moon Luring Frost dropped down, the artillery shell whistling past his head.

Falling Blossom Form!

This Level 75 skill had extremely high priority in the air and had a knockdown effect. Du Ming was using it to get down.

Sword petals filled the air, preparing to cut down Boundless Sea.　

But Boundless Sea simply retreated in an extremely dirty manner too, dodging this attack.

"Would it kill you to let me look cool for a bit!!!" Du Ming cursed at Fang Rui. He was obviously unhappy that his attack had missed.

I'm almost dead. Can't you just let me leave a good impression with one final display of might?

"What's cooler than dying at my hands?" Fang Rui responded slickly. Boundless Sea pulled back his hands and then pushed out.

Air Rend Palm!

Qi condensed into the shape of a handprint. With a pa, it struck Moon Luring Frost, stunning him.

Flash Burst!

Fang Rui wasn't polite at all. Seeing how close they were, he immediately let out a high-level skill!　

The qi couldn't expand in this narrow alleyway. It could only burst forth in what little space there was. After Flash Burst came Qigong Blast. Qi filled the alleyway, turning the entire area hazy.　

Dancing Rain's artillery support came down in coordination with Fang Rui's assault.

"Fuck..." Du Ming couldn't help but leave a profanity in the chat. Along with a yellow card from the referee, he left the field.

Chapter 1622 - Cruel Hand Speed

The moment Du Ming left the battlefield, the stadium erupted with wild cheers. The cheers came from the away team stands.

The Happy fans that had followed the team to their away game couldn’t contend against Samsara’s fans. If you weren’t listening carefully enough, it was almost impossible to hear the shouts and cheers for Happy. However, despite their feeble existence, the Happy fans never gave in. They were doing their best to cheer for their team.

Too many people had scoffed at the thought of Happy reaching this step. Some of them even thought of Happy making their way to the finals was a lucky fluke. Losing to Samsara would be a glorious end to their season.

But the Happy fans that had followed their team to Samsara’s home stadium disagreed. They had come to cheer on their team despite the overwhelming opposition because they thought that there was glory in defeat.

What they wanted was for Happy to win, to become the newly crowned champions.

Even if others might laugh at them for overestimating themselves, their thirst for victory wouldn’t waver.

No matter how weak the team was, all of them dreamed of becoming the champions. Happy had struggled their way through the season. Glory in defeat? A glorious end? They didn’t need any of that. They wanted to win. Only by winning and becoming the champions would they be satisfied.

This was why Happy absolutely could not lose this match. It was their final chance.

But no matter how determined they may be, they knew that today’s match would be extremely challenging. Happy was playing in their away game, and their opponents had a one game lead. Happy carried an enormous amount of pressure going in.

A lot of people might have forgotten about this aspect. In their eyes, there was no pressure for Happy because losing was normal. Happy shouldn’t have any hopes of winning.

But reality trumped rhetoric. Happy was showing everyone that their efforts weren’t just to welcome defeat. Despite being on the backfoot, they were still aiming to win.

Two point lead in the group arena.

One person lead in the team competition.

It didn’t matter what had lead to this situation. It didn’t matter what the outcome of this match was. Right now, how stimulating! Happy’s performance was too stimulating! Happy’s fans felt like they had been injected with drugs, especially the ones cheering from the stadium. The noise that they made was a challenge to the devilish home crowd.

So what if we don’t have as many people as you guys? We’re winning. We have a huge three point lead.

From a match perspective, Happy’s lead was enough to leave their opponents speechless, especially after killing off Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost with such ease. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain had taken zero damage, and the damage that Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea had taken was from the pincer by Lu Boyuan and Du Ming earlier. This lead had been earned almost perfectly.

But how could the Samsara fans endure the overjoyed expressions on the Happy fans. Even if they had nothing to back up their cheers, they weren’t going to let themselves be outdone.

The noise in the stadium reached a new high. Samsara’s fans had been able to overwhelm Happy’s fans in the end. However, they were just relying on their numbers advantage. The contribution from each individual couldn’t compare to a tenth of a Happy fan.

Hurry up and do something!

It would be a lie to say that Samsara’s fans weren’t worried, especially seeing how the opposing fans were so delighted. Even if they could overwhelm their opponents in noise, it didn’t give them a sense of victory because victory wouldn’t be decided by which side shouted louder, but by the players on stage. If their team couldn’t beat their opponents, then their cheers and shouts were just empty words.

Come on! Come on!

Samsara’s fans thought to themselves. But there didn’t seem to be any possible turning points right now. Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost had died. Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song had automatically entered the field, and Lu Boyuan’s Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was hurrying over to convene with him. Protecting the healer was a bigger priority than counterattacking.

Did they need to search for hope on the other side?

Trash room.

The conflict between Ye Xiu and Samsara’s three players hadn’t stopped. There hadn’t been any direct clashes, but Ye Xiu being able to escape again and again was enough to astonish everyone. But in return, Ye Xiu had suffered greatly, whether it was himself as a player or his character.

His tempo was starting to falter. His control over Lord Grim was no longer as precise as before.

Zhou Zekai, Sun Xiang, Jiang Botao.

Any one of these three players had the ability to contend with Ye Xiu one on one. None of them could be underestimated. However, Ye Xiu needed to fight against the three of them by himself. The amount of energy he put in wasn’t nearly as simple as three times the amount.

This could be seen from the hand speed statistics. Ye Xiu’s hand speed averaged 340 APM overall this round. As for the team competition itself, his stats were calculated starting from when Lord Grim started clashing with Samsara’s three players. His hand speed for the team competition averaged 510.

510!

For many pro players, this was their limit, but right now, it was Ye Xiu’s average.

Seeing this number, the viewers couldn’t help but gasp in astonishment. But to the pro players watching, they had forgotten to be astonished. This average hand speed of 510 was a form of cruelty.

It was cruel to the opponents and cruel to Ye Xiu himself.

His opponents were dealing with this hand speed, although to be more accurate, it was more the other way around. Ye Xiu needed this hand speed to deal with the pressure that his three opponents were giving him. This cruelty was being undertaken by Ye Xiu alone.

“Too reckless…” Even Han Wenqing made a note of Ye Xiu’s craziness, and he was always fearless in battle.

Zhang Xinjie furrowed his brows, carefully observing the curve given by the data. After all, 510 was an average. His hand speed wasn’t constant. There were ups and downs. As a result, Zhang Xinjie tried to look for relatively clear flat areas. He reckoned that Ye Xiu was resting during these flat periods. That was the only way he could maintain an average hand speed of 510.

But no…

The hand speed curve was extremely messy with huge ups and downs. From this chaotic curve, Ye Xiu’s difficulties could be seen clearly. His actions were being forced out by his opponents. If he didn’t keep up this hand speed, Lord Grim would already be a corpse.

And from the changes in the curve, Ye Xiu was having more and more trouble holding on. Samsara’s three players was aware of this point, so even though they knew that Ye Xiu stalling all three of them was unfavorable for Samsara as a whole, they didn’t make any adjustments. When Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost fell and his name turned gray, they even became more decisive with their attacks.

This was the price of perseverance. It was only by killing Lord Grim would they make up for this price.

Soon!

Lord Grim still had 52% of his health left. He still had more than half of his health left. However, the three on Samsara could feel Ye Xiu’s reaction speed and response slipping. They knew that Ye Xiu was on the verge of defeat.

“Ye Xiu’s nearing his limits…” Huang Shaotian said gravely. Yu Wenzhou didn’t make any objections. Sitting in front of them, Wang Jiexi and Tiny Herb’s hand speed expert Liu Xiaobie were also silent.

“Uh…” But on the other side, there were people who wanted to say something but were hesitating.

Lou Guanning, Zou Yunhai, Wen Kebei, Gu Xiye, Zhong Yeli.

Team Heavenly Swords had come to watch the match as well. Even though all of them had powerful and wealthy family backgrounds, in the pro circle, they were the younger generation. Their skill couldn’t compete with the top players. But while their seniors had come to the same conclusion, these five disagreed. When Wen Kebei heard Huang Shaotian say “he’s nearing his limit,” he couldn’t help but say something. But when he saw that no one was paying attention to him, he hesitated and decided against it.

“What is it?” someone asked. It was Sun Zheping, who had come with them.

“I don’t think… this is God Ye Xiu’s limit?” Lou Guanning said.

“What?” Sun Zheping was doubtful.

“You guys all think this is limit?” Wen Kebei had been too afraid to speak up because everyone else had come to a different conclusion than him.

“It seems like you guys know something?” Sun Zheping asked.

“Uh…” The five on Heavenly Swords looked at one another.

“We’ve experienced his hand speed before,” Lou Guanning said.

Sun Zheping laughed. Ye Xiu’s hand speed. Hadn’t he experienced it nine years ago? At that time, Ye Xiu had been at his peak. No matter how unwilling Ye Xiu might be or how great he still was, his age was there. Certain things couldn’t be decided by pure willpower.

“That’s not what I mean. We saw his hand speed through different means,” Lou Guanning saw that Sun Zheping had misunderstood him. They were rookies. How could they dare to talk about experience facing someone as senior as him?

“Different means?” Sun Zheping didn’t understand.

“Piano!” Lou Guanning said.

“What?” Sun Zheping was very interested. “Piano?”

“Piano!” Wen Kebei affirmed.

“What about it?”

“God Ye Xiu can play it!”

“Are you thinking of someone else?” Sun Zheping wasn’t the type to waver, but hearing them talk about Ye Xiu playing piano, he was having trouble believing them.

“Of course not! During last year’s All-Star Weekend…” Lou Guaning quickly told them about their dinner party that night.

“The tempo in a piece is fixed, so based on the amount of time that Ye Xiu used to finish the piece, we can calculate his hand speed. Playing piano is different than playing Glory, but at least for piano, Ye Xiu’s max hand speed should be…” Lou Guanning suddenly stopped at the crucial moment.

“How much?” Sun Zheping asked.

“900…” Lou Guanning’s voice trembled. He knew the answer beforehand, but he was still scared by it, “48 seconds, a steady 900 APM.”

Chapter 1623 - A Serious Mistake

“900? Impossible!!” Sun Zheping blurted out.

He might not know that much about playing piano, but he had fought against Ye Xiu in game before. Ye Xiu’s hand speed was indeed very fast, and right now, the three on Samsara had forced him to an average hand speed of 500. 900? What did that mean? It was a hand speed nearly twice as fast as his current one, and that wasn’t a peak, but an average over 48 seconds.

“It’s true though…” Lou Guaning said. He could understand Sun Zheping’s reaction. They had the same reaction as him when they saw it. In the beginning, they just felt like Ye Xiu was playing really fast. They had no concept of the exact numbers up until Lou Guanning calculated it. The number had nearly shattered their eyes.

900!

Lou Guanning and the others might not be as experienced as Sun Zheping, but they could imagine how terrifying such a hand speed was. Later, they looked through a bunch of Ye Xiu’s matches, but they never saw him come close to such a high hand speed in any of them.

Playing piano was different from playing Glory. The left and right hand did completely different things for one…

The five of them could only explain it with this reasoning, but they truly had a hard time convincing themselves. After all, 900 was a terrifying number. Pro players averaged around 300. When a more complicated or chaotic event happened in the team competition, their hand speed might go up. For example, Ye Xiu was playing 1v3 against Samsara and had been forced to a hand speed of 500. Even so, 500 was a huge difference from 900!

Maybe it was because piano and Glory were different that Ye Xiu couldn’t reach a hand speed of 900 in Glory. But there were plenty of numbers lower than 900. Even if you subtracted 200 or 300, it was still a hand speed of 600 or 700; 500 shouldn’t be his limit, right?

That was their opinion at least. After Sun Zheping accepted that Ye Xiu had reached an APM of 900 when playing piano, his view was no different from theirs.

“That guy’s… still holding back?” Sun Zheping thought about it for a moment, but immediately shook his head.

This was the finals. Playing 120% wouldn’t even feel like it was enough. Hold back? What a joke!

Maybe it is because you can’t actually get to an APM of 900 in Glory?

Sun Zheping couldn’t think of any other reasoning, but even if was using this reasoning to convince himself, from this moment on, he began to look forward to what might happen next. Who cares if there’s a difference between piano and Glory? From this moment on, to Sun Zheping, Ye Xiu’s highest average hand speed was 900!

How terrifying! In that case, did his true maximum break past 1000?

Sun Zheping was thinking of it from a Glory perspective. He didn’t know that on that day, when Ye Xiu had played piano, he had just been playing it for the sake of playing fast. There were no changes in rhythm like there were in Glory.

So what is the answer? Hurry up and let us see it!

While the other pro players felt like Ye Xiu couldn’t hang on for much longer, Sun Zheping and the five on Heavenly Swords had different thoughts.

While their conversation had gone on, Ye Xiu’s situation worsened. Under the siege from Samsara, Lord Grim was forced into a corner, an actual corner in the trash room. There was no place for him to hide any longer.

Victory is in sight!

The Samsara fans had started getting excited. Even though they had lost a player first, if they could take down Lord Grim, the trade would be worth it. Similar to how Su Mucheng and Fang Rui had dispatched Du Ming without taking much damage, it would be the same for the three on Samsara. They hadn’t taken much damage in their fight against Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. Now, it just depended on how troublesome Ye Xiu’s final struggle would be.

“Careful!”

Jiang Botao warned in Samsara’s chat. They had to keep cautious to not give Ye Xiu any chance to deal damage to them. They didn’t immediately attack. Instead, they waited until every one of them was in the perfect position, so there wouldn’t be any openings when they started their attack.

“It’s over!” Sun Xiang declared.

He had always longed to beat Ye Xiu. He wanted to surpass him. Unfortunately, they were currently in a 3v1 situation. It probably wouldn’t be considered a win in his eyes, but it wasn’t important. It was true that Sun Xiang wanted to surpass Ye Xiu, but he wouldn’t bicker too hard over it. In the end, his ultimate priority was to win the match. If they didn’t win, even if he beat Ye Xiu on his own, it wouldn’t have any meaning.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

One Autumn Leaf charged forward with the powerful momentum of a Battle Mage to seal off Ye Xiu’s final hopes.

Surpassing you will have to wait. Today, the most important thing is to win this match!

Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf charged forward, carrying this conviction. Suddenly, his screen turned dark.

What’s going on?

Sun Xiang nearly leapt out of his seat. Had his computer malfunctioned?

That was his first thought, but he soon discovered that it wasn’t that his computer had crashed. It was because there was an indicator showing on the screen that his character couldn’t see.

Blind?

Where did it come from?

He had been carefully observing each and every movement from Lord Grim. When had he used a skill that inflicted Blind?

Unable to see his opponent, Sun Xiang couldn’t control his Dragon Breaks the Ranks. He heard a gunshot. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer had started firing. However, those bullets didn’t seem to be going towards where he was going? Lord Grim had already run over there?

Sun Xiang was utterly confused. The crowd had exploded too. Through their spectator view, when One Autumn Leaf charged forward, a hazy pitch-black light quietly descended. The area covered by the dark light was surrounded by faint magical symbols in a giant circle. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf had entered this zone. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves was at the edge of it too. As a result, their screens instantly turned black. The two of them had been Blinded.

This is…

Ghostblade’s Dark Boundary?

But with how carefully they had been watching over Ye Xiu, there was no way they wouldn’t notice him casting a Ghostblade boundary, let alone letting him finish casting it. What’s going on?

Most of the crowd was just as confused, up until Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer started firing, not towards Lord Grim, but towards a corner of the trash pile. When he moved laterally to get a better view, their confusion was cleared up.

One Inch Ash!

Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash had appeared here.

The crowd went wild. Practically no one had noticed. On one side was the battle between Fang Rui, Su Mucheng, Du Ming, and Lu Boyuan. On the other side was Ye Xiu, Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, and Sun Xiang. It was already difficult enough deciding which of the two battles they should watch. How could they bother paying attention to someone who wasn’t a part of either battle?

When did Qiao Yifan get there? How did he get there without anyone noticing him?

Many of the viewers blanked. Their last impression of One Inch Ash was him splitting up with Fang Rui and Su Mucheng to search for the two on Samsara. After that, he had been forgotten.

And now, his sudden appearance had rescued Ye Xiu from what had seemed to be certain death.

The three on Samsara had made a mistake. Their highly focused attention had turned into their weakness. They had only been following Ye Xiu’s every move.

“A beautiful stall,” Wang Jiexi sighed.

His explosive 510 hand speed wasn’t just to hold on against the combined assault from Samsara. He had responded back strongly to capture the complete attention of the three from Samsara, so they would make this mistake.

Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash came to the trash room and got into this position without any of the players on Samsara noticing.

This was a mistake, but no one could blame Samsara for it. The viewers, who could see everything if they chose to, had been absorbed by the intense fighting. They hadn’t noticed Qiao Yifan either. How could they expect the three on Samsara to, when they themselves couldn’t?

Sun Xiang and Jiang Botao had been blinded. For a moment, they didn’t know what had happened.

With the two of them blinded, Ye Xiu was able to easily make his way past them. As for Zhou Zekai, who hadn’t been affected by the Dark Boundary, he could only shift his attention to One Inch Ash.

The control capabilities of a Phantom Demon were too powerful. Right now, it was just a Dark Boundary. If Qiao Yifan was left alone to do as he pleased, an Ice Boundary, Ash Boundary, Silence, and so on would come one after the other. If that happened, they would be the ones in trouble.

Qiao Yifan!

He had once been a nobody in Tiny Herb, and now, in the finals, he was the one who Glory’s number one, Zhou Zekai, was personally taking care of. The people, who had taken note of Qiao Yifan’s arduous path to his current state, felt deeply moved.

The spectating pro players couldn’t help but glance at Tiny Herb for their reactions. Qiao Yifan had been given up on by Tiny Herb, and now he had reached the finals ahead of them. What were the Tiny Herb players thinking right now?

You can do it, Yifan!

Gao Yingjie didn’t say anything, but he was quietly cheering for his best friend. Many of the pro players had also overlooked Qiao Yifan due to the two separate battles taking place, but Gao Yingjie wasn’t one of them. No matter what else was going on in the match, he would always be mindful of Qiao Yifan.

When Fang Rui sent the message asking for help, Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan had both turned around. He had originally thought that Qiao Yifan would be heading towards Fang Rui to help him, but to his surprise, Qiao Yifan had gone towards the trash room.

“A brilliant decision.”

“What outstanding situational awareness.”

Gao Yingjie heard the praise pouring out from his seniors beside him. He was happy for Qiao Yifan, and proud.

During their time together in Tiny Herb, the two of them were often compared to each other. Gao Yingjie shined with his fame as a prodigy. On the other hand, Qiao Yifan was completely overshadowed by him. From the start, it seemed like Qiao Yifan would never reach the same heights as Gao Yingjie.

But now, Qiao Yifan had gone ahead to the finals before him, and he had made an outstanding play on stage.

Now, I’m the one chasing after you. I hope that we’ll be able to meet in the finals someday, Gao Yingjie thought to himself.

Chapter 1624 - No Longer Alone

His best friend was proud of him, but what about Qiao Yifan himself?

He was calm.

He was considered a major threat by Glory’s number one. Perhaps this might’ve had him shaking in excitement back when he was just a no name player in Tiny Herb, but now it wouldn’t.

Because this was the battlefield, and there was no such thing as being of a higher or lower standing here, only victory and defeat. On the battlefield, you should be focused on one thing: how to claim victory. This was something he had learned from Glory’s number one, the other Glory’s number one.

One Inch Ash leaped back, dodging the first wave of Cloud Piercer’s bullets. Zhou Zekai had Cloud Piercer continue his advance, but that was when he suddenly realized something.

They had neglected to consider Qiao Yifan, but was Qiao Yifan the only one they had missed? Wasn’t there another member of Happy that had yet to appear? Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was here, so what about the other one?

Cloud Piercer suddenly jumped up, turning his body around in the air, continuing his attack as he scanned the area.

Fwoosh!

A pure white flame lit up the area he just jumped away from.

Sacred Fire, as expected!

As he spun, he searched for the quickly fading glimmer of holy light that marked the use of Sacred Fire. Though it was weak, it stood out in this dim lighting of the warehouse.

It wasn’t just Qiao Yifan who had come, but also Happy’s healer, An Wenyi, and his Cleric, Little Cold Hands.

1v3? That was just now! It was now a 3v3, and Happy had a healer.

However, whether Qiao Yifan or An Wenyi, their reputation couldn’t compare to any of the three members of Samsara. In terms of strength, as well, they were at a disadvantage. Even if they had a healer, this wasn’t necessarily an advantage.

Still, compared to before, this was already a massive difference, especially with how Happy’s two had suddenly launched their assault when Ye Xiu most needed it, completely destroying Samsara’s rhythm.

Jiang Botao and Sun Xiang had lost their camera sight, having been blinded, but that didn’t mean that the team chat would disappear as well. They soon got the gist of the current situation from Zhou Zekai in the team chat.

No matter what, leaving the Dark Boundary was their current top priority, but even for pro players, being blinded made it nigh impossible to accurately orient themselves. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf had just finished a Dragon Breaks the Ranks, which brought him near to the edge of the Dark Boundary. Unfortunately, it also brought him to the trash room wall and he couldn’t move forward anymore, not even a step. This direction wouldn’t provide an out to the Dark Boundary. Luckily, Sun Xiang had a vague impression of the area, so he had One Autumn Leaf turn. Even without being able to see anything, One Autumn Leaf still managed a perfect 180-degree turn.

These seemingly insignificant details were a great indicator of a player’s skill. Those who understood sighed in admiration, yet then Lord Grim flicked his arm and sent a grenade One Autumn Leaf’s way.

Sun Xiang couldn’t see, so he had no idea that Ye Xiu was taking advantage of his blindness. The watching Samsara members wanted nothing more than to charge up there and warn him, but then there was a bang and a rumbling explosion. Zhou Zekai had gotten Cloud Piercer to destroy the grenade.

In the end, not only did the grenade not hit One Autumn Leaf, the explosion it made even acted like a guide for Sun Xiang. Although relying on sound meant that he wasn’t as precise as he would’ve liked, One Autumn Leaf did head in Lord Grim’s direction, Evil Annihilation levered in front of him. Even blinded, he never lost his offensive pose.

Boom…

But immediately afterwards, One Autumn Leaf was consumed by light and fire. Ye Xiu had opened fire with the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella again. Anti-Tank Missiles used the boom of the grenade as cover to fly at One Autumn Leaf. The two weren’t that far away, so even if Zhou Zekai wanted to warn him in the team chat, it would be too late. One Autumn Leaf still ended up hit and staggered back several steps from the explosion. While blinded, it was already impressive that he could keep his balance, but his sense of direction was completely shot.

Zhou Zekai wanted to send messages to guide him, but he didn’t have a chance. His split in attention had Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash safely finishing the cast of a boundary. Then when he tried to go and help, One Inch Ash’s phantom ghost’s power fell and a chill instantly spread into a boundary. He had summoned an Ice Soul, Ice Boundary.

Crack crack crack…

The sound of ice crystals breaking crawled up Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves, freezing him solid.

Originally, Jiang Botao was in a better situation than Sun Xiang. At the very least, he didn’t get blocked by a wall. After being blinded, he had Empty Waves back up rapidly. With just a few more leaps until the edge of the boundary, he was hit with One Inch Ash’s Ice Boundary and just happened to get frozen, too, stopping him within the Dark Boundary.

Blinded and immobilized, Jiang Botao had basically been taken out of the game for now. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer turned to attack One Inch Ash again, but this time Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim leaped at that heap of trash, drawing his sword in midair and striking.

Cloud Piercer bent backwards to dodge the sword light, a grenade already heading for the leaping Lord Grim.

But Ye Xiu didn’t have Lord Grim dodge. With a flash of light, he sheathed his sword, and the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella became tonfas. Lord Grim’s body trembled…

Boom!

The explosion enveloped Lord Grim, but was unable to stop his leap.

Reinforced Iron Bones!

Ye Xiu had activated this skill for Lord Grim and brute forced his way through. As for the damage, he didn’t care, because he was no longer fighting solo. An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands darted forward and sent Lord Grim a Holy Cure without any hesitation.

Pure white light enveloped Lord Grim before blooming outwards. This was the visual effect of a critical heal, even managing to overpower the visual effect of the explosion for a moment.

Twenty-four percent!

This instant cast, high healing Holy Cure with a lengthy cooldown of five minutes had crit and restored Lord Grim’s health by twenty-four percent instantly, making Samsara’s three’s efforts seem insignificant. They had struggled with Lord Grim for so long, only managing to take out forty-eight percent of his health. Now half of that had been annihilated by a single Holy Cure from An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands. The Samsara fans could practically feel their hearts breaking.

With Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim advancing forcefully, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer had no choice but to retreat. He had an important task right now: protect Jiang Botao and Sun Xiang’s characters the best he could. He couldn’t let them fall completely into One Inch Ash’s boundaries.

One Inch Ash was casting again. Zhou Zekai could see that. Without caring about his own situation, Cloud Piercer’s gun aimed towards One Inch Ash. Unexpectedly, Lord Grim’s form darted forth in front of him, using his body to block his attack, courageous and fearless.

Zhou Zekai had no time for playing games with him. Cloud Piercer rolled to the side, once again putting One Inch Ash into the line of fire.

Bang!

The gunshot rang out but Zhou Zekai then saw the bullet bounce. Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had stretched over, open, knocking the bullet away.

However, Cloud Piercer had two guns. His right gun might have been sealed, but what about the left.

The mouth of his left gun was outside of Myriad Manifestations Umbrella’s block, but… he couldn’t see!

Bang!

The gun went off without being able to aim properly, Zhou Zekai could only wager a guess.

Unfortunately, this bullet didn’t hit, heading somewhere at least three body units away from One Inch Ash.

Whirlwind Kick!

Zhou Zekai ignored the result of that shot and quickly had Cloud Piercer kick out.

Lord Grim had already changed the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella into its shield form, so the class was switched to Priest as well. Reinforced Iron Bones was a Fighter skill, so it lost its effect under the Priest Class.

In that moment, Zhou Zekai still had such a clear judgement. He didn’t panic at all due to the disadvantageous situation.

This kick still ended up blocked by Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, but then Cloud Piercer’s left hand gun, Shattered Frost, erupted with gunfire!

Whirlwind Kick had two goals. One was to try and swept Lord Grim to the side, the other was that the downwards leaning movement gave him a small window to strike.

Just one glance and it was enough for Zhou Zekai to lock onto his target.

Whirlwind Kick and his view of One Inch Ash were quickly blocked by the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, but in that moment, he had locked One Inch Ash’s position into his mind. Cloud Piercer’s left hand was extremely steady. Even though Zhou Zekai couldn’t see, he knew that his gun was aimed at One Inch Ash.

Bang!

A gunshot, and then the bullet flew, just brushing past the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

This was just a normal attack, but it was enough to interrupt any casting.If the caster moved or was hit, the casting would be interrupted.

There was enough time!

From the Phantom Ghost’s Power coming off of One Inch Ash’s blade, Zhou Zekai could tell he was summoning a Silence Boundary.

Silence Boundary sealed the skills of the characters that were caught within. With such a disgusting effect, it was obviously counted as a high level skill, and thus the cast time was longer.

However… the flashes of light that rose soon after told Zhou Zekai, he had still failed. His bullet hadn’t hit.

Silence Boundary was similar to Dark Boundary, but the visual effects were more intense, making it murky inside the boundary. It couldn’t blind people, but this murkiness made things hard to see.

Dark Boundary, Ice Boundary, Silence Boundary, three overlapping boundaries. They couldn’t see, couldn’t move, and now they couldn’t even use any skills, only normal attacks.

However, Zhou Zekai couldn’t help them. Ye Xiu didn’t want him interrupting One Inch Ash just now, which was why he was on the defensive, getting in the way all the time. Now, with Silence Boundary out, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was immediately thrust forward at his face.

Shield Attack!

This skill had a Dizzy effect, so even if it didn’t deal damage, it was a bad idea to take it. Cloud Piercer hurriedly rolled to the side and glanced towards One Inch Ash, seeing Little Cold Hands standing guard there. It seemed that Little Cold Hands had taken the bullet for One Inch Ash just now.

One Inch Ash began to cast a fourth Ghost Boundary.

Chapter 1625 - Not Perfect, But the Best

Ghost boundaries wouldn’t last forever. A smart Phantom Demon would plan out when and where to place down their ghost boundaries to maintain an uninterrupted flow of crowd control on the battlefield.

But right now, Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was placing down ghost boundaries one after the other. Dark Boundary, Ice Boundary, Silence Boundary. All of these were ghost boundaries with powerful crowd control. Usually, these boundaries would be linked together such that the opponent would always be under the effects of one of them. However, Qiao Yifan had set all three down on top of each other to completely seal off Sun Xiang and Jiang Botao. One Inch Ash was even in the midst of casting a fourth ghost boundary.

This sort of set up was often only seen during critical moments, but today, because of One Inch Ash’s abrupt arrival, the Dark Boundary had caught Samsara completely off guard. Sun Xiang and Jiang Botao were robbed of their sight temporarily as a result. His Dark Boundary was extremely effective. Adding an Ice Boundary and a Silence Boundary on top of it didn’t seem to be necessary.

“Was Qiao Yifan a bit too hasty?” Seeing that a fourth ghost boundary was about to be placed down, Pan Lin couldn’t help but ask.

“It was a dangerous situation. With this being his first time on the grand stage, it’s hard not to be a bit nervous.” Li Yibo was quite understanding. But he was also implying that he agreed with Pan Lin’s viewpoint.

“Li Xuan, what do you think?” Before Qiao Yifan even finished setting down the three ghost boundaries on top of each other, the pro players were already discussing the issue. In the end, everyone pushed the question onto Li Xuan, who was considered the number one Phantom Demon.

“If it were me, just one Dark Boundary would be more than enough,” Li Xuan spoke his thoughts. At first, it sounded pretty much the same as Pan Lin’s and Li Yibo’s viewpoint, disagreeing with Qiao Yifan’s excessiveness. However, the other pro players could hear the difference.

Because he said, if it were me…

Not long after finishing the sentence, Li Xuan looked to be a bit hesitant. After saying “um” for a bit, he added: “And Xinjie.”

And Xinjie?

Xinjie was, of course, referring to Zhang Xinjie. Why’d he mention him?

The pro players quickly caught on.

Li Xuan meant switching An Wenyi with Zhang Xinjie.

In other words, if it were Ye Xiu and him, and Xinjie too, he would be confident that just one Dark Boundary would be enough.

“Tch!!” Everyone clicked their tongues in disdain at Li Xuan.

Ye Xiu, Li Xuan, and Zhang Xinjie. That was a lineup even grander than Sun Xiang, Jiang Botao, and Sun Xiang. Zhang Xinjie was a Cleric too. Their class composition would be superior to Samsara’s too. Li Xuan was basically saying that under these circumstances, one Dark Boundary was enough to take control of the battle.

The two on the field were Qiao Yifan and An Wenyi, who weren’t as experienced or as skillful as Li Xuan and Zhang Xinjie. Just relying on the two of them as support, Ye Xiu might not be able to hold off the three from Samsara.

This was why Qiao Yifan didn’t hold back and try to be as efficient as possible. He quickly placed down one ghost boundary after another to ensure that Sun Xiang and Jiang Botao would be completely imprisoned.

He wasn’t looking to control the battle for a long period of time, but rather for a quick burst.

Was this because he was lacking confidence? Of course not! Even the number one Phantom Demon, Li Xuan, couldn’t guarantee that he could do it with just one Dark Boundary. He even needed to add in Zhang Xinjie to it.

This wasn’t a lack of confidence. It was a careful consideration of the situation, a decision based on a clear recognition of his own limits.

While everyone was still in discussion, the densely layered ghost boundaries suddenly burst open. The ghost souls danced about, creating foul wind and bloody rain, stealing away Empty Waves’ and One Autumn Leaf’s life.

After Qiao Yifan placed down the fifth ghost boundary, he had One Inch Ash activate Ghost Feast right before his first Dark Boundary disappeared.

Nervous?

Not at all. The placement of the fifth ghost boundary and the perfect Ghost Feast was the biggest proof. Anyone who thought that he had been placing down ghost boundaries out of panic was completely wrong.

The pro players couldn’t help but applaud Qiao Yifan’s performance.

His play wasn’t perfect. Perfect would be slowly placing down ghost boundaries at the right time to take complete control of the battle until the battle was over.

But it was the pinnacle of what was possible given the circumstances. In this situation, he had made the best possible decision and executed it brilliantly. It wasn’t possible to have done it any better.

Beautiful! Very beautiful!

His outstanding situational awareness allowed him to clearly examine the problem from an overall perspective. He had taken into consideration that he and An Wenyi were relatively weak. He had also taken into consideration that Ye Xiu was exhausted after a long battle against three of Samsara’s players. Then, he made his decision based on all of these factors, a decision that was making everyone gasp in amazement.

The pro players exclaimed in admiration. At the same time, they couldn’t help but glance at Team Tiny Herb. They had let go of such an incredible player. They must be regretting it, right? Especially since Tiny Herb had a Ghostblade player!

Zhou Yebai.

Tiny Herb’s Ghostblade player was also a Phantom Demon. Right now, he was already regretting coming to watch this match. Everyone else was staring at him, their gazes cutting into him like a dagger.

Qiao Yifan used to be a nobody in their team, and now, he had actually grown to such an extent? He just had to change classes to a Ghostblade and choose to be a Phantom Demon too. Everyone was constantly glancing at him, openly showing pity that Tiny Herb had let go of Qiao Yifan and treated him as the real nobody in Tiny Herb.

Zhou Yebai felt extremely uneasy. He really didn’t want to admit that he was worse than Qiao Yifan, but he also knew that if he was confident, he wouldn’t be feeling uneasy. He was afraid that his teammates would also compare him to Qiao Yifan. He was afraid that they would look down on him and then cast him away just like how they cast away Qiao Yifan before…

“Focus on the match.”

A voice suddenly interrupted Zhou Yebai’s thoughts. He turned his head to look at who said it and saw the serious expression on his captain’s face.

Zhou Yebai relaxed, and stopped feeling afraid. Because he could tell that his captain, Wang Jiexi, wasn’t affected by the other pro players’ views. Wang Jiexi was only unhappy with him because of how he was letting it get to his head.

He wasn’t here just for fun, sitting there and enjoying the lively finals match. He was here to watch the teams play and learn from them.

He had been thinking too much.

Qiao Yifan was playing incredibly well, but he wasn’t the best. Li Xuan was better. The only difference was that Qiao Yifan had once been a part of Tiny Herb, but who cared? What was important was that he worked hard to better himself and do what needed to be done. Competition was everywhere in the pro scene. Qiao Yifan was just one of the many competitors. He was used to this sort of competition. Why should he be afraid now? He should be working hard so that one day he would win praise from everyone else just like Qiao Yifan had done.

He’s really making me a bit jealous! How annoying!

Zhou Yebai no longer felt nervous because of Qiao Yifan, but rather became more motivated. If even a nobody could come this far, then why couldn’t he?

After collecting his thoughts, he calmed down and focused on the match again.

Triggering Ghost Feast also meant sacrificing the crowd control on Samsara. While the two Samsara players were being devastated by Ghost Feast, Qiao Yifan had One Inch Ash retreat.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Seeing One Inch Ash’s retreat, Ye Xiu immediately followed. Lord Grim completed the hand seals for Shadow Clone Technique while in combat against Zhou Zekai. His real body teleported away, and he ran away together with An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands.

Cloud Piercer chased after them furiously, but Lord Grim lay the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella on his shoulders, protecting his back, preventing any interference from his pursuer.

Sharpshooters had powerful attacks, but their crowd control was rather weak. They controlled the pace of the battle through attacks. But because Lord Grim was holding his shield up, none of his attacks were landing. In the blink of an eye, Lord Grim and Little Cold Hands made a turn at a trash pile and disappeared from Cloud Piercer’s sight.

Zhou Zekai didn’t stop his pursuit though. The Ghost Feast was ending, and Jiang Botao and Sun Xiang would quickly be back to normal. It was their time to regroup and counterattack. They couldn’t give Happy a chance to rest. The spectating pro players thought the same. Zhou Zekai had a clear understanding of their situation. Qiao Yifan had burst them down because he wasn’t confident that they could win in a prolonged fight. Samsara knew this as well. Zhou Zekai wasn’t going to let his opponents leave so easily.

Cloud Piercer rushed to the edge of the trash pile and jumped. Using Aerial Gun, he glided through the air and made the turn. Lord Grim and Little Cold Hands were once again within his sights. Zhou Zekai didn’t have Cloud Piercer jump down from the trash pile. As a Sharpshooter, the tall trash pile was an advantageous position for him to shoot from.

Bang bang bang bang…

As soon as he landed on top of a new trash pile, Cloud Piercer’s dual guns began firing furiously towards Lord Grim and Little Cold Hands. On the other end, Jiang Botao and Sun Xiang had gotten away from the Ghost Feast. Their characters rushed out with traces of the ghostly power still lingering on them. They saw Cloud Piercer shooting, pointing them in the right direction. They gnashed their teeth in anger as they hurried over.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

Seeing Cloud Piercer’s shooting trajectory, Sun Xiang immediately deduced where Happy’s characters were located. One Autumn Leaf swung his Evil Annihilation and used a Rising Dragon Soars the Sky at that trash pile.

3v3, we’re not afraid! Sun Xiang and Jiang Botao were quite determined.

But the viewers really wanted to tell them: 3v3? Not for much longer… Su Mucheng and Fang Rui were almost there.

Chapter 1626 - An Existence Surpassing Common Sense

"Samsara's falling apart!"

The pro players started discussing the issue spiritedly. There had been two separate battles taking place. On Happy's side, there was Qiao Yifan and An Wenyi. Now, Su Mucheng and Fang Rui were on their way to help after resolving their battle. Happy's two sides were gradually coming together, beautifully linking up with each other.

As for Samsara? They had failed to take down Ye Xiu in a 3v1. They had failed to take down Fang Rui in a 2v1. Then, Su Mucheng arrived and worked together with Fang Rui to take down their Du Ming.

It wasn't that Samsara didn't care about linking their two sides together, but rather that their link had been thoroughly severed by Happy. As for how, the pro players looked at each other in dismay.　　

One side had been stalling 1v3, while the other side had been stalling 1v2. What type of tactic was this? This was a Star Tactic!

Happy versus Samsara. Samsara was the only team in the Alliance with four All-Stars. Of these four, three of them were ranked among the top ten. Samsara couldn't shine any brighter, yet they had actually been stifled by a Star Tactic from Happy?

The standard Star Tactic was to rely on the team's star player to fight against the opposing team at a numbers disadvantage. By doing this, his teammates would conversely have the numbers advantage in their battle, which would then be used to win. There could be two or even three separate battles taking place, but in either case, there would be one battle where the team would be at a numbers disadvantage and another battle where the team would be at a numbers advantage. The battle where there was a numbers disadvantage would depend on the star's superior skill to make up for it. This was the crux of a Star Tactic.

There had indeed been battles this match where Happy was at a numbers disadvantage, but Happy didn't use it to get a fight where they had the numbers advantage.

Happy had undoubtedly employed a Star Tactic. The usual tactic wasn't seen, not because Happy didn't have a choice. Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, and Qiao Yifan had gone to intercept Happy's healer with clear intentions of fighting Samsara with a numbers advantage. It was just that they ended up in a situation, where the terrain for the fight was advantageous enough that they didn't need the numbers advantage. Since Qiao Yifan wasn't needed, he went to go help Ye Xiu, who was stalling 1v3.

Ye Xiu was the reason that Happy had the upper hand. From the hard numbers, of the four attackers on Happy, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim might have the lowest DPS and the lowest health. However, he was the key to why Happy was able to obtain this lead. Without his efforts as the foundation, none of what happened would have happened.

This was Glory's number one player!　

A single player holding off against three top ten players. Among these was Zhou Zekai, who was ranked first on the All-Stars list.

Using the word "star" to describe this performance was too degrading. This was a superstar, an ultra superstar!

No one knew how to describe using words what Ye Xiu had done because it didn't seem like something a human could do.

It wasn't like Happy had never employed this type of tactic before. You wouldn't even need to look too far back. The most recent case was in their first game against Blue Rain in the playoffs. Happy had relied on Wei Chen to stall Blue Rain, 1v2. It could be considered a Star Tactic, but it wasn't a very thorough one. Wei Chen hadn't actually established an equilibrium in his battle. In reality, his role was more as a sacrifice. He had sacrificed himself to stall for as much time as possible so that the others on Happy could accomplish their true objective. It was a bit different from a Star Tactic on a fundamental level.

On the other hand, in their away game today against Samsara, Happy was employing a true Star Tactic.

Moreover, in this Star Tactic, Ye Xiu needed to hold off against top players. In fact, their current fame even surpassed Ye Xiu's. Unfortunately, the three top players on Samsara had been held off. In front of Ye Xiu, their star power appeared dim and dull.

The Star Tactic wasn't just a tactic, but also a display of skill: using overwhelming skill to fend off against superior numbers. This was the core of the Star Tactic.

It was hard to argue against this point, and it was precisely for this reason that no one thought Ye Xiu would be able to succeed against the likes of Sun Xiang, Jiang Botao, and Zhou Zekai. How could he not be defeated?

To everyone, it wasn't even a question. Samsara was no exception. That was why they didn't think they would fall apart. They thought that they would be able to quickly make short work of Ye Xiu. Who would think otherwise? It was practically common sense. The pro players watching the match had thought the same.

But...

Ye Xiu was an existence that surpassed common sense.

The situation seemed to be getting more and more disadvantageous for Samsara, but the players themselves were still quite upbeat.　　

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf swung at the trash pile.　　

The loosely piled up trash didn't form much of a resistance. The magic transformed into a dragon and pierced straight through the trash. However, the grab-priority Rising Dragon Soars the Sky was quite an imposing attack. Such an explosive force created quite a lot of noise. Ye Xiu and An Wenyi didn't act like they hadn't noticed.

Dodge!

Lord Grim and Little Cold Hands immediately moved away from the garbage heap. Then, they saw dots of light coming out from the trash. The light became more and more dense until the dots of light converged together to form a brilliant ball of light that seemed to be dissolving everything it touched.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!　

A flying dragon tore through the garbage heap. If Ye Xiu and An Wenyi had reacted slightly slower, they would have likely been devoured by the attack.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky missed, but it had disrupted Ye Xiu's and An Wenyi's movements. Zhou Zekai was watching them intently from behind. How could he miss such an opportunity? Bullets rained down. Jiang Botao used the bullets as cover to close the distance.

Light Wave Slash!

Empty Waves rushed out and swung his sword, using the Spellblade's fastest wave slash skill. The attack was tricky too. It wasn't directly aimed towards Lord Grim or Little Cold Hands, but rather right in the middle between them.

As a result, if the two wanted to dodge the attack, they would need to dodge in opposite directions. It would force the two of them apart by one or two steps of distance.　

Don't look down on a distance of a few steps. In this situation, it was a heavy blow. This separation would likely make it so that the two of them would have to escape from their pursuers on their own.

Ye Xiu had the ability to contend against the three of them,but An Wenyi? Without Ye Xiu's protection, he would certainly die.

So the attack couldn't be dodged!

Hua!

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened up.

Because of the burst from Cloud Piercer, the shield form wasn't a good option. However, right now, it was the only option. The durability on the umbrella was quickly being depleted.

Happy had the upper hand?

Yes, from an overall perspective. However, they first needed to get past this current obstacle. No matter how you looked at it, they were facing one of Glory's strongest trios, and none of them had lost any of their fighting strength.

Chapter 1627 - Stake Everything in One Throw

An Wenyi definitely wasn’t the best in terms of technique, but his ability to assess the situation was absolutely at the top.

Lu Boyuan saw that Du Ming had stayed behind to stop Fang Rui and Su Mucheng from reaching him, so he resisted the urge to turn back and rescue Du Ming. What about An Wenyi? He was in a similar situation, being protected by Ye Xiu. He didn’t hesitate and immediately had Little Cold Hands run away.

Ye Xiu was thankful.

Chen Guo didn’t like this part of An Wenyi, but Ye Xiu was quite thankful for it. A healer needed this sort of calm and rationality. In the beginning, when he first met An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands, it was his clear judgement and machine-like precision that had gotten Ye Xiu’s attention. Later on, he discovered that An Wenyi also possessed this rationality. For Ye Xiu, it was like buying one thing but getting another for free. How could he not be happy?

An Wenyi didn’t lose this characteristic of his on the competitive stage. Even if he had always been regarded as Happy’s weakness, he didn’t stop trying his best to seize every opportunity he saw.

He had survived in Happy as their weak point. Happy had devised strategies revolving around him as the weak point. Not only did An Wenyi not object, he cooperated with them earnestly.

It was impossible for him not to feel a bit embarrassed or worried, but he was a rational person. He recognized that this was the best way to use him. That was why he didn’t object or let these emotions affect him.

He was constantly trying to improve. During this process, he wanted to make himself as useful as possible to the team. Whether it was using his strengths or his weaknesses, he would find the most suitable way to coordinate with the team. If it wasn’t for his almost heartless rationality, it would be very difficult for him to achieve this goal.

His rationality was the true source of his value on the team.

Because of his rationality, he was able to play in a way that caught Ye Xiu’s attention out of the countless number of other players in the game.

Because of his rationality, even though he wasn’t the most skilled, he knew how to do what the team needed, whether that need was a usage of his strengths or his weaknesses.

Because of this rationality, he could worry but never waver when facing a difficult choice.

He had persevered.

Two years ago, he had been just another player in the Heavenly Domain. He was someone who couldn’t even make it to the elite ranks of Tyrannical Ambition.

Two years later, he had made his way to the playoffs. Here, he eliminated Tyranny’s vice-captain, Glory’s number one healer, Zhang Xinjie. Now, he stood together with his team together in the finals, at the highest stage in Glory.

An Wenyi was an extremely rational person, yet everything that had happened sounded like nonsense.

The journey hadn’t been an easy one, and it only made him treasure it all the more. He treasured using everything at his disposal to help the team win.

This was why he ignored whether Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim lived or died. His Little Cold Hands turned tail and ran, ran for his life.

Because this was the best way for him to help Happy win.

3v3?

It didn’t feel like a 3v3.

Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash had taken a different route than them. An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands and Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim retreated together, but during their retreat, they encountered a problem. Lord Grim had been tossed aside so that Little Cold Hands could get away. In the blink of an eye, it was Ye Xiu versus Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, and Sun Xiang again.

For a moment, Samsara had trouble digesting this sudden change. From their understanding, An Wenyi should have stayed behind to help Lord Grim hold them off until Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash looped back around to their rescue.

Based on this understanding, they had already planned out how they could take advantage of this somewhat clumsy Cleric to trouble Ye Xiu. The healer needed to be protected, after all.

But that Cleric just threw Ye Xiu aside and ran away.

It went against common sense. Where was the loyalty, the self-sacrifice? The three on Samsara felt uncomfortable, not at Ye Xiu’s situation, but at their own. With An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands running away, they would once again be facing Ye Xiu in a 3v1. It was the exact same situation as before. They would rather have Little Cold Hands stay behind for a 3v2. That way, they could use Little Cold Hands to hinder Lord Grim. A 3v2 would actually be easier for them.

As a result, One Autumn Leaf rushed out.

Sun Xiang was the one who wanted to surpass Ye Xiu the most, but right now, he gave up on Ye Xiu. With Cloud Piercer and Empty Waves suppressing Lord Grim, he had One Autumn Leaf chase after Little Cold Hands. The three on Samsara felt like this was better than focusing only on Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. Ye Xiu was truly too troublesome to deal with.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella suddenly let out a cold light. The umbrella was still floating in the air, but Lord Grim had made his way to One Autumn Leaf’s side.

Shining Cut!

Sun Xiang wasn’t able to react to it, and the Shining Cut hit him. Even though the attack didn’t have a strong knockback, it had caught Sun Xiang off guard. One Autumn Leaf stumbled into the nearby garbage heap.

Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao were startled. This mixup had come as a complete surprise. Lord Grim had made his way to One Autumn Leaf’s side, but his weapon was still in its original position? Did he… throw his weapon away?

Soul Guidance?

Any pro player would think it was Soul Guidance when they saw a weapon being thrown, but that would be impossible! Because Lord Grim had used Shining Cut. Although Soul Guidance would toss out the weapon, it wasn’t a drop. The weapon was considered equipped, and only skills pertaining to the weapon’s class could be used. It wasn’t possible to switch weapons while using it either.

But Lord Grim had clearly used a skill from a different class. If he didn’t have the right weapon equipped, it wouldn’t be possible for him to use Shining Cut.

Had he brought along a second weapon?

Or maybe the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella could be split into two? He dropped one half of it, but continued to use the other half?

How confusing… For now, it wasn’t possible to figure out what had really happened. However, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella being dropped onto the ground was a fact. Jiang Botao reacted immediately. Empty Waves rushed towards it without regard for anything else. The only thing in his sights was the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. If could pick it up, wouldn’t Lord Grim become completely useless?

Picking up the opponent’s weapon in a competitive match…

It had never happened before in the Glory Alliance. No one remembered if the competitive rules had anything regarding it. Even the veteran, Li Yibo, wasn’t certain. He wasn’t sure what to say, although luckily for him, there was no time for him to say anything.

Just when Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves was about to grab the umbrella, a very unfamiliar move on the competitive stage, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella suddenly flipped over. There was no thrusting motion, yet the umbrella was already pierced through Empty Waves. Lord Grim once again appeared right before him.

Impossible! How could he be so fast!

Jiang Botao looked to the side out of instinct. As he turned around, Lord Grim used Circle Swing.

As a result, Jiang Botao saw Lord Grim again, standing where One Autumn Leaf had been. In his hands was a dagger.

A shadow clone…

Shadow Clone Technique!

Jiang Botao’s screen turned pitch black.

Blind?

No.

Lord Grim had thrown him into the garbage heap using Circle Swing. The garbage was physically blocking his sight.

The garbage heap loosened, and Empty Waves plunged straight into it. His two legs were dangling in the air.

The Samsara fans wanted to laugh, but they couldn’t. It was extremely embarrassing. On the other hand, the pro players had no pity for him. They had started roaring in laughter.

“He definitely did it on purpose!!” Chu Yunxiu pointed at Lord Grim onscreen, laughing uncontrollably.

Everyone agreed.

Tossing the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella as bait, Shining Cut to block One Autumn Leaf, Shadow Clone Technique to get back, and then a Circle Swing to throw Empty Waves into the garbage heap. Everything had been calculated. If Ye Xiu wasn’t confident he would succeed, how could he have thrown away his character’s lifeline so easily?

“Senior Ye Xiu really is brave though…”

The rookies couldn’t manage to laugh. They had been frightened to death. Let alone a weapon as important as the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, the thought of throwing even a normal weapon scared them. This sort of method was truly difficult for them to accept.

Even though Ye Xiu had probably calculated it all beforehand, matches were always full of twists and turns. What if the Shining Cut had missed One Autumn Leaf, and Sun Xiang counterattacked? What if while he was using Shadow Clone Technique, Cloud Piercer hit him before he finished the seals?

Although none of that happened, the possibility of a mistake gave the rookies lingering fear.

“That’s why they say, the truly capable are daring!” someone sighed.

The truly capable are daring? Everyone fell silent. It didn’t feel quite right. The truly capable? That was a gamble risking everything!

Had that moment really been that important? That he needed to stake everything in one throw?

A scare and a laugh. In the end, they analyzed the play like they normally did. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had already rushed out towards Cloud Piercer, who was standing on top of a nearby garbage heap. At the same time, the sound of cannonfire boomed.

Su Mucheng!

Dancing Rain!

She had finally arrived. Her ultra long range firepower was in coordination with Lord Grim’s assault. The Season 4, Season 5, Season 6, Season 7 Best Partners were finally pairing up for the first time in this team competition.

Chapter 1628 - Interweaving Battle

Boom!

Dancing Rain fired at the garbage heap, but her goal wasn’t as simple as just splashing scraps into the air. When Cloud Piercer twisted his body to dodge the artillery shell, the explosion left a huge hole in the trash pile. The scraps of trash launched into the air rained down.

Amidst the rain of trash and the reflection from the flames, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim rushed out.

Bang bang bang bang…

Zhou Zekai hadn’t given up on attacking Lord Grim. Even while dodging the artillery fire, Cloud Piercer’s dual guns were aimed steadily towards Lord Grim.

The fire and light from the explosions, the raining trash, and the flying bullets constructed a chaotic scene, and Lord Grim pushed his way through it, one step, two steps…

Lord Grim moved swiftly, growing closer and closer to Cloud Piercer. Although Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer was moving away to keep their distance apart, he wasn’t able to do it perfectly under Su Mucheng’s barrage of artillery shells, especially since he was against Ye Xiu as well.

Fortunately, he wasn’t alone.

Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves would need a bit of time to climb out from the garbage heap, but Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf had only taken a stumble from the Shining Cut. He quickly regained his balance. He originally wanted to continue chasing after An Wenyi’s Little COld Hands, but he heard the sound of cannonfire from behind him and turned to look. He saw explosions threatening Cloud Piercer and Lord Grim closing in.

Help?

This was Sun Xiang’s first thought, but One Autumn Leaf rushed out in a different direction instead, continuing his chase onto Little Cold Hands. When he broke into a run, he also swung his spear towards Empty Waves, who had plunged head first into the garbage heap. Empty Waves wouldn’t be affected by the attack, but the spear knocked away much of the trash burying Empty Waves, helping him out quite a bit. Sun Xiang left the responsibility of helping Zhou Zekai to Jiang Botao, while he gave up on his attachment towards Ye Xiu. He made the more proactive choice: continue to pressure the enemy healer to suppress the entire team.

Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves freed himself from the trash. He looked around and instantly understood the situation. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was about to reach Cloud Piercer. Jiang Botao didn’t say anything and decisively swung his sword.

Fire Wave Slash!

Raging flames swept towards Lord Grim.

Fire Wave Slash was the strongest of the wave slashes. It was quite fast too. In the blink of an eye, it had arrived behind Lord Grim. At this moment, Lord Grim jumped forward. If he continued along his current path, he would undoubtedly be hit by the flames. His figure flickered…

Boom, hit!

The crowd erupted into applause. The Fire Wave Slash sent Lord Grim crashing into the garbage heap. Jiang Botao had gotten his revenge.

But Jiang Botao felt uneasy.

It hit? It actually hit?

Yes, he was very surprised. The timing had been good, using it just when Lord Grim was jumping, making it harder for him to respond. However, he really hadn’t expected the attack to connect. His goal had been to stop Lord Grim from continuing forward. Who would have thought it would actually hit? It shouldn’t have against someone like Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu must have let it hit him. Jiang Botao was certain.

Sure enough!

When the flames from the Fire Wave Slash receded, all that remained was a burnt mark on the garbage heap. Lord Grim had vanished.

Where did he go?

Underground Tunneling Technique!

Lord Grim suddenly popped out from the top of the garbage heap. However, Cloud Piercer had just passed by him!

Ye Xiu didn’t have Lord Grim dodge the Fire Wave Slash. He used the momentum to make his way into the trash pile so that he could Underground Tunneling Technique.

But Zhou Zekai’s intuition was outstanding. Once Lord Grim lay himself against the garbage heap, he wasn’t able to see him anymore. At that moment, he immediately gave up on keeping his position at the top of the garbage heap and had Cloud Piercer jump down.

Missed!

The Underground Tunneling Technique wouldn’t be able to touch Cloud Piercer. Was Lord Grim just going to let this opportunity go by thouogh?

No!

Ye Xiu reacted quickly. He could only see the corner of Cloud Piercer’s jacket when he tunneled out, but it was enough for him to make his decision. He cancelled Underground Tunneling Technique. While in the air, Lord Grim twisted his body. A cold light swung out, Falling Light Blade!

His two hands pressed down on the sword, chasing after Cloud Piercer. The Falling Light Blade let Lord Grim fall much faster than Cloud Piercer.

Gunshot.

Ye Xiu had acted immediately when he saw the jacket on Cloud Piercer. On the other hand, when Zhou Zekai heard a sound from behind him, he immediately realized that Lord Grim had appeared behind him. It would be too late for Cloud Piercer to turn around and aim, so he placed his two guns on his shoulders and shot behind him.

Bullets flew out!

Sword light swept down!

It was difficult to tell which one was faster, but in an instant, the two characters were tangled together. Cloud Piercer’s bullet shot into Lord Grim’s skull at point blank range. Lord Grim’s sword pierced through Cloud Piercer’s back, the sword tip sticking out from his chest…

Who won, who lost in this sort of entanglement? Even the spectating pro players couldn’t immediately make the call. Lord Grim and Cloud Piercer crashed towards the ground together. Both characters seemed to have lost their balance.

Then, an explosion, a magic wave!

Their reliable partners had come to their support at practically the same time.

The explosion swept away Cloud Piercer, while the magic wave swept away Lord Grim. The two of them separated, but their fight was far from over. Both of them had lost their balance, but everyone could see that they were both fighting to regain it. Bullets shot out from Cloud Piercer’s guns. Lord Grim raised his hands, and the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was thrown into the air. Shooting stars rained down, Exorcist skill, Starfall!

Cloud Piercer was hit by Starfall and smashed into the trash. Lord Grim was also repeatedly hit by the bullets and fell into the trash as well. Neither of them could dodge. They could only do their best to attack the enemy. In the end, the two were separated, and if they kept this distance away from each other, wouldn’t Zhou Zekai’s Sharpshooter have the upper hand?

A Satellite Beam descended from the sky, straight down onto Cloud Piercer.

Zhou Zekai and Ye Xiu were evenly matched, but their two supports became the dividing line. When the two were unable to keep up their attacks, Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain decisively fired a Satellite Beam, dealing a heavy blow to Cloud Piercer. As for Jiang Botao? He could only cry. It wasn’t that he didn’t want to. His class didn’t have that sort of attack. Lord Grim and Cloud Piercer had fallen into the trash pile. Su Mucheng’s Launcher had a way to attack from the skies, but his Spellblade? Waltzing Wave Slash?

He could only send out a Waltzing Wave Slash.

The Divine Chains in Empty Waves’ hands leapt into the air, forming a rainbow that dropped down onto Lord Grim.

Jiang Botao had executed it beautifully. The rainbow Waltzing Wave Slash was also pleasing to the eye, but how could a Waltzing Wave Slash compare to a Launcher’s most powerful skill, Satellite Beam? No matter how beautiful the Waltzing Wave Formation looked, its damage couldn’t compare to Satellite Beam’s. It was just better than nothing.

Lord Grim was hit by the attack and was then immediately able to stand up. As for Cloud Piercer? The Satellite Beam was still in place, pressing down on Cloud Piercer. The trash surrounding him was thrown into the air. The Satellite Beam had blasted the trash pile apart.

Jiang Botao could only watch as Dancing Rain attacked from afar. He had no way to stop her or interrupt her. All he could do was prevent Ye Xiu from adding oil to the fire.

Light Wave Slash!

The wave slash went straight for Lord Grim.

But Ye Xiu had clearly expected that Jiang Botao would attack him. After Lord Grim got up, he immediately used a movement skill to dodge the Light Wave Slash. He jumped into the air, Aerial Gun, and then Rotor Wings. In the blink of an eye, he had reached the other end of the trash pile into Dancing Rain’s Satellite Beam and down the hole…

The Satellite Beam had blasted a hole in the garbage heap, and Cloud Piercer was at the bottom of it. Surrounding him was trash, and above him was a giant beam of light. He was completely immobilized. Zhou Zekai tried hard to get himself some space, but before the Satellite Beam ended, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim dropped down into the hole.

Papapa, Lord Grim stepped on him with Eagle Stamp. How could Zhou Zekai dodge it? He could only have Cloud Piercer trade blow for blow with Lord Grim. However, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim activate Reinforced Iron Bones. The bullets connected, but couldn’t move him. After the Eagle Stamp, he elbowed Cloud Piercer in the forehead. And then, while the two were practically touching each other, he used all sorts of close combat techniques.

The Satellite Beam had ended, but Cloud Piercer was in an even more precarious situation than before. The trash surrounding him seemed to be Ye Xiu’s helpers, burying his guns. Knee Strike! It hit, but Lord Grim was still in front of him. The Sharpshooter martial art skills didn’t have strong knockback. There was no way for him to clear a way out by himself.

Light!

The surrounding trash suddenly lit up.

Nebula Wave Slash!

Jiang Botao used the Spellblade’s Level 75 skill, destroying the trash from the outside. He was planning on fishing Cloud Piercer out. The light from the Nebula Wave Slash continued to penetrate the trash, but before the last push, flames swept towards him.

Chapter 1629 - The Match Point Outside the Equilibrium

Heat-Seeking Missile!

Jiang Botao heard the sound of the missile whistling through the air, but he wasn’t able to have Empty Waves dodge while using Nebula Wave Slash. The Heat-Seeking Missile’s area of effect wasn’t something that could be evaded by just twisting around. To dodge it, he would need to move away by a considerable distance.

Dodge, or continue with Nebula Wave Slash? He could only choose one!

There was still time for him to dodge, but it would interrupt his Nebula Wave Slash. If he continued with Nebula Wave Slash, he wasn’t certain he would succeed. If he didn’t, everything would be lost.

What should he do?

The thought flashed through everyone’s mind. On the stage, Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves didn’t budge. He continued to pour magic into his Divine Chains. He didn’t hesitate. He chose Nebula Wave Slash.

Will he succeed?

The missile fell. Empty Waves swung his sword, completing the last of Nebula Wave Slash…

Boom!

A mushroom cloud sprouted. The powerful shockwave pushed away the impacted trash. Empty Waves was in the center of the explosion, which launched him into the air.

Nebula Wave Slash? Had it been interrupted?

No, it hadn’t!

The instant the mushroom cloud set off, the trash hit by Nebula Wave Slash suddenly let out a glimmer of light. The magic waves spread out, lifting the pile of trash, breaking it apart like a shattered magic cube. Cloud Piercer and Lord Grim suddenly appeared in everyone’s view. Cloud Piercer was exempt from Nebula Wave Slash’s damage, but not the shockwave from Heat Seeking Missile. Lord Grim wasn’t affected by Heat Seeking Missile, but the Nebula Wave Slash sent him flying into the air.

Three characters had been affected by the attacks. The only one unaffected was Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain, who continued to provide artillery support. The previous assistance from Lord Grim became the greatest starting point for her. Explosions revolved around Cloud Piercer. Su Mucheng was still focusing Cloud Piercer.

However, Zhou Zekai was no longer trapped and wouldn’t let the long-ranged gunfire hit him so easily. With a smooth Quick Recover, Cloud Piercer rolled and got up from the scattered pile of trash. His arms were crossed against his chest, his two guns shooting towards both Lord Grim and Dancing Rain.

His technique was beautiful to see, but because he was attacking two separate targets, his firepower towards each of them was cut by half. To pro players, it wouldn’t be any threat to them. Both Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng would have no problems dealing with it. But through these attacks, Zhou Zekai was able to find his footing again.

Jiang Botao seized the opportunity to stabilize Empty Waves. His attacks wouldn’t be able to threaten Dancing Rain at this distance. Lord Grim was his only possible attack target at the moment. Wave slash after wave slash was thrown at him.

Both sides were attacking and defending back and forth. Their battle was as brilliant as ever. One side was Samsara’s Zhou-Jiang duo that had won two championship titles together, the other was the Ye-Su duo that had won Best Partners four years in a row, yet had never lifted the championship trophy together. The two greatest duos in the Alliance didn’t disappoint. Each high point was replaced by another. But no matter how brilliant their battle was, the two sides were evenly matched. There wouldn’t be any breakthroughs coming from this side. This 2v2 wouldn’t be decided so quickly.

What was the match point?

Pan Lin and Li Yibo analyzed this issue. The director changed the camera angle according to their discussion. The live crowd was undoubtedly having the time of their lives. Not only did they have the projection technology showing them the overall situation, the numerous screens in the stadium displayed all the little details. Because of this, they didn’t have the same focus as the viewers watching in front of their TV or computer. While these viewers were watching the battle between Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, Ye Xiu, and Su Mucheng, they didn’t have much information on any other players.

Would Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf be able to catch An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands?

When would Samsara’s other two players arrived to help their teammates in the trash room?

Since most of the live audience were Samsara fans, they particularly concerned about these questions.

Lu Boyuan, Fang Minghua. Although these two hadn’t yet arrived at the trash room, they knew what was happening there. With multiple battles taking place separately, the players needed to constantly update each other on their situation. Using that information, they could make adjustments accordingly. It was necessary. As a result, whether it during the 3v1, or when Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi, and Su Mucheng disrupted their plans, the two had a general understanding of the situation through the team chat.

They had to go help, of course. The viewers were also waiting for the moment they arrived.

But Fang Rui and his Boundless Sea became their biggest hindrance.

Not long after sending off Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain, he found a place to ambush Lu Boyuan and Fang Minghua.

Practically the moment Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain rushed into the trash room and started providing support, Lu Boyuan and Fang Minghua reached there. They just happened to see Jiang Botao’s report concerning Su Mucheng.

There was no mention of Fang Rui.

This was the issue that the two immediately noticed from the report. Communication between the team members needed to be immediate and accurate. If Jiang Botao didn’t see Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea, then he wouldn’t mention him. If he didn’t mention him, then he hadn’t seen him.

But the two didn’t see Boundless Sea either, so they immediately sent back the information. They were aware of the terrain in the trash room and of Fang Rui’s dirtiness. Jiang Botao’s message only said that they hadn’t seen Boundless Sea, but it didn’t mean that he definitely wasn’t there. Happy’s support had layers. It was very possible that Fang Rui didn’t immediately appear after entering, instead waiting for an opportunity to make the decisive blow.

Just when they sent the information on Fang Rui, Fang Rui ambushed them.

The two hastily updated their information on Fang Rui, correcting their previous report. This was extremely important. An incorrect report could lead to the players on that side making an error in judgement.

Then, the 2v1 unfolded. No one felt like the situation was too serious. Fang Rui staying behind to ambush them was likely just to stall for a bit of time. Seeing how the ambush spot and trash room wasn’t far apart, it didn’t seem like it would cause any major complications. After all, Samsara could just have Lu Boyuan tangle with Fang Rui, while Fang Minghua’s Cleric continued forward. It would make the ambush completely meaningless.

The theory was very simple, but the problem was that it didn’t happen!

Fang Rui’s target was very obvious: Fang Minghua’s Cleric, Laughing Song. Boundless Sea let them run past him a bit and then he quietly sneaked up behind them and used Cloud Grasping Fist.

Fang Rui had underestimated their caution. They didn’t forget to constantly look around. Fang Minghua turned his head and noticed Boundless Sea. He immediately had Laughing Song dodge. Lu Boyuan noticed the change and was even more resolute. He directly put himself in front of Laughing Song.

They had considered the possibility that Fang Rui had entered the trash room but hadn’t appeared yet, but they had also considered the possibility that he was on the outside waiting to ambush them. Because of Fang Rui’s dirtiness, it was hard to guess.

As for the latter possibility, they had their own plans ready. As soon as they saw Boundless Sea, Lu Boyuan had Chaotic Cloudy Mountain put himself in front. Fang Minghua didn’t hesitate. Laughing Song continued to move to leave Lu Boyuan to deal with Fang Rui.

“Where are you running!”

The public chat had been quiet the entire time up until Fang Rui made his move. A message popped up. Fang Minghua obviously wasn’t going to actually stop running just because Fang Rui told him to stop. Fang Rui’s message did nothing to the people facing him right now. It was more to distract the players on the other end who didn’t know what the situation was.

As for whether or not it actually distracted them, Fang Rui didn’t care. Cloud Grasping Fist grabbed Lu Boyuan’s Chaotic Cloudy Mountain, locking him down. Fang Rui obviously wasn’t going to grab the Grappler over to himself. That would be suicide.

Cloud Grasping Fist was cancelled. Boundless Sea rushed forward. He lowered his body, immediately giving a sense of dirty play.

Lu Boyuan’s Chaotic Cloudy Mountain moved forward to intercept him. The crouching figure in front of him was truly quite irksome.

Fang Rui’s dirty movements had proved to be effective. Everyone acknowledge that his movements were quite logical. By making himself smaller, he was making it harder for the opponent to hit him.

This sort of method wasn’t only used by Fang Rui. However, whenever Fang Rui did it, apart from looking dirty, no one knew how else to describe it. As soon as anything touched his hands, it would stink of rotten meat.

Lu Boyuan looked at the opponent in front of him and had no choice but to adjust Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s stance. Usually, he could just use his hands to grab the opponent’s shoulders and start wrestling with him. But because Boundless Sea had lowered himself, he would have to make a slightly wider movement, making it different than against a normal opponent.

Charge!

Lu Boyuan chose to take the initiative to attack in an attempt to proactively take control of the battle. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain bent down, his two arms hanging in front of him like a big gorilla. This stance would make it easier for him to grab Boundless Sea.

The distance between the two sides quickly pulled closer. Lu Boyuan watched Boundless Sea’s hands carefully. If there was even the slightest movement…

It’s coming!

Boundless Sea suddenly hid his hands. Lu Boyuan knew an attack was coming.

Qi Bullet!

An attack shot at Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s face. All Lu Boyuan could see was a bright light in front of him.

Blocking his view, an old trick! Chaotic Cloudy Mountain tilted his head slightly, and he could see again. His two arms spread out, ready to wrap around Boundless Sea. But then, he saw Boundless Sea twist around to dodge to the side. Lu Boyuan had expected it though, and adjusted himself accordingly.

How fast!

Suddenly, Boundless Sea accelerated and whistled past Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s clutches.

Cloud Wind Body!

Chapter 1630 - Grab That Healer

Cloud Wind Body was a skill that buffed the user’s senses. It gave the user greater control over qi and allowed the user to sense their targets with qi. Boundless Sea’s sudden acceleration wasn’t a result of Cloud Wind Body, but rather a different skill: Qi Flowing Cloud.

Qi Flowing Cloud increased the Qi Master’s speed in every way: movement speed, attack speed, cast time, and so on. Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea had two buffs stacked on top of each other, Cloud Wind Body and Qi Flowing Cloud. As a result, he sped up and had greater control over his increased speed. He just barely brushed past Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s fingertips, narrowly escaping from the danger. However, with this dodge, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was instantly left behind him.

Lu Boyuan knew that this spelled trouble. By the time Chaotic Cloudy Mountain turned around, Boundless Sea was already two body lengths away from him.

Two body lengths…

This distance was painful to Lu Boyuan. Of the 24 classes, not including the two healers and the solely long-ranged attackers like Launchers, every other class posed a threat at this distance, including Strikers and Brawlers. All of them had skills that could cover this distance. The only exceptions were Grappler.

And now, Boundless Sea just had to be two body lengths away from him. With his currently buffed movements, Fang Rui had done this on purpose. He was putting himself on the edge of danger in order to be as efficient as possible. From start to finish, he had never regarded Lu Boyuan’s Chaotic Cloudy Mountain as his opponent, but rather as an obstacle. Everything he had done was to get past this obstacle in the most efficient way possible. His true target was Laughing Song.

It was as if Fang Rui had simply sprinted in a straight line. Fang Minghua hadn’t expected that Fang Rui would be able to get past his protector, Lu Boyuan, so easily as if he were a ghost. Just like this, Boundless Sea made his way behind him.

It was too late for Fang Minghua to think of a way to block him. Boundless Sea raised his hand and grabbed towards him, Fling!

Laughing Song was thrown backwards. Lu Boyuan’s Chaotic Cloudy Mountain rushed back, but Boundless Sea rolled away, avoiding Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s clutches. Boundless Sea got up and sprinted towards Laughing Song.

Cloud Grasping Fist!

Lu Boyuan knew that in terms of speed, he couldn’t match the buffed Boundless Sea. Step by step, he fell behind. He might as well use the skill that he added to his weapon today in an attempt to pull Boundless Sea towards him.

But Fang Rui was truly cunning. He had clearly been running towards Laughing Song, but midway through, he suddenly rolled. As he rolled, there would be an instant, where he would be able to see behind him. In that instant, Lu Boyuan noticed the flow of qi in the air.

Qi Blade!

It was too late for regrets. Lu Boyuan should have activated Reinforced Iron Bones before using Cloud Grasping Fist. He hadn’t thought about it meticulously enough, and had been fooled by Fang Rui.

The Qi Blade flew towards him. Cloud Grasping Fist would definitely be interrupted. Lu Boyuan could only cancel the skill and then dodge it. With no other options, he could only chase after Fang Rui.

In just a few steps, Boundless Sea would reach Laughing Song, who had rolled and was getting up. Fang Minghua wasn’t some nobody. Previously, he had been caught off guard because he didn’t think Fang Rui would be able to get past Lu Boyuan so quickly. This time, he was prepared. When Laughing Song got up, a bright light shone from his cross, Angel’s Protection. The light spread out in a circle.

Angel’s Might, a 360 degree halo of light that forced the target back, ignoring Super Armor. This Paladin skill was the skill that Fang Minghua had chosen to put on his weapon.

Once the skill animation came out, there was no chance of dodging or resisting it. Shields could counteract numerous skill effects, but the knockback from Angel’s Might was an exception.

Boundless Sea could do nothing against it. With how close of a distance they were at, everyone didn’t even think Fang Rui could react to it. However, the moment the Angel’s Might touched him, he quickly pushed forward with his palms.

Cloud Pushing Palm!

It was a low-level skill that dealt little damage, but it could pass through space to strike the target and had a knockback effect. The knockback effect was inversely proportional to the distance. The closer you were, the stronger the knockback.

When Boundless Sea used Cloud Pushing Palm, Angel’s Might swept over him, forcing him back. The Cloud Pushing Palm had worked. As the light spread out from Laughing Song’s Angel’s Might, his body slid back.

The knockback from Angel’s Might was far stronger than that of Cloud Pushing Palm. However, Laughing Song’s Angel’s Might was only level one, so it didn’t push him too far. The bigger problem was that behind Boundless Sea was Chaotic Cloudy Mountain. If he was grabbed, even if it was just once, then there was no hope in him pinning down Laughing Song any longer.

Even the average viewer knew it, let alone the players on stage.

The moment Angel’s Might came out, Lu Boyuan immediately prepared himself, staring intently at Boundless Sea. As Boundless Sea was pushed back, he sunk down. He was planning on putting out a dirty stance, so he could dodge the moment he could move again.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain sprinted over, lowering his center of gravity as well. But to his surprise, Boundless Sea kept sinking down. His two hands were about to touch the ground… was he planning on running on all fours?

Just when this thought flashed by Lu Boyuan’s head, Boundless Sea’s two hands really did hit the ground. But Boundless Sea was already within his reach. The Angel’s Might was still pushing him back. It was too late to dodge, no?

Fling!

Lu Boyuan didn’t use any high-level skills. He simply planned on using this low-level grab skill to throw Boundless Sea far away from Laughing Song, and the problem would be solved. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s grabbed towards him, but the distance between him and Boundless Sea was getting farther and farther.

Boundless Sea was getting lower and lower. How could he be getting farther and farther? Fang Rui dodging downwards had been within Lu Boyuan’s calculations. Right now, it wasn’t just that Boundless Sea was dropping lower and lower. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was rising higher and higher…

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was airborne.

Boundless Sea pressed his hands on the ground, not so that he could crawl away on his four limbs, but to use the Qi Master skill: Landmine Quake!

It was an offensive skill, but the way Fang Rui did it made everyone forget that it was one. They thought he was pretending to be some sort of stupid brute. Nevertheless, in the end, he was able to get off a sneak attack.

The viewers didn’t know what to say.

Those who hadn’t realized that it was a Landmine Quake were angrily cursing at Fang Rui’s despicableness. Those who had somehow realiazed it were cursing at Lu Boyuan for being so stupid.

In any case, Lu Boyuan had been fooled. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain shot into the air. This was the key part. Boundless Sea went into a roll, and using the knockback from Angel’s Might, he rolled right under Chaotic Cloudy Mountain.

By the time he got up, Angel’s Might had ended. Boundless Sea pushed out with his palms, shooting a Sky-Piercing Strike at the airborne Chaotic Cloudy Mountain.

Lu Boyuan’s Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had failed to grab Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea. On the contrary, his Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was blasted away by Boundless Sea.

Amazing!

Fang Rui was performing brilliantly. However, this was Samsara’s home stadium. His spectacular play only received a bit of applause. Most of the viewers were anxious. If Fang Minghua and Lu Boyuan were stalled here, it would have a huge impact on the fight going on in the trash room.

Even the broadcast had given up on showing the intense fight between the championship duo and the Best Partners. The chase between Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Life and An Wenyi’s One Autumn Leaf wasn’t given much attention either because Little Cold Hands had found a helper: Qiao Yifan and his One Inch Ash. Happy was trying to connect the two ongoing battles in the trash room to make it a 4v3. Because of this, Fang Rui’s 1v2 against Fang Minghua and Lu Boyuan became the turning point.

This… was another Star Tactic?

Previously, Happy had relied on Ye Xiu’s 1v3 to seize the upper hand. This time, it was through Fang Rui’s 1v2.

1v2 and 1v3, it sounded like the 1v3 was more impressive, but the two situations were entirely different.

Ye Xiu had done a 1v3, but he didn’t need need to control the battle. His only objective was to survive under the combined assault from Samsara’s three players. A 1v3 was a large enough advantage that it was enough to attract all of his opponents’ attention.

On the other hand, for Fang Rui’s 1v2, he needed to be the one with the initiative. He needed to completely shut down Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song and prevent him from leaving. He was facing one fewer player, but his task wasn’t any easier than Ye Xiu’s 1v3. When people saw this battle, they weren’t thinking about whether or not Fang Rui could keep Fang Minghua here, but rather for how long.

The pro players were already placing bets from ten seconds to a minute. People were constantly yelling out their bets, and money kept being passed around.

Ten seconds, fifteen seconds, twenty seconds, twenty-five seconds, thirty seconds…

Bet after bet was lost. At first, placing down the bets was just for a bit of fun, but after thirty seconds, all the fun was lost. No one could pay attention to it anymore.

They were completely absorbed by Fang Rui’s playing.

Lu Boyuan wasn’t some nobody, and neither was Fang Minghua. Both of them were experienced and skilled players. They had been on the same team for many years as well, so they had built up quite the synergy. However, they weren’t able to escape from Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea. They weren’t even able to get one of them to leave.

This…

The pro players were used to placing themselves in the shoes of the players on stage. They could only throw aside their amusement and watch in awe at Fang Rui’s performance.

Chapter 1631 - Perseverance Creating an Opportunity

The broadcast, the pro players, and the more skilled viewers were focused on Fang Rui’s battle with Lu Boyuan and Fang Minghua. Only the viewers who were mostly there to watch the flashy stuff continued to linger on the battle in the trash room.

The battle taking place there was indeed incredible as well, and it could also decide the match. However, from an overall perspective, Fang Rui’s suppression towards the two Samsara players was the true match point. The outcome of this match would likely depend on Fang Rui.

And right now, he had vastly exceeded everyone’s expectations. To think he would be able to hold them off in a 1v2 for so long. Samsara’s two players were unexpectedly unable to get past him.

Of course, if Lu Boyuan’s Chaotic Cloudy Mountain wanted to go, Fang Rui wouldn’t mind at all. Fang Rui’s goal was clear. He wanted to stall Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song. If Lu Boyuan was going to give him trouble, then he would deal with him. If Lu Boyuan wanted to leave, then he would be more than happy to let him leave.

Lu Boyuan had already abandoned Du Ming once. Whether it was from a strategic perspective or a mental one, he couldn’t abandon Fang Minghua too. Samsara was already down one player in the team competition, and down a total of three points overall.

This bastard…

Lu Boyuan grit his teeth, trying to catch Boundless Sea. He just needed to grab him once, and the deadlock would be over. Fang Minghua also understood this reasoning and did his best to help Lu Boyuan.

But Fang Rui was just too crafty. He was bringing out his dirtiness to his limits. Boundless Sea weaved in and out, and there were plenty of times where he had brushed past Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s fingers. The difference was just by a hair.

This wasn’t a matter of luck.

Fang Rui was playing at his peak. It wasn’t like he couldn’t dodge more safely, but he was intentionally making the margin of error as small as possible. He had done this ever since Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s first attempt to block him. From beginning to end, he had gotten past Lu Boyuan as efficiently as he could so that he could have more time to deal with Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song. If not, there was no way he would have been able to hold down Samsara’s two players for so long. This was why the pro players were so astonished. For such precise movements, once or twice, nothing too special. But for him to do it again and again for so long? How focused did he have to be? How tiring must it be?

Yes, very tiring!

Fang Rui soon could feel the fatigue hitting him, and he had only held them down for not even a minute.

He had been mentally prepared, though. He knew how difficult it would be. In Ye Xiu’s 1v3, Ye Xiu had used his overwhelming disadvantage to keep his opponents’ attention on him. However, for his 1v2, he needed to take the initiative and proactively seize control of the battle.

And he did it.

So far, only the word “perfect” could describe what he had accomplished.

He was exhausted, yet he was still constantly racking his brains to win control over his opponents.

He had played to his limits in the group arena as well. After only a short rest, he had to play again in the team competition.

Persevere, persevere to the end!

Fang Rui knew how important his task was. If it was said that their foundation had been established through Ye Xiu’s 1v3, then their final path to victory would be brought out by him.

He had never thought of himself as this team’s core. All he wanted was to perform well enough to match his pay and position. He knew that this was a moment that could likely decide the match. All he needed to do was to persevere.

He didn’t set himself a goal, counting down. Fang Rui only had one thought: persevere, persevere until the end. He would hold down these two players until the moment they won. Before that moment came, he would never relax.

One minute…

One and a half minutes…

Two minutes…

Two and a half minutes…

Fang Rui persevered, playing absolutely perfectly. Not even the slightest opening could be seen in his plays. More and more people started shifting their attention to his side. More and more people were noticing the inconceivable. The pro players had forgotten about their bets long ago.

One minute. That had been the upper limit of their bets. There had only been a single person who called out this time, Team Wind Howl’s Ruan Yongbin. The second highest bet was 45 seconds. When Ruan Yongbin shouted out one minute, no one had taken him seriously. Everyone knew that Ruan Yongbin and Fang Rui were former teammates, and the two had a good relationship with each other. He had yelled out one minute as a way to cheer his friend on.

But now, a minute?

Wrong. Everyone had been wrong, very wrong. Even Fang Rui’s friend, Ruan Yongbin had underestimated Fang Rui’s capabilities.

Two and a half minutes. This was the current record, and it was still going. His perfect playing made it so that Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song couldn’t escape, which in turn made it so that Lu Boyuan’s Chaotic Cloudy Mountain couldn’t leave.

The battle in the trash room had lasted for two and a half minutes too. It was no longer two separate battles. The two sides had grouped together, turning it into a 3v4.

Samsara was at a numbers disadvantage, but these three top ten players were nothing to scoff at. From the looks of it, they were actually the ones on the offensive. The three were using Little Cold Hands as their breakthrough point, constantly sending out attacks towards him.

On Happy’s side, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had become Little Cold Hands’ flower protector. He practically never moved more than an inch away from him. Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan were on the side, providing them support.

Fang Rui was playing out of his mind in the 1v2 to win Happy this 4v3, yet Happy wasn’t able to turn this into an intense back and forth. In fact, they were the ones on the defensive. It was hard not to feel that it was a bit of a pity. However, the experts knew that although Happy was on the defensive, they weren’t feeling burdened. Their defensive position was because they saw what the opponents wanted and were going along with them.

Focusing the healer was a very standard strategy, but no team’s healer had ever been so disgustingly focused like Happy’s during the season. With so much experience facing this strategy, Happy was very proficient in these situations. What’s more, they had put in great effort into practicing and studying how to take advantage of this weakness since their very beginnings.

For other teams, when the enemy focused their healer, their conditioned reflex was to protect their healer. But for Happy, when the enemy focused their healer, their conditioned reflex was to look for opportunities to kill their opponents.

This sort of intuition had become Happy’s style. Even if they hadn’t made any preparations before the match, if they ever came across this situation, Happy’s players would instinctively look for ways to turn it around.

Every team’s protection over their healer was purely defensive. Only Happy was different. Their protection over their healer was extremely aggressive. Their healer had originally been their weakness, but as the season went and their weakness improved, Happy had also set up all sorts of barbs. You could target their weak point, then you wouldn’t come out unscathed. More often than not, it would end up being your guillotine.

It wasn’t that Samsara didn’t know this point. As their opponent in the finals, they had researched Happy thoroughly. However, their current situation was out of helplessness.

They were attacking, Happy was defending. However, the health they were losing wasn’t low. On the other hand, Happy had a healer healing them. After two and a half minutes, the damage was building up.

“!!!!”

The three of them hadn’t sent out this message just once. They were also very surprised to see that their support still hadn’t arrived yet. The thought of Fang Rui stalling their two players for this long hadn’t even crossed their minds. If they had known, they definitely wouldn’t have fought in this way. They would have created an opportunity to get out of the trash room and reconvene with their other two players.

But they didn’t know, so they kept waiting. Half a minute, a minute and a half, two and a half minutes…

The inconceivable had happened. Fang Rui had held down Lu Boyuan and Fang Minghua for a two and a half minutes.

At this point, the three of them had lost the possibility of turning this around!

During these two and a half minutes, it wouldn’t have been impossible to have Lu Boyuan abandon Fang Minghua and go in to help the rest of his teammates. Or the three could have escaped from the trash room and made contact again with Fang Minghua and Lu Boyuan. However, turning points happened in an instant. After two and a half minutes, the three of them couldn’t keep up the same aggressive offense as before. They had no choice but to be more cautious about their character’s health. Who let them attack so unrestrained before? The reason that they had been so unrestrained was because they kept thinking that their support would arrive at any second. How could they have known that not a single sign of them would come even at this point?

Rush out of the trash room now?

The three looked at the health on their characters. If they gave in even a little, Happy’s four would definitely counterattack with everything they had. During those two and a half minutes, they could have forcefully made their way out. However, if they forced their way out now, they would definitely lose one or two people.

Having already lost a player, Samsara was down by three points. Until the last moment, Samsara didn’t want to take the risk of losing another. No matter how they looked at it, hoping for the 2v1 over there to have a breakthrough was more reliable than the three of them forcing their way out.

The three minute mark was approaching. In the end, Samsara chose to wait.

The spectating pro players didn’t feel like Samsara was doing anything wrong. Right now, everything was because of Fang Rui, because of his miracle. At the beginning, everyone just thought that Fang Rui’s stalling would just help Happy win some time and widen the lead a bit more. But now, Fang Rui’s stalling had become the deciding point of this match.

How much longer could Fang Rui hold on for? If Lu Boyuan and Fang Minghua successfully broke through right now and successfully got to their teammates, Happy would have a lead, but not a win. The tradeoff would truly be somewhat disappointing.

Time continued to pass.

Everyone’s attention continued to be focused on Boundless Sea’s battle with Samsara’s two players.

Angel’s Might!

Suddenly, Laughing Song’s cross let out a brilliant light. Fang Rui had held down the two of them long enough for Laughing Song’s Angel’s Might to come off cooldown.

Chapter 1632 - Unbreakable Wall

2 minutes and 45 seconds, the cooldown on Angel’s Might. Fang Rui had held off Fang Minghua and Lu Boyuan for nearly three minutes, until this skill came off cooldown.

Fang Minghua immediately had Laughing Song use Angel’s Might. Angle, position, and timing. Fang MInghua wanted to use this opportunity to finally break this stalemate.

The halo of light burst forth!

Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea couldn’t dodge it or resist it. He could only be forced back. And this time, his previous Cloud Pushing Palm wouldn’t work. It wasn’t that he couldn’t use it, but that the distance was too far. Because of their positioning, if he pushed Laughing Song with Cloud Pushing Palm, he would just be helping him leave faster.

After Laughing Song cast Angel’s Might, he immediately turned and ran. Lu Boyuan didn’t have Chaotic Cloudy Mountain follow after him to protect him. Instead, he sprinted straight towards Boundless Sea. Even though it looked like this Angel’s Might had given Fang Minghua enough space to escape, Lu Boyuan felt uneasy. He wanted to use this opportunity to completely shut down Boundless Sea and prevent any future regrets.

Charge!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain sprinted towards Boundless Sea, who was starting to lower himself. Boundless Sea’s two hands moved towards the ground.

This trick again?

No one would fall for Fang Rui’s act this time, but maybe he was doing it precisely for this reason? With Fang Rui’s dirtiness, what couldn’t he do?

Thinking about it was too complicated, so Lu Boyuan didn’t bother thinking too deeply on whether Fang Rui would repeat the same trick. He regarded it as a possibility, and when he attacked, all he would have to do was be on guard against it, no?

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain sprinted over diagonally. Lu Boyuan had calculated how far Boundless Sea would be pushed. By rushing over right now, he would reach Boundless Sea’s final destination. Lu Boyuan had set his sights on that location, and Boundless Sea was moving towards it just as he was expecting.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain didn’t stop to take a rest. He jumped.

Aerial Twist!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain dropped from the air, his two legs grabbing towards Boundless Sea’s neck. By doing it this way, Boundless Sea’s Landmine Quake wouldn’t able to affect him.

Fall!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s two legs moved towards Boundless Sea. This 1v2 would finally end here. Even though Fang Rui wasn’t able to last long enough to clinch Happy’s victory, no one overlooked Fang Rui’s efforts and impact on the match during these three minutes. His freakish plays had vastly exceeded everyone’s expectations. He had played spectacularly. He wasn’t able to win Happy the game, but he had helped Happy win an enormous lead.

If… many people, including Samsara fans, were thinking about ifs.

If Happy’s four players hadn’t been Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Qiao Yifan, and An Wenyi, and instead been what Li Xuan had envisioned: Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Li Xuan, and Zhang Xinjie, players on an equal level as Samsara’s three players, the time won by Fang Rui might have been able to lock in Happy’s win…

What a pity!

While praising Fang Rui’s performance, everyone couldn’t help but feel a bit regretful about the outcome.

But just when everyone was thinking this, Boundless Sea’s head suddenly dropped, and then…

Missed!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s Aerial Twist missed?

Quite a few crowd members, including people watching at home, couldn’t help but stand up in shock. They needed to confirm that it wasn’t that the attack missed, but Boundless Sea had dodged it.

Yes! He dodged it!

Boundless Sea rolled to get away from Chaotic Cloudy Mountain. Afterwards, he went straight for Laughing Song.

Qi Flowing Cloud!

Boundless Sea activated this buff again. Angel’s Might had come off cooldown. The same went for Qi Flowing Cloud. Boundless Sea moved as if he were riding the wind, quickly closing the distance between himself and Laughing Song. Behind him, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s two legs formed a weird arc as he landed on the ground. He didn’t have time to make another move, and unexpectedly fell to the ground just like that…

Lu Boyuan’s mind was a mess.

He hadn’t felt like his Aerial Twist would hit for certain. After all, there hadn’t been any set-up. He was just using the knockback from Angel’s Might. He wouldn’t be too surprised if Boundless Sea dodged it, and he had thought of countermeasures in case he did dodge it.

But he was very surprised right now.

Not surprised at how Boundless Sea dodged it, but when.

Not just Lu Boyuan, but everyone had thought that the Aerial Twist would hit, yet Boundless Sea was able to complete a dodge. Fang Rui’s movements had been so precise and tight that even a needle wouldn’t be able to get through…

Lu Boyuan had panicked at that moment, and instinctively did what he had planned on doing if Fang Rui dodged the Aerial Twist. He cancelled Aerial Twist, and turned it into a Circle Sweep Kick. His two legs went into a weird arc because he had used this skill…

But Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was too close to the ground. Because Boundless Sea had lowered himself, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s target had been low to the ground. And with how precise Fang Rui’s timing was, when the Aerial Twist missed, there was no time for him to make another move. Even though Lu Boyuan was able to use the skill, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was only able to do half of a Circle Sweep Kick before hitting the ground. As a result, he looked like he was kneeling now.

“This guy…” Let alone the normal viewers, even the pro players were all stunned. Fang Rui’s condition and playing couldn’t be described with just “great,” “spectacular,” “on fire,” those usual descriptions. Fang Rui himself might not even fully realize what exactly he had achieved during these few minutes. But everything that happened on stage would leave its mark on stage, in everyone’s mind, and turn into Happy’s win!

Boundless Sea had once again caught up to Laughing Song. With a Downwards Qi Flow, he knocked Laughing Song down and then with a Fling, he threw Laughing Song behind him.

Three minutes!

Samsara’s two players had once again been stopped by Fang Rui. Just how long could he last?

No, this was no longer the right question.

It should be, how long were Samsara’s two going to take to break through Boundless Sea’s airtight wall?

As for Ye Xiu and the others? They should be taking advantage of this opportunity, no? Even if they couldn’t see what Fang Rui was doing, it had been three minutes, yet Samsara’s support still hadn’t arrived. The others on Happy should have realized by now what sort of situation Fang Rui had set up for them. The opportunity had been created by Fang Rui, but they had to be the ones to grasp it!

Chapter 1633 - Godly Play and a Clumsy Method

Attack!

Fang Rui had fought hard for this opportunity, yet why weren’t the others on Happy attacking?

Anyone that wasn’t a Samsara fan was practically screaming in their heart. They didn’t want to see Fang Rui’s godly performance be buried because his teammates weren’t doing anything.

The camera turned around.

The crowd turned around.

Fang Rui had brought about an opportunity. The following question was whether this opportunity would be grasped. Happy playing safer previously could be explained by not expecting such a godly performance from Fang Rui. However, now that the battle had gone on for so long, and Fang Rui was still stopping Samsara’s support from arriving, if Happy didn’t make a more aggressive move, it would be rather puzzling.

Attack!

Countless people clenched their fists, waiting for this moment to happen. The Happy fans in the stadium had already stood up, but none of them made any noise. They stared intently at the stage, their attention on the ongoing battle in the trash room.

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi.

Lord Grim, Dancing Rain, One Inch Ash, Little Cold Hands.

It’s time!

Go!

Use everything you have and win!

Explosions rumbled. The battle taking place here had never stopped, but at this moment, everyone seemed to hear a change in the tempo from these explosions. Dancing Rain’s artillery fire had begun pushing forward, and Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had finally moved away from Little Cold Hands.

Armor-Piercing Missile! Colliding Stab!

Under Dancing Rain’s cover, Lord Grim rushed out, colliding with One Autumn Leaf, who had been focused on attacking Little Cold Hands. Facing the character that had once been his, Ye Xiu didn’t hold back. The sharp sword in Lord Grim’s hands stabbed towards One Autumn Leaf’s chest in an attempt to push him back.

Little Cold Hands had started casting a spell. Holy light began to spread outwards, enveloping his surroundings. This was the Cleric’s AoE heal, God’s Protection. The skill began as soon as the chant began and ended when the chant ended. During the skill’s duration, all allies within its range, including the healer, would receive powerful heals. The amount of mana needed to keep up the chant was massive, significant enough to reduce how much longer the Cleric would be able to heal in the future. The healing efficiency of God’s Protection was actually quite low, and the range was very limited. As a result, the skill was rarely seen in pro play. Pro players preferred using their own methods to achieve the same effect but at a much smaller cost.

But for An Wenyi, this was his weak spot. Even though he was improving, it had only been about a year. It wasn’t possible for him to become a healing god in such a short amount of time.

An Wenyi was clear about where his weaknesses lay, so he chose to use God’s Protection, a skill that normal players thought of as a godly skill, but pro players considered as beneath them.

Suddenly, Lord Grim, Little Cold Hands, and One Inch Ash were bathed in holy light. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain had a range advantage, so she was rarely threatened by Samsara. Although she wasn’t inside the healing range, she also didn’t need to be healed.

God’s Protection only covered three characters, making it even more wasteful. But anyone could see that this skill was the signal for their fierce counterattack.

Bang bang bang bang bang!

Gunshots rang!

No matter how subpar An Wenyi may be as a healer, for Samsara’s trio, he was their biggest threat.

Cloud Piercer’s dual guns fired countless bullets towards Little Cold Hands. During God’s Protection, the healer wouldn’t be able to move. Once the chant was interrupted, the skill would cease. Lord Grim, who had been guarding Little Cold Hands previously, had finally moved away. Samsara had gotten this far by sticking to their strategy. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf dragged Lord Grim away, while Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer immediately attacked Little Cold Hands. Their focus wasn’t misplaced.

Lord Grim had moved away, but a new guardian had taken his place.

One Inch Ash activated Shadow Image, summoning a ghost that shielded Little Cold Hands. An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands had previously helped him block bullets, and this time, Qiao Yifan was returning the favor.

Their talent might not be extraordinary, and they might not have any crazy technical skill, but they could still use this clumsy method to contend with their opponent. Even if their opponent was Zhou Zekai, Glory’s Number One, an existence far above them. But at this moment, they knew that Zhou Zekai must be feeling more anxious than them. Their clumsy method was extremely effective at restraining their opponents’ attacks!

Gunshots rang again, but Happy’s offense couldn’t be stopped. Happy had begun their counterattack. Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng, the Golden Partners, led the way, while Qiao Yifan and An Wenyi, the two rookies, supported them from behind using their clumsy methods. Everyone suddenly felt like it might not necessarily be the case that Happy would be better off with players better than their rookies.

Qiao Yifan and An Wenyi weren’t Gods, nor were they top players. However, they had their own way of playing, their own way of competing.

A godly healer could rely on their own skill and reactions to prove large-scale healing. But An Wenyi was using a skill that people looked down on, God’s Protection, to the same effect.

A godly Ghostblade player could create an inescapable net through their ghost boundaries, making every step taken by their opponents difficult. But Qiao Yifan, even if it was just using his ghosts to block bullets, he made himself known at the most crucial moment, thwarting his opponents’ plans just the same.

They weren’t the best, but they had their own remarkable aspects.

What they did might not be the most optimal, but their impact on the battle was just as considerable.

Victory was approaching them step by step. This was Samsara’s home stadium, a demonic stadium where Samsara had never lost. But at this moment, Happy, a team that had started only last season in the Challenger League, was once again setting a new record, creating a miracle, creating history.

In the second game of the finals, Happy won against Samsara, ending Samsara’s perfect win record this season in their home stadium. There were countless highlights in this match alone, but the one that left the deepest impression on everyone was Fang Rui and his godly play that decided the match.

Golden Right Hand?

Today, what everyone witnessed was a pair of God Hands!

Chapter 1634 - Joyful in Victory, Calm in Defeat

“Happy wins!! Second match of the finals, Samsara’s home game, Happy obtained victory, they did it!!!” In the televised broadcast, Pan Lin excitedly announced the final result of the match.

Happy’s performance was infectious. Many neutral parties in the audience ended up hoping for a Happy victory. Pan Lin was one such person. He was a commentator, so he should have been the most impartial, and no matter what hope he might have in his heart, he shouldn’t display it so passionately. But in this moment, he couldn’t hold himself back any more. As a professional commentator, even if he sometimes couldn’t analyze a match well enough, even if he was sometimes laughed at and faceslapped, Pan Lin still truly loved this work, and Glory as a game.

A commentator couldn’t be biased, but he wasn’t a robot, there were times where he couldn’t restrain himself. Such as now, like too many other people, he was infected by Fang Rui’s godlike performance and he didn’t want to see Happy miss this opportunity. And now, Happy fulfilled all hopes; the audience and Pan Lin found their hopes fulfilled. In this moment, he couldn’t think about too much, he was completely wrapped up in satisfaction just like those in the audience.

“Samsara’s players also all performed well, but Happy’s players performed better, especially Fang Rui!” After expressing his emotions, Pan Lin probably quickly realized that his self-control had slipped, and he quickly recovered the correct tone.

“Yes. Fang Rui is unquestionably the MVP of today’s match.” Li Yibo was quite loyal to his partner, immediately adding on to the sentence to help Pan Lin recover. He was much calmer than Pan Lin. After all, he was a pro player who had experienced the struggle for the championship, so he was quite worldly.

“Yes, yes. Aside from that, Ye Xiu’s performance was very eye-catching,” said Pan Lin.

“Of course,” Li Yibo agreed.

Defeating Zhou Zekai in the group arena, 1v3 in the team round, hand speed flying toward 500 APM. If Fang Rui’s godlike performance hadn’t upstaged him, awarding today’s MVP to Ye Xiu would also be entirely rational.

By now, the players had all walked out of the competitor booths onstage. But after Happy’s players gathered together, they swept in a circle, but didn’t find their hero of the match, Fang Rui.

“This guy, is he trying to be all dramatic?” Su Mucheng laughed.

Ye Xiu also laughed. He looked at Fang Rui’s competitor booth, and then at the replay on the large screen in the stadium.

Even though this was Samsara’s home stadium, they wouldn’t purposely ignore the outstanding performances of the opposing players. If they lost, they still needed to lose with dignity. Right now, the screen was showing from multiple angles simultaneously the most thrilling moment of the match, Fang Rui’s performance. And this was what Ye Xiu and the others, standing at Fang Rui’s side, hadn’t seen.

Accurate judgment to the extreme, flawless technique, a dirty method of expression. Using these, Fang Rui pinned down Lu Boyuan and Fang Minghua from start to finish.

Yes, from start to finish.

One minute? Two minutes? Three minutes? Four minutes?

None of these were the limit, and at the very end everyone had basically forgotten this statistic, because it had already lost meaning. From start to finish, Lu Boyuan and Fang Minghua had been unable to escape. Did they still need this statistic?

It was a shocking performance, but as Ye Xiu watched and watched, his original smile grew a bit heavy. He glanced at Fang Rui’s booth again, and seeing that there was still no movement, he quickly walked over.

The rest of Happy all realized this as well, and they quickly followed. When the stadium saw this sudden movement of the Happy players, they also seemed to realize something, and they began whispered discussion.

They pulled open the door of Fang Rui’s competitor booth. Ye Xiu looked inside, and saw Fang Rui sitting there in the competitor chair in a very comfortable position, almost lying down. When he heard the door open, this guy turned his head, and seeing that it was Ye Xiu, he grinned and said, “Incredible, right?”

“Incredible!” Ye Xiu nodded.

“We won.”

“We won!”

“Hahahahaha…” Fang Rui laughed loudly, but as he laughed and laughed, it was clear that he was out of breath.

“It wasn’t for nothing!” he said fiercely, and then stood up from his chair. Reluctant to leave, he savored the sight of the screen displaying their victory, and then walked toward Ye Xiu.

“You all came to see the miracle?” Fang Rui laughed, seeing all of Happy gathered behind Ye Xiu.

Seeing that Fang Rui was still in perfect condition, everyone let out a sigh of relief. When the audience saw Fang Rui appear, the Happy fans sitting in the away team area simultaneously burst into cheers and applause. And then, the whole stadium also burst into applause. Even though these were the opponents that defeated them, everyone respected Fang Rui’s performance. Any gamer who understood or liked Glory had no reason not to.

The stadium sent their applause to the away team.

To Fang Rui, this was extremely rare. Because of his style, when he did anything remarkable, it was often also infuriating, and during away matches, this meant that the opposing team’s fans were furious and couldn’t give him any respect or appreciation. But this time, it was different. Even if there was still sneakiness and dirty play mixed in, he did what everyone thought was impossible.

“Are you alright?” Su Mucheng asked him from the side.

“Why wouldn’t I be?” Fang Rui replied, and then waved his arm, acknowledging the applauding crowd. Su Mucheng watched his back, and then looked at Ye Xiu.

Even though Ye Xiu was still smiling, that heaviness from earlier still hadn’t faded. When he saw Su Mucheng looking at him, he returned the gaze, answered Su Mucheng’s doubts.

The two teams walked toward the center of the stage and began to shake hands. Compared to the pre-match ceremony, this was much more casual, they weren’t forced to line up. Fang Rui was the first to walk over, and so he was the first to greet the Samsara players.

“Do you admit defeat?” Fang Rui asked, shaking Zhou Zekai’s hand. He and Zhou Zekai were from the same season. And because the All-Star experts from this season all had their own fresh and unique characteristics, they were called the strangest season of players.

The Season 5 rookies ultimately produced three All-Star level players. One developed dirty playing to the peak, dirty until it couldn’t be any dirtier – Fang Rui; one was frustratingly silent offstage and yet demonstrated explosive and elegant technique onstage – Zhou Zekai; and the third, Team Void’s Wu Yuce, was a fierce and direct… Ghostblade.

Strangeness was the most distinctive trait of their season’s players. As same-season rookies, they knew each other quite well, and many were good friends. Some made childish and naïve arrangements with each other during their rookie days.

Fang Rui and Zhou Zekai hadn’t done anything like that. After all, Zhou Zekai’s personality was right there. But the two of them were indeed familiar with each other.

Zhou Zekai’s tendency was to go with the flow, his words as rare as gold. When Samsara heard Fang Rui’s chatter about admitting defeat, they really were afraid that Zhou Zekai would just say “Yes.” That would just hurt their morale too much.

But Zhou Zekai only smiled a little, and said one word to Fang Rui: “Incredible.”

“Hahaha, as long as you know to be scared.” Fang Rui was smug! Seeing this, the Samsara players were annoyed. Zhou Zekai clearly hadn’t said he’d admit defeat, he said “incredible,” he’d avoided the question. But Fang Rui was shamelessly twisting this casual remark. It was clearly an avoidant, polite statement of praise, but this guy actually just interpreted it as Zhou Zekai saying “yes.”

“Looking forward to seeing this kind of exciting performance next match.” Because Zhou Zekai didn’t like speaking, Samsara usually had vice-captain Jiang Botao speaking to the other party on behalf of everyone. The meaning behind his words now was clear: Samsara didn’t fear another godlike performance from Fang Rui. Next match, they were confident that they would defeat Fang Rui.

“Hehe, looking forward to seeing this kind of exciting result next match.” Fang Rui repeated the sentence structure. Trash talk was his strength as well! How could the Master of Dirty Playing be weak at trash talk.

“Ha ha!” Jiang Botao just laughed and didn’t answer. He knew that with Fang Rui’s personality, continuing to talk would only make him more smug.

Pushing this guy aside, Jiang Botao went to talk with the rest of Happy. And then Fang Rui saw Lu Boyuan, Fang Minghua, and Du Ming, gathered together and glaring at him.

“Hahaha! You guys really suffered this match!” Fang Rui immediately went to greet them with great enthusiasm. The three of them wanted to ignore him, but they also didn’t want to be impolite. These past two years, Samsara had won more often than not, and they were all sorts of daring and energetic. After victory, they wouldn’t be high and arrogant when interacting with the losers, but after a loss, they wouldn’t be petty and small-minded when interacting with the victors. Team Samsara’s popularity had been rising these few years, not just because they were champions, but because this team did many things well. They always acted carefully and appropriately.

Seeing that Fang Rui had clearly just come over to mock them, these three from Samsara didn’t react much. They just gave him plain congratulations.

“Good luck next match!” Fang Rui continued to speak in a mocking tone.

The three of them had been mocked quite intensely, and were now covering their injuries. As though they couldn’t hear the mockery in Fang Rui’s voice, they responded quite seriously with phrases like “let’s all work hard” and whatnot.

As a team that rarely met defeat, after losing such an important match, Samsara’s players were still very calm. Although the stadium fans had felt depressed after this loss, they were gradually moved by this attitude that Samsara demonstrated. Slowly, applause rose up once again in the stadium, and this time, it was no longer respect given toward the victors, but support given toward their own team.

This kind of attitude, this kind of calm after defeat, this caused everyone’s faith in Samsara to be renewed for the third match of the finals. Their Team Samsara would not fall so easily.

Chapter 1635 - Class Change, Return to Godhood

Amidst applause, the curtain closed on the match. In the post-match press conference, Samsara continued to display the attitude they’d had when exchanging greetings with Happy right after the match. They had lost, but they were calm. They didn’t lose control of themselves, and demonstrated the appropriate bearing of a championship team. Although they were regretful that their home game win streak had been broken, they expressed that this allowed them to set down some pressure.

And then the victorious Happy came up. The reporters had an armful of questions they wished to ask, but surprisingly, Fang Rui, the player that had attracted the most attention during the match, didn’t appear in the press conference at all.

This was quite unreasonable.

Players who did poorly were often protected after a match and not sent out to the press conference. This, the reporters could understand. But for players that did well, stepping into the spotlight again during the press conference was something that both the reporters and the team would want to see. And Fang Rui was no rookie, there was no need for this kind of protection.

When they thought about Happy’s unusual actions onstage after the match, the reporters suddenly realized something. After congratulating and praising Happy’s victory, someone immediately asked, in a half-joking tone, why Fang Rui was hiding away.

And then, they heard an answer that they had already guessed in their hearts: Fang Rui had expended a lot of energy during the match, and was feeling a bit worn out.

However, the one who gave this answer was Ye Xiu, so the reporters had to think it over.

Before, no one had any experience interacting with Ye Xiu, but after this season, the reporters for all of the major media outlets complained about him incessantly. They knew all too well that this person wasn’t easy to deal with. His answer right now, was it true or false? Was it a smoke bomb for the last round of the finals?

When they thought about this, the reporters decided, they didn’t need to worry about whether it was true or not. The plot to deceive the enemy had already been deployed. Whether or not Fang Rui would make it onstage in the finals, Samsara could go and guess!

Since there were such sinister motives, they definitely wouldn’t be able to get anything about Fang Rui’s condition. After experimentally throwing out another few questions and receiving answers that were clearly ambiguous on purpose, the reporters were clear and they didn’t tangle with the issue any longer. From Happy, Fang Rui’s performance was the most eye-catching, but the performances of the other players were all very attention-grabbing as well. There was still much to ask…

Fang Rui hadn’t accepted any post-match interviews, but he was still the protagonist of all the news articles released the next day. Esports Weekly had even used “Fang Rui! Class Change! Return to Godhood!” as their headline, acknowledging Fang Rui’s godliness right at the top.

Because he’d changed classes, because his performance had fluctuated, because of his unique dirty Qi Master style, Fang Rui hadn’t been chosen as an All-Star this season, even though he used the number one Qi Master, Boundless Sea. From that day, there was endless discussion over whether or not this class change would be his end. When he performed well, people would come out to praise him; when he performed average or poorly, people would proclaim his decline.

Esports Home was the authority in the circle, so there were of course articles about his class change. But with Esports Home’s level of professionalism, they were very attentive to detail in their analysis, they didn’t rely on simple surface-level discussion. But today, relying on his performance in this one match, Esports Home concisely acknowledged and approved Fang Rui’s class change.

Fang Rui! Class change! Return to godhood!

As she ate breakfast, Chen Guo held this week’s report. Whenever their team or their players made the headlines, it would always put her in high spirits. She had even saved and organized all of the newspapers from this season that featured Happy in the headlines. But seeing this bold headline today, Chen Guo couldn’t be as excited as she was before.

Because Fang Rui’s condition right now really wasn’t very good. That day, he’d energetically greeted the crowd and mocked Samsara right after coming out of the competitor booth, and he’d gleefully boasted to his teammates as well. But after returning to the prep room, Fang Rui had all but collapsed. It was as though all of his energy had suddenly run out, and everyone could see how exhausted he was.

Fang Rui was exhausted, so he hadn’t attended the press conference. Ye Xiu had spoken the truth, even though the reporters didn’t believe him and thought it was a smokescreen. But this time, this smokescreen had affected even Happy themselves. No one could say for sure how well Fang Rui would recover for the final match in two days. Even though Fang Rui stubbornly insisted that he would be fine, everyone was already quietly preparing for the scenario where Fang Rui was unable to play.

Losing Fang Rui would be a massive blow to their strength. No one could imagine that this kind of thing would happen at such a critical moment. Compared to the physical competition of normal athletics, it was fairly rare in Glory competition for a player to be unable to appear because of illness or injury.

Chen Guo stared at the paper’s headline without flipping the pages to read the content. Holding a cup of milk, she sat in the dining room in a daze.

The final match was in two days. Because Samsara had ranked higher than Happy in the regular season, the third match would be held in Samsara’s home stadium. In order to demonstrate determination, Chen Guo had booked hotel rooms here for Team Happy all the way until the end of the third match. Now, as they hoped, the third match awaited them. But because of Fang Rui, another shadow weighed upon everyone’s hearts. Last night, Chen Guo hadn’t slept well, and now that she looked at this paper, the shadow floated back.

“So early?” As she was spacing out, she suddenly heard someone talk. She lifted her head to see Ye Xiu holding breakfast as he sat down across from her.

“Mm…” Chen Guo nodded.

Ye Xiu’s gaze landed upon the Esports Weekly report in front of her.

“Fang Rui! Class Change! Return to Godhood!” Ye Xiu read the title, and after clicking his tongue in marvel, he made no comment.

“How is he?” asked Chen Guo.

“Probably still sleeping,” said Ye Xiu.

“I meant, for the match in two days, will he be alright?” Chen Guo said.

“We’ll see when the time comes!” Ye Xiu said.

Uncertainty.

The final battle was imminent, but Happy had this uncertainty. But Chen Guo understood that this wasn’t the time to be deeply worried. There needed to be determination.

“Then we should let everyone prepare,” said Chen Guo.

“That’s straightforward enough.” Ye Xiu smiled. “Fortunately, the maps for this last match are random, and the roster usually isn’t decided until after the map is chosen. Everyone will be fully prepared.”

“But… No matter what the map is, have you thought about not letting Fang Rui go onstage?” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu fell silent.

Chen Guo was often rendered speechless by Ye Xiu, and she had often hoped for the chance to do the same to him one day. But now, faced with a Ye Xiu that truly had nothing to say, she didn’t feel happy at all.

Chen Guo knew that she had hit the nail on the head.

No matter which map was chosen, Happy couldn’t go as far as to bench Fang Rui. Even though he wasn’t the absolute core of Happy, he was still a part of the central axis. And with Fang Rui’s style and resourcefulness, there really weren’t any maps that would impede his performance.

Silence.

Chen Guo didn’t ask any more questions. She quietly drank her milk, and quietly watched Ye Xiu as he rapidly finished his breakfast.

“Does it matter if he goes on or not?” Ye Xiu said, after wiping his mouth with a napkin. “Either way, we’ll win.”

Chen Guo laughed.

This wasn’t logical at all! But after hearing Ye Xiu say this, she suddenly felt very relaxed and very calm. Because in her mind, Ye Xiu had never said anything that he couldn’t do. Not a single time.

“So that’s to say, we’re the champions?” Chen Guo said.

“If not, then why are we here?” Ye Xiu looked at Chen Guo, astonished, as though he were looking at an alien.

“I’ll go see if that Fang Rui’s awake yet,” Chen Guo said, standing up.

“Give the newspaper to him, it’ll lift his spirits,” said Ye Xiu, gesturing toward the paper on the table.

“What about you?” asked Chen Guo as she took the paper.

“I’m not full yet.” Ye Xiu held his plate, looking around.

Chen Guo left first, returning upstairs to Fang Rui’s room. It was the finals, so to make things convenient for everyone, they were all in separate rooms. But when she arrived at Fang Rui’s room, the door was already open, and when she looked inside, there were many people. Everyone from Happy was here…

What was this?

As Chen Guo was about to enter, she already heard Fang Rui chattering away. “Did you guys think I was dying or something?”

Chapter 1636 - Review

“You seem pretty energetic!” Chen Guo said, walking in. Hearing Fang Rui making all this noise, she suddenly felt much better.

“All you guys crowding around me, and no one brought me breakfast?” Fang Rui said indignantly.

“Brought you a newspaper.” Chen Guo held up the paper in her hand so that Fang Rui could see the headline.

The title was very eye-catching, so Fang Rui saw it immediately. His eyes lit up, but right after, he pretended as though it were nothing. With an expression of “this brother has seen the big stage” he dismissively said, “Tsk, that’s nothing.”

Fang Rui wasn’t lying on the bed. After all, esports competitions were carried out while sitting in front of a computer. Even though they could still be exhausting, they weren’t so exhausting that a player would be unable to get out of bed. Chen Guo casually tossed the newspaper toward the bed, and then carefully studied Fang Rui. He didn’t seem any different from normal.

Before she’d come here, the others had already spoken with Fang Rui. It was a bit of a tight squeeze, so many people in this one room, so after a greeting, they began to disperse.

“Do you need me to call breakfast for you?” Chen Guo asked Fang Rui.

“No, it’s fine, I’m gonna take a walk in a bit, I’ll get something to eat then,” said Fang Rui.

“Alright, then I won’t bother you any longer.” Chen Guo didn’t ask Fang Rui anything like “how are you, can you make it.” She followed everyone else out of the room.

Fang Rui stood by the window. The newspaper lay face-up on the desk next to the table, and the rays of light streaming through the window shone down upon it, illuminating the words, dazzlingly bright. Fang Rui lowered his head and looked at it, but he didn’t pick it up. He only laughed a little, then turned to look outside the window. Today’s weather really was quite good.

Happy didn’t have any plans in the morning. After such an intense battle, they wanted to rest up as much as they could. They scheduled a strategic meeting for the afternoon. It wasn’t any high-intensity practice, it was just a review of the match that they just played. This was something that pro teams would do after every match. And in the playoffs, where the matches were at a higher level and teams would play the same opponent multiple times, review became a highly effective method of adjustment. Summarize the successes and failures of the previous match, take the chance to plan strategy and tactics for the next match, it was a very focused method. Compared to the regular season, these reviews held greater significance during the playoffs.

And so, at 1:30 in the afternoon, Happy’s members gathered in the conference room they booked at the hotel. Ye Xiu had of course organized the match recordings beforehand, and when everyone arrived, he didn’t waste any time with unnecessary words, and began playing the recording.

“Let’s watch the team competition first!” Ye Xiu said, as the screen displayed this match’s team competition.

“In this team competition, to put it briefly, I believe that Samsara lost largely to surprise. Too many unexpected situations happened, messing up their plans. This meant that their strategies did not completely come into play,” said Ye Xiu.

“Take the beginning, for example, with Samsara’s advance.” Ye Xiu pointed out Samsara’s initial formation, with Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, and Sun Xiang advancing first, while Lu Boyuan stayed behind to protect Fang Minghua. “Clearly, this formation was to take advantage of the map’s high points.”

“The changes afterward were really quite simple. As for the surprise that happened during this point, I don’t think I need to go into detail,” said Ye Xiu.

The surprise here referred to Ye Xiu holding off Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, and Sun Xiang all by himself. This was Ye Xiu’s accomplishment, but during the review session, his tone was neither humble nor bragging. He simply told things as they were.

“In this part of the match, we can take another look at the cooperation between these three Samsara attackers. This is something that we have studied many times before,” said Ye Xiu.

Of course it had been many times. It wasn’t just Happy, any team in the Alliance that was aiming for the championship would definitely treat this as a crucial topic of study. Regarding this content, they couldn’t say that they had a thorough understanding, but they at least analyzed it to the best of their ability.

Ye Xiu said that they were looking at the attack coordination between these three, but in reality, they focused more on how Ye Xiu countered the attacks that the trio set up. As Ye Xiu was the player in question, he of course knew everything the most clearly. But right now, he was sharing the thought process with everyone. Because everyone played different characters with different class skills, they would all use different methods to deal with the same situation. Only by understanding the fundamental thought process could they learn from this 1v3 situation and apply it to their own class and character.

Ye Xiu would talk about what happened, someone would raise a question, someone would express an opinion, discussion, debate…

Chen Guo quietly stood to the side.

She always attended Happy’s strategy meetings. In the very beginning she would happily talk, ask some questions, express her point of view. But gradually, she began to just quietly stand to the side and listen, just like she was doing now.

Compared to the beginning, Chen Guo’s experience had increased dramatically, and if she gave her opinions now, she would probably be correct more often than not. But Chen Guo didn’t talk anymore, because no one had ever left out a point she wanted to make.

Look at Tang Rou. Two years ago, she was a complete noob, but now, Chen Guo sometimes couldn’t even keep up with her reasoning.

She would be lying if she said she wasn’t saddened at all. In her heart, Chen Guo still wished that she could be a pro player as well, that she could fight onstage alongside all of these partners.

But unfortunately, that was reality. All she could do was make their lives offstage a little better.

It was a bit disappointing, but it was nothing to hang her head about. Because Chen Guo understood very clearly that she was a member of this team as well. While they fought toward their goal, they had never left her behind, they were still tied together…

The final match was in two days. Everyone, good luck!

Chen Guo stood to the side and silently cheered everyone on. Right now, she wasn’t thinking at all about whether or not Fang Rui would be able to play. Because, just like Ye Xiu had said to her that morning, whether or not he could play, their goal wouldn’t change. Victory. Champions.

The review continued.

Chen Guo just stood to the side silently, all the way until the end.

“Tonight, does everyone have their own plans, or do you want to get dinner together or something?” Chen Guo asked.

“This… I feel like if we had a celebratory feast right now, that wouldn’t be too good. If the media found out, what would they say about us?” Wei Chen said.

Chen Guo glared at this old man. Even though he was saying nonsense, he did express his meaning, that he would prefer free time.

“Everyone, you’re free to do whatever! If you want to obey our boss’s plans, then just follow her,” said Ye Xiu.

Chen Guo gave him a glare as well. What kind of statement was that! Free, obey, weren’t those antonyms? How come he just put them together?

Mo Fan left first. He was always very uninterested in these sort of group gatherings.

Luo Ji was discussing something with Qiao Yifan, and An Wenyi joined them as well. The three of them, still in discussion, left together. Steamed Bun was prepared to join them too, but then he was caught by Wei Chen, who said something to him. Steamed Bun was instantly cheerful, and went along with Wei Chen.

“Boss, you know… Last match was very tiring for me, I’m heading back early to rest.” Appearing to be very meek and obedient, Fang Rui came over to let Chen Guo know.

Chen Guo couldn’t say anything except “go.” In the end, it was just her, Tang Rou, Su Mucheng, and Ye Xiu – three girls and one guy. Ye Xiu was organizing data, and clearly had no intention of “obeying” her plans. Chen Guo had long given up on the hope of a big get-together, and after saying goodbye to the others, she and Tang Rou left together.

Just two of them were left. Su Mucheng stood behind Ye Xiu, watching him reclassify the recordings, articles, images, etc. from before and save them.

“How do you feel?” Su Mucheng suddenly asked.

“How do I feel? You mean about Fang Rui?” Ye Xiu said, without turning his head.

“No, I’m talking about you… how are you?” Su Mucheng asked.

Ye Xiu, in the middle of busily organizing the files, visibly stopped.

“I’m… alright,” he said.

Chapter 1637 - If Life Were Long

“Alright in what way?” Su Mucheng asked, very seriously. She walked forward, until she could see Ye Xiu’s expression.

“That’s not the important point.” Ye Xiu lifted his head. He didn’t try to hide – he looked at Su Mucheng with a smile.

They’d been together for many years, and their mutual understanding ran perhaps even deeper than they thought. Often, just one look was enough to understand the other’s intention. Ye Xiu knew what Su Mucheng was worried about, and he didn’t explain, nor did he try to cover it up. If he’d given that response to Chen Guo, she probably would have instantly filled with rage and yell at him about what was the important point. But Su Mucheng only nodded, and said nothing more.

That’s not the important point.

Now that they were here, only one thing was important: victory, champions!

For the sake of this, he could pay anything. He could give up anything.

And so Su Mucheng said nothing more. She would, while Ye Xiu was putting in all his effort, simply do all that she could to help him, to make that sole important point into reality. That was Ye Xiu’s important point, and it was her important point as well, it was the important point that no pro player would ignore.

Ye Xiu continued to organize the data. For every file, he had the habit of opening it to double check what it was, then saving it in the correct location. But when he opened the next recording, he didn’t immediately close and move it like he had with the others. The video continued to play, and Ye Xiu watched it blankly.

Since it was a review of Samsara’s match, most of these files were of course material on Samsara. This video was as well, and onscreen, this season’s Best Partners Cloud Piercer and One Autumn Leaf were fighting side-by-side.

Shocking talent, outstanding technique, these two characters charged forward and knocked all others out of their way, entering into an empty space. And this was an official match from the regular season. Just like that, the opponent fell into chaos from these two characters, and Samsara easily took the victory.

Zhou Zekai, Sun Xiang.

This duo had only become partners this season. Countless people had placed high hopes on them, believing that they would be the rulers of this next era of Glory. In his heart, Ye Xiu didn’t disagree.

But right now, that wasn’t what he was thinking about. Su Mucheng watched him, and she too knew that he wasn’t thinking about that.

“It’s a strange feeling, isn’t it?” Ye Xiu said.

Su Mucheng knew what he was referring to, but she shook her head. “I don’t feel it… I actually never played Glory seriously with my brother.”

“That’s right…” Ye Xiu nodded. At the time, he and Su Muqiu spent all day in front of the computer, playing games, but Su Muqiu had sent Su Mucheng to school. He didn’t want to raise his little sister into a pro gamer or pro player or anything like that. But this wasn’t because he felt that it was difficult or embarrassing. It was the opposite, in fact. Su Muqiu sincerely loved what he did. He loved gaming, he loved Glory, and he was proud of what he did.

Regarding Su Mucheng, he simply took a neutral stance, neither supporting nor opposing.

“For something like this, she has to choose herself!” That was what Su Muqiu said. At the time, he was still just a kid in his teens, but he talked like a life coach, carefully thinking about his little sister’s future.

“She’s grown up watching us play games and Glory, I feel like she must have some interest, like when she named our characters…” Ye Xiu eyed the mistake in the name “One Autumn Leaf” onscreen.* To be honest, it had always bothered him.

“Tsk, what do you know? Little kids often have a rebellious spirit. Maybe after seeing us play all day, she really hates it?” Su Muqiu said.

“You can’t say that like it’s a given. Not every kid has a rebellious spirit,” said Ye Xiu.

“Says the one who ran away from home?” Su Muqiu was unimpressed.

“I raised a little brother, so I have experience,” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh? How old is he?” Su Muqiu quickly asked.

“Just a little younger than me, we’re twins,” said Ye Xiu.

“Fuck off!” Su Muqiu replied with two words.

“One Autumn Leaf! Autumn Tree**! Where’d you two run off to!!” At this moment, a number of messages from the group leader suddenly flashed in the chat.

“Oh no, we’re going the wrong way,” Su Muqiu suddenly realized.

“Damn, could you not get too distracted while chatting!” said Ye Xiu.

“Where is this?” Su Muqiu quickly pulled up the map.

“We can’t go back, that bridge back there breaks when the story’s triggered,” Ye Xiu said.

“We’ll have to fight our way through here.” Helpless, Su Muqiu adjusted his camera and looked forward.

“That’s our only way…” Ye Xiu felt similarly helpless.

And so the two of them continued forward. After half an hour, the system issued an announcement: One Autumn Leaf has killed Leader Sake, dungeon complete.

“What the hell! What are those two bastards doing!!” All sorts of scolding instantly flooded the group. They had only made it halfway through the dungeon when the final Boss was already killed.

“My bad, I took the last hit,” Ye Xiu said.

“So rude!” As Su Muqiu spoke, he pulled out a notebook and quietly made a note. The year, month, day, hour, minute, dungeon, Boss, final kill: One Autumn Leaf, 474th time.

And himself? Su Muqiu flipped to a previous page. 318 times, what a gap!

“How many times was that?” Ye Xiu leaned over.

“Only 400, just a little ahead of me.” Su Muqiu closed his notebook with a snap.

“Hehe, do you think you’ll ever have the chance to surpass me in your lifetime?” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Kid, don’t be too reckless. The road of life is very long,” Su Muqiu scoffed.

The road of life is very long…

If the road of life really were so long, Ye Xiu thought, watching the video in silence, then what would be the two names recorded here now?

Shaking his head, Ye Xiu closed the video.

“Let’s go!” he called to Su Mucheng.

“Yeah,” Su Mucheng nodded, “let’s go.”

“Do you find Glory fun?” As they walked out the door, Ye Xiu suddenly asked this question.

“And what kind of important point is this?” Su Mucheng laughed.

“Because we were actually never really sure,” said Ye Xiu.

“It’s very fun, I’m very sure,” said Su Mucheng.

“Then that’s good.” Ye Xiu let out a breath.

“Why?”

“Winning the championship will be even more fun,” Ye Xiu said.

“Of course,” said Su Mucheng.

“So…”

“So what?”

“What do you want for dinner?”

“I don’t care.”

“Let’s just wander around and find somewhere?”

“Okay.”

Chapter 1638 - The Championship is Ours

Culture Square, one of City S’s famous shopping areas. The giant open-air screen hanging on the outside of the north building was far more spectacular than any screen hanging inside a Glory stadium.

And right now, this screen that had become a symbol of the city was currently playing the highlights from last night’s match between Samsara and Happy.

Ten years ago, this would have been unimaginable. At that time, even though esports had already developed to a certain extent, it still didn’t attract much attention, and it was still far from mainstream. But today, clips from the finals would be played in a public city square. It seemed like Samsara had become the pride of city S. Because of Samsara, so many people in this city were now concerned about the Glory finals.

Of the people passing through this square, perhaps some would stop in their tracks and watch for a while, perhaps some would just spare a glance before continuing to walk. Some were paying close attention to these matches, some didn’t know much, but if someone were to say that they didn’t even know what this was, then they would certainly earn some disdainful looks.

Glory was no longer just the glory of the players, the teams, or the fans. It was now the glory of an entire city. And the weight of the hopes carried by the players and teams was greater than ever before.

“What a shame, if we won yesterday, we would have had three straight championships!”

Tang Rou heard the man standing ahead of her speaking regretfully.

“Yeah, too bad!” The person standing next to him was sighing as well.

Tang Rou had been standing here for a while. She knew that these two hadn’t known each other beforehand, but because they had both paused to watch and happened to be standing next to each other, they began a discussion.

Tang Rou could tell that these two weren’t Glory players. Their dialogue was full of that half-understanding, hearsay, exaggerated public opinions.

But from start to finish, the word they used was: we.

These two people weren’t Glory players at all, but they were still paying attention to this match, they still felt a strong connection to their city’s team, they still held high hopes for the championship. This was the best evidence of Glory’s ever-expanding presence and influence.

Tang Rou smiled.

Even though these people supported the opposing side, she deeply appreciated this attitude. She herself had started as an indifferent passerby, gradually investing more in all of this. Even in the beginning, she hadn’t even felt that Glory was all that interesting. All she wanted to do was become a bit stronger, and then defeat that guy who’d forced her to lose over a dozen games in a row.

But now?

It’d been a while since she’d cared about that. Now, she aimed for a larger goal than defeating Ye Xiu.

Like all of the other pro players, she yearned for victory. She hoped to win the championship.

Was this because she always strove to outdo others?

Maybe a little! But if she only cared about that, then perhaps her vision would have remained fixed on Ye Xiu. But now, when she looked at Ye Xiu, she thought about how to better cooperate with him, and then achieve victory together.

This was no longer simply a desire to outdo others. There was another feeling quietly growing in her heart. She no longer fought just for her individual interest. She now had things she was carrying upon her back. Her teammates, the fans, and those like the two people in front of her now, who didn’t understand the game, but still drew pride from it.

It was a bit unfortunate that she hadn’t gone onstage yesterday. But the team had won, and that was more important than anything. Right now, this was Tang Rou’s truest feeling.

“The championship is ours!” Tang Rou suddenly shouted. Without waiting for everyone’s eyes to land upon her, she spun around and left.

Everyone paused. The match displayed on this massive screen was quite exciting, but for them, for this city, it felt a bit oppressive.

Because in yesterday’s match, victory did not belong to them. Victory had gone to Team Happy. Right now, everyone was gathered here and watching this match, but their minds had already gone to the next match. They were looking forward to victory in the next round, and then, they would have the championship.

The championship is ours!

This sentence truly expressed the sentiment in everyone’s hearts. Even though it came out so suddenly, catching everyone off-guard, soon they were set aflame by the passion in this simple statement.

“Yes, the championship is ours!” Someone echoed the shout, and then, more and more, more and more. In this square, whether or not they understood Glory, as long as they knew this competition, they hoped for the championship, and they joined in this shouting.

Only those senior players who were very familiar with the Glory competition found the short-haired silhouette leaving the crowd. They were stunned.

“That girl… Wasn’t that Happy’s Tang Rou?” someone said.

“You’re saying, this year’s rookie king, Tang Rou?”

“The Tang Rou who promised to retire after failing a 1v3, but backed out?”

“That really pretty Tang Rou?”

More and more sets of eyes looked in that direction. Tang Rou walked farther and farther away, but everyone believed more and more, this was indeed Tang Rou.

“So, what she shouted just now…” someone suddenly realized.

“So that ‘ours’ was referring to Happy?” They were instantly dumbfounded.

And right now, the good citizens of City S in the square were currently shouting “the championship is ours” in a surge of public feeling. Thinking about how this “ours” was actually referring to Happy made them all sorts of uncomfortable.

But how could they explain it now? And even if they could, so what? Were they not allowed to use the word “ours”?

Tang Rou shouted “ours,” we’ll shout “ours,” and the “ours” that we’re shouting refers to Samsara. Everyone understood this clearly.

After getting this point clear, these loyal Samsara fans had nothing more to worry about. They would simply accept this mistake and make the best of it, shouting along with everyone: the championship is ours!

The shouts grew louder and louder, but Tang Rou didn’t look back. She strolled along the road, all the way back to the hotel.

Heading upstairs, she saw Ye Xiu hanging around in the hallway, smoking. When he saw her, he waved.

“Where’d you go?” he asked casually.

“I just took a walk,” said Tang Rou.

“Oh. Good luck tomorrow!” No moving, sensational encouragement. Ye Xiu simply said this offhand sentence to Tang Rou.

“Tomorrow?” Yet Tang Rou still found a fault in his words.

“More good luck for the day after,” said Ye Xiu calmly.

“Haha,” Tang Rou laughed, without saying anything. But then, she noticed that the room Ye Xiu was headed toward didn’t seem to be his own room.

“Where are you going?” she asked, curious.

“Some kids wanted some data, I’m bringing it to them,” said Ye Xiu.

In Happy, aside from Wei Chen, Ye Xiu would casually call everyone “kids.” Tang Rou didn’t know who he was referring to, but she saw him walk into Luo Ji’s room.

Now that her curiosity had been piqued, Tang Rou followed. In Luo Ji’s room, he, Qiao Yifan, and An Wenyi were all circled around one computer.

“Here.” Ye Xiu held out a USB.

Luo Ji accepted it and inserted it into the computer. He soon found what he was looking for and pulled it up onscreen alongside his own document. He also had his notebook open, covered in writing, and he began theorycrafting with An Wenyi and Qiao Yifan.

Ye Xiu stood to the side, arms folded, smoking, listening very attentively.

Tang Rou hid a smile.

She suspected that, regarding what Luo Ji was explaining right now, even she understood more than Ye Xiu. This kid was once again using his numbers to analyze some probabilities.

But he was speaking too in-depth. A formula here, a derivation there, An Wenyi and Qiao Yifan looked as confused as Steamed Bun.

Finally, Ye Xiu could take it no longer. He finally moved, and pointed to a spot on Luo Ji’s screen. “Take a look here.”

Tang Rou was shocked. The part of the document that he pointed out was the calculation of the characteristic function through a Fourier transform of the probability density function.Ye Xiu was able to understand something that complex? Even she only knew what the words were but, nothing of the details.

After pointing it out, Ye Xiu was already turning around to leave, and he was met with Tang Rou’s shocked expression.

“Another lesson for you,” Ye Xiu said, walking by Tang Rou. “Not just your opponents, you can’t underestimate your teammates either!”

He had already walked past, and Tang Rou could only continue to stare wide-eyed at his retreating back. But then, from behind her, she heard Luo Ji ask: “What’s wrong here?”

“There’s a bit of dirt there,” said Ye Xiu, walking out of the room.

“Oh oh!” Luo Ji hurriedly pulled out his glasses cloth and rubbed at that spot on his screen.

Chapter 1639 - The Final Battle

The first rest day after the match passed just like that. Aside from the review in the afternoon, Happy’s players didn’t gather together. Instead, each did their own thing.

Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng just ate and chatted, treating it like any other day.

Tang Rou took a walk by herself, to keep her mind off things.

Fang Rui and Mo Fan closed themselves in their rooms and didn’t show their faces again.

And Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi, and Luo Ji, these three youths seemed to make the most of their time. Even now, they were still diligently investigating something.

The ones who ended up giving Chen Guo the most worry were Wei Chen and Steamed Bun. After the afternoon review, they left, and she didn’t see them at all after that. She’d said that everyone was free to do their own thing, so of course she felt it would be rude to ask. But as it grew later and later, these two still hadn’t returned, and Chen Guo gripped the phone in her hand, debating whether or not she should call and ask. At the same time, she listened hard for any sound of their return in the hallway.

She would wait ten more minutes. If they still weren’t back in ten minutes, she would ask where they were.

Chen Guo carried this determination, but ten minutes became twenty, and then an hour. By this time, it was already 11:00 at night.

Finally, Chen Guo couldn’t hold back any longer. She picked up her phone, and dialed Wei Chen’s number.

An unfamiliar ringtone sounded, right from the hallway!

They’re back?

Chen Guo didn’t hang up, instead directly rushing out of the room to look.

As expected.

In the hallway, Chen Guo saw Wei Chen and Steamed Bun beaming as they walked along. Because his phone was ringing, Wei Chen was currently feeling around in his pocket. When they saw Chen Guo rush out, the two of them casually greeted her, and then Wei Chen pulled out his phone, and saw who was calling him.

“Looking for me?” Wei Chen asked Chen Guo.

“Oh, I saw that you two still weren’t back, so I wanted to ask,” Chen Guo said, as naturally as she could. She didn’t want them to think of her as a worrisome old woman, even though she did feel much calmer seeing their return.

“Oh, we were just at that Internet café at the corner!” Wei Chen said.

“Why did you two go to an Internet café?” Chen Guo was confused.

“Running a black inn,” said Wei Chen.

“It’s really fun, Boss you should come with us next time!” Steamed Bun enthusiastically invited her.

Chen Guo was speechless. “Running a black inn” was a gaming term for something commonly seen in Internet cafés. To put it simply, a few players would sit together, so that they could see each other’s screens and easily communicate offline. With this advantage, they would be able to reach extremely good coordination, and they would bully their opponents, strangers that had been randomly grouped together.

This kind of behavior wasn’t worthy of being condoned, of course. As a devoted Glory fan, Chen Guo always gave dirty looks to the raucous guests running black inns in her Internet café. She couldn’t drive them out just for doing that, but whenever the Internet café held events, like discount cards, she definitely wouldn’t give these people preferential treatment.

But now, Team Happy, a professional team that had made it to the finals, two of their pro players had actually gone to an Internet café to run a black inn.

Right now, Chen Guo had only one thing to say to them.

“Do you really have to be like this?”

“Ah, if only you could do this during a match, that would be great.” Steamed Bun actually said this, with deep feeling.

Chen Guo glared furiously at Wei Chen. This was definitely all his idea.

“It’s getting late, go to sleep! If we ever have some free time later we can go again.” Wei Chen, completely ignoring her, said goodbye to Steamed Bun.

“Okay okay.” Steamed Bun cheerfully returned to his own room. But Wei Chen looked at Chen Guo, chuckled and said, “You think we’re very low for doing this, don’t you?

“Very much so.” Chen Guo nodded.

“Actually, this is a type of religious practice,” Wei Chen said.

“What do you mean?” Chen Guo asked.

“Next time, you can come along,” Wei Chen said.

“Oh, okay!” Chen Guo automatically agreed.

Wei Chen smiled, said goodnight, and also returned to his room.

Chen Guo stood there dumbly for another half a minute, and felt like crying.

Morals! Where had her morals gone! What religious practice, this guy was making it up, right? He was just completely and utterly shameless!

Just like that, the first rest day passed by. The second day was also free time for everyone. Because there was no strategy meeting like the review, Chen Guo didn’t even see everyone.

Chen Guo really was very curious as to what everyone was doing, and she really wanted to send a “what’s everyone doing” message to the group chat.

But, restraint!

Chen Guo didn’t want to bother everyone. In her heart, she truly trusted everyone. Even though these Happy players all had different personalities, and some were all sorts of strange, Chen Guo felt that this was a very reliable team. Taking Wei Chen and Steamed Bun running a black inn, for example, Chen Guo believed that it was a sort of religious practice for them, a way for them to relax.

As for staying out so late at night, she’d said she was worried, but it might have been more curiosity.

So Chen Guo restrained herself. She didn’t want her curiosity to ruin everyone’s personal rhythms. If there was anything she wanted to know or ask, she could wait until the day the match ended!

The second day swung past. On the night of the third day would be the final, championship match of this season. And on this day, the team would have a team practice, for the sake of warmup.

And so, in the training room, Chen Guo saw everyone gathered together for the first time since that review meeting.

Nervous!

As the final match approached, Chen Guo couldn’t help but grow more and more nervous. She was scared, she was scared that after everyone had worked so hard for a year, they would miss this final step. That disappointment, that frustration, Chen Guo truly had no idea how to face it.

The team practice lasted for around two hours, but they didn’t interact much. The atmosphere was a bit oppressive, but under this atmosphere, Happy’s players were fully focused. No one said anything to try and relieve this atmosphere. They reached a sort of harmony with the pressure.

Ye Xiu seemed to be very satisfied with this way of handling the situation. After the two-hour team practice ended, he was smiling as he began speaking.

“Is everyone ready?” Ye Xiu asked.

Some nodded, some spoke, it was all in agreement.

“Then, let’s win this!” Ye Xiu said.

Once again, they nodded.

And then, head out! Toward Samsara’s home stadium, toward the final match of this season, Happy stepped onto their final journey.

The stadium was packed starting very early. Even the pro players had entered the stadium very early, and were now waiting patiently for the match’s start.

For the final match, the victory poll had been opened once again, and this time, what caught people’s attention was no longer just the comparison in percentage. This time, the number of people casting votes was incredibly few, far fewer than those of any previous playoffs matches.

This was the final, championship-deciding match. How could people not pay attention?

But to pay attention, and abstain from casting a vote, there was naturally only one explanation: many people didn’t know to whom their vote should go. Aside from those who were firmly biased toward one side, those who were neutral or those relying on logic to analyze the question had no way to predict this match’s outcome.

In the first game, Samsara defeated Happy at Happy’s home stadium. Such a strong performance had instantly destroyed the powerhouse Happy image that had been built up after Happy versus Tyranny. Thus, in the second game’s vote, Samsara completely suppressed Happy.

But then, in the second game, Ye Xiu led Happy by defeating Zhou Zekai in 1v1, and then in the team competition, all sorts of godly performances shook the stage. People found that they had been very wrong in their assessments that Samsara would win for sure.

Happy won in Samsara’s demonic home stadium, breaking Samsara’s perfect home record. Samsara defeated Happy at Happy’s home, and they retaliated by defeating Samsara in their home.

On paper, Samsara’s strength was greater than Happy’s, anyone would admit this. But if Happy once again had this kind of godlike performance?

Happy’s unpredictability caused everyone who wanted to rely on logic to become lost. Right now, everyone wanted to use the phrase that commentator Li Yibo often fell back upon when he couldn’t clearly determine the situation: let’s wait and see.

Wait and see, Glory Pro League Season 10, the championship-deciding final match! Amidst blinding lights and deafening cheers, it began.

The two teams’ players lined up onstage. The curtain was about to close on this season’s journey.

Who would be the champion?

Samsara!!

With the home stadium advantage, Samsara’s fans took the lead in making noise.

Chapter 1640 - Inevitable Confrontation

No matter how much support they received on the Internet.

No matter how many neutral Glory fans were beginning to favor Happy.

But in this stadium, the support for Samsara would always be unrivaled. This was their home stadium. Here were their most diehard fans. No matter what, they would never give up on supporting their team.

“Samsara is the champion!” The stadium was filled with such shouts. Perhaps influenced by what had happened yesterday at Culture Square, the Samsara fans in the stadium today very carefully used “Samsara” as the subject of their cheers.

Even though Happy’s fans were unwilling to show weakness, it was indeed difficult to take the upper hand when the other side had this kind of momentum. After going through the trials of this season, Happy’s fan group now had experience of challenging the opponent’s home stadium. As the away team, because of the vast numbers disparity, there was no way to knock over the opponent through sheer sound. In this situation, they had to rely more on chants and banners, creating visual momentum. These, at least, could not be covered no matter what. But there was a big pitfall to this strategy, which was… holding up a large sign would block the view of the row or rows sitting right behind.

This pitfall largely limited the usage of posters and banners. But today, Happy’s fans went ahead with it regardless. In the away team audience section, row after row of signs declared victory, so dense that the section looked like a mountain forest. The section seemed to be entirely banners, no people. Aside from the audience members sitting in the very front, there was practically no row whose line of sight could escape.

Even though the match still hadn’t officially begun, for the Happy fans to prepare their banners to create such a magnificent sight, it could be seen how conscious the fans were of this match. Their sound couldn’t resound in this stadium, but this continuous expanse of banners became the focus of attention in this stadium, and the television broadcast gave them extra screen time.

If they hadn’t prepared beforehand, this kind of thing could never happen spontaneously, no matter how many fans Samsara had. They had no other choice, they could only bring forth even more volume, to fight against Happy’s visual momentum.

Beneath the clashing swords, the two teams completed the pre-match exchange very calmly. After simple handshakes, however, the new height of pre-match excitement arrived.

Because this match would determine to whom the championship belonged, the Alliance arranged for the championship trophy, the symbol of supreme glory, to be revealed before the match. The stadium’s lights extinguished all at once, and before the audience even had time to utter shouts, the spotlights all converged on the podium. At some point, the trophy had already been placed there, but under the absolute concentration of light, in this instant, it seemed like the sun hanging in the sky, flashing with infinite radiance. The players, the audience, everyone’s gazes were captured by this sight.

The spotlights dispersed, the stadium’s normal lighting came back on, and instantly everything was back to normal. But everyone’s gazes continued to linger on that championship trophy, gazes filled with desire and anticipation.

“Fuck, what a cheap gimmick.” Someone among the pro players complained, sounding extremely scornful, but no one answered. In that instant where the championship trophy had been lit up, whether or not they had won the championship before, every single one of them had felt their hearts stir.

This was a gimmick, but it was an extremely effective gimmick. Even for the one who had complained, there’d been some longing in his tone, a refusal to resign. This match, this sort of gimmick, it really provoked a certain sadness in their hearts.

The match was about to begin, but the two teams didn’t immediately return to their player areas. They gathered in front of their respective competitor booths, and everyone looked up toward the giant display screen, waiting for the group arena’s random map selection.

With a sound, the selection began. Images flashed by onscreen for around five seconds, before suddenly coming to a halt. A digital voice clearly announced the name of this map: Inevitable Confrontation.

“The name of this map really fits the occasion!”

No information was released beforehand about the random maps used in the playoffs. Even the broadcast commentators were only learning about the map now, and the commentary of course began from the name.

Championship, finals, an encounter on a narrow road – inevitable confrontation. There was no more description more fitting. And now, the map that had been chosen had this name.

The holographic projection and the stadium display screen began a simple overview of this map’s layout and characteristics.

A narrow valley, a bit twisting, but not complex. On both sides were steep and towering cliffs. As for whether they could be climbed, aside from a Nightwalker carrying a ninjato, it was hard to say. At this time, people would automatically think of Lord Grim’s many changing techniques, but because these cliffs were so high, as soon as they reached the top, they would be too far away to pose any threat at all to those at the bottom. As for whether or not there were any ambush points along the wall, that could not be seen clearly from such a brief introduction.

“It doesn’t look like there’s anything particularly special about this map?” Pan Lin said, after seeing this simple overview. There were definitely many maps in the original selection that had this kind of simple feature, and this map had been specially made for the playoffs. If they’d only designed this valley with a few extra twists and turns, there was really nothing new about this at all.

Just as everyone was wondering the same question, suddenly, there were screams of murder from the holographic projection. Everyone watched as horses and men appeared at both ends of the canyon, and ambushes also appeared on both mountain walls. Soon, the men and horses met at the center of the canyon and began to fight, killing each other ferociously. On the cliffs, the ambushes activated, and all sorts of boulders and wood tumbled down. In a few moments, both armies were completely wiped out.

Everyone was stunned.

What was this?

It surely wasn’t an animation just added to complement the name “inevitable confrontation,” right? This was the finals, they needed to introduce the map information in an orderly way. How could such empty showiness be allowed?

So, this wasn’t some animation created to enhance the atmosphere. This was something that would actually happen on this map.

It wasn’t just about the topography, they were actually introducing interfering events. Regardless of the outcome of this match, this design would inevitably trigger much discussion and controversy afterward. But at the moment, the audience was very curious to see how the players would respond to such a map with events and NPC interference.

Yet right now, there was pitifully little information about this interference. Was the timing of this event completely random, or set for a certain time? Would it only happen once per battle, or multiple? From their attacks, it seemed like the two groups on opposite ends of the canyon and those on the cliff walls formed three separate teams. What would be their attitudes toward the players’ characters?

Too much information that was needed to understand this map was not given before the match, and because of the ingenuity of this design, acquiring information about this map would be much more complicated than simply observing the terrain characteristics. The first and even the second players of both teams would have to do a lot of work in this aspect. So, who would the two teams send up?

Everyone was very curious. But on television, commentators Pan Lin and Li Yibo were very evasive. Although they had some ideas in their minds, they didn’t dare speak easily. They had truly been face-slapped too many times.

“This time, continuing to send out Ye Xiu first is a very appropriate choice for Happy!” Over in the pro player section, they didn’t have anything holding them back, and after discussion, they all agreed on this prediction. Facing such a complex situation, it would be best to send out Ye Xiu, someone who was experienced and had extremely good awareness. While gaining information, he had a very high chance of winning battles in such unpredictable situations.

“As for Samsara…” From Happy, Ye Xiu was the best choice, everyone recognized this in a glance. Not only did it make sense, it could continue the psychological oppression that his win streak had established. On the other hand, Samsara was definitely aware of Happy’s best choice, so their choice of player would, to a certain extent, have to counter it. Who was most appropriate on Samsara’s side?

While everyone was discussing, Samsara’s Jiang Botao reported their first player to the judge. And at the same time, from their roster, Sun Xiang was already walking toward the competitor booth.

Chapter 1641 - You Can’t Have Openings If You Don’t Act

Seeing Sun Xiang walk toward the competitor booth just like that, the pro players were stunned.

It wasn’t that they doubted this choice of player or anything, but… as of now, the judge still hadn’t announced the final player choice of both teams. But from Samsara, Sun Xiang was walking toward the competitor booth just like that?

He was exposing information.

Because of the random nature of the third round of playoffs, the player order was decided on the spot. If one went before the other, then it would be like revealing your move too early when playing rock-paper-scissors. The competition system couldn’t allow this kind of flaw, so following normal procedure, the two teams would first report their players to the judge, the judge would confirm, and then it would be announced to the stadium through the big screen. Only then would the players go onstage, verified by the judge.

This was the normal procedure because it amplified the atmosphere of the live match. Often, the name would be announced at the same time as the player went onstage. But in reality, the player had been determined long beforehand. Otherwise, if one team’s player stood up first, then the other team could see that and say, oh, that player, then we’ll send this player up…

This was the problem with Sun Xiang exposing the roster order. Right now, Happy actually hadn’t reported their player order yet, but he was already walking toward the booth. Then, if Happy made any arrangements specifically targeting Sun Xiang, then that wouldn’t be breaking any rules. They would just be getting a bargain.

And on Samsara’s side? They had no way to make any further changes. Jiang Botao had already reported the first player to the referee.

This was a huge oversight! Sun Xiang, that guy, this crucial match hadn’t even started yet and he’d already made such a low-level mistake!

Pro players were very familiar with the match format and paid attention to the rules, so they immediately realized that Sun Xiang’s actions didn’t seem right. But the ordinary audience members didn’t have this professional sensitivity. Right now, they were actually applauding and praising Sun Xiang’s appearance!

Was this a trick?

Seeing that the other Samsara players didn’t have any reaction to Sun Xiang’s action, the pro players couldn’t help but begin to think in this direction. It was one thing for just Sun Xiang himself to get confused, but there was no way that not a single person in Samsara realized the problem, right? But if this really were a trick, then the team’s reactions didn’t seem quite right, either. If they were pretending, they should at least pretend to be alarmed at Sun Xiang’s actions, right? And then when Happy made counteractive arrangements, they would suddenly change players. They could then say that Sun Xiang was just wandering around the stage. There was nothing against the rules about that.

That was what that plan should look like, but it didn’t look like Samsara was doing that, either. Nor did Happy have much of a reaction. Ye Xiu walked toward the judge, reporting their first player, and then he headed toward the competitor booth.

As expected, Happy’s first player was Ye Xiu. Even when Samsara had leaked information, they stuck with their original, obvious plan. One after another, Sun Xiang and Ye Xiu entered their respective competitor booths.

Bold, confident!

Samsara displayed the kingly attitude of a championship team. They didn’t engage in any of those schemes that people were imagining. Upright and honest, they sent out their first player, who boldly walked into the competitor booth.

No trick.

Was there really no trick?

“The trick is that there is no trick,” Blue Rain’s Yu Wenzhou suddenly said.

“In other words, if you feel that there is no trick, then there is no trick; if you feel that there is a trick, then the trick comes,” he added.

Xiao Shiqin nodded, Wang Jiexi also nodded, Zhang Xinjie did not disagree, but no one said anything else.

Most of the others were still at a loss. Only after thinking hard did they begin to understand, and they all felt that their brains weren’t enough.

“How black-hearted…” Those who could follow the twisting logic were all sighing. And at this time, the judge announced, the first battle of the final match group arena began now.

Map loaded, characters loaded.

A narrow, slightly winding canyon, extending from north to south. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf loaded in on the north end of the canyon, while Lord Grim was on the south end.

Behind each of the two characters was usually the map boundary. Right now, the televised broadcast showed a close-up of the area behind the characters.

The so-called “map world” behind the characters was filled with two military camps of NPCs, each with a wooden sign at their entrances, with words written very clearly on them: Military Area, Death to Intruders!

The players watching the match suddenly understood. This map world was like the edge of a cliff, an abyss, a place that the characters would suffer damage just from entering. This kind of boundary design wasn’t unique in Glory, and this map simply used a particular method to implement this design.

However, this kind of scene, would it be like an abyss where once you fell, there was no way to survive? No one knew. In this kind of crucial match, there was no way anyone would test it out for themselves. If they were to test, they would want to think of a way to send the opponent’s character there. Right now, as soon as Ye Xiu and Sun Xiang realized the design behind them, they immediately controlled their characters to stay far away.

Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf steadily stepped forward. Even though Ye Xiu could control Lord Grim to use the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella’s Ninjato form to scale the canyon walls, right now he did the exact same thing as Sun Xiang – control his character to steadily advance.

The two character’s actions at the start of the match were exactly the same. The audience watched as the two characters, one heading south, one heading north. Both were looking left and right at their surroundings in the same way. If not for their entirely different equipment, it would be hard to distinguish who was who.

At last, the two characters reached the middle, where there were no twists and turns. Very quickly, they saw their approaching opponent.

The movement pace of the two characters instantly became cautious.

No turns, no way to circle around. This was the so-called inevitable confrontation, a direct collision on a narrow road, where there was no way to evade.

Closer, step by step.

Lord Grim’s attacks could reach far, and right now the opponent was already within his attack range. But Ye Xiu didn’t attack. He simply maintained his rhythm, allowing Lord Grim to approach step by step.

Sun Xiang was even less likely to attack. A Battle Mage was a class that needed to be close enough to reach their full battle potential. As the distance closed, options gradually opened up to him, such as Dragon Breaks the Ranks, which could instantly eliminate the distance between the two characters right now. But Sun Xiang still did not make a move.

Neither side attacked. And then, as though the two of them agreed, one suddenly went left, one went right, both moving at a slant.

Just as the distance between them looked like it was about to be closed, the two suddenly controlled their characters to move diagonally, increasing the distance horizontally.

Were these two planning to let each other go by just like that, and continue to study this map?

Seeing this scene, many people already began to think in this direction. But the pro players all knew that this kind of investigation wasn’t very necessary. Their offstage teammates had the same omniscient view as the audience, and investigation was shared. So that half of the map that Lord Grim hadn’t stepped in yet, Happy’s players had already seen it from the point of view of Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf. The only one who didn’t know that area was Ye Xiu himself.

Similarly, Sun Xiang had experienced one half of the map for himself, and was still unfamiliar with the other half.

In this kind of situation, would they really let the other go by to understand that half of the map they still hadn’t experienced?

No pro player would have such a harmonious and friendly thought. In this moment, for the players onstage, this one half known, one half unknown was their strength and weakness. Thus, when they met, the main goal of their confrontation should be to force the opponent toward the area that they were familiar with and that their opponent was unfamiliar with, and decide victory there.

That was why neither player attacked. Their characters drew closer and closer, both of them looking for this kind of opportunity, to bring the opponent into the half of the map behind them.

But neither of them found such an opportunity, because both of them were very cautious, and neither left any openings. This made it seem like there was a high level of unspoken understanding and coordination between them, but in reality neither forgot that their opponent was their opponent. They paid attention to the other’s movements solely to find a chance. As soon as there was an opening, that there was an opportunity to be seized, both of them would destroy this coordination without hesitation.

Their north-south distance was practically zero, but because of their slanted movement, there was still around six units of distance between them horizontally. Both characters had their backs facing the canyon wall. Unlike before, they were no longer looking around. They were focused entirely on the opponent in front of them.

Movement stopped. Stand-off.

Six units of distance. Lord Grim had too many skills he could use to attack the opponent, and One Autumn Leaf could also attack the opponent at this distance. Because of the long reach of a Battle Mage’s weapon, their attack distance was a bit longer than things like fists or swords.

But the two players simply continued to face each other without moving. No movement. The display showed their hand speeds as zero, two flat lines on the graph leisurely progressing forward.

One second, two seconds…

But even though there was no movement, that didn’t mean that it wasn’t draining their energy. Both of the players were currently extremely focused. The rhythm wasn’t just slow, it had completely stopped, and no one knew who would attack first. They only knew that in this kind of static stand-off, it would be very difficult to break the equilibrium first. The game wasn’t like reality. As long as there were no inputs, the character could maintain its posture and position for years. And moving could potentially create an opening. Despite the many experts watching this match, they were at a loss as to how to break this absolute stand-off.

No one could have predicted that these two would engage in a stand-off to this level. In order to avoid creating openings and eliminate flaws, they continuously made their moves simpler and simpler, decreasing their movements, lowering their speed.

At last, they sunk to the limit, to the very lowest.

If you didn’t act, there would be no openings.

This was no longer a situation, it was a state, a state that only pro players could appreciate.

It would be very difficult to break this state from within. To break from the outside, there was typically only one reason – the judge deciding that this was “improper player conduct” and getting involved. But this stand-off wasn’t improper conduct, it was that there was simply no way to act. There were no controls being made, but the confrontation never stopped. This was a battle of spirit. If this were truly broken by the judge for “improper conduct,” the beauty of the scene really would be ruined.

Fortunately, today’s map happened to have another outside method to break this stand-off.

Event refresh!

Chapter 1642 - The Mountain Storm Has Arrived

As the saying went, a coming storm is foretold by the rising mountain wind. But right now, it wasn’t just the wind – the storm itself was upon them.

From the two ends of the canyon, the area forbidden to the players, the two camps of NPCs charged forth like rushing water. War cries and pounding footsteps rose up, sending clouds of dust billowing as they made their way toward the center of the map. At the same time, the hidden ambushers on the canyon walls began to make their move, paying attention to the situation below them as they made their way toward the center of the canyon as well.

The audience could see all of this very clearly. But Ye Xiu and Sun Xiang were unaware. The two continued to stand there, unmoving.

The two sides grew closer and closer. The sound carried through the canyon, and wavering forms began to appear at the very limits of their vision.

The two still did not move.

Right now, they were no longer competing in just patience or concentration. It was more a battle of willpower.

With the interference of the NPCs, the two would have to move sooner or later. And now, they were about to see who could endure until the very last moment before moving.

In a typical match, players were competing to be the first to do something, and they would fear that their controls weren’t fast enough, that they couldn’t beat the opponent in speed. But today, in this battle between Ye Xiu and Sun Xiang, the two of them had suppressed this match to this extent. It was as though they were playing a game where whoever moved first would lose.

Reality, of course, wasn’t that absolute. In fact, whoever moved first now might even be able to take the initiative. But neither of them took this risk.

Yes, risk.

The very simple action of breaking the unmoving situation to attack was actually considered a risk by the two of them. In this battle, the level of caution they were taking could be described as insane. If that weren’t the case, they would have never become locked in a stalemate like this.

But Ye Xiu doing this was one thing – the pro players were shocked to see Sun Xiang doing so as well. This haughty, impatient youth was actually able to restrain himself and compete in patience, compete in willpower?

In their view, Sun Xiang was competing with his weakness against the opponent’s strength. In this kind of stalemate, he couldn’t just toss his keyboard and mouse to the side. It required high concentration, maintaining a calm and steady mental state.

Anyone could do this for a short bit of time. But maintaining this steady state for a long time was very difficult, especially for someone with a personality like Sun Xiang’s. Not many people felt that he could keep control.

And right now, he was faced with a big test, the event refresh. The armies of NPCs approached, blocking the already-narrow canyon so tightly that even water couldn’t escape. This next test was no longer just the problem of the opponent.

Time was running out, the distance was closing. The NPCs were lined up in battle formation. Glory’s NPCs were also divided into the classes of Glory players, but their skill trees were much simpler. The more ordinary NPCs normally only had one or two skills, Boss level ones typically only had 3 or 5. Very few would have a complete skill tree. However, mixing skills across classes was fairly frequent.

And the charge after the event activation had been shown by the map introduction earlier. If the players had been paying attention, they should have taken note of the NPCs’ class composition and battle methods.

Neither Happy nor Samsara had overlooked this point, and right now the unfolding position of the NPCs was exactly the same as had been shown in the preview video.

In the front row were Knights. Once they had gotten close enough, they all lifted their shields. Instantly, there were no people to be seen on either side, only shields. It was as though Lord Grim and One Autumn Leaf were sealed in a rectangular box.

And then, boom boom boom, the sound of cannonfire. Hidden behind the shields, the Gunner classes of the two sides launched their attacks first, and they had all chosen the same skill: Stinger.

Stinger, ten of them!

The number of shots was also something that the players had paid attention to during the map introduction, and indeed, there were this many. The timing of the fire was also exactly the same. As for the flight path, everyone had originally wondered whether they would adjust depending on the exact position of the two players, but now, they saw that they still followed the rhythm of the introduction. In other words, right now, the two armies of NPCs were still ignoring Lord Grim and One Autumn Leaf. They were not the major targets of the Stingers.

Bang bang bang bang bang…

Soon after, the Stingers exploded like fireworks in the air. One artillery shell would explode into eight, making 160 Stingers in total. Even though Lord Grim and One Autumn Leaf hadn’t changed the attack rhythm of the NPCs, the wide AoE of this skill meant that their position would still be covered by this attack.

These two were really enduring to this extent. The Stingers were almost upon them, were they still not moving?

They moved!

The first one who moved was actually Lord Grim? The one who couldn’t last any longer was actually Ye Xiu?

Those who didn’t understand the subtleties of this scene didn’t think that this was a big deal, and in fact a number of people were thinking about how Ye Xiu’s reaction was faster. But the pro players were extremely surprised. Sun Xiang was actually steadier than Ye Xiu?

Right now, Lord Grim moved first, and Sun Xiang could finally begin to attack. But then, Lord Grim’s arms came up, his hands moving in a blur.

Sun Xiang wanted to cry…

Shadow Clone Technique!

Lord Grim had actually used this technique. Stand-off, restraint, both sides were waiting for the best chance to move, all the way until they had been surrounded by the NPCs. Ye Xiu could endure no longer, he made the first move, and Lord Grim moved, to run…

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Sun Xiang, who had already realized that something was wrong, used his fastest reaction and fastest hand speed. One Autumn Leaf lifted Evil Annihilation and rushed forward, instantly shattering Lord Grim.

But Sun Xiang’s heart sank.

Shattering meant that this was a Shadow Clone. The Shadow Clone Technique had been successfully cast, Lord Grim had already left from this position.

Where was he?

Sun Xiang lifted the view of One Autumn Leaf, and the first thing he saw was a Stinger about to land right upon his face. There was no time to dodge.

Boom!

The explosive power of a Stinger wasn’t actually very large, but it could easily cover a head. In this moment, it was as though One Autumn Leaf’s head exploded.

Through his fire-blurred vision, Sun Xiang could see Lord Grim land atop an outcropping on the cliff face, but in order to be well-prepared, the ninjato in his right hand was also firmly stuck in the stone. Sun Xiang had only managed one look before Lord Grim was moving again, nimbly using his ninjato to climb the wall.

Stalemate? Restraint? Wait for the best moment to attack? Who moved first would lose?

Sun Xiang truly no longer knew if Ye Xiu had even had these thoughts. Perhaps it had been like that at the start, but as the situation changed, his thought process had changed as well; or perhaps from the very beginning, he’d been purposefully putting on this act, all to lead him into this trap now…

After the widespread explosions of the Stingers, the two teams of NPCs continued to advance. According to the map introduction video, what came next would be the Knights’ Charge, and then the shields of both sides would brutally crash together.

Indeed, that seemed to be what was happening. The lines of Knights were already lowering their shields and rushing forward with Charge. But unlike the video, this time there was an extra One Autumn Leaf in the middle. Sun Xiang was like the layer of cream stuck between two cookies.

Clang clang clang clang…

The shields clashed together, producing a deep, ringing sound. In the end, One Autumn Leaf did manage to escape being squished into cream. A Dragon Breaks the Ranks allowed him to charge to the mountain wall, and then he jumped up, kicking against the cliffside. The second jump gave him the height he needed at the crucial moment to avoid the shields crashing below him.

Dragon Tooth, Double Stab, and the stab from a normal attack.

Midair Four Hit Combo was instantly completed, striking against the wall, and they accurately struck against the same place. The razor-sharp Evil Annihilation ultimately pierced through, and just like that One Autumn Leaf hung in the air. He still had to curl his lower body, lifting up his two legs in order to avoid the NPCs clashing beneath him.

“Not bad!” Praise from Ye Xiu flashed in the chat. Sun Xiang lifted his camera view and saw that Ye Xiu had already found another outcropping. Lord Grim stood steadily atop it, and this time he had retracted his ninjato. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was balanced in his right hand, and at the tip of the umbrella, the gun’s muzzle was a black hole. In his left hand he held a grenade, and just as Sun Xiang controlled One Autumn Leaf to lift his head, that grenade came tumbling down, and immediately after, boom boom boom, three Anti-Tank Missiles were flying toward him.

One Autumn Leaf, dangling in midair, desperately hanging onto Evil Annihilation with legs curled, was pathetic enough. How could he avoid this kind of attack? But in the moment that the grenade and the missiles were about to strike, One Autumn Leaf’s body suddenly shrunk into nothingness, as though he’d been squeezed into a void.

Teleport!

Last match, this was the skill that Sun Xiang had chosen to add to One Autumn Leaf’s weapon. This match, it was the same.

The attack was dodged, and it seemed like One Autumn Leaf could use this move to find a temporary landing point.

But suddenly, Lord Grim lifted his right leg, and kicked out.

Front Kick!

And then, everyone saw as a figure tore out of the void right into this foot. One Autumn Leaf was sent flying.

The pro players watching this all sighed and shook their heads. When it came to mind games, even ten Sun Xiangs combined were no match for Ye Xiu!

Chapter 1643 - True Initiative

Front Kick, knockback effect, but right now One Autumn Leaf was in midair, so the knockback became a blow away.

How had this attack been so accurate? How did Ye Xiu make such a godly prediction? Most of the normal players were freaking out, but the pro players all understood that to call the prediction godly was a bit excessive. Ye Xiu simply made a fairly good response to one possibility among many.

If Ye Xiu had truly completely predicted that Sun Xiang would control One Autumn Leaf to teleport here, then a better move for him would have been to use a stronger attack. But instead, he only used a Front Kick, a short and fast skill. When using this skill, his first consideration was that even if Sun Xiang hadn't controlled One Autumn Leaf to teleport here, it wasn't a big deal if the kick missed. This one kick wouldn't affect his own position.

But right now, this kick had served a purpose. And if this Front Kick were only perfunctory, without any follow-up attack, that would be too unbefitting of his God level.

The Front Kick landed, and then Lord Grim leapt forward, chasing after the flying One Autumn Leaf.

But Sun Xiang was no weakling. True, he was no match for Ye Xiu when it came to playing mind games, and Ye Xiu had predicted his actions this time. But when it came to a battle of technique, Sun Xiang feared no expert.

Even in this situation, he still completed an attack.

Circle Swing!

Even as One Autumn Leaf was in midair, his attack was still that fast, that accurate, that fierce. The spear Evil Annihilation became a streak of dark light, striking toward the pursuer Lord Grim.

But then, Lord Grim suddenly waved his hand, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella switched to ninjato form and stuck in the mountain wall. With that, Lord Grim's body halted. In the end, the dark streak that was Evil Annihilation just barely missed him.

:)

Ye Xiu actually still had time to send an emoticon in the chat. The pro players who saw this screen couldn't help but hear Ye Xiu's shameless laughter ringing in their ears. Their imaginations were enough to replicate his voice.

But Sun Xiang wouldn't accept defeat lying down. The Circle Swing missed, but the retracted Evil Annihilation swung behind him, jabbing out sideways, piercing the mountain wall.

Flying backwards, One Autumn Leaf crashed into this obstacle that he'd created for himself. But to everyone's surprise, One Autumn Leaf actually curled his body, and used the force from colliding against Evil Annihilation to change direction, doing a roll.

This was… a Quick Recover?

Not just the ordinary audience members, even the pro players were shocked.

On the narrow shaft of the spear, Sun Xiang had actually managed to control One Autumn Leaf to perform this Quick Recover roll. Like an acrobat, One Autumn Leaf ended up balanced on the spear's shaft.

This definitely wasn't a control that a player would practice normally. This was something that Sun Xiang had invented on the spot, demonstrating his incredible adaptability, as well as his high hand speed and precise control.

Like this, Sun Xiang was actually able to control a Battle Mage to what a Ninja did.

But the Ninja had this ability largely by relying on the special properties of the ninjato. That long rope attached to the end of the blade was the key to allowing one to climb. And Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf could only perch on Evil Annihilation like this, because his hands needed to hold onto Evil Annihilation. Otherwise, he would be dropping the weapon.

In this situation, it was relatively easy to jump out horizontally, and he could pull out the spear as he did so. But if he wanted to jump upward, then the spear firmly lodged in the mountain wall supporting the character's weight became an obstacle. This problem had been studied long before, and the conclusion had been that it was too difficult and probably wasn't worth it. In the end, no one wasted their energy to try to make it happen.

What would Sun Xiang do now?

Everyone was suddenly very curious, and the stadium was already filled with thunderous applause just for that acrobatic feat Sun Xiang had just completed.

But, was the important thing right now what Sun Xiang would do?

No. The one who had the initiative right now was definitely Ye Xiu. What Ye Xiu would do would direct the upcoming situation of this battle.

So even though Ye Xiu also very impressed at Sun Xiang's Quick Recover, it didn't cause him to slow down the pace. Just as One Autumn Leaf stabilized himself atop the spear, Lord Grim was already flying toward him.

One Autumn Leaf was balanced on his weapon. If he pulled it out, the character would fall; if he didn't pull it out, how could he use skills to fight back? Everyone had just been praising Sun Xiang's ingenuity with his move, but right now, it looked like his ingenuity had blocked him off in a dead end?

At this moment, as One Autumn Leaf crouched on the spear, his left hand still tightly gripped Evil Annihilation, while his right palm thrust forward.

Falling Flower Palm!

An attack with decent priority and AoE.

However, the attack distance was too short, which was the obvious mistake. The Falling Flower Palm came out, but Lord Grim was already slashing toward him with a sword. When it collided with the magic energy of Falling Flower Palm, it didn't lose in priority at all. In fact, it could be said that it completely pierced through the magic energy from this palm.

"How evil…"

After this attack came out, the pro players all sighed.

Wave Wheel Slasher!

Ye Xiu had actually controlled Lord Grim to use this attack in midair. With the priority of this attack, how could the Falling Flower Palm blast it aside? It was naturally at a large disadvantage. The swordlight wiped past, the ripples of energy immediately locked onto One Autumn Leaf, and following the direction pointed by the sword, tore him in that direction.

Evil Annihilation was pulled out of the mountain wall, One Autumn Leaf was locked in midair by the rippling energy from Wave Wheel Slasher and began to take damage. But everyone could see that the key point right now wasn't this bit of damage, but that One Autumn Leaf had been completely sent into the air without a single bit of support.

Left? Right?

Even if Evil Annihilation had been another one and a half times as long, he still wouldn't be able to reach either mountain wall. One Autumn Leaf could only hang there and wait for the Wave Wheel Slasher to finish, before free-falling down into the clashing armies of NPCs below him!

After Ye Xiu's Lord Grim sent One Autumn Leaf flying with a Wave Wheel Slasher, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella changed form again. Lord Grim, pressed against the mountain wall, stood steadily as One Autumn Leaf fell into the chaotic battle below. They were about to see what kind of attitude these two armies of NPCs would have toward a stranger that had snuck his way into their ranks. But for Samsara, this experiment was a bit cruel, as their player's character became the guinea pig.

One Autumn Leaf falling.

If one's eyes were sharp, they could see that One Autumn Leaf was making adjustments while in the air. The grab of a Wave Wheel Slasher didn't have as overwhelmingly high priority as a Circle Swing or the many grab attacks of a Grappler. As soon as the damage ended, the character could be controlled by the player again.

One Autumn Leaf stretched himself out in midair, the spear Evil Annihilation was already lifted to his head, and the instant he landed, Evil Annihilation came down, shaking the earth.

Shattering the Lands!

This was Sun Xiang's response.

Chapter 1644 - The Final Choice

In Season 7, Sun Xiang stepped onstage for the first time and immediately received widespread attention. Even though he came from a weak team like Conquering Clouds, his performance was exceptional, breaking through the rookie wall and easily collecting the Best Rookie award.

At that time, “prodigy,””the star of hope,” all sorts of extravagant praise rained down upon him. Sun Xiang very quickly became pleased and satisfied by all this.

Amidst all of this, there was much commentary about how if Sun Xiang weren’t held back by the rest of his team, or if he had a top god-level character, then perhaps Sun Xiang would have had even better results in his first season, or even made history.

Sun Xiang deeply appreciated this kind of talk. He also felt that his abilities hadn’t reached their full potential, and that he needed a bigger space to shine.

He needed a better team, and he needed a top-notch character.

Battle God One Autumn Leaf was undoubtedly the most godly character in Glory, and Ye Qiu, called the Glory Textbook, was the top God in Glory history.

But Sun Xiang didn’t think that it was such a big deal.

He of course knew of Ye Qiu’s past glory, but by the time he’d gotten into Glory, all he saw was the performance of Ye Qiu and Excellent Era decline year by year.

So, when Excellent Era extended an olive branch to him in Season 8, Sun Xiang was overjoyed – he felt that this was a match made in heaven. He needed exactly this kind of team, this kind of character.

He came to Excellent Era, replaced Ye Qiu, accepted the Battle God One Autumn Leaf.

Sun Xiang was puffed up with pride. He felt that a new era was upon him. With this kind of top-notch team and character, he would immediately soar up into the sky.

But that season, Excellent Era was relegated.

No result was more painful than this. That season, even Conquering Clouds, who’d aspired for the playoffs while Sun Xiang was still there, hadn’t fallen to that extent after Sun Xiang left.

What had happened?

Sun Xiang, whose professional career was still only two years, would be lying if he said he hadn’t panicked.

He had a top-notch character, a championship team. How could their final result be relegation? Where had they gone wrong? Was his own skill not enough? No! Of course that couldn’t be the reason.

At that time, Sun Xiang was already beginning to doubt himself, but he was unwilling to believe it, he was unwilling to ponder this question seriously.

He was anxious to prove himself, and he had considered leaving Excellent Era sooner, but the team’s quick actions after becoming relegated ultimately convinced him to place his expectations on this team.

But then, that season, in the Challenger League finals, Excellent Era lost to Happy. He lost again.

He lost to Ye Xiu, lost to this person that he’d squeezed out of Excellent Era, the guy who’d lost everything.

Top-tier characters? Happy had none.

An incredible roster? Happy didn’t have that, either.

Just by relying on this kind of team, Ye Xiu was able to defeat Sun Xiang and Excellent Era. This wasn’t just the victory and defeat of one match, nor the victory and defeat of an entire season. This completely destroyed Sun Xiang’s sense of what had value in Glory.

With a top-tier character and strong teammates, he could soar right up into the sky.

This was what Sun Xiang had always believed.

And Happy had none of these things. And yet, Happy won.

From Best Rookie, to transferring to a top powerhouse, in the span of a short year and a half, Sun Xiang had experienced the shining peak of life that countless people would never reach. And then in the next year and a half, relegation, failure in the Challenger League, this was a blow that many, many pro players had never experienced.

Three years, in the first three years of his professional career, Sun Xiang had experienced many things. But when he looked back, he discovered that he was still so far away from the playoffs, never mind the finals stage.

Wasn’t he a prodigy? Wasn’t he brimming with talent? Wasn’t he the star of tomorrow?

Excellent Era disbanded, and Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf joined Samsara.

He still controlled the top character, he had even stronger teammates by his side. This was the two-consecutive-championship master of kings. Amidst the gray of his professional career, a new chance came to turn things around. In fact, it could be said that he’d reached an even higher level.

But this time, Sun Xiang would not be the arrogant and complacent person he was before. He began to attentively scrutinize himself, study how he could become better.

He did well. He swiftly integrated with the rest of Team Samsara. It wasn’t like how many commentators had warned, where there might be internal conflicts because of issues about the core position. He and Zhou Zekai, one close and one long-range, their Double One partnership ultimately took the Best Partners award for this season.

He finally fixed his attitude. And in this season’s battles, he once again met Happy, once again met Ye Xiu. And again, they met in the finals, facing off directly against each other. This battle had even given them an appropriate map – Inevitable Confrontation.

Sun Xiang wanted to win.

He wanted to defeat Happy, and wanted to defeat Ye Xiu even more.

He admitted that it was thanks to Ye Xiu and Happy that he had woken up, but this only made him want to defeat them even more. He hoped to let all of Happy, let Ye Xiu see, that he was no longer the Sun Xiang that they had defeated before.

And so he was cautious, he was prudent, he didn’t allow himself to make any mistake in this match. It was for the sake of Samsara’s victory, and at the same time it was to fiercely prove himself in front of the person who had defeated him before.

In the end, he had still ended up in such a pathetic position.

But this time, he wasn’t angry, wasn’t resentful, wasn’t like before, where he found fault in everything except himself.

Immediately, he began to evaluate himself, and he realized, perhaps he had used the wrong method.

Caution, psychological battle, these weren’t his strengths, but in order to prove himself, he still chose to use this playstyle that didn’t quite suit him.

Even though he very much hoped that he could surpass Ye Xiu in all aspects, in reality, everyone had their strengths and weaknesses. Sun Xiang’s strengths didn’t lay in these areas.

He should choose to use the playstyle that he was good at. Because, on the battlefield, his goal was to win, not to surpass! The only thing that people needed to surpass was themselves. Following his own footsteps, one step after another surpassing himself. Only then would he become stronger and stronger.

Ye Xiu, or anyone, they should not be targets to be surpassed. Rather, they should be defeated!

Shattering the Lands!

A Level 75 skill, this was Sun Xiang’s final choice. In the face of uncertainty regarding the NPCs’ attitude toward the players, he was no longer careful, he was no longer trying to think it over carefully, because those were not his strengths. He could not become one of those players who relied on their minds to fight.

He took the initiative in attacking the NPCs. Shattering the Lands sent magic energy surging through the ground, causing these obstacles in front of him to go flying into the air.

These people in my way, all of you can die!

In this instant, the imposing aura that One Autumn Leaf displayed was just like the Battle God under Ye Xiu’s hands back in the day.

Chapter 1645 - One Autumn Leaf’s Strongest State

The event NPCs were interference, but at the same time they could be used. If used well, this could be an extremely intelligent match.

In the past, Sun Xiang had thought that he was all-powerful, that there was nothing he couldn’t do in Glory. But now, he could admit that these games involving lots of calculations weren’t his strong point. So, he didn’t bother with thinking about whether these things could be any use to him. If it’s interference, then wipe it away!

Shattering the Lands tossed the nearby NPCs into the air. Offstage, the players from the two teams were seizing the chance to observe. Without clashing with the NPCs like this, it would be very difficult to judge how strong they were. Aside from that, how would these NPCs react to someone taking the initiative to attack them? Before this, the two armies seemed to have mostly ignored the presence of Lord Grim and One Autumn Leaf. While the two of them had been climbing the mountain wall, the NPCs hadn’t specifically directed any attacks toward the two of them.

But right now, after being directly attacked like this, if the NPCs still had no reaction, then this event’s design would be fairly boring. Glory, this classic game, would never have that kind of meaningless design, whether in-game or on a competitive map.

Indeed, after being attacked by Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf, the two teams of NPCs no longer ignored them. Both sides suddenly had a clear attack target: One Autumn Leaf.

Cannon shots, magic spells…

One Autumn Leaf had already cleared the area immediately surrounding him, so the first attacks that arrived were all long-range. Aside from those that caused damage, there were also a few curses with controlling effects. The class composition of these NPCs was quite well-rounded.

But Sun Xiang had predicted this possibility. When the attacks reached him, the end animation of Shattering the Lands had completed. One Autumn Leaf darted forward like an arrow, leaving many attacks behind him. At the same time, he swung his arm again, tossing forth a Tyrant’s Destruction toward the NPCs falling from the air like dumplings.

A streak of dark light. The many NPCs tumbling in front of One Autumn Leaf were swept aside by the Tyrant’s Destruction. Each of them flew backward toward the mountain wall, where Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was still cheerfully watching the show!

Sun Xiang didn’t forget who his opponent was, he didn’t forget the goal of this battle! While sweeping away this disruption, he was already beginning to attack Ye Xiu.

Sun Xiang had turned the NPCs into human cannonballs, but the blowback of the Tyrant’s Destruction wasn’t very strong. These human cannonballs didn’t fly very quickly, and could be blocked by any casual attack. Even using a grab skill to throw these cannonballs back at One Autumn Leaf would be a very simple thing to do. But Ye Xiu chose to dodge. Lord Grim jumped down from his original position, once again displaying the capabilities of the ninjato. Lord Grim climbed along the cliff face, carefully avoiding all of the NPCs that Sun Xiang sent toward him.

“What is this guy doing?”

The pro players couldn’t quite understand. Sun Xiang was already suffering attacks from the NPCs that he’d been harassing. This was a perfect chance to add oil to the fire and grab victory. But Ye Xiu still stayed out of it, looking like his only plan was to watch the show. The watching pro players were confused.

And then, when those NPCs sent flying by the Shattering the Lands finally crashed back down against the ground, another wave of long-range attacks came toward him, and close-range fighters rushed toward him as well. Seeing the movements of the NPCs, the pro players suddenly understood.

“This guy is too sneaky!” everyone exclaimed.

Ye Xiu could have begun his offensive now, but he chose not to, solely because he didn’t want to draw the aggro of the NPCs. Right now, the NPCs were already moving against One Autumn Leaf. If Lord Grim attacked One Autumn Leaf at a time like this, it would be very easy for Sun Xiang to direct his attack onto an NPC.

And so, he chose to avoid it all. He had no conflict with any of the NPCs, nor did he give Sun Xiang the chance to create such conflict.

This sort of sensitivity to the aggro of NPCs was really something that could only be trained after spending large amounts of time in-game. The high and mighty pro players clearly weren’t sensitive enough to this, to the extent that not a single one of them had immediately recognized Ye Xiu’s intention.

The battle continued.

But it had already become a struggle between Sun Xiang and the NPCs. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim perched upon the wall unscathed as he watched the battle, and then it became time for his trash talk.

“Right, right.”

“Left, left.”

“Above.”

“Nice reactions!”

“14 o’clock direction.”

“That’s just 2 o’clock!”

“Haha tricked you.”

“Hm you didn’t believe it?”

Messages flashed nonstop in the channel. Looking down from above, Ye Xiu gave pointers on the chaotic battle between Sun Xiang and the NPCs. The Samsara fans felt tightness in their chest. Most of them felt that this battle wouldn’t turn out well for Sun Xiang. However, the pro players didn’t have such a simple view of the problem. They quickly noticed that even though Sun Xiang was amidst all this chaos, One Autumn Leaf wasn’t suffering very serious injuries, and was in fact getting braver and braver as he fought.

“The NPCs aren’t very strong!” the pro players said.

This was the reason why their opinion was different from that of ordinary gamers. Because their skill levels were different, their worldviews were different. Surrounded by so many NPCs, ordinary gamers would think that this was a death sentence. But for a pro player, this was a still a situation that they could deal with.

There was another point, too. The NPCs didn’t forget about their own battle just because of the interference of Sun Xiang. Right now, they were still attacking each other as well, and Sun Xiang was very cleverly able to take advantage of this.

That silhouette amidst the chaotic battle became clearer and clearer. Around him swirled all sorts of magic energy.

Neutral Chasers, Light Chasers, Dark Chasers, Fire Chasers, Ice Chasers…

Five types of Chasers, five colors. Right now, One Autumn Leaf was adding them up without interruption. Aside from this, there was a gold aura surrounding him, so bright that it practically outshone the light of those five types of chasers.

Battle Spirit!

The Awakening skill of the Battle Mage, a status activated after enough combos. After the Level 75 upgrade, it could reach eight stages. It was a classic skill that was loved by countless players in-game.

And right now, the blinding golden light that flashed around One Autumn Leaf was that of the eighth stage. It had been extremely rare to see in this professional season, especially in a 1v1. Eighth stage battle spirit required a 150-hit combo.

Such a steep requirement, there was practically no chance of it appearing in an individual battle. An opponent that you could hit a 150-hit combo on was basically a wooden dummy. By that point, activating Battle Spirit would basically be pointless.

Because of this, many pro Battle Mage players wouldn’t add many points to this skill. Awakening skills were all extremely strong, and costed a significant amount of skill points.

But who was One Autumn Leaf? This was the character named the Battle God, the number one character in Glory, his Battle Spirit had definitely been leveled up to the max. Before, Ye Xiu had used this character. After Sun Xiang received it, with his kind of personality, he believed that he could do anything that Ye Xiu could, so he didn’t adjust the points on Battle Spirit. The Level 75 update came around, adding another rank to the skill, going from a max seven stages to eight.

The Sun Xiang that arrived at Samsara was already beginning to reevaluate himself. Still, he didn’t erase the points on the Battle Spirit skill. This kind of skill, relying on technique to increase battle power, he felt that it suited his style very well. It was very difficult to reach that high of a rank in a solo battle, but there was still a chance in a team round. It would still be difficult, but Ye Xiu had done it back in the day!

Even though many people believed that Battle Spirit wasn’t practical on the professional stage, in the hearts of the Battle Mage players, this was still a glory that belonged to them. To ignite the brilliant fire of the highest rank Battle Spirit on stage, this was something that every Battle Mage player had dreamed of, even though most would only put a few points into the skill in the end.

And Sun Xiang, he dared turn this dream into reality, he wanted to light up with the flaming golden light of Battle Spirit.

And today, he accomplished it.

Even though it had been convenient with the setup of this map, if he hadn’t had this kind of goal from the beginning, perhaps today’s One Autumn Leaf would only have a second or third rank Battle Spirit. He wouldn’t be aflame with such a glorious battle aura.

“This time, Ye Xiu played around for too long, huh?” the various pro players exclaimed.

The NPCs’ battle ability wasn’t anything incredible, they hadn’t completely controlled Sun Xiang. One Autumn Leaf paid a bit of price in health, but he managed to ignite the strongest state of the Battle Mage. If this continued, these NPCs wouldn’t be any obstacle at all, and Ye Xiu would have to face a One Autumn Leaf that had reached an incredible level of power. This was something that even he, as One Autumn Leaf’s creator, had never witnessed before.

Chapter 1646 - What Is Your Intent

Sky Strike, Falling Flower Palm!

A small combo created from low-level skills. Falling Flower Palm’s powerful Blow Away sent one NPC into the air, crashing toward Lord Grim, who was still hanging onto the wall. The offensive against Ye Xiu resumed.

As the saying went, Ye Xiu had tried riding a tiger and now found it hard to to get off. At least, this was what many pro players thought.

He hadn’t acted first because he’d been concerned about drawing the aggro of the NPCs. He’d hoped the NPCs’ battle ability could wear out Sun Xiang.

But no one had thought that these NPCs were so weak. From the very start, they hadn’t dealt much damage to One Autumn Leaf. Instead, they’d served to buff One Autumn Leaf.

Five types of chasers, golden Battle Spirit. One Autumn Leaf was in his peak state right now, the highest peak he’d ever reached in these ten plus years.

And right now, the one he was attacking was the one who had brought him into this world, Ye Xiu.

What should Ye Xiu do?

He hadn’t attacked at first, and if he attacked now, he would still attract the NPCs’ aggro. If, under the interference of the NPCs, he was then attacked by this One Autumn Leaf in peak form, he really should have just acted earlier.

Now that things were at this point, maybe his best option was just to continue avoiding battle!

This was what everyone was thinking. But this time, Ye Xiu didn’t control Lord Grim to continue dodging. Even though Falling Flower Palm’s Blow Away effect was strong, strong enough to send a character flying this high, the character would only fly slower and slower. By the time it arrived, it posed no threat. Lord Grim stretched out his hand and easily grabbed the NPC. With a Fling, he tossed it back at One Autumn Leaf below.

Everyone was caught off-guard. They thought that this was the really worst decision. Ye Xiu surely would have calculated this, right? What was this guy planning now?

The pro players in the audience began to ponder this, but onstage, Sun Xiang didn’t think twice. He had already decided to stop trying to engage in mental battles against Ye Xiu. He was focusing all of his energy in carrying out his offensive.

No matter how Ye Xiu would respond, there was only one plan in his heart: knock him down, get rid of obstacles, knock him down!

Dodge!

One Autumn Leaf dodged the NPC that Lord Grim tossed at him. Evil Annihilation flashed out, sweeping up another NPC, and throwing this human cannonball at Lord Grim once again. And when Lord Grim grabbed the NPC, he immediately attracted the attention of all the NPCs, and a few long-range attacks were already beginning to point toward him.

Boom!!

A round of cannonfire came toward him first, but Ye Xiu, who’d predicted this, was already controlling Lord Grim to dodge. When the NPC that One Autumn Leaf had thrown came toward him, Lord Grim dodged again.

Sun Xiang was already beginning to attack Ye Xiu, but he wasn’t in a hurry to rush up to him. He was continuing to spend a lot of effort dealing with the NPCs that came at him, and whenever he had the chance, he would keep throwing these NPCs at Lord Grim.

No matter how good Ye Xiu’s technique was, this kind of struggle on the side of a mountain wall was still more difficult that the freedom of movement that being on the ground offered. Facing the combination of attacks thrown at him by Sun Xiang and the NPCs, he soon found himself too busy to deal with them all.

“Why bother?” The pro players once again expressed their confusion.

If he was still going to dodge the attacks, then why do that grab and Fling earlier, inviting so many attacks upon himself? It wasn’t like he couldn’t have dodged that, and if he’d dodged, then he’d only have to deal with Sun Xiang right now. If he only had to deal with the human cannonballs that One Autumn Leaf was tossing at him, Ye Xiu could easily keep controlling Lord Grim to dodge, all the way until the end.

“I don’t understand!” Practically everyone was shaking their heads. They couldn’t figure out what Ye Xiu was planning. As for the televised broadcast, the commentators were even quieter. If even the pro players couldn’t see the intention, how could Pan Lin and Li Yibo dare discuss it? They might as well pretend that this question didn’t exist.

Only Zhang Xinjie, Team Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie, the Zhang Xinjie who never overlooked any detail, appeared to have a thought.

“What is it?” Han Wenqing asked. He understood his teammates, and seeing him like this, he knew that Zhang Xinjie had thought of something. When he asked this, the surrounding players who had heard all looked over. Everyone wanted an answer to this question.

“The ambushing troops atop the cliffs will likely act soon,” Zhang Xinjie.

“Oh?”

Everyone looked at the screen. From the aerial viewpoint, they could see the NPCs atop the cliffs. After the two armies of NPCs had appeared, they had also started moving, but it looked like nothing but preparation. Even now, there was no sign that these NPCs were about to attack. How could Zhang Xinjie tell?

“It’s not clear what the condition is for activating their ambush, but I imagine that it is one of two options. One, that it’s time-based, and once a certain time is reached, they activate. Two, that it depends on the damage taken by the NPCs, and once they suffer enough damage, they come and sweep the field for good,” Zhang Xinjie analyzed. Everyone had seen the map introduction earlier. The hidden troops weren’t on equal footing as the two groups of NPCs down below. They could be considered the final victors of this battle. They were waiting for the two armies to wear each other down, and then without any risk to themselves, they could descend and wipe out both sides.

“Ye Xiu is waiting for this?” someone asked.

“It seems so. During the intro video, I took note of the time the ambush began and the number of NPCs left on both sides. Both conditions will be fulfilled soon,” said Zhang Xinjie.

“But so what if he waits until these ambushing troops activate? How will that change the situation?” someone wondered.

Zhang Xinjie didn’t answer. He simply continued to think deeply. Clearly, this was a question that he hadn’t found the answer to yet, either. Judging from the time that Ye Xiu began to attack the NPCs, it should have something to do with the hidden troops, but Zhang Xinjie also couldn’t determine how they could be useful to Ye Xiu. They were only ambushing troops, they weren’t his reinforcements. They would attack all of their enemies, and they wouldn’t go out of their way to avoid attacking Lord Grim or One Autumn Leaf. It was more likely that the ambushing troops would also treat them as targets to be destroyed. What was Ye Xiu thinking?

At this moment, atop the canyon, a small rock was suddenly carelessly pushed by an NPC. The rock tumbled down without anyone noticing, and even when it reached the ground, it didn’t attract any attention. However, it seemed as though this were a signal, for the NPCs hidden on both sides of the canyon suddenly began to move. They didn’t make any greeting. As soon as they appeared, a wave of boulders was pushed down.

Boom boom boom boom!!

The sound of tumbling boulders echoed through the canyon, and a number of NPCs were hit and directly smashed into pulp. The NPCs also began to use all sorts of long-range Glory skills to attack. With this ambush, the canyon instantly fell into complete and utter chaos. But the two ground armies didn’t seem to be in too much of a panic. Those who could were immediately counterattacking the NPCs above, the close-range NPCs were still fighting amongst each other below, and they didn’t forget about Lord Grim and One Autumn Leaf, either.

There were still NPCs tangled around One Autumn Leaf, but most of Sun Xiang’s attention was on Lord Grim. The activation of the ambushing troops, he’d seen this scene as well. The NPCs on the ground wouldn’t be able to last too long, and after that, it was unclear whether or not the ambushing troops would continue to attack them. For now, it seemed like their attacks were aimed at the two players’ characters as well as the other NPCs.

Sun Xiang didn’t care about any of this, nor did he think about how he could use this situation to his advantage. He was focused entirely on Lord Grim. When this ambush rained down, Ye Xiu had no way of keeping Lord Grim perched on the cliffside, and Lord Grim finally landed on the ground.

Charge!

One Autumn Leaf charged!

Lord Grim charged!

Amidst the chaos, as attacks rained down upon them from all sides, the two of them were still focused on their true opponent. Swift and fierce, they rushed toward each other.

Tyrant’s Destruction!

Sun Xiang had One Autumn Leaf to unleash a Tyrant’s Destruction. A 180-degree sweep, pushing away three NPCs at once.

But Ye Xiu wasn’t that easy to deal with. Lord Grim unsheathed his sword, Collapsing Mountain! He actually used this skill to jump right over the Tyrant’s Destruction, and came crashing down toward One Autumn Leaf.

Retreat!

One Autumn Leaf retracted the skill and backed away. Five types of Chasers, stage eight Battle Spirit. One Autumn Leaf’s power and speed were both at the peak, and his movements were nimble like never before.

Facing this kind of One Autumn Leaf, surrounded by hostile NPCs. Under these conditions, Ye Xiu actually still wanted to fight him directly?

What was he thinking!!

The pro players were all incredibly anxious. They believed that Ye Xiu had calculations, they believed that he wouldn’t just fight an unprepared battle like this. There must be something here that they had all overlooked.

Upwards Slash!

The Collapsing Mountain missed, so Lord Grim swiftly swung his sword into an Upwards Slash.

But, Draconic Crusher!

Evil Annihilation swung down with all the power of Mount Tai. The accumulation of so many buffs gave him incomparable speed. Under normal conditions, a Battle Mage would have no way of displaying a Draconic Crusher that was even faster than an Upwards Slash.

Draconic Crusher had very high priority. Never mind one Upwards Slash, even if there had been five Blade Masters doing Upwards Slash together, they would still be slammed down by this Draconic Crusher.

Boom!

Evil Annihilation struck the ground. This attack had cleaved Lord Grim from head to toe. But Lord Grim hadn’t fallen – Evil Annihilation had simply passed right through his body!

Shadow Steps!

At last, the first skill that Ye Xiu had chosen to add to his weapon for the final match was revealed. The Blade Master skill Shadow Steps.

But One Autumn Leaf’s Draconic Crusher had come so quickly that there was no way Ye Xiu had activated that skill then. Shadow Steps had perhaps been used even before the Collapsing Mountain. Ye Xiu had simply used the skill so quickly that when the skill was used, the shadows hadn’t even had the chance to fan out before he’d already completed the controls for Collapsing Mountain. With this Collapsing Mountain, the one who’d leapt forward was still one person, but by the time he came down, the Shadow Steps had fully taken effect, and the one Lord Grim who finished the Collapsing Mountain was a shadow, one of four Lord Grims.

By the time Evil Annihilation had pierced Lord Grim’s head, Sun Xiang already realized that something was wrong. He immediately wanted to cancel this skill and adjust, but by the time he did the controls to cancel the skill, the Draconic Crusher had already struck the ground.

Moonlight Slash, Full Moonlight Slash!

Two streaks of bladelight flashed, leaving two streaks of blood on One Autumn Leaf’s body, lifting him up into the air.

“Do you have enough experience to control a One Autumn Leaf in this state?” Ye Xiu asked in the chat.

Chapter 1647 - A High-End That Can’t Be Appreciated

The message hung in the chat, just like that.

If this were the key to victory, then this kind of statement should have been said only after victory was certain. Revealing this to the opponent halfway through was a bit amateur.

But Ye Xiu said it in the chat, and everyone had seen it, of course including his opponent Sun Xiang.

Because there was a keyword in this sentence: experience!

A word that would frequently be mentioned when analyzing a player’s strength, a term that had no feeling of newness.

A term that would be analyzed again and again, that always had a crucial impact on victory.

Once again, in this peak, championship-deciding match, it came up.

Experience experience experience…

Young people probably didn’t like this term, because they were always criticized for their shortcoming in this area, and this thing was so difficult to obtain. It wasn’t like talent or natural gifts, which one could be born with.

Accumulate. Aside from accumulating, there was no other way.

Sun Xiang had debuted in Season 7, and after today he would have completed four full seasons. And starting from Season 7, he had always been the core of his team. True, he had spent Season 9 in the Challenger League. But after these four years, although Sun Xiang was still young, he was far from being a rookie. Not enough experience? By now, this was something of the past. The Sun Xiang of today could no longer be said to lack experience.

He didn’t lack it, but if comparing the total amount of experience, Sun Xiang was still far inferior to Ye Xiu, who had debuted a full ten years ago.

Although experience was important, and would sometimes become the key point in determining victory, it was not the only factor. Sun Xiang’s experience couldn’t compare to that of Ye Xiu or the other older players, but his experience was still enough to deal with professional matches. He would not make mistakes from his inexperience.

Yet now, what Ye Xiu pointed out about him was “experience,” and it was a very particular type of “experience.”

Do you have enough experience to control a One Autumn Leaf in this state?

The message simply hung there, as Sun Xiang had no chance to reply. As soon as Ye Xiu sent that message, he immediately controlled Lord Grim to attack. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf was forced on the defensive, hurriedly backing up. The attacks from the NPCs caused him even more confusion. A number of them were actually aimed at Lord Grim, but under Ye Xiu’s purposeful direction, they also aimed toward Sun Xiang in the end.

Ye Xiu was a bit better at handling this kind of chaotic situation than Sun Xiang was, which wasn’t too surprising. From the very beginning, many pro players had believed that Happy’s best choice was to send Ye Xiu up first, exactly for this reason. They believed that Ye Xiu’s experience was the best weapon in dealing with this kind of chaos.

When they saw Sun Xiang control One Autumn Leaf reach this peak state, their opinions changed. In front of such a powerful One Autumn Leaf, the interference of the NPCs was just that weak. No one doubted that Sun Xiang had the ability to sweep all of these NPCs away like dust.

So when Ye Xiu controlled Lord Grim to attack anyway, everyone felt that it was an unwise move. Because Ye Xiu could do no more than deal with this chaos, while Sun Xiang, in their eyes, could disregard the chaos completely.

But in the end, once Ye Xiu entered the fray, this One Autumn Leaf in peak form suddenly seemed as though he couldn’t get his bearings. After that Draconic Crusher and being slashed twice by Lord Grim, Sun Xiang’s rhythm was thrown off for good.

And Ye Xiu dared to write out Sun Xiang’s problem and send it in a message, precisely because even if Sun Xiang was aware of the problem he faced, he had no way of addressing it.

Five types of Chasers, plus stage eight Battle Spirit.

Indeed, this was a peak form Battle Mage that up until now had never appeared on the professional stage. Not in the team competition, and certainly not in an individual battle.

The other teams didn’t know if Sun Xiang had ever undergone training specifically to control a Battle Mage in this state. But from typical reasoning, it was unlikely that he’d practice a lot, because it was simply too difficult to reach this state. Even if a player were purposely aiming for it, they should be aware that wanting it wasn’t enough to get it. Spending all that energy to train this very difficult-to-obtain state, this definitely was not a training plan that a pro player should follow. Nor would a team’s training allow players to waste their precious time on training in this entirely unrealistic situation.

Furthermore, even if Sun Xiang had actually trained with this state, this was still the first time he’d been able to bring it onstage.

And this time, the opponent he was facing was Ye Xiu. The Ye Xiu who had immersed himself in Battle Mage for no fewer than ten years, the Ye Xiu who had controlled One Autumn Leaf for no fewer than ten years.

Even if he didn’t use Battle Mage after that, even if he no longer controlled One Autumn Leaf, just based on these no fewer than ten years of experience, Ye Xiu would be no worse than Sun Xiang at understanding or controlling Battle Mage One Autumn Leaf in this condition. And “no worse than” logically led to “better than.”

Lunge, Knee Strike, Earthquake Sword, Falling Flower Palm!

Four consecutive skills, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella shifted between four forms, once again attacking the openings that One Autumn Leaf exposed. The last was a Battle Mage’s Falling Flower Palm, blowing One Autumn Leaf away.

“Besides, you have an injury that everyone seems to have overlooked.” Ye Xiu was still speaking in the channel.

“You’re a player who class changed to Battle Mage. Many people have probably forgotten this by now, no?” Ye Xiu said.

Class change!

Correct, Sun Xiang had actually changed classes before. In the early days, the Sun Xiang who had debuted with Conquering Clouds to win Best Rookie didn’t play a Battle Mage.

Berserker!

That was the class that Sun Xiang had used when he debuted, the class that helped him to break past the rookie wall and win Best Rookie. But in the end, in order to chase after the pinnacle God-level character, Sun Xiang resolutely gave up his original class and trained his Battle Mage. Even though he’d immediately demonstrated an outstanding foundation, so much so that people hardly thought at all about the problem of his class change, now, after two and a half years, Ye Xiu brought up this old issue, and even called it an injury.

In everyone’s eyes, Sun Xiang’s class change had been a success. Everyone had practically forgotten that he had class change experience, forgotten that he’d debuted as a Berserker. This could be said to be the greatest proof of a successful class change.

But now, in Ye Xiu’s eyes, this was an injury?

Everyone stared with eyes wide, including the most most most God-level players of the Alliance.

If Ye Xiu’s words weren’t meant to be deliberately mystifying, then all they could say was that Ye Xiu was simply too far above them in terms of Battle Mage expertise, far above what they could even perceive.

The peak form One Autumn Leaf, in Ye Xiu’s eyes, was simply a One Autumn Leaf that Sun Xiang couldn’t control, a One Autumn Leaf with deep injury? This was a high-end that they couldn’t appreciate at all.

“This blow is too much…” the pro players discussed.

Ye Xiu really didn’t need to say these kind of words, but to put them in the chat now, it was simply a psychological attack!

Chapter 1648 - Insurmountable Difference

A peak form reached, in a chance of a lifetime, only for it to be viewed as an injury, something that Sun Xiang couldn't handle. Anyone would feel extremely embarrassed, never mind someone as prideful as Sun Xiang. In the midst of countless things to worry about, Ye Xiu still took the time to send this message. It was clearly more than just pure mockery, it was an extremely deep psychological attack.

In response to these kinds of words, how would Sun Xiang react? Go crazy? Fall into depression? The pro players were throwing around guesses. They felt that no response would be surprising, that they were all reasonable. But in the end, Sun Xiang's response still managed to be outside all of their expectations.

One Autumn Leaf, Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

But he wasn't charging forward to attack, he was… running away!

That confident, prideful Sun Xiang, after bringing One Autumn Leaf to this peak state and then suffering this kind of embarrassment, didn't fall into chaos because of this, nor did he desperately try to prove himself. His ultimate choice was to control One Autumn Leaf to run away.

This final answer caught everyone off-guard.

After reaching this level, after the words had gotten to this point, that prideful, self-important Sun Xiang had actually chosen to flee?

Never mind him, any pro player in his place under those conditions would want to fight, fight to the death! Even if they'd lose in the end, they would refuse to be underestimated like this.

But Sun Xiang had chosen to flee.

This meant that he agreed with Ye Xiu's judgment, that he admitted that he couldn't control this peak form One Autumn Leaf.

He set down his pride, set down his self-respect. Everything was for the sake of victory!

Because, right now, running away was the wisest choice. He could escape the chaotic situation, wait for some of One Autumn Leaf's buffs to run out, allow One Autumn Leaf to remain in a state that Sun Xiang could comfortably control.

And then return again to fight!

Applause rose up from the pro players. The sound wasn't loud, but it had real worth.

Sun Xiang wasn't a very well-liked player, and in the circle he wasn't very popular. As a Season 7 debut, he didn't have much seniority either. He had won Best Rookie, received all sorts of praise, but this was the first time he had received such genuine, weighty respect from the pro circle.

Because he did what many people might have been unable to do.

Pride, self-respect!

Every pro player had these things, but not every player could set them down in this kind of difficult situation.

Everyone had a certain understanding of Sun Xiang, so they knew how difficult it was for this youth to do this. But as they watched, he set those things down. Whether or not it would be enough to win, the very fact that he had done this was enough for people to feel moved.

Using Dragon Breaks the Ranks in this way was even more difficult than using it to charge the enemy line.

Ye Xiu was similarly surprised.

Sun Xiang's change this season had been obvious, but even Ye Xiu hadn't thought that he would be able to throw away his pride and self-respect to this extent. Even though they were opponents, Ye Xiu couldn't help but want to applaud Sun Xiang, to raise a glass to him.

But, that was all.

When it came to victory, Ye Xiu would not back down a single step.

Shining Cut!

Lord Grim was already chasing One Autumn Leaf's silhouette. Ye Xiu had no plans to let Sun Xiang have a chance to breathe so easily.

The two characters suddenly rushed out of the chaotic fighting. The NPCs had aggroed both of them, but it wasn't single-minded focus. Their fighting amongst themselves had never stopped. Now that the two of them had escaped, they only threw a few attacks their way when it was convenient. They didn't make any overall organizational changes to attack them specifically. But the NPCs that were hidden on the cliffs to ambush them, these NPCs immediately chased after the two of them to attack. Right now, they were the ones with the upper hand in this battle.

No one had the ability to stop their attacks. Ye Xiu and Sun Xiang could only dodge the attacks that rained down upon them as they continued to control their characters.

At last, Lord Grim managed to catch up to One Autumn Leaf, but Sun Xiang had already delayed this to the greatest extent. When Lord Grim finally caught up, he didn't hastily initiate a desperate fight. The peak form One Autumn Leaf actually demonstrated a completely defensive stance.

"Too calm! Too rational!"

"It doesn't feel like Sun Xiang at all!"

"Right, if we didn't already know, I really couldn't have guessed this was Sun Xiang."

The pro players all discussed amongst themselves. Sun Xiang was the greatest talking point of this battlefield right now. His change, his attitude on the field right now, all of the players found it completely new. This season, Sun Xiang had been constantly adjusting himself, and everyone couldn't help but wonder, when they met him in the future, how should they deal with him? This kind of Sun Xiang, who could set down everything and focus only on victory, would only become harder to deal with.

"Ye Xiu is also very steady." At this time, someone else spoke.

Sun Xiang's unexpected moves made him the center of the pro players' attention, and so to some extent they'd overlooked Ye Xiu's constant focus. Sun Xiang had made changes and adjustments, but he'd only been able to pull the situation back to the original starting point. Ye Xiu hadn't suffered any turbulent waves because of this. The starting point was the starting point. Whether facing the Sun Xiang who couldn't control his peak form character, or the Sun Xiang would could set down his arrogance and give up on the peak form to return the situation to the starting point, Ye Xiu had implemented nothing but a single-minded pursuit of victory. Nothing would cause him to change on this point, to waver on this point. Even if he was moved by Sun Xiang's actions, he would now only become more determined and work even harder to win this match.

The battle continued, their health bars whittled down.

But during the time Sun Xiang had been unable to control his character properly, One Autumn Leaf had lost some health when trapped in the encirclement and suffering attacks from Ye Xiu. Right now, Sun Xiang had readjusted himself, pulling himself together to battle anew, but this little disparity still hadn't evened out, because Ye Xiu didn't give him the slightest chance to do so.

Maintaining this difference, the health of the two characters continued to fall. There weren't any big drops, they just dripped away bit by bit. It was clear how carefully and meticulously both sides were playing.

The entire audience was nervous, watching Sun Xiang. When Ye Xiu had sent his messages in the chat, they had thought that Sun Xiang would lose for sure. None of them had thought that the battle would return to this kind of situation. They might not fully understand the significance of Sun Xiang using that Dragon Breaks the Ranks to run away, but right now, they could see Sun Xiang's determination to win.

Catch up!!

Samsara's fans stared desperately at that health difference. They cheered and hollered and hoped for it to wear away.

But this difference remained stubborn and unsurmountable. The health of One Autumn Leaf and Lord Grim dropped and dropped, but when one side's health finally reached zero, the difference was still there.

In the first match of the group arena, Ye Xiu obtained victory. He finally established his legend of winning every single 1v1 in the entire season, including the playoffs.

Chapter 1649 - Killing Intent with Back to the Wall

The victor was Ye Xiu. The Samsara fans in the stadium couldn’t be too happy about this no matter what. But they couldn’t blame Sun Xiang.

Ordinary viewers truly had no way of detecting a lot of the subtleties of this match.

Sun Xiang couldn’t control the peak form One Autumn Leaf, Sun Xiang had the injury of his class change. These were all words that Ye Xiu had directly said in the chat, but for ordinary gamers, even searching with this guidance, they couldn’t see how Sun Xiang couldn’t control his character, how he had this injury.

They could only see from his dropping health how Sun Xiang had been at a disadvantage at that point in time. But soon enough, Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf had used a Dragon Breaks the Ranks to break free. When he fought against Lord Grim, he had stabilized his position.

In the subsequent battle, neither side could be said to have a great advantage, and that difference in health from before was maintained all the way until the battle ended.

13%.

This was that difference, and was the amount of health that Lord Grim had remaining. Ye Xiu had won, but Sun Xiang’s answer sheet was by no means ugly. In fact, in the eyes of the pro players, who understood things a bit better, Sun Xiang had earned a very high score.

Sun Xiang, coming off stage, earned applause.

Samsara’s fans were encouraging Sun Xiang not to be discouraged. They had no idea right now that Sun Xiang had grown beyond their imagination.

With Sun Xiang coming off stage, it was time for Samsara’s second player to step up. Because of the unique format of the third match, no one knew who would be the second player that Samsara sent up. Perhaps even Samsara themselves were waiting until Sun Xiang lost and they could see the current situation to determine who would be their second player.

At that moment, Samsara’s captain Zhou Zekai stood up to welcome the returning Sun Xiang. No one paid much attention.

Zhou Zekai greeted Sun Xiang, the two of them high-fived like in a relay, and still no one paid much attention.

And then, the two of them brushed shoulders as they passed each other; Sun Xiang returned to his team and sat down, while Zhou Zekai continued to walk forward. The entire stadium went wild.

Team Samsara, their second player was actually Zhou Zekai, their captain Zhou Zekai?

This was even more shocking than Zhou Zekai playing first in the previous group arena. In that round, Samsara had at least left Sun Xiang as their fifth player. Their first player was very strong, but they still had a reliable anchor. Even though the final outcome wasn’t what they’d hoped for, at least there was this kind of logic in their arrangement.

But this match?

Sun Xiang had already gone first, so setting Zhou Zekai as the fourth player was the most logical choice; putting him in fifth would give more stability, putting him in third would be more aggressive. But now, they put him right in second… what was this?

The order of the players was decided on the spot. If Sun Xiang’s performance as the first player had been especially strong, a 1v2 or even a 1v3, then sending up Zhou Zekai second to aim for as many points as possible was still fairly logical. But right now, first player Sun Xiang had fallen without any victories, yet Samsara didn’t save Zhou Zekai to anchor. Instead, they directly sent him up as their second player. Truly, not many people could understand this stance.

“They’re sending up Zhou Zekai second? This…” In the broadcast, commentator Pan Lin faltered in his words.

“Can’t understand it at all!” Li Yibo, who always liked to save face, no longer tried to stay vague. He directly admitted this.

What was Samsara thinking?

In the end, the ones who could understand their logic were still the other pro players. After getting over their initial shock and thinking it over, they could understand the thought behind Samsara’s arrangement.

Sun Xiang first, Zhou Zekai second.

This was a whole, these two things couldn’t be considered separately. In this group arena where the battle order could be changed on the spot, Samsara hadn’t taken full advantage of this point. From the very start, they had worked out an order, and the core of this roster was Sun Xiang first, Zhou Zekai second.

So, at the very start of the match, Sun Xiang hadn’t cared about whether Happy had reported to the judge yet, he had simply directly walked to the competitor booth.

This wasn’t because he was careless and overconfident, nor was it because Samsara was trying to play any tricks. This was the plan that Samsara had decided upon for this final match from the very beginning, a roster order that was sharp to the extreme.

Sun Xiang first, that was necessary.

Zhou Zekai second, that was also necessary.

This was a kind of “back to the wall” killing intent. Even though Samsara wasn’t facing that kind of desperate situation right now, they still brought out this kind of determination.

So, Sun Xiang didn’t care at all whether Happy had reported to the judge. No matter who their first player was, he would be fighting them.

Nor did Zhou Zekai care about whether Sun Xiang had played the opening match well. He resolutely continued as Samsara’s second player.

Fighting with their backs to the wall, that meant they could only advance, they could not retreat. Even though Sun Xiang’s loss meant that Samsara’s arrangement was facing a very big difficulty, it was exactly for this reason that Zhou Zekai couldn’t back down. If he retreated now, if they made further adjustments, maybe they could create a seemingly-more stable roster, but for Samsara, that back to the wall determination and killing intent would disappear.

Therefore, Zhou Zekai didn’t back down.

This player, who was silent to the extreme offstage, had absolute confidence and courage when it came to battle. He had the determination to carry everything on his shoulders. Because he was the true core of this team, because he was the captain of this team, he led this team forward, lifting up everyone’s morale, relying not on words, but on actions.

Applause rose up.

It was unknown how much of Zhou Zekai’s determination and conviction Samsara’s fans could sense. They only knew that when it came to their captain, they needed to support him unconditionally, no matter the time or place.

Second battle of the group arena, begin. Happy, Ye Xiu, Lord Grim; Samsara, Zhou Zekai, Cloud Piercer!

Ye Xiu could be said to be the last one in the whole stadium to know of Samsara’s arrangement. When he saw Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer appear on screen, he was very surprised as well.

But very quickly, he was like those pro players who had determined Samsara’s thought process. Ye Xiu sensed the back to the wall killing intent of the other side.

And right now, Sun Xiang had already fallen. This killing intent was almost entirely reliant upon Zhou Zekai to maintain. If he, the second player, also didn’t play as well as they hoped, then Samsara’s group arena today might be even more disastrous than last round’s. Samsara’s energy was entirely gathered upon Zhou Zekai right now.

13%.

This was the health that Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had remaining. There was no chance that he could defeat Zhou Zekai with this amount of health, but if he could cause even a bit of trouble to his opponent, then that would be a direct hit blow to Samsara.

Stay firm, quick and forceful, no pretense!

While many people were sure that Ye Xiu would have Lord Grim recover some health and then slowly wear down the opponent, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim charge forward.

Chapter 1650 - Ten Seconds to Decide Victory

Lord Grim, Cloud Piercer.

Both characters moved swiftly. No delay, no hesitation, no conversation. The two looked like they weren’t even thinking, putting all their focus into just moving their characters.

Focus. Maximum speed. The two characters appeared in each other’s sights after 16 seconds.

Boom boom boom!

Open fire!

This was the maximum range of Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in gun form. At max range, the power of ranged attacks were limited. Thus, many ranged characters would not open fire as soon as they were within their attack range.

But Ye Xiu was up against Glory’s number one long-range attacker, and still chose to use this exact method.

Everyone thought that at this long range, Zhou Zekai wouldn’t break a sweat dodging with Cloud Piercer. But at the same time, Cloud Piercer also raised his dual pistols, and flames licked both gun muzzles.

Bang bang bang bang!

Gunshots rang out like rain.

Lord Grim’s attack range was only a tiny bit longer than that of Cloud Piercer’s. After all, the Launchers’ super long attack range was from their skill “Artillery Mastery,” and Lord Grim didn’t possess this skill. The tiny range difference disappeared in the blink of an eye, and Zhou Zekai unexpectedly had Cloud Piercer to start attacking too. At that moment, he was also at his character’s maximum attack range.

The two characters started from this longest range possible and followed up by just charging forward. Lord Grim, the character who showed his true power at close range, rushed forward. Cloud Piercer, the character whose true power was displayed at a distance, also unexpectedly rushed forward. It felt like they were driving two race cars playing chicken: the rules were that whoever braked first would lose.

This match was not a battle of skill. Or awareness. Or experience.

This was a battle of fighting spirit!

To meet your enemy in a narrow alley and courageously advance without half a step backwards, that kind of fighting spirit!

Samsara needed to display this kind of spirit.

They put their best players in the group arena’s first and second spots. Sun Xiang had already lost. At this time, if Zhou Zekai had even slightly hesitated or shown weakness, it would heavily impact on Samsara’s morale and fighting spirit.

Therefore, Zhou Zekai decided to fight resolutely and decisively. He wanted the whole team to carry his fighting spirit. He wanted to take this match in one fell swoop.

What about on Happy’s side?

Many people felt that it was not necessary for Ye Xiu to do this.

Because if you sound your war-drums once, you will give your troops’ courage. If you sound your war-drums twice, you will sap your troops’ courage. If you sound your war-drums thrice, you will make your troops’ courage disappear**.

If Zhou Zekai was so intent on forcing a fight, shouldn’t you just avoid him? Slow the pace of the match and bring it to a deadlock. Completely diffuse his attacking intentions. This would sap the wind right out of their sails. Without this fighting spirit, the weakness in Samsara’s player order choice would be blasted wide open, and their group arena would fall into a deep disadvantage.

But the normally calm Ye Xiu did not choose to do this. He also seemed like he was in a hurry when he had Lord Grim charge out aggressively into the fray.

The reason was actually very simple. It was only because his opponent was Zhou Zekai!

Slow down the pace and bring it to a deadlock?

In theory that sounded easy. But Zhou Zekai was the best of the best in Glory when it came to offensive play. If he chose to come at you like this, who dared claim they could slow down or stalemate him?

Nobody dared.

Therefore, Ye Xiu simply gave off a fighting spirit that didn’t lose to Zhou Zekai’s. He carried the same attitude and charged forward aggressively.

Even though the outcome of the match was already decided, Ye Xiu could at least make sure he didn’t lose in spirit. Losing a character is fine, but he wouldn’t lose in fighting spirit. If the so called “smart” way to play were ever to be countered by Zhou Zekai, then he would lose his character and seem to have a weaker spirit, which would be worse.

Ye Xiu’s choice for a direct confrontation seemed obtuse and impulsive. But in reality, it was the most stable play available.

Bang bang bang bang…

Gunshots rang out endlessly. As Lord Grim got closer, the variety of attacks he could unleash became greater. Of all the low-level skills from the 24 classes, those that were in range were thrown out without pause.

Shuriken!

A flick of his hand and the Ninja’s flying projectile shot out.

Cloud Piercer’s feet did not pause. His body simply tilted and the Shuriken grazed by his chest. His right arm was still raised up, and his Wildfire continued to spit flames.

Bang bang.

A bullet flew by.

Lord Grim dodged to the side, avoiding the bullet and sending out a palm.

Qi Bullet!

This low level Qi Master skill was not instant, but the cast time was miniscule. Ye Xiu seized this small gap and had Lord Grim use Qi Bullet.

The concentrated qi went directly for Cloud Piercer’s face. This move was very reminiscent of Fang Rui’s dirty Qi Master playstyle; it was a trick he loved to use. Maybe it was because Fang Rui was part of Happy, but Samsara seemed to have kept special attention to small tricks like these. Zhou Zekai seemingly didn’t even acknowledge the Qi Bullet. Cloud Piercer continued sprinting forward, and the qi was flung behind his head in an instant.

Hit!

There was no doubt it was a hit.

The qi hit Cloud Piercer’s face and dispersed.

But so what?

It had zero effect on Cloud Piercer’s posture. The obstruction of Zhou Zekai’s field of view was minimized by him. During this moment of blindness, he used his memory of Lord Grim’s position and his deductive skills to predict his position and never stopped attacking. He didn’t give Ye Xiu any window of opportunity during this tiny moment.

Bang bang bang!

More bullets flew. Lord Grim looked like he was forced to dodge horizontally; his body was like a jumping salmon in mid-air, and the bullets whizzed past.

Zhou Zekai quickly readjusted. The gun muzzles realigned and quickly found the airborne Lord Grim.

Lord Grim went poof. A Shadow Clone!

Roundhouse Kick.

Cloud Piercer’s leg flew out. At the same time, his arms crossed over and his pistols continued firing wildly: Random Firing!

Bullets sprayed out frantically in every direction. Ye Xiu used Shadow Clone Technique to get closer, but was immediately sent further again by the strong gale of bullets from Random Firing; but not before he sent out a flash of sword light and left a sword wound on Cloud Piercer.

Zhou Zekai couldn’t care less. After he ascertained Lord Grim’s position, he immediately concentrated Random Firing in that direction, and the attack’s intensity immediately multiplied.

Shadow Steps!

Lord Grim had just given Cloud Piercer a cut and took advantage of this skill, and afterimages spread out. However, the Random Firing that was just concentrated spread out once again. The four Lord Grim afterimages were all hit. Zhou Zekai bluntly used this method to tell which of the four afterimages was real.

Collapsing Mountain!

It didn’t matter which one was real or fake; Lord Grim had already jumped out with another skill.

Too close!

Zhou Zekai figured out the true body quickly, but of all the attacks Lord Grim sent his way, could not dodge this one.

Knee Strike!

In the end, Cloud Piercer managed to squeeze out this low level skill to compete with Collapsing Mountain. In terms of attack priority, Knee Strike could not compete with Collapsing Mountain. He still ended up receiving a chop to his face. Such a direct hit meant that the damage dealt was far more than that of Knee Strike too.

But Knee Strike had a very important skill: the character would gain Super Armor when using it. So even though Cloud Piercer received a square hit to his face, his posture did not move. In the next moment, the muzzles of his dual pistols were practically pressed against Lord Grim’s head.

Bang bang bang bang…

Flames spurt out from the gun muzzles, and Lord Grim’s head exploded in blood. But at the same time, sword light in the shape of a cross lit up Cloud Piercer’s chest, and blood in the shape of a cross burst out.

The two characters moved away from each other. They had no choice: the momentum from being hit forced them back.

But the two characters were still attacking. As long as their opponent was within their attack range, they would not hesitate in the slightest.

Bullets continued to punch blood out of Lord Grim’s body, and sword light continued to carve blood out of Cloud Piercer’s body.

Besides blood there was only more blood. The blood flew out like rain…

When the rain stopped, Lord Grim fell. After all, he only started with 13% health.

Cloud Piercer remained standing, but he still had both guns trained on Lord Grim in his ending pose, as if Lord Grim would suddenly spring back up alive.

He lost 11% of his health.. He lost slightly less than Lord Grim, but this slight difference wasn’t worth arguing over. It couldn’t really prove if one of them played better.

Because it was really too short, too fast.

By 16 seconds, the characters met.

By 26 seconds, the match was over.

From the first shot that Lord Grim fired, to the moment he fell, the battle lasted no more than ten seconds.

Ten seconds to decide victory!

Chapter 1651 - Difficult Player Decisions

Ten seconds.

The real battle only lasted ten seconds. Victory was also decided in those ten seconds.

The pace was unbelievably fast. Many spectators were in the process of strapping themselves in for an epic battle when the characters first encountered each other. As it turned out, the battle was over before they even adjusted their seats.

Time to reflect?

Reflect on what?! They didn’t even see the match clearly. What could they reflect on?

Everyone sat dumbfounded. The Samsara fans even forgot to give their team victory cheers. Even the big screen in the stadium didn’t have highlights ready for a moment.

The fight was only ten seconds long, but to comb out the intense moments and intricacies would take far longer.

The live crew and the broadcast crew were all floundering. They hadn’t even settled into their regular working mentality, yet the match had already finished. Even though Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had little health, that 13% was able to bring about some enjoyable content. The two players were able to control their characters to have a fierce duel in these ten seconds.

Ye Xiu walked out of the competitor booth.

Finally, the spectators seemed to come to their senses slightly. The Samsara fans began to applaud; after all, this was their team’s victory.

But just as Ye Xiu predicted, by fighting Zhou Zekai head on, he lost the battle but did not lose in spirit. Samsara were being applauded for their victory right now, but Happy’s players and fans did not feel any loss of morale.

The highlight reel was finally ready.

In the end, it was only ten seconds’ worth of action. Compilations couldn’t stretch time out. The numerous screens in the stadium just replayed the ten second battle from different angles. This highlight reel did not use any slow motion, and played at normal speed. Ten seconds, and another ten seconds, and yet another ten seconds. The audience seemed to not mind these ten seconds being repeated. Everyone tilted and turned their heads with interest, and watched repeats of these ten seconds from every angle.

By then, Ye Xiu had returned to Happy’s area. He also had to decide on the next person Happy was to send up.

But this was not an easy decision.

Even though Ye Xiu did not lose in spirit to Zhou Zekai, not even he could suppress the opponent’s confidence. Zhou Zekai would continue his fight-to-the-death attitude and launch an aggressive offensive. Happy needed to send up someone with lots of experience and ability to quickly adapt to changes to tango with Zhou Zekai.

Fang Rui!

He was the most suitable choice. When Ye Xiu thought this, his gaze wandered in Fang Rui’s direction. But just as he did so, his heart sank a little.

Fang Rui was also looking back at him, but his gaze gave off an abnormal sense of calm.

Ye Xiu understood Fang Rui. Even though he was the epitome of playing dirty, he was definitely not the kind to bully the weak and avoid the strong. Fang Rui must also understand how crucial this coming match was. In these moments, judging by Fang Rui’s usual personality, he probably would have already volunteered to play next without being asked.

But now, not only Fang Rui did not speak up, but he still stayed silent when he caught Ye Xiu’s eyes.

Ye Xiu immediately knew that Fang Rui wasn’t at his best. The burden from last match probably hadn’t been completely erased by the two days’ worth of rest. Fang Rui staying silent was his way of not hurting Happy’s morale. But at this moment, he decided to stay silent after he exchanged looks with Ye Xiu. This was because he knew Ye Xiu would understand him right away.

If Fang Rui couldn’t go next, then who could?

While Ye Xiu was still hesitating, Su Mucheng had stood up voluntarily.

“Let me go,” Su Mucheng solved the conundrum almost nonchalantly. After she smiled faintly at Ye Xiu, she headed towards the stage without waiting for his confirmation.

“Be careful.” Ye Xiu didn’t end up saying much either, because he knew that Su Mucheng was fully aware of the current situation, and also that this was why she was able to so casually answer the conundrum. He didn’t need to give any extra instruction, because she knew clearly what she needed to do in the situation she was about to face. A “be careful” was already not necessary for the match, but was more of a personal remark instead.

“I will.” Su Mucheng smiled again and went on stage.

Ye Xiu turned back around and stole another look at Fang Rui. Knowing that Fang Rui was painstakingly trying to hide his current condition, Ye Xiu certainly wouldn’t press to interrogate him on the spot.

The third match of the group arena quickly began: Happy’s Su Mucheng versus Samsara’s Zhou Zekai. After the map loaded and the characters spawned, Zhou Zekai did not let anyone’s expectations down, especially his Samsara teammates. Cloud Piercer resolutely charged forward, without pause or hesitation.

What about on Happy’s side?

Su Mucheng did not lose in intensity. Dancing Rain also charged out. It could be seen that she had no intention whatsoever of slowing the tempo of this match.

Surely they wouldn’t have another rapid battle with a quick conclusion again?

Everyone, including the audience, stadium workers, broadcast crew and such, were caught unprepared by the last ten-second match. Now, they quickly gathered up twelve minutes’ worth of attention in a second.

“Alright!” Pan Lin’s spirits were also roused. “We can see that Zhou Zekai is charging out with Cloud Piercer just like last game. But on the other side, Su Mucheng also isn’t hesitating and is also directly charging out. This is probably going to turn out to be another exciting duel! What a rare sight on the grand final stage!”

“Too true! Usually in this kind of match, both sides would err on the side of caution, and fight for an advantageous position while minimizing mistakes. But today, this is not true just looking at Samsara’s player arrangement. To start with Sun Xiang and to have Zhou Zekai follow… many people would already consider this a mistake. However, Samsara took this “mistake” of an arrangement to give themselves fighting spirit. On the competition stage, there is no absolute right or wrong. If Samsara lost, then it would be a problem; but what if Samsara won? The momentum would have a decisive influence. Samsara focused on this, because they came to win! They would not think about what would happen after they lose!” Li Yibo continued on from Pan Lin.

“I know what you mean. Samsara’s player arrangement displays a type of determination. They only have victory in their eyes. A determination that they will definitely win!” Pan Lin said.

“Correct, ” Li Yibo said. “After Sun Xiang lost to Ye Xiu, Samsara’s player arrangements became much riskier. Even so, Zhou Zekai still went up because Samsara was determined and tenacious. They wouldn’t think about the consequences of losing.”

“You’re too right. I think you have a lot of thoughts on this matter! You must have had the same feeling back when you won the championship with Tyranny, right Coach Li?” Pan Lin took the chance to butter Li Yibo up again.

“Haha,” Li Yibo laughed. Of course he remembered the victory clearly. However, if it wasn’t for Cold Seasons’ miraculous Life-Risking Strike one-shotting Ye Xiu, who knew what would have happened.

Chapter 1652 - No Retreat

As Pan Lin and Li Yibo discussed the match, Su Mucheng and Zhou Zekai were finally about to come across each other. Zhou Zekai didn’t slow down, but Su Mucheng didn’t either. Dancing Rain was a long-ranged Launcher, yet it looked like she was charging in like a close-ranged character.

Just before the two characters were about to meet, Dancing Rain suddenly stopped.

This is?

The audience was puzzled, but the pro players reacted much faster! With the help from their spectator view, they immediately deduced Su Mucheng’s goals.

The canyon wasn’t a perfectly straight line. There were twists and turns. If Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain continued to charge ahead like in the previous round, the outcome would be the same as before. The two opposing sides would see each other outside of their attack range. Even if Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain had a longer range than Lord Grim and Cloud Piercer, the outcome would not change.

This time, Su Mucheng had Dancing Rain stop ahead of time. She was going to guard a tree stump, waiting for a rabbit. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer would need to pass through a turn. By the time he came into Dancing Rain’s sights, the two sides would be at a much closer distance.

The pro players quickly saw what this distance would be. It was a distance that would allow long-ranged attackers to better display their capabilities. Su Mucheng had given up on steady, drawn-out fight. When she and Zhou Zekai fought, it would be an explosive battle.

No!

It wasn’t just that!

Having seen Su Mucheng’s impressive “Firing Line” multiple times recently, the pro players had started looking into it more carefully. At this moment, seeing this distance, they quickly realized that it wasn’t just a distance that would allow the two long-ranged attackers to fully utilize their firepower. This distance was a firing line distance that Su Mucheng had complete control over. In other words, this distance wouldn’t just let her fully utilize her range, it would also elevate her firepower to its peak!

Mounted Gun!

Su Mucheng calculated how much time Cloud Piercer would need to reach here, and had Dancing Rain set up her Mounted Gun. In the very next second, Cloud Piercer arrived.

Boom boom boom boom!!

Dancing Rain’s artillery fire instantly unfolded. It was almost impossible to tell what her sequence of skills were. The moment Cloud Piercer appeared, the battlefield erupted in explosions and smoke. The explosiveness was even more intense than what everyone had expected. Dancing Rain’s DPS instantly reached a peak.

Cloud Piercer’s situation obviously wasn’t great. No one would have an easy time facing Su Mucheng’s firing line.

However, if he really wanted to get away from Dancing Rain’s firing line, it was truthfully very simple. All he needed to do was back away a bit.

Cloud Piercer had been in the midst of making a turn in the canyon, when he appeared in Dancing Rain’s sights and was bombarded with artillery shells. All he needed to do was retreat a bit, and he would disappear from Dancing Rain’s sights. No matter how strong her firing line may be, if she didn’t have a target she could hit, then it was useless.

But all of the pro players knew that while backing away was easy and effective, Zhou Zekai wouldn’t choose to do it.

Because what he pursued wasn’t the outcome, but the circumstances. If he backed away, avoiding Su Mucheng’s momentum, his own momentum would decrease, and Samsara’s momentum would decrease even further.

It was like a high-speed race in auto racing. Even if they saw an obstacle up ahead, instead of slowing down and going around it, it would be more satisfying crashing through it. Braking and slowing down would kill the excitement. Cloud Piercer taking a step back was equivalent to completely stopping the racecar, going in reverse, and then going back forward. It would be extremely disappointing!

Zhou Zekai wouldn’t retreat, even if it was the safer choice. What he pursued, what Samsara pursued was to push forward, sweeping away everything in their path. Zhou Zekai was the team’s captain, the core of the team. He needed to be strong. He needed to carry out their goals. At this crucial moment, he would never drop the ball because he was someone who used actions, not words. He used his actions to give voice to himself and his teammates.

Charge!

Cloud Piercer charged forward. Facing the explosive Launcher firing line, he fired back. This choice wasn’t wise. If this were the game, anyone who made this sort of bad decision would be seen as a noob, who would be looked down upon disdainfully and then lectured by the veterans.

But now, Glory’s number one had made this choice in the deciding match of the finals. On the stage, there was no such thing as absolutely right or wrong.

An act so noobish that anyone would laugh at the person doing it, but what if the person who did it was Zhou Zekai? Who dared to laugh at him? Seeing Zhou Zekai’s decision, the normal players let out an expression of fear. In their eyes, this was what it meant to make the impossible possible. No wonder he was Glory’s number one! No wonder he was a top player!

The crowd went wild.

Just like the pro players predicted, although this decision was unwise, it was absolutely breathtaking. Everyone loved to see the impossible become possible!

Boom boom boom boom!

Bang bang…

With the buffs from Mounted Gun, Dancing Rain’s artillery fire was extraordinary. Cloud Piercer was firing back, but his gunshots seemed so weak and frail.

But Zhou Zekai didn’t cower.

As soon as the match started, the word “retreat” wasn’t in his dictionary. No matter the circumstances, no matter how unwise it might be, even ten million foes would not bend his will. That was the sort of mentality he came into the match with.

He was clearly a Sharpshooter, a class that didn’t have the ability to charge straight into a trap, but he went for it nevertheless. The people watching couldn’t help but recall that before Sun Xiang’s addition to the team, Samsara had lacked a direct attacker.

Yet even without one, Samsara had still been able to win two championships in a row.

In the finals two years ago, Samsara had eliminated Blue Rain, the team filled with unique yet synergistic players. In the previous finals, they had eliminated Tyranny, the experienced veterans who had put in their all to win.

At that time, who had been their team’s attacker?

Zhou Zekai!

Besides healing, there was nothing he couldn’t do.

These words weren’t just empty words or an exaggerated description. Zhou Zekai had the ability to do what was impossible.

Advance!

The current him was like a brave warrior facing an archer. He had no choice but to press forward.

Cloud Piercer charged ahead.

One step, two steps, three steps. Burns could be seen all over him from the countless explosions. No one could break through a Launcher’s firing line unscathed. A close-ranged class would do everything they could to break past a Launcher’s wall. Most of the time, they would choose to circle around and do something unexpected to get closer to the Launcher. But in this map, it wasn’t possible to circle around. The only path was forward. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer did what even close-ranged characters would try to avoid, getting closer and closer to Dancing Rain.

He was approaching and attacking.

This was the difference between himself and an actual close-ranged class. He didn’t need to fully close in to attack. As he gradually escaped from the firing line, Cloud Piercer’s attacks became more and more dense, more and more threatening.

But Su Mucheng didn’t cower either. Every time Cloud Piercer took a step forward, Dancing Rain’s firing line would move back as well. She had the ability to create a perfect firing line for quite a range.

But this sort of explosiveness couldn’t last forever. Even a normal player understood this logic.

Because this peak explosiveness required chaining together as many skills as possible in the shortest amount of time. To achieve this firepower, she couldn’t think about cycling her skills or about the aftermath.

Su Mucheng’s explosiveness had been at its peak ever since the first shot. But even this sort of burst wasn’t able to completely suppress Zhou Zekai, how could she hold back?

Su Mucheng didn’t think too much.

She had predicted that Zhou Zekai would push forward in today’s match. That was why she chose this strategy despite it having such an obvious flaw. It was to make things difficult for Zhou Zekai.

Even so, she still wasn’t able to shut down Zhou Zekai. Victory wasn’t so easy to obtain. And although Zhou Zekai had chosen to push forward, he wasn’t charging at her blindly, tanking everything. He was also taking a look at the situation, observing Dancing Rain’s firing line. He knew that this sort of explosiveness couldn’t last forever. Su Mucheng would have to slow down at some point, unless she was confident that she could kill him during this time.

But seeing the situation, it looked to be impossible. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer was holding on under the barrage of artillery shells. His health was dropping chunk by chunk, but he wouldn’t fall so easily. And because Dancing Rain was using Mounted Gun, when he counterattacked, he didn’t need to worry about her dodging his attacks. Even though the damage he dealt couldn’t compare to Su Mucheng’ firing line, he knew that the turning point was about to come.

Boom boom boom boom.

The explosions continued, but even the normal players could see that Dancing Rain’s firing line was going downhill. The broadcast and the stadium screens displayed Dancing Rain’s skill tree to let everyone see all the skills that were on cooldown.

The crowd erupted into cheers. Samsara’s fans knew that their opportunity had arrived.

“What a pity…” The pro players lamented.

Knowing what her opponent would do, Su Mucheng had created an enormous obstacle for him, an obstacle that couldn’t be avoided. Was there a better set-up? No. Everyone racked their brains, trying to think of a better method. Her strategy fully utilized the strengths of her own class and her opponent’s situation.

If it had to be said that she did something wrong, then it would perhaps be that she had pushed her limits too far. Failure meant death.

She hadn’t left herself any path for retreat either.

Chapter 1653 - Terrifying Victory

The Firing Line was broken through!

Some of the normal players might still have hope. After all, they had seen Su Mucheng’s incredible control over her Firing Line. They had seen how she was able to produce an explosiveness at the level of a Firing Line at a seemingly impossible distance.

However, the pro players understood that it wasn’t a question of distance right now, but rather that Dancing Rain had used up too many skills. It wasn’t possible for her to continue any further. It wasn’t something that could be resolved no matter how skilled you were.

This battle could be described by the phrase “the river flows twenty years to the east, twenty years to the west.” Right now, Su Mucheng’s twenty years to the east was over. Next was Zhou Zekai’s twenty years to the west.

Could she make a comeback?

The people supporting Happy prayed for the possibility of a comeback, but to the pro players, very few of them looked at Su Mucheng’s situation optimistically.

“She used up too many skills,” The pro players shook their heads and sighed.

“But I feel like she shouldn’t have needed to use so many!” A voice called out. Everyone looked to see who it was: Team Miracle’s Guo Shao.

Team Miracle had joined the Alliance this year along with Team Happy and ended the season at 13th. For a new team, it was a very good achievement. After all, most new teams seemed to just be taking a tour of the season. They came in haste and left in haste.

Unfortunately for Miracle, a devil called Happy came with them. They had come as a new team and made it all the way to the finals, taking the defending champions, Samsara, to their third game. Under Happy’s glory, Miracle’s originally impressive achievement was overlooked.

However, Miracle’s rookie, Guo Shao, had received quite a bit of attention. He had been one of the contenders for Best Rookie. There were rumors that many top teams had taken an interest in him.

His sudden outburst confused the former Excellent Era seniors beside him. There were countless experts and Gods present. Who needed a rookie like you to say your opinion?

But Guo Shao’s words had piqued the curiosity of quite a few Gods. They looked at Guo Shao and soon had the same doubts.

The Gods sitting closer to each other quickly started discussing the issue. The other players saw the Gods and looked again at the screen, watching the replay carefully.

“Zhou Zekai…” Someone suddenly pointed to a player.

“Under the suppression of the Firing Line, he intentionally slowed down the pace,” someone added.

What?

Everyone’s heart jumped. They looked towards Tiny Herb’s God, Wang Jiexi, who had spoken. Then, they watched the replay and noticed the numerous clues.

He’s right!

Everyone agreed with Wang Jiexi’s viewpoint. This was the main reason why Guo Shao brought up the point that Su Mucheng shouldn’t have needed to expend so much. At the time, he hadn’t been able to find the reason, but he felt like something was off. He had quite the keen intuition.

Right now, no one was paying attention to Guo Shao’s keen senses. After confirming the reason, they felt their scalps go numb. A chill went down their spine.

How terrifying!

Under the barrage from Su Mucheng’s Firing Line, instead of getting out of it as fast as he could, he intentionally slowed down the tempo, prolonging Su Mucheng’s offense and forcing her to send out more attacks.

This was the final deciding match! Everyone knew very well what burden Zhou Zekai carried. Yet despite these circumstances, he still dared to take the risk. Before, he had displayed an unrelenting determination and momentum, and during this process, he had quietly laid down the winning hand.

Everyone was silent, just like how Zhou Zekai usually was.

Everyone knew he was someone who spoke with his actions, but he had been almost too thorough, a thoroughness that exceeded their imagination.

Even though they hadn’t looked at Su Mucheng optimistically, they at least had a thread of hope for her. However, once they noticed his winning hand, this last thread of hope disappeared.

Zhou Zekai won!

The rest of the fight went as expected. After Cloud Piercer broke through the Firing Line, he began his counterattack. Against his three to five step fluctuating Gun Fu, even if Dancing Rain had all of her skills available, at this distance, it was hard to contend against a Sharpshooter, let alone a Sharpshooter like Zhou Zekai who was playing like a close-ranged class.

Thunderous applause!

His fight with Ye Xiu had been too even, and wasn’t able to boost the fans’ morale. On the other hand, this fight had an extraordinary effect.

In the first half, Cloud Piercer had been shut down by Dancing Rain’s artillery fire, Zhou Zekai had displayed a fierce tenacity during this stage. Then, once he broke through the Firing Line, he directly went for the win. The entire process had been too satsifying to watch.

Oh oh oh!

Samsara’s fans cheered and screamed. When Su Mucheng walked out from the player booth, she was welcomed with a storm of noise.

Had she played poorly?

No one thought so. No one thought they could have done a better job than her. But in the end, she had lost. The brilliance that she left on stage would naturally be much duller. To many people, it felt like Su Mucheng had been killed in one combo.

The fight had been a short one, taking 1 minute and 7 seconds. There had been numerous back and forths, but from an overall perspective, it felt like each player had made just one move.

One move to win, and the one to win was Zhou Zekai.

Su Mucheng returned to her seat. She didn’t seem to be dispirited by the loss. Not waiting for anyone to console her, she let a smile, telling everyone that she was fine.

Samsara had made a comeback, taking the lead against Happy. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer still had 45% health left.

It was a significant lead, but what was more terrifying was Samsara’s morale. The Samsara fans were nearly out of control from excitement. The players on Team Samsara had expressions of joy, including Sun Xiang, who had lost in the first match.

Happy needed to kill Samsara’s momentum. Then, the players on Happy saw Mo Fan stand up.

He didn’t say anything. His intentions were clear. Everyone then looked at Ye Xiu. In the end, who went next was Ye Xiu’s call.

Ye Xiu was quite straightforward. He nodded his head. Mo Fan didn’t say a word and walked towards the stage.

Ye Xiu hadn’t said anything when Su Mucheng went on stage because he knew that Su Mucheng knew. But Ye Xiu didn’t say anything for Mo Fan either.

Ye Xiu wasn’t actually sure if Mo Fan knew the urgency of their situation, but if he was willing to volunteer to go, then he must think he could win. Ye Xiu didn’t want to disturb Mo Fan’s mentality. He could only hope that all of Mo Fan’s focus would be on the match, on his opponent, on the win.

Mo Fan’s playstyle was quite suitable for putting Samsara’s momentum to stop. Even if hadn’t volunteered, Ye Xiu had considered sending him up.

Two players who didn’t like to talk were now facing each other. These two players preferred to use their actions to speak for themselves.

The match soon began.

This was a crucial match, and Happy had sent up a rookie. Any other team would have certainly been put under much scrutiny. It made more sense for Happy though. In this new team, apart from Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Fang Rui, the rest were rookies. Although Wei Chen was an old general, no one really considered him as a major fighting force.

But Happy had Fang Rui, who had yet to go. Given their situation, it didn’t feel like it was the time to hold back.

“Wouldn’t it be better for Happy to put in Fang Rui?” Pan Lin believed.

“Usually, that would be the case. It isn’t the time to put in a rookie. However, Happy’s only remaining experienced player is Fang Rui. Putting in Fang Rui right now isn’t ideal. There would be no chance for a large comeback. Putting Mo Fan might actually be better. He can act as a buffer, making it much easier for Fang Rui next,” Li Yibo analyzed.

“That makes sense. Then, let’s all watch the match!” Pan Lin said.

The battle began. The map hadn’t changed. The area at the center of the map still had traces left over from Ye Xiu’s fight against Sun Xiang. Most of these traces were left by NPCs.

Next were the two fights won by Zhou Zekai. Both battles had been fast paced. The plot of the map hadn’t been touched, when the battles ended.

What about this round?

Zhou Zekai had charged forward fiercely the previous two rounds, what about this time? Would he slow down for a steadier pace?

No!

As soon as the match started, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer rushed out decisively just like in the last two rounds. He was going with the same pace and the same energy to beat his opponent.

No one felt tired by the same strategy. In fact, they felt even more excited. The crowd started chanting Zhou Zekai’s name, chanting for a 1v3.

Yes! If Zhou Zekai won, it would be a 1v3. Even if his first opponent, Ye Xiu, had been nearly dead when they played, the data would show that Zhou Zekai would beat three players. Cloud Piercer would have killed three.

A 1v3 was shocking enough. Of course, three full-health enemies would have been the cherry on top, but even so, there was no need to bicker about it not being the case.

1v3!

1v3!

1v3!

The Samsara fans hollered. They weren’t satisfied with just winning. They were looking for more. On this final stage, a 1v3 couldn’t be more perfect!

Chapter 1654 - Even Luck Isn’t Here

“Zhou Zekai is really driven today!” Like many others, Pan Lin could feel the unwavering determination and energy from Zhou Zekai.

“But I have to commend Mo Fan. It really isn’t easy for a rookie,” Li Yibo said.

It was a very important round, yet Happy had sent Mo Fan against Zhou Zekai. The pressure he was under wasn’t light. After the round began, although Deception’s movements weren’t fast or hurried, he wasn’t slow either. He was moving forward at a very ordinary pace.

His steady pace let everyone know that Mo Fan was calm right now. He wasn’t impatient, and he wasn’t afraid. As a rookie, on this grand stage, in this crucial match, it truly wasn’t easy. That was why Li Yibo commended him.

As the two characters gradually approached, Mo Fan’s Deception finally stopped. He moved closer to the canyon wall, and then used his ninjato to begin scaling the canyon. Soon, he found himself a foothold. Deception landed on it, and then curled up into a ball.

The broadcast and stadium screens quickly switched to a different camera angle, one that looked up from down below on the canyon floor.

Deception could faintly be seen from this angle. He wasn’t completely hidden. Moreover, this distance was within a Sharpshooter’s attack range. Cloud Piercer could easily reach him.

Deception looked around, checking his surroundings. Then, he suddenly stood up.

Mo Fan had been studying his position, but in the end, he wasn’t satisfied with it. After checking his left and right, Deception continued to climb.

This fight clearly wouldn’t be as direct as the previous fight. Mo Fan went with his usual strategy, searching for an ambush spot on this map. During the previous group arena rounds, he had noticed a few spots through his spectator view, but he wasn’t experienced enough to judge each spot thoroughly at just a glance. He needed to examine them further personally during the match. As it turned out, the first spot that he noticed was unsuitable.

Deception soon found a new foothold. This spot was lower than the previous one. This time, Mo Fan’s Deception didn’t even look down. He looked ahead, and then immediately left.

That spot was too low.

Next.

Deception continued to scale the walls. Even though he was moving nimbly, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer was getting closer and closer. If Cloud Piercer arrived before Deception could find a suitable hiding place, then Mo Fan’s plans would be completely wasted.

Happy’s fans were anxious, hoping that Mo Fan could hurry up and find a good spot.

Samsara’s fans were anxious too, hoping that Zhou Zekai could hurry up and get there.

Through the direction Deception was moving in, the broadcast team was able to figure out which foothold Mo Fan would look for next.

The next foothold was rather high up. Ambushing from there would actually be a bit far. However, the height and the area of the protrusion made it appear as if it would be able to completely hide a character, unless the other side also climbed up there.

It would be inconvenient to attack from there, but at the same time, Mo Fan would be out of Zhou Zekai’s sights, and he could set up an ambush.

Who was faster?

One was moving forward, while the other was moving up.

Cloud Piercer appeared, but Deception was nowhere to be seen!

He made it in time…

The camera switched to Cloud Piercer’s perspective. The moment Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer reached the area, he immediately checked the walls surrounding him. But just like before, when he looked around, he didn’t find anyone.

Samsara’s fans were worried. They hoped that Zhou Zekai would instinctively sense that something was wrong. Happy’s fans were also scared and on edge. They hoped that Cloud Piercer would continue dashing forward, leaving his back open to Deception.

Suddenly, at this moment, a chance occurred.

The hidden NPC troops cropped up from on top of the canyon. Zhou Zekai immediately noticed them. In the next second, the NPCs fired all sorts of long-ranged attacks, straight towards a certain spot on the wall.

Deception!

The NPC hidden troops had attacked where Deception had been hiding. The spells and explosions obliterated that protruding rock. Deception quickly jumped away to dodge the assault.

Zhou Zekai had been completely prepared. He immediately looked all around him, looking for incoming attacks. But to his surprise, there was nothing.

The hidden troops on the two sides of the canyon had unexpectedly only aimed for Deception. They seemed to have completely ignored Cloud Piercer down below.

The situation was clear enough. The spot that Mo Fan had chosen had triggered the NPC troops hiding on top of the canyon.

This definitely came as a surprise. After all, this was a random map. No one except the developers knew the characteristics of this map. However, it could also be said that Mo Fan hadn’t thought about his plan carefully enough. He hadn’t considered that he would trigger attacks from the hidden troops.

It was a bit of an unfair criticism though, something an armchair expert might say. After all, the NPCs up above were quite patient from what they had observed up until then. It wasn’t until the NPCs started getting entangled did they begin throwing stones at someone who fell down a well. Mo Fan’s Deception had been climbing higher and higher, but he was still quite far from them. No one knew what the logic behind the AI was, and it was impossible to reach a conclusion.

In any case, for Mo Fan, for Happy, it couldn’t get any worse than this.

In the first round of the group arena, Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf ended up being attacked by the NPCs, while Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim rested easy up on the wall. But in order to avoid aggroing the NPCs, he didn’t make any attacks. The NPCs weren’t enough to stop Sun Xiang, which was why the whole series of events afterwards happened. If Ye Xiu had instead attacked One Autumn Leaf along with the NPCs, Sun Xiang would have been in major trouble.

Mo Fan was in the same sort of crisis. His situation was different than Sun Xiang’s. The hidden troops on the two ends of the canyon were only throwing long-ranged attacks at him. They didn’t seem to have any intentions of approaching any closer. Right now, if Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer attacked, he wouldn’t need to worry about the NPCs unless his marksmanship somehow turned extremely poor.

Zhou Zekai instantly grasped the main points. For him, it was as if an opportunity had fallen right into his lap. Zhou Zekai wasn’t polite. He kindly accepted the gift. Gunshots echoed throughout the canyon, bullets shooting towards Deception.

Despite having such an enormous advantage, Zhou Zekai didn’t act carelessly. His first attacks were aimed to prevent Deception from continuing to climb up because he noticed that Mo Fan wanted to rush to the top of the canyon.

However, with Zhou Zekai’s impediment, Mo Fan didn’t succeed. Climbing the mountain wall wasn’t as easy as moving on flat ground.

Mo Fan was forced into helplessness. He could only have Deception land back onto the ground.

Did the NPCs stop attacking?

This was what Happy’s fans hoped for, but they knew that it was unlikely, very unlikely…

As expected!

The attacks didn’t stop. The hidden troops on opposite ends of the canyon continued to attack. Cloud Piercer would sometimes be implicated in the attacks, but he clearly wasn’t the main target.

Head shakes and sighs…

The more neutral pro players shook their heads and sighed. It was impossible to predict these sorts of surprises before the match, and it just had to happen in such an important match.

This one point was practically a free gift. Given these circumstances, if Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer lost even a single drop of health, it would be considered his loss.

And he didn’t!

Zhou Zekai didn’t relax at all even with this enormous advantage. In fact, he became even more vigilant. Cloud Piercer kept an appropriate distance from Deception at all times. Mo Fan tried to close in several times, but failed every time.

Zhou Zekai had been bravely charging forward the entire time. Even when he was facing Su Mucheng’s explosive firing line, his Cloud Piercer didn’t back down a single step. But now, he was no longer showing the same determination and bravery. He was playing very carefully because he knew that in this situation, in these circumstances, this sort of playstyle would better strangle Happy’s morale.

The turning point was lost just like this.

In this critical confrontation, Mo Fan was utterly defeated. He wasn’t even able to land a single blow on his opponent.

What could be more cruel, more painful than this sort of defeat?

What was even more frustrating was that everything, whether it was his strategy, his execution, his playing, had come crashing down because of one single bout of bad luck.

1v3. Zhou Zekai had done it. The third round’s victory had practically been gifted to him.

But that alone wasn’t all because this round told everyone that it wasn’t just technique, decision-making, knowledge, intuition, energy, even luck was standing by Zhou Zekai’s and Samsara’s side.

How could this sort of team be beaten? What weakness did this sort of opponent have?

When Mo Fan walked down from the stage, the away team crowd was dead silent. Samsara’s fans weren’t too enthusiastic either. They were showing how relaxed they were as if victory was already within their grasp.

Zhou Zekai, Cloud Piercer, 45% health left. Behind him were three Samsara players, while Happy only had two players left.

He was fighting like his life was on the line, relying on his own strength to take down Happy in these dire straits. This was Zhou Zekai, the Zhou Zekai who had led Team Samsara to two back-to-back championship wins.

No weakness could be found on him. Even the illusory Lady Luck was on his side.

This… was this the new King of Glory?

Samsara’s fans filled the stadium with cheers for Zhou Zekai. The moment Mo Fan returned to Happy’s seats, it was as if the match had been decided.

Tang Rou looked at Ye Xiu. Others might be thinking that Happy had already lost, but her fighting spirit hadn’t diminished at all.

Ye Xiu was just about to give her the nod, when someone suddenly stood up, cutting off their line of sight.

Pu!

Fang Rui lifted his Golden Right Hand to his mouth, spat on it, combed his hair, and said: “Looks like you guys are hopeless without me!”

Chapter 1655 - The Hindrance of Cannon Fodder

“Happy’s Fang Rui is going to play next,” Pan Lin saw the scene going on at Happy’s player area. He felt a bit regretful.

He felt like Fang Rui should have played last round, but Happy sent Mo Fan out instead. Li Yibo immediately had a discussion about the merits of it, and Mo Fan’s calm and unhurried tempo affirmed their opinion that Happy’s decision was fine.

But then, a dramatic change happened. If you looked at the outcome, then sending out Mo Fan had been a grave mistake. Not only did he lose an extremely pivotal match, he had been utterly crushed. The loss was a huge blow to Happy’s morale. As for Samsara? Their state of mind could be seen through Samsara’s fans, who were sitting there pleased, confident that victory was already in their grasp.

Group arena: 4 to 2. Ever since the new competitive format for the playoffs came into play, let alone the finals, no group arena in the playoffs had ever had such a huge disparity. What was worse was that in this 4 to 2 group arena, Zhou Zekai, who had won three rounds in a row, still had nearly half of his health left.

“1v4!!!”

The crowd was already chanting for a 1v4. Before today, no one thought it was possible for a 1v4 to happen in professional play. However, today, Zhou Zekai’s condition, as well as Cloud Piercer’s health and mana, made everyone feel like a 1v4 was a genuine possibility.

“The difference between Happy and Samsara is really being shown here…” Li Yibo suddenly said.

“Happy only has one Ye Xiu, while Samsara has a Zhou Zekai, and now a Sun Xiang,” Li Yibo said.

Sun Xiang.

He was seen as the final piece of the jigsaw puzzle for Samsara, becoming this season’s Best Partners with Zhou Zekai.

Sun Xiang had blocked off Happy’s biggest threat, Ye Xiu. Afterwards, Zhou Zekai took down what little health remained on Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. Then, he went on to beat Su Mucheng and Mo Fan. Now, Cloud Piercer was like a tiger looking for his next prey.

As for Fang Rui?

Last round, Pan Lin thought that it would be safer for Happy to send out Fang Rui. However, for this round, Pan Lin didn’t look at Fang Rui as favorably as he had last round.

This was because of Zhou Zekai’s momentum. Even an All-Star player like Fang Rui didn’t seem like he could stop Zhou Zekai’s momentum. It felt like Fang Rui was just cannon fodder.

And this was the feeling they got even not knowing Fang Rui’s actual situation.

“You gonna be okay?” Ye Xiu grinned as he asked Fang Rui.

For the other Happy players who didn’t know that Fang Rui wasn’t himself right now, it didn’t sound like anything was wrong. The team had four senior members. Apart from Su Mucheng, the other three weren’t exactly the most serious people. It was common for them to talk trash about each other.

But Fang Rui knew that these seemingly normal joking words had real meaning today.

“Even if I’m not, I’ve got to go. The team really can’t do without me,” Fang Rui said proudly.

The others on Happy didn’t find anything wrong, but Ye Xiu could hear what Fang Rui was implying: Yes, we don’t have any other choice. No matter how things are, I have to go.

Ye Xiu didn’t say anything more. He wasn’t completely clear how Fang Rui’s condition was, but he knew that Fang Rui was a responsible player. He wasn’t going to play if he didn’t think he could win. It could only mean that he could still fight. He didn’t want to go before probably because he only wanted to fight if it was necessary, and right now was the time.

“Watch me bully him!” Fang Rui clenched his Golden Right Hand and walked towards the stage. But this time, whether it was Ye Xiu or Fang Rui, their easy going attitudes weren’t able to infect the others. Everyone on Happy looked exceptionally solemn. All of them knew how grave their situation was.

Mo Fan, who hadn’t contributed anything last round, looked even more dejected when he returned. The comforting from his teammates were completely ignored.

“Don’t worry,” Ye Xiu looked towards him.

Mo Fan walked right past him. Those words were too light. How could he casually wave off such a devastating defeat?

“Your teammates are still fighting,” Ye Xiu continued.

Mo Fan turned his head. Ye Xiu was no longer looking at him. Mo Fan followed Ye Xiu’s gaze to Fang Rui, who was still holding his clenched right hand up in the air.

“So we haven’t lost,” Ye Xiu turned his head to look at him.

We haven’t lost yet, we…

Mo Fan stared blankly into space as he sat down at the corner that had always belonged to him, at the corner where no one would disturb him.

But at this moment, Mo Fan suddenly felt like he wanted to sit a bit closer. That way, perhaps he’d be able to see the match more clearly?

The fifth round of the group arena began.

It was only the fifth round, and Happy was down three players. Their fourth player went on stage to challenge Samsara’s second player, Zhou Zekai, who still had 45% health.

The shouts for a 1v4 shook the stadium. Happy’s fans were in low spirits. At this moment, they couldn’t find the energy to compete with Samsara’s fans. They could only grit their teeth and watch the next match.

The map loaded, the characters spawned.

Even though it was the fifth round, apart from Ye Xiu vs Sun Xiang, all the other rounds had gone by quickly. None of them had gone over two minutes.

What about this round?

Everyone paid attention to Zhou Zekai and his Cloud Piercer. The broadcast didn’t make an exception. As soon as the round began, they directly focused on Cloud Piercer, ignoring Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea.

Because it was the first time anyone had done a 1v3 in the finals. It was a feat that no other famous God had done before. Just this alone was enough to be written into the annals of Glory history. However, right now, he had the chance to take it one step further. He was making his way towards the even more unbelievable 1v4.

Nothing shined brighter than Zhou Zekai right now. He was the focus of everyone. Fang Rui? Boundless Sea? In their eyes, he was just a hindrance, a hindrance to history. Everyone was just waiting for him to be broken apart!

Fang Rui wasn’t given any attention by the camera, but he was going to make himself known: “How arrogant! It looks like you haven’t gotten your fill of fighting yet!”

Everyone laughed.

What sort of situation are you in? Yet such big words. How hilarious.

Ignore him!

Everyone hollered in their hearts. Sure enough, Zhou Zekai ignored him. Cloud Piercer rushed out.

He rushed out again!

Excited screams filled the stadium.

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Mo Fan, and Fang Rui. Zhou Zekai was just as determined, decisive, and unwavering as before.

Anyone who didn’t support Happy was probably aflame with excitement.

The broadcast finally gave in and gave a bit of focus towards Fang Rui. Zhou Zekai had once again charged forward. What was Fang Rui doing?

The scene shown by the camera suddenly turned still.

The canyon walls on the two sides weren’t blurry from movement, and there was no shaking from the character looking around. The camera seemed to be displaying an image. Everything in the image was still. The point of view seemed to be moving, but it was very very slow. Sometimes, he’d be looking left. Sometimes, he’d be looking right. Sometimes, he’d be looking behind, at a wooden sign saying “Military Area, Death to Intruders”

Boundless Sea wasn’t moving. After four rounds of the group arena, someone had finally made the decision not to take the initiative to attack, choosing instead to wait for the opponent to come. After checking the surroundings, Boundless Sea began spinning around in place.

What is he planning?

Everyone thought to themselves. People began noticing this hindrance, this person who had been regarded as cannon fodder.

Fang Rui, the master of playing dirty, Fang Rui. What could he do besides playing dirty!

Everyone immediately thought of the wooden sign that they saw from Fang Rui’s viewpoint.

Military Area, Death to Intruders!

This bastard. Was he thinking of some sort of scheme to directly send Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer into the area designated “Death to Intruders”!

But how could it be that easy?

For one, Boundless Sea was closer. Plus, Cloud Piercer was a Sharpshooter. He wouldn’t let Boundless Sea get close to him easily. In that case, how was Fang Rui going to send him to this forbidden zone?

Everyone felt like it was impossible, but they couldn’t help but worry…

Chapter 1656 - Intentional or A Mistake

Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea simply idled his time away at the spawn point, a bend in the canyon. He was showing that he intended on standing around and waiting there.

Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer quickly made his way past the midpoint and then began paying attention to his surroundings. Although Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea couldn’t climb like a Ninja could, there were quite a few footholds on the walls. Reaching the top of the canyon wasn’t a feat that only a Ninja could accomplish. It was just much easier for them.

The canyon walls continued to blur past him. Even though he had begun checking his surroundings, Cloud Piercer hadn’t slowed down. He was already carrying his two guns in his hands. Boundless Sea hadn’t appeared yet, but his guns were still pointed straight ahead, filled with killing intent.

The viewers watching knew that all of Zhou Zekai’s efforts right now were futile because Fang Rui refused to move. There was no need for him to be so vigilant.

When they thought of how unnecessary it was, Cloud Piercer’s biting cold killing intent didn’t seem as imposing as before.

Closer and closer.

A player of Fang Rui’s calibre would know how long it would take Cloud Piercer to reach him. Boundless Sea finally started moving. He moved left until he hit the canyon wall and then backed away. Just before he stepped into the “Death to Intruders” territory, he stopped.

Then, he started curling into a ball. But not completely. In the end, he waited there, maintaining a half-crouching half-standing stance.

What was the meaning of this?

Everyone was puzzled.

Did he think he could hide himself like this? Seeing Boundless Sea’s rather funny stance, everyone wanted to laugh.

To explore this point, the broadcast and the stadium screens got involved, showing a viewpoint looking towards this spawn point.

Boundless Sea could be seen as plain as day. Not a single part of him was hidden.

There were people in the crowd who were already laughing out loud. What was Fang Rui smoking?

At this moment, the camera began to pull back, gradually pulling away. At a certain distance away, everyone suddenly discovered that this half-crouching Boundless Sea disappeared.

It was a matter of angle.

Everyone understood. The canyon wasn’t flat and straight. The twists and turns would have an effect on the player’s line of sight. No one really knew how exactly the line of sight was affected at this position, but in any case, Boundless Sea couldn’t be seen.

But wasn’t it too naive to think that you could hide just like that? Even if Boundless Sea was hidden at this distance, if you just took one step forward, Boundless Sea would be visible again.

The broadcast and stadium screens wanted to tell everyone this point. The camera moved forward and backward several times, and Boundless Sea appeared and disappeared several times.

Then, the camera continued to pull back farther and farther. The viewers didn’t understand what the point was until it stopped. Soon afterwards, the image showed the distance between its current position and the spawn point.

Those familiar with Cloud Piercer suddenly understood. This distance was Cloud Piercer’s attack range. In other words, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer could start attacking from here, but he wouldn’t be able to see him from here.

Cloud Piercer needed to continue forward if he wanted to find Boundless Sea. If he moved to the other side of the canyon, he would be able to find Boundless Sea sooner. However, the precondition was that he had this awareness.

Finally, a diagonal line was drawn in the canyon. With one glance, the diagonal line showed where Cloud Piercer would need to cross to see Boundless Sea. Right now, it was a question of whether Cloud Piercer leaned left or leaned right. If he leaned left, he would be able to find Boundless Sea from farther away. If he leaned right, then closer. The problem was that even if he leaned all the way to the right, Cloud Piercer would still be at least ten steps away from Boundless Sea. This wasn’t a distance that posed a problem for Sharpshooters. In fact, this distance was a Sharpshooter’s optimal distance.

No one could understand what Fang Rui was trying to do. Was he hoping that Cloud Piercer wouldn’t step into the area past that diagonal line? After not finding Boundless Sea, maybe Zhou Zekai would think that Boundless Sea had somehow gotten behind him without noticing and then turn back to investigate? Then, Fang Rui would make his move?

This…

It wasn’t impossible.

When everyone thought about the view from that corner, it did have a faint feeling like you could already see everything from there. If you believed in that illusion, then it really would feel like there couldn’t be anyone there.

What will happen?

Everyone felt uneasy as they waited. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer finally arrived.

After reaching here and not seeing anything in front of him, Zhou Zekai clearly paused and had a moment of confusion.

He looked to his left and right again, and then behind him. He slowed down, and it seemed like he was going to go with the possibility that everyone had been worried about.

Keep going!!

Countless people were anxiously screaming in their hearts. The Samsara fans in the stadium had started shouting “Keep going!”

Everyone was staring intently at that diagonal line provided by the broadcast. Zhou Zekai naturally couldn’t see it, but the viewers could clearly see Cloud Piercer move closer step by step.

Keep going!

Keep going!

Keep going!

The crowd’s shouts were organized and powerful, but Cloud Piercer’s footsteps were moving in opposition to their wishes. With every shout, every step became slower and smaller as if he would turn around at any moment. It made everyone incredibly worried.

Keep going!

Countless people couldn’t bear the anxiety. The shouts were starting to sound desperate.

Zhou Zekai seemed to have suddenly confirmed something.

Cloud Piercer didn’t turn around. He kept going and sped up.

He’s crossed it!

The diagonal line was crossed, and not just by one step, but by two steps, three steps. Cloud Piercer suddenly accelerated, and Boundless Sea appeared in his sights. His two arms were perfectly straight, his dual guns aimed steadily at that corner.

Oh oh oh oh!

The crowd suddenly cheered. Their captain, their ace player wasn’t going to let them down.

Slowing down? Was that hesitation?

No, he was still going forward, but he slowed down to mix up his speed to mess up Fang Rui’s predictions. This was because Zhou Zekai understood Fang Rui. They had joined the pro scene in the same season. Even if he couldn’t see Boundless Sea, he knew that Fang Rui must be waiting to ambush him.

That was why he slowed down and then sped up. If neither side was amply prepared, then the sudden clash would be a contest of their reaction speed.

Open fire!

Bullets flew out.

Boundless Sea scuttled out. Sure enough, Fang Rui had been waiting there for him. Even if Zhou Zekai had messed up the rhythm, Cloud Piercer’s sudden appearance didn’t catch him off guard.

The bullets instantly set off sparks, but there was no sound of bullets hitting flesh. Boundless Sea had a Qi Wave Shield propped up, blocking the first wave of attacks.

Bang bang bang bang!

The dual guns fired again.

Even though the Qi Wave Shield wasn’t shattered yet, the surface area was too small. It wasn’t like Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella which covered his entire body. Moreover, after a Qi Wave Shield was formed, it wouldn’t move.

Roll!

Fang Rui tried to have Boundless Sea roll to dodge the attacks, but he didn’t have much room to maneuver around at the moment. The area behind him was a forbidden zone. In other words, he was quite limited with his movements.

Pu pu pu!

This time, the bullets hit flesh. At this distance, in these confines, Fang Rui wasn’t able to completely dodge all of Cloud Piercer’s attacks. However, he wasn’t knocked back by the bullets. The force of the impact had no effect on him.

Reinforced Iron Bones!

Fang Rui had Boundless Sea activate Reinforced Iron Bones, but he still had Boundless Sea roll forward as a feint. It likely reduced the damage he received, but at the same time, he was also hiding his next move while rolling. This was a very common trick that he used when he played as a Thief.

Qi Bullet!

A blast of qi shot towards Cloud Piercer’s head.

But right now, the viewers couldn’t focus on their fight because they realized that NPCs had spawned in the forbidden zone. After the NPCs spawned, all sorts of skills were thrown out.

Artillery shells, spells, curses, qi attacks flew out from the forbidden zone.

Knight’s Charge, Berserker’s Colliding Stab, a tide of NPCs of all different classes had come charging out.

Event refresh?

It wasn’t fixed? It was random?

It just happened to occur right now?

The projection technology and the broadcast split off a section, showing that the forbidden zone at Samsara’s spawn point was quiet.

This wasn’t happening randomly. Something had triggered it. Was it because they were fighting too close to the forbidden zone? There was a setting like that?

The viewers and the pro players were all trying to guess the reason. But the broadcast team and other staff members had other means to investigate the trigger.

And soon, the answer was found.

On the stadium screens and the broadcast small screen, a replay was given of what Boundless Sea was doing when Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer rushed out.

Boundless Sea had formed a Qi Wave Shield and also rushed out, but for his very first step, he crossed over into “Death to Intruders” zone.

Boundless Sea wasn’t immediately killed, but the NPCs had been summoned because of this small movement. It was a part of the map setting. It wasn’t that complicated. If the entire character ran through the zone, that was trespassing. If a single foot stepped into the zone, that was trespassing.

And so the NPCs spawned and began attacking. Their focus was Boundless Sea, but they wouldn’t intentionally avoid Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer either.

The battle instantly turned into chaos. As for the step that triggered it, had it been intentional? Or a mistake?

Chapter 1657 - True Thoughts

Boom boom boom!

Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer rolled through a chain of explosions.

He could tell that these attacks weren’t aimed towards him. However, long-ranged classes such as Launchers and Elementalists often dealt AoE damage. The attacks might miss, but the AoE would still reach him. Zhou Zekai couldn’t completely avoid taking damage.

He was dodging. Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea was also dodging. Seeing how he was calmly luring the NPCs towards Cloud Piercer, the spectating pro players immediately grasped his plans. It wasn’t an accident. Fang Rui had done it on purpose.

“Death to Intruders.”

What exactly did the sign mean by “death”? Instant death?

No one had tested this setting before in the previous rounds, but Fang Rui had Boundless Sea cross the line anyways. This move was truly daring and risky. If crossing the line really did mean instant death, then Samsara would have instantly won this fight. Zhou Zekai would have won even more perfectly than his fight against Mo Fan. Cloud Piercer had at least lost some mana that round.

But it wasn’t instant death. The NPCs were summoned and began chasing after Boundless Sea. And seeing how Fang Rui was intentionally guiding their attacks, it could be seen that he had been ready long beforehand. In other words, he had been waiting for this moment.

At Happy’s seats, Wei Chen laughed smugly.

This was the plan that he and Fang Rui had come up together. When Mo Fan’s Deception triggered the ambush from above, Fang Rui had begun preparing for his fight. He had pulled Wei Chen over to the side to discuss how the “Death to Intruders” setting might work.

The system didn’t automatically come up with rules. The map designers, in other words, the Glory game designers had engineered the settings of the map.

Guessing the design was equivalent to guessing how the designers thought about the game and the principles that the game had followed for ten years.

Within these ten years, many of the employees had come and gone, but there would always be people who had kept with the game since the beginning. Wei Chen was one of these people. His professional career had only lasted two years, but he had never left the game. He had constantly immersed himself with the design principles of Glory. He was likely more familiar with the game than most of the Glory employees.

Wei Chen deduced that “Death to Intruders” didn’t mean instant death.

His reasoning was very simple. He hadn’t seen any tools or equipment that could kill someone instantly. Glory had always strived to be as logical as possible. If crossing the line meant instant death, then the designers would set up some way for the death to happen. It could be a sudden lightning strike from the sky, but there would definitely be something that would trigger and guide the lightning strike. The lightning strike wouldn’t just appear out of nowhere.

It wasn’t a difficult conclusion to reach, but there were very few people who would be as confident as Wei Chen.

This was the Glory finals. A mistake in judgement would mean that Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea would be instantly killed. All of Happy’s efforts this season would be destroyed in an instant.

The outcome of this mistake was too terrifying. How many people could take responsibility for such a disastrous mistake?

Wei Chen dared to!

He had just made a call. That was it. But the current him was like the captain who once lead Team Blue Rain. He had always been someone brave, someone who had the confidence to carry a huge burden.

“I’m certain,” Wei Chen told Fang Rui confidently.

Thus, when Fang Rui went on stage, he crossed the line for just an instant, entrusting Boundless Sea’s life to Wei Chen’s judgement.

Wei Chen had judged correctly!

It wasn’t an instant death. The NPCs spawned and then went after Boundless Sea.

It was a logical conclusion, and Fang Rui had gone with it.

The NPCs spawned, and while their attacks were aimed at Boundless Sea, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer was implicated along with him.

Zhou Zekai’s situation was similar to the situation in the first round Ye Xiu and Sun Xiang battle. The difference was that the NPCs had been chasing after Samsara in that round, while this time, it was Happy being chased. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf had been put at a disadvantage because of the NPCs, but Fang Rui had brought this onto himself on purpose.

What was his goal? Wouldn’t this just be similar to Mo Fan’s fight in the previous round? He would be facing the combined assault from the NPCs and Zhou Zekai, no?

Those who thought this would happen quickly realized the difference.

The difference was that Mo Fan had triggered the ambush from above. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer could attack, and he wouldn’t hit the NPCs.

But this time, the NPCs were rushing out on flat ground. If Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer attacked Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea, if he missed, the bullets would land on the NPCs, and he would become the new target.

As a result, Zhou Zekai couldn’t coordinate his attacks with the NPCs.

So what could he do?

Thinking of this question, everyone couldn’t help but think of the first round of the group arena. It had just happened not too long ago, so it was still fresh in everyone’s minds.

That round, Ye Xiu didn’t want his attacks to aggro the NPCs, so Lord Grim climbed up the wall and watched free of worries. But Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf was able to reach a max-stage Battle Spirit along with a full five Chasers. His battle strength had reached its peak, and then… the rest didn’t need to be talked about. Everyone at least knew that the NPCs weren’t enough to eliminate a pro player. For example, if Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer just ran away and watched from the side, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea would clean up these NPCs. Even though it wouldn’t be enough to kill him, he would certainly lose a lot of health. Zhou Zekai could wait at ease for his exhausted foe.

The other option was to attack. His attacks would definitely aggro the NPCs. The two would fight it out amidst the besiegement from the NPCs.

No matter how you looked at it, the first choice seemed much easier. Qi Masters weren’t like Battle Mages, who got stronger the longer they fought.

It seemed like quite an easy choice, but Zhou Zekai, who had been decisive this whole time, seemed to hesitate. It didn’t seem like Cloud Piercer had made a decision yet. It seemed as if he were still wavering over which choice to make.

“It looks like Zhou Zekai is having a hard time making a decision. What is he hesitating over?” Pan Lin said what everyone wanted to say.

“Haha,” Li Yibo laughed, “Right now, avoiding battle and watching Fang Rui get taken apart by the NPCs is the better choice, but don’t forget how Zhou Zekai has been playing this entire time! Forward, forward, and forward. Attack, attack, and attack. If he suddenly stopped and ran away, his momentum would fall.”

“That’s why Fang Rui is sure that Zhou Zekai won’t retreat, and why it will force the two of them into a messy fight?” Pan Lin said.

“That seems to be the case,” Li Yibo smiled.

“If that’s the case, why does Fang Rui think he’ll have the advantage in a chaotic fight?” Pan Lin said.

“Ah?” Li Yibo was visibly stunned by the question.

A chaotic battle is more advantageous for Fang Rui? He really hadn’t considered this question, but when he thought about it for a bit, he discovered something: “Yes, a chaotic battle is advantageous for Fang Rui because Zhou Zekai is a Sharpshooter!”

Sharpshooters were long-ranged attackers. Not only did they need a good line of sight on their target, they needed space for their bullets to fly. In this sort of chaotic battle, it was too difficult for a Sharpshooter to focus only on one target. Looking for a good angle, a good shot, there were too many factors to consider. Even Zhou Zekai would be held back in this sort of environment.

No wonder he wanted to end each fight as fast as possible.

No wonder he charged out so decisively every fight.

It wasn’t just to boost the team’s morale. It was because a drawn-out battle in this map was unfavorable for Sharpshooters. It was because of the chaos that the map would spawn.

At this moment, Li Yibo fully grasped Zhou Zekai’s thoughts.

Chaotic battles were disadvantageous for Sharpshooters. This was a very junior view of the situation. But when watching Zhou Zekai, it was hard not to ignore this point because of how skilled he was, skilled to the point that this sort of junior view didn’t seem like it could affect a God like him. But Zhou Zekai didn’t think so. He was truly skilled, but he wasn’t arrogant. He was decisive, fierce, and unrelenting to protect himself against his weakness in this map.

This was why he was wavering right now. Not solely because of momentum, but becauses Fang Rui’s method had exposed his weakness.

Too many people had overlooked this weakness, but not Zhou Zekai. And Fang Rui had also thought of it. He had chosen this risky method to summon the NPCs and create this situation. In Fang Rui’s mind, these NPCs focusing him weren’t enemies, but allies.

“Don’t run! I’ve given you so many helpers, what are you so afraid of?” Fang Rui wasn’t exactly in a great spot with so many NPCs attacking him, but he still had the time to trash talk. Fang Rui wouldn’t miss this sort of opportunity and let out a word. He understood Zhou Zekai and their current situation. His words wouldn’t be able to affect Zhou Zekai’s decision, but he knew that there were lots of people outside who didn’t quite understand the current situation. In their eyes, the situation was just like he described. If Zhou Zekai ran away, it would be very unmanly. Fang Rui’s words were meant to destroy his image. His trash talk was still quite incisive.

“Can’t run.” Zhou Zekai actually responded to Fang Rui, perhaps it was because Cloud Piercer was at a completely safe distance right now. He didn’t have anything to do.

He watched as the NPCs chased after Fang Rui. Everyone realized that he had come to a decision. The trash talk that Fang Rui had squeezed in hadn’t affected him. He understood Fang Rui well though. When Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea took a step across the forbidden area, he quickly grasped Fang Rui’s goals.

Fang Rui wasn’t going to just let him stand on the side and watch. He planned on “leading” these NPCs to surround him. True, he could run and run, but run to where? Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim could climb up the walls and hide because he had Ninja skills. He had much more freedom in his movements on the walls compared to other classes. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf was a close-ranged class too. But Zhou Zekai? His Cloud Piercer could only rely on jumping to move around on along the canyon wall. His movements were very limited. His Aerial Gun would be restricted. If his bullets landed on the NPCs, he would pull their aggro. Fang Rui’s Qi Master also had more long-ranged attacks than a Battle Mage. While Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim could keep running away safely, it wouldn’t be possible for Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer.

In the end, if he kept running, he would eventually reach the forbidden area on the other end of the canyon. Either way, he would need to win over Fang Rui amidst this chaos. And when that time came, how much damage would the NPCs have dealt to Fang Rui?

Zhou Zekai watched for a bit. Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea moved around craftily and didn’t attack much. He prioritized his survival and his movements. He wanted to bring those NPCs towards Zhou Zekai. Even by the time they reached the other side, he wouldn’t have lost much health.

“If you’re not going to run, then I’m coming!” Fang Rui shouted.

This time, Zhou Zekai didn’t reply, but his Cloud Piercer charged back.

This was the usual him, speaking with his actions.

Chapter 1658 - Situational Control

Zhou Zekai didn’t back down. He charged ahead as always, but this time, he would truly encounter a challenge. The pro players had analyzed the merits and drawbacks of his decision, and understood that this sort of chaotic battle was unfavorable for him.

However, most of the viewers didn’t realize this issue. In the eyes of the loyal fans, their captain was invincible. He had no weaknesses. What applied to others didn’t apply to him.

The pro players agreed to a certain extent. A top player like Zhou Zekai couldn’t be looked at with common sense. Controlling bullets as fast and accurate as a sword, was that common sense?

Everyone was used to thinking about him differently, but Zhou Zekai himself wouldn’t forget common sense. He wouldn’t leave his opponents any opportunities. However, Fang Rui was utilizing this map to set up a trap.

Zhou Zekai hesitated for a while, but in the end, he didn’t retreat. Cloud Piercer charged forward bravely.

Was he planning on breaking common sense? The pro players thought to themselves. The crowd had already erupted into thunderous applause.

He charged forward, but he didn’t attack.

The tip of his gun was aimed at Boundless Sea, getting closer and closer but never firing.

Fang Rui had been ready for a fight with Zhou Zekai under these circumstances. Seeing that Zhou Zekai wasn’t retreating, he welcomed him warmly. Boundless Sea immediately rolled, dodging two attacks while also approaching Cloud Piercer.

The instant he rolled, an artillery shell flew out from behind him. A Launcher NPC had fired at him. With this dodge, the artillery shell was now heading towards Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer.

Cloud Piercer rolled to the side, evading the missile. Boundless Sea suddenly shot up and pushed out with his two palms.

Sky Piercing Strike!

Fang Rui had chained together his attack with the Launcher NPC. The Sky Piercing Strike went straight for where Cloud Piercer was rolling towards. He didn’t care if he hit the NPCs. After all, the NPCs were already targeting him. He didn’t mind taking down Cloud Piercer along with the NPCs.

The AoE from Sky Piercing Strike wasn’t small. Cloud Piercer looked as if he would be hit. With the swarm of NPCs surrounding them, his escape options were much more limited. Fang Rui wasn’t attacking randomly. Fang Rui had considered many factors from dodging two attacks to baiting the artillery shell from the Launcher behind him to the Sky Piercing Strike to Cloud Piercer leaving an opening…

It was too much. To normal players, everything might seem normal, but to the pro players, all of the little details involved made them feel dizzy.

Can he dodge this attack?

Many of the pro players didn’t think so. But common sense didn’t apply to someone like Zhou Zekai. Cloud Piercer suddenly jumped up and fired two shots.

It was just a normal jump. It wasn’t fast enough, but with the help from recoil, Cloud Piercer sped up. As he jumped, he raised his legs, and just like this, the Sky Piercing Strike whistled past him.

Fire!

Cloud Piercer fired at the NPC crowd. However, these two shots didn’t grab any of the NPCs’ attention. The ones near him continued to focus on Boundless Sea. None of them turned their head to even take a glance at Cloud Piercer.

He had fired two shots at the NPC crowd, but neither of the shots landed. Zhou Zekai wasn’t so quick to compromise. He was still looking for opportunities within the chaos.

Bang bang!

But at this moment, the airborne Cloud Piercer fired another two shots.

The bullets flew out towards Boundless Sea. Besides him, there was no second choice.

The two characters were quite close at this point. The two gunshots had come all of a sudden. Seeing Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer jump and then fire carefully, missing the NPCs, no one thought he would attack so easily in this chaos. To everyone’s surprise, he actually had Cloud Piercer fire twice while swaying in the air.

Pu! A hit, and a spurt of blood.

The two shots had been too close and too sudden. Fang Rui didn’t have time to completely react. Boundless Sea hastily dodged, avoiding one of the bullets.

It was just a normal shot, so the damage wasn’t anything noteworthy. Fang Rui and everyone else was more concerned about where the bullet he dodged would end up at.

Pu! Another hit, but there was no blood. The bullet had hit the ground, whistling by all of the NPCs.

Zhou Zekai wouldn’t have Cloud Piecer fire rashly if he didn’t think he had a good grasp of the situation. He had Cloud Piercer attack because he was confident.

Cloud Piercer landed gently onto the ground. There just happened to be an NPC rushing over to attack Boundless Sea. He moved aside. He had no intentions of blocking the NPC’s path. The Wildfire in his right hand was pointed straight ahead towards Boundless Sea.

With so many NPCs moving around, Boundless Sea would appear and disappear from his sight. He didn’t attack, but he didn’t change stances. However, his two previous shots let everyone know that it wasn’t that he couldn’t attack, but that he needed the right opening. Even amidst this chaotic battlefield, he was able to fire at Boundless Sea without hitting any of the NPCs. His skill was just that incredible.

“Amazing.”

Not just the normal players, even the pro players were in awe.

“His aim is great, but what’s more impressive is his control over the battle.” On Team Tiny Herb’s side, captain Wang Jiexi commented on the match to his players.

“A chaotic battlefield is unfavorable for Gunners. This is an indisputable fact,” Wang Jiexi continued, “But Zhou Zekai’s two gunshots were a signal to Fang Rui. Even in this chaos, I can still attack you. This is where it differs from what the average player might think. Even if Zhou Zekai doesn’t attack, the threat of his attacks requires Fang Rui’s attention. While dealing with the NPCs, he also has to be wary of leaving openings for Zhou Zekai to attack.”

“Then what should he do?” A rookie in the team asked.

“Be proactive,” Wang Jiexi said.

Fang Rui clearly understood this reasoning. At this moment, he had to be proactive. He couldn’t just let Zhou Zekai stand there, waiting for the right opportunity to appear.

Turn, move, roll!

Boundless Sea dodged the attacks from the NPCs, while moving towards Cloud Piercer.

Zhou Zekai saw his movements. Cloud Piercer didn’t move up, but he didn’t back down either. However, his guns were constantly following Boundless Sea’s movements.

Pressure!

Anyone would feel threatened by Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer aiming at them. The only reason he hadn’t launched a rain of bullets onto Boundless Sea was because he didn’t want to hit the NPCs. From this perspective, these NPCs really did become Fang Rui’s protective umbrella.

Boundless Sea continued to tumble about, avoiding the NPCs through Fang Rui’s unique way of moving around. His point of view was constantly spinning. The normal players looking at it had no idea what they were looking at. They couldn’t even tell what direction they were going in. They might not be able to tell from Fang Rui’s point of view, but Boundless Sea’s movements were clear as day from the spectator view.

His movements didn’t look complicated, but the spinning made anyone looking through his point of view want to vomit.

It wasn’t as simple as just dodging the NPCs’ attacks. He had to observe his surroundings. He needed to know how the NPCs were attacking and moving because he needed to know this to win. Just relying on this chaos to make it difficult to shoot him wouldn’t be enough to take down Zhou Zekai. If he wanted to win, he needed to take it to the next step. He had known this from the start.

This was very difficult, especially for the current him.

Fang Rui knew what condition he was in. He hadn’t wanted to play in the group arena. He had wanted to save his energy and strength for the more important team competition. But the group arena was going so disastrously that he couldn’t wait until then.

But dealing with Zhou Zekai would be even more strenuous than the team competition!

His blurred view finally stabilized for a moment, locked onto Cloud Piercer.

Chapter 1659 - Wooden Sign

Qi Blade!

Fang Rui launched another attack, borrowing the NPC in front of him as cover. From start to finish, none of Fang Rui’s movements could be seen by Zhou Zekai. That NPC seemed to be colluding with Fang Rui. The moment the Qi Blade flew out, the NPC moved aside.

Cloud Piercer immediately appeared in Fang Rui’s sights. The two guns were locked onto Boundless Sea. Behind Boundless Sea were three NPCs lined up side by side, charging towards him. Boundless Sea had enemies in front and behind, yet Fang Rui didn’t seem worried at all.

He was aware of Boundless Sea’s situation. In front was Cloud Piercer. Behind were three NPCs. The distance between them were all within his calculations.

Would Cloud Piercer attack?

Fang Rui wasn’t certain. He only knew that at this distance, if Cloud Piercer attacked, he had some confidence in dodging a few of the bullets. As a result, the NPCs behind him would be hit by the bullets, and Cloud Piercer would aggro the NPCs. That wasn’t what Zhou Zekai wanted.

So then, attack!

With a Cloud Pushing Palm, Boundless Sea mercilessly pushed away the NPC that had provided him cover, so he could leave himself as open as possible for Cloud Piercer to fire at him.

Bang bang!

Gunshots!

Cloud Piercer fired. Two bullets flew out from the Wildfire in his right hand and the Shattered Frost in his left hand.

Fang Rui had been ready. He immediately crouched.

The two bullets streaked across, brushing past Boundless Sea’s shoulders.

Dodged!

Fang Rui was overjoyed at first, but then he didn’t hear the sound of a bullet hitting a target that he had expected to hear.

A formidable enemy was in front of him. Fang Rui didn’t have the time to turn around to check behind him. However, the spectators could see everything clearly. Although the three NPCs had been lined up side by side, there was a bit of space between them. No matter how close together they were, even if they were shoulder to shoulder, there would be a gap between the heads.

Boundless Sea had dodged the two bullets. Then, the bullets flew through the gap between the NPCs’ heads, not hitting any of them.

Samsara’s fans applauded wildly. They knew what Fang Rui had planned, but it failed because of Zhou Zekai’s precise aim. It was an incredibly exciting sight to see.

But Fang Rui wasn’t done yet. The crouching Boundless Sea continued forward displaying Fang Rui’s signature dirty style.

Qi Blade!

The sneak attack from Boundless Sea had now reached Cloud Piercer. But Zhou Zekai was clearly aware of it. After firing twice, Cloud Piercer crouched down. The Qi Blade flew past him. Cloud Piercer may be crouching, but his two guns were still aimed firmly towards Boundless Sea.

Bang! Bang!

Another two gunshots, but compared to the previous two, there was a delay between the gunshots. Zhou Zekai wasn’t focused solely on Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea. He was carefully watching the NPCs behind Boundless Sea. He had delayed his shots so that he wouldn’t hit them.

At this distance, it was very difficult to dodge a bullet, but Fang Rui wasn’t an ordinary player. With a dirty stance, Boundless Sea went from a crouch to a roll without a second thought.

Cloud Piercer missed again, but Zhou Zekai had taken the three NPCs into consideration. The low altitude bullets went for the gaps in their footsteps.

The applause was never ending. Zhou Zekai was able to prevent his attacks from aggroing the NPCs. His technique was impeccable.

Amazing!

Four bullets in a row, yet none of them hit the NPCs. Fang Rui naturally knew that Zhou Zekai’s four gunshots had been aimed at the small gaps between the NPCs. He knew how difficult it was to pull off.

Difficult was difficult. Amazing was amazing. But if you had to say threatening, then the answer was no.

Zhou Zekai was being restricted. In order to not aggro the NPCs, his hands and feet were bound. He couldn’t establish a sustainable tempo. These sorts of attacks were nothing threatening.

You think you can scare me with just that?

Fang Rui laughed coldly. Boundless Sea continued to change his route. In front of him, to the left, to the right, behind him, there were NPCs approaching from every direction. All sorts of long-ranged attacks were raining down on him.

Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer didn’t just stand there. He was moving nimbly amidst the chaos, searching for an angle and an opening to attack.

Gunshots would ring from time to time. He continued to attack. He couldn’t establish a set tempo, and his attacks weren’t very threatening, but Fang Rui couldn’t stop them from coming. Zhou Zekai wasn’t playing as aggressive or domineering as before. He was patiently kiting around Fang Rui. He wasn’t in a hurry. The one taking more damage was Fang Rui, whether it was the player himself, or the character’s health and mana. Facing these NPCs weren’t a problem for pro players, but it wouldn’t be a walk in the park either.

A subtle change had begun to take place.

Zhou Zekai was being restricted by the NPCs, but Fang Rui wasn’t without burden.

Who would be the first to make a mistake? Who would be the first to grasp the first large opening?

Boundless Sea went in circles with the NPCs, while Cloud Piercer was constantly looking for an opening. While Zhou Zekai searched, he was also closely observing the NPCs’ movements. He knew that these NPCs weren’t only being used as shields by Fang Rui.

After he dodged another sneak attack from Boundless Sea, with a flicker, Boundless Sea suddenly vanished.

Over there!

Zhou Zekai at least had the general direction. Boundless Sea suddenly stopped rushing towards Cloud Piercer. He had unexpectedly dashed into a group of NPCs.

Cloud Piercer immediately moved to the side. Truthfully, every time Boundless Sea did something unexpected, Zhou Zekai would feel a bit nervous. He knew how crafty and dirty this same-generation player was.

Moving to the side allowed him to see from a different angle, but Boundless Sea still couldn’t be seen. That mob of NPCs seemed to have taken a hold of Boundless Sea. More and more NPCs and attacks started gathering there.

Hong!

The flat ground suddenly let out a muffled noise. Zhou Zekai’s vision began to shake. The ground itself was trembling.

Cloud Piercer only felt a bit of swaying, but many of the NPCs in the mob were directly launched into the air.

Landmine Quake!

Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea had undoubtedly used Landmine Quake.

But he had taken the initiative to gather the crowd of NPCs. Now, he was using this skill to disperse them. What was he scheming?

Boundless Sea seemed to be trying to escape with all his might, but Zhou Zekai didn’t have Cloud Piercer step forward to stop him. Instead, he backed away two steps.

He was no longer pushing forward relentlessly. He was displaying a patience with no openings. If he didn’t fully have a grasp of the situation, he wouldn’t rashly interfere.

Hong!

Another muffled sound. A burst of qi exploded in the center of the NPC mob. Countless more NPCs were thrown into the air, or sent tumbling towards the ground towards Cloud Piercer.

Cloud Piercer suddenly made a move. He suddenly rolled forward!

With a lowered view, he was able to see from below. Behind one of the NPCs flying out was a curled up Boundless Sea in the air.

Exposed!

Boundless Sea had tried to hide his movements by mixing in with the NPCs, but Zhou Zekai had caught him. Right now, Fang Rui had no other choice but to brace himself and attack.

A wave of qi descended!

Boundless Sea pushed out with his two palms, sending out a blast of qi.

Cloud PIercer had gotten up from his roll, attacking above from below. Even if he missed, his bullets would be flying up towards the sky. It wasn’t possible for him to hit an NPC.

As a result, Cloud Piercer didn’t hold back.

Kaka.

While he had been rolling, the dual guns in Cloud Piercer’s hands had turned into a long sniper rifle. It was aimed straight at Boundless Sea, bullet loaded. Fire!

Thunder Snipe!

At such a close distance, it wasn’t possible to react to the Thunder Snipe. Zhou Zekai had went for the highest DPS possible during this window. His snipe naturally went for Boundless Sea’s head.

Pa!

The snipe had been extremely accurate. It hit Boundless Sea’s head, dealing double damage. Blood blossomed into the air.

The powerful impact changed Boundless Sea’s original trajectory.

But Zhou Zekai wasn’t done yet. When there were no openings, he could wait patiently until one came. When an opening came, he would seize it full-force.

Dual Load!

Cloud Piercer refreshed Thunder Snipe. He raised his sniper rifle again and fired another shot towards the head, the head showered in blood.

Bang!

Another gunshot.

Another headshot, double damage.

Blood burst forth again, but this time, amidst this blood, a sharp cry sounded out.

This is…

The sound of a Young Wyvern.

Zhou Zekai stared blankly. He saw a Summoner’s Wyvern fall from the air. The Wyvern had been hit by the Thunder Snipe, and was now just a dead corpse.

Immediately afterwards, the NPCs began attacking Cloud Piercer.

Aggro established!

Zhou Zekai laughed bitterly. In the end, he had been tricked by Fang Rui. A Wyvern just happened to be rushing towards Boundless Sea from behind when he attacked. Zhou Zekai didn’t think it was a coincidence. He had lured the Wyvern over to take the attack. All the signboards had been a facade. The true signboard had been Boundless Sea.

Since the aggro had been established, there was no need to be cautious anymore.

Random Firing!

Bullets flew from Cloud Piercer’s dual guns, creating a protective circle around him. However, a good number of the bullets were still focused on Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea.

Pulling aggro only put him in a difficult situation. It didn’t mean that he had lost. The winner would be decided by what came next. After Zhou Zekai established aggro from the NPCs, he immediately burst forth. It seemed like he planned on bringing down Boundless Sea in one wave.

Fang Rui had carefully crafted his scheme. Boundless Sea was still soaring through the air. He wasn’t able to land due to Cloud Piercer’s Random Firing. He was tumbling in midair, once again exposing his back.

Extremely close behind him was an Elementalist NPC who had been standing there silently for who knew how long. But right now, his staff was burning brightly with fire magic. This Elementalist was clearly preparing for a powerful spell. Cloud Piercer wasn’t able to react in time and interrupt the cast. The Elementalist pointed with his staff, and a ball of flame burst forth. The fire expanded and formed a majestic fire bird.

Level 75 Elementalist skill, Fire Bird.

Boundless Sea’s signboard wasn’t as simple as just a Wyvern!

Chapter 1660 - Thorough Usage

Fire Bird, Level 75 Elementalist skill. These NPCs only had so-so fighting capabilities. The threat of their attacks were limited. However, the pressure given off Fire Bird wasn’t lacking at all.

A ball of fire floated above the staff. The flames spread its wings and flew out, burning everything in its path.

The distance was too close. Fire Bird had a long cast time, but the attack itself was fast. Zhou Zekai’s screen instantly turned bright red. In an instant, Cloud Piercer was swallowed by the raging flames.

Cloud Piercer wasn’t able to dodge the attack, but that didn’t mean Zhou Zekai couldn’t do anything. Everyone saw him raise his knees just before the flames struck.

The average viewer just thought that Cloud Piercer was trying to dodge the attack, but was hit by the Fire Bird before he could take a second step. However, when the pro players saw Cloud Piercer stand steady inside the flames, they knew that it wasn’t as simple as just taking a step, but rather a Knee Strike.

Knee Strike was a low-level skill limited to close combat. However, even though Sharpshooters tended not to choose to fight at close range, Knee Strike was a very important skill. Launchers, Mechanics, and Spitfires, it was a must-learn skill for the other Gunner classes too.

Because when this skill was used, the user would have a brief moment of Super Armor.

There wasn’t a definite number for how long the Super Armor lasted. Many skills in Glory had hidden effects that wouldn’t be made public. However, Knee Strike was a skill that had been in the game since the start. Its uses had been uncovered long ago by players and pro players.

In particular, for Gunners, this brief Super Armor was extremely useful.

This was because Glory skills didn’t have “shared cooldowns.” In theory, if you were fast enough, you could use ten skills all at once.

Of course, this was just in theory. Although Glory didn’t have “shared cooldowns,” there were other ways the game design limited the available options. For example, character movements could not conflict with each other. Even if there were no “shared cooldowns,” there weren’t many skills that could be used simultaneously.

Knee Strike was a skill that was extremely compatible with other Gunner skills. Lifting the knees wouldn’t conflict with raising the arms to shoot a gun. Knee Strike also had a low cooldown, so it was often used to guarantee that other attacks successfully went off. Many players had blind faith in this technique. They wanted to combine Knee Strike with every attack, and for a while every Gunner was like a one-legged person.

However, this technique wasn’t as easy to use as people originally thought. First, in order to use two skills at the same time, the player needed to have a fast enough hand speed. Second, the Super Armor effect from Knee Strike was very short. Making use of the Super Armor required precise timing and judgement. For most players, using the technique depended on luck. Whether they succeeded or not was like a blind cat trying to find a dead rat.

People failed most of the time, and it was always because too many inputs would mess up what would otherwise be a simple movement. In the end, most people stopped trying to blindly test their luck and went toward more useful things.

Zhou Zekai’s skill naturally didn’t need to be questioned. There was no time for him to dodge, so he used this Knee Strike technique. However, the Super Armor from Knee Strike was very brief, while Fire Bird was a powerful attack. Relying on this brief Super Armor to resist the Fire Bird’s momentum was impossible. Zhou Zekai used it when it would be most effective, the moment the Fire Bird struck.

Flames swept past. Cloud Piercer didn’t move when he raised his knee, but the Super Armor quickly disappeared, while the remaining impact followed through. However, the impact was reduced enough for Cloud Piercer to eliminate by stepping back appropriately.

Most people thought that the NPC’s Fire Bird wasn’t strong enough to send Cloud Piercer flying away, overlooking Zhou Zekai’s perfectly timed Knee Strike.

Really troublesome!

Fang Rui saw everything clearly. He couldn’t help but curse. He had been setting things up for this moment for a long time. Cloud Piercer had established the NPCs’ aggro and was hit by Fire Bird, but Cloud Piercer was still much farther away than Fang Rui had been hoping for. He had hoped that the Fire Bird would directly send Cloud Piercer over to him. The NPCs who were now targeting Cloud Piercer would attack, while he helped from the sidelines. That way, he would be able to take out Cloud Piercer in one go.

But there was still a bit of distance from the perfect scenario that he had envisioned.

Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer wasn’t sent flying. He stumbled back a few steps before steadying himself. His two guns were aimed straight towards Boundless Sea just like before. He wanted to continue his offense.

Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow!

But Boundless Sea moved faster.

This situation wasn’t as perfect as Fang Rui had envisioned, but he had to recognize that this was much more realistic. Zhou Zekai wasn’t so easy to beat. Killing him in one go was just a dream.

Flames still lingered on Cloud Piercer. The flames didn’t deal any damage, but they were like a marker. The Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow soared over.

Dodge!

Cloud Piercer didn’t stop to take a breath after making it past the Fire Bird. From the start, Zhou Zekai was focused on movement. As he dodged the Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow, he began his counterattack.

Bang bang bang!

Gunshots. The counterattack didn’t come any slower than Boundless Sea’s Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow.

Boundless Sea used Slap, sending the Elementalist next to him spinning. The Elementalist became a meat shield to block Cloud Piercer’s attacks.

This wasn’t Zhou Zekai’s target. Cloud Piercer continued to move to the side to get to a different angle. Boundless Sea dodged to the other side.

Dragon Wave!

Qi gathered and formed into a fierce dragon. The qi moved slower than the bullets, and relying on this difference, the qi dragon made its way to Cloud Piercer.

Cloud Piercer immediately dodged to the side. However, Dragon Wave could be controlled. It wasn’t so easy to escape from. Interrupting the skill was crucial.

Cloud Piercer aimed his gun at Boundless Sea, but an NPC suddenly came out from nowhere, putting itself in between Cloud Piercer and Boundless Sea.

Zhou Zekai could only have Cloud Piercer take a few more steps. But the Dragon Wave didn’t chase after Cloud Piercer. Instead, the dragon suddenly went backwards, moving in front of Cloud Piercer, blocking Zhou Zekai’s sight again.

Qi had no color, but when enough of it gathered, the qi was thick enough to create a masking effect.

When Zhou Zekai saw Fang Rui’s movements, he immediately felt that something wasn’t right. Fang Rui was putting in an excessive amount of effort into blocking his vision. Fang Rui was probably providing cover for another NPC.

The NPC that had stuck itself between the two of them suddenly popped into Zhou Zekai’s mind. He still remembered that the NPC had been moving towards him, but what class?

Battle Mage!

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

The Dragon Wave suddenly moved out of the way, revealing a figure charging forward.

Zhou Zekai reacted fast as lightning, but he was only able to act the moment the Battle Mage attacked. It was because the battlefield was too chaotic. The two couldn’t only pay attention to each other. They needed to also avoid interference from the NPCs. There were all sorts of things moving around all at once from the left, behind, to the right, to the left. Even so, Zhou Zekai shouldn’t have been so distracted as to miss something as conspicuous as a Battle Mage charging straight for him.

Not only had Battle Mage blocking his line of sight, the Battle Mage had borrowed Fang Rui’s Dragon Wave as cover to suddenly appear in front of him.

Zhou Zekai reacted almost instinctively. Cloud Piercer just barely dodged the Dragon Breaks the Ranks. But a Berserker NPC just happened to be there. The Berserker swung its sword. Behind the Berserker was a Warlock casting a curse. Zhou Zekai had been aware of it. But more importantly, there was Fang Rui. The Dragon Wave was on its way back, blocking his last possible path of retreat.

Boom!

Countless attacks landed on Cloud Piercer all at once.

Chapter 1661 - Too Smooth Isn’t Good Either

This was already Zhou Zekai’s fourth match in the group arena. But even when Cloud Piercer had been trapped by Dancing Rain’s powerful firing line, he had never been in such a passive state before.

He himself had chosen to have Cloud Piercer enter Dancing Rain’s firing line.

He himself had chosen to charge through Su Mucheng’s barrage.

He himself had chosen to put himself in a predicament, demanding that he broke through it.

But not this time!

In this chaotic battlefield, Fang Rui crafted meticulously calculated plans. As soon as he saw an opening, he would utilize every resource that he had to seize it. There was also his dirty playstyle that was impossible to grasp. All those added together finally put a stop to Zhou Zekai. It was the first time in this group arena that Zhou Zekai was completely out of options. He had no way to escape from this predicament. Cloud Piercer was trapped.

From Boundless Sea’s Dragon Wave.

From a Berserker NPC’s Destruction Slash.

From a Warlock NPC’s Grasping Ghosts.

A Spitfire NPC’s unknown grenade.

A Witch NPC’s Acid Rain.

The Battle Mage NPC that had missed the Dragon Breaks the Ranks was turning back around. Countless close-ranged classes were charging over aggressively.

There were no openings. There was no way out. Besides taking this wave of attacks, nothing else could be done. The flames from the Fire Bird had yet to recede. Sparks of fire still floated in the air.

In an instant, the sparks were swallowed into nothingness by the incoming attacks. And although Cloud Piercer could no longer be seen with all the explosions and light everywhere, everyone could see that he still existed from his rapidly falling health.

The NPCs weren’t very strong, but there were a lot of them. With so many attacks gathered together in one area, how could the damage not be terrifying? Whether it had been the match between Ye Xiu and Sun Xiang, or the match where Mo Fan triggered the NPC ambush from above, none of them had taken so many attacks all at once.

Fang Rui had fully taken advantage of the chaos. With one move, he threw Cloud Piercer into the abyss.

But Fang Rui didn’t relax yet.

Many of the NPCs were still throwing attacks at Boundless Sea. As he ran around, he paid close attention to any movements from Zhou Zekai.

This wave of attacks would inflict heavy damage onto Cloud Piercer, but it wouldn’t be enough to kill him. And the NPC attacks wouldn’t be as focused and calculated as a player’s. There would certainly be an opening after the wave was over. Zhou Zekai would definitely want to escape through this opening. Fang Rui needed to find a way to patch up this gap.

Papapapa…

Gunfire.

Sure enough, after the wave of attacks, Zhou Zekai made his move. With a Roundhouse Kick, he swept away the four NPCs closest to him. Several gunshots followed one after the other. Zhou Zekai didn’t hold back, activating “Rapid Firing” to fire off as many shots as possible.

At the same time, Firearm Martial Arts!

With buffs from Rapid Firing and Firearm Martial Arts, Cloud Piercer’s movements became incomparably quick. Then, he went for the hole that he had opened up, and saw Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea.

As expected…

Zhou Zekai wasn’t surprised. He had pretty much grasped Fang Rui’s plans. He knew that his biggest obstacle in escaping this predicament was Fang Rui. It was similar to the previous match against Mo Fan. Deception had drawn the aggro from the NPCs, but the one who made it the most difficult for Mo Fan was Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer.

Spiral Qi Rush!

Boundless Sea took a step forward and pushed with his palms, sending out a wave of qi. The opening that Cloud Piercer had created for himself was instantly patched up with spinning qi.

Cloud Piercer couldn’t continue forward. However, there were no ways out from the rear, left, or right either. The NPCs had them blocked. Where could he run to?

Zhou Zekai was once again helpless this fast?

Many people had this thought, but not Zhou Zekai.

It looked like there was nowhere to run, but Cloud Piercer retreated a third of a step backwards.

Cloud Piercer raised his guns and fired!

Bang!

The gunshot was unusually loud, and the bullet looked to be quite big. Anyone who had a sense of how fast a bullet typically moved would know that this bullet was moving very slowly.

Stun Bullet!

It was a Spitfire low-level skill. However the Stun effect was too useful. It was similar to a Freeze. The Stun would interrupt and lock up the target’s movements and skills.

This was why the skill was loud and slow. It had been intentionally designed to make the attack difficult to land.

Zhou Zekai had only moved back a third of a step to get off this shot. It could be seen that the distance between Cloud Piercer and Boundless Sea was extremely close. No matter how slow the Stun Bullet moved, it would cross that distance in just an instant.

Zhou Zekai had once again pulled off what everyone had thought was impossible. It was almost infuriating to watch.

And because of how easy it was to recognize Stun Bullet, Fang Rui knew how troublesome this attack would be.

If he continued with the Spiral Qi Rush, the Stun Bullet would interrupt it. The interrupt wasn’t so bad, but the stun… Being stunned when facing the attacks of so many NPCs would be a death sentence.

He had to dodge it!

Boundless Sea quickly twisted to the side and lowered himself. Fang Rui did everything he could to dodge the bullet.

But it was useless.

The distance was too close. Zhou Zekai’s aim was too poisonous. Boundless Sea had moved before he was hit, but he wasn’t able to dodge it. The bullet simply didn’t land exactly where he wanted it to land, that’s all.

The skill effect didn’t care about that though. Boundless Sea went rigid. He wouldn’t be able to dodge the NPC skills coming after him.

Zhou Zekai obviously wasn’t going to show him any sympathy. Seizing this opportunity, Cloud Piercer rushed out, but to his surprise, a scythe came swinging at him from where Boundless Sea had turned away from.

Zhou Zekai was startled. He wanted to dodge, but the area covered by the scythe was too large. There was only a third of a step between them. With the NPCs so close, there was no room to run.

Hit! A talisman glowing with the symbol “定” flew out and attached to Cloud Piercer. If a scythe with a talisman effect landed, it could not be dodged.

The “定” symbol… Immobilizing Talisman…

Cloud Piercer was unable to move. At least, compared to Boundless Sea, he could still attack. But for a Gunner, relying on just attacks to push off an incoming enemy was impossible.

Fang Rui wasn’t able to avoid Zhou Zekai’s terrifying precision, but Zhou Zekai wasn’t able to avoid Fang Rui’s follow-up. The stadium screens focused on the two players. Both were smiling bitterly.

The storm of attacks instantly swallowed the two characters. Boundless Sea was stunned, unable to move in any way. Cloud Piercer was only immobilized. He could still attack, and was trying his hardest to fend off against the enemies so he could survive longer.

Crowd control effects wouldn’t last too long, but these short few seconds felt endless to the two of them.

Who would recover first? This became a crucial question.

Zhou Zekai knew that his Stun Bullet should last 4 seconds. Accounting for the stats on Boundless Sea, the stun would be reduced to at least 2-3 seconds.

As for the NPC’s Immobilization Talisman, the effects couldn’t be too strong. In the end, Cloud Piercer should be immobilized for around 3.5 seconds.

Boundless Sea should recover before Cloud Piercer did, but Cloud Piercer wasn’t stunned and could still attack. This would help him defend against Boundless Sea. Zhou Zekai could only hope that there would be no interference from the NPCs during that time. He wasn’t able to move, and he was helpless against many of the incoming attacks. He could only bet on luck.

1 second, 2 seconds…

Zhou Zekai paid close attention to Boundless Sea.

2.5 seconds…

Boundless Sea recovered!

Fang Rui also knew that this was a key moment. He could already see Cloud Piercer aiming at him.

Fang Rui hastily had Boundless Sea curl up. He thanked the NPCs around him. They were being good partners right now, providing him with exceptional cover.

He flipped over his palms and gathered qi. Boundless Sea wanted to strike Cloud Piercer along with the NPCs. Cloud Piercer didn’t have much health left. If he was able to land this sort of attack, it would be his win.

But Fang Rui didn’t realize that there was actually a small opening in the cover provided by the NPCs.

The opening was very small, perhaps enough for a single bullet to go through. But it was an opening that Cloud Piercer could use.

Bang!

A gunshot.

Zhou Zekai saw this small opening. There was no time to hesitate. He immediately aimed and fired.

The bullet pierced through the crowd.

If he was just slightly off, the bullet would hit an NPC, and he wouldn’t be able to interrupt Boundless Sea’s attack.

But his aim was on point.

Pu!

Blood spurt out. A bullet pierced through this tiny opening, interrupting Boundless Sea’s attack. At the same time, it made it so that Boundless Sea wasn’t able to dodge an incoming NPC attack.

Perfect.

Cloud Piercer finally recovered from the Immobilization Talisman. But at this moment, light glowed from underneath his feet. A pillar of light shot towards the sky. Zhou Zekai hastily tried to get away, but he wasn’t able to.

Hexagram Prison!

A Warlock NPC’s attack.

If Zhou Zekai hadn’t been paying attention to Fang Rui, if he hadn’t needed to focus all his attention to attack through that small opening, perhaps he wouldn’t have overlooked such a powerful CC attack and would have instead had Cloud Piercer interrupt the Warlock’s cast.

Sure enough, things going too smoothly against Fang Rui wasn’t a good sign.

As Zhou Zekai thought about this, Cloud Piercer was swallowed by another wave of NPC attacks and was killed.

Group arena, fifth round, Fang Rui won!

Chapter 1662 - Fighting to Go First

In the end, Zhou Zekai lost.

Zhou Zekai had been Samsara's second player in the group arena. His first match was against Happy's first player, Ye Xiu, before finally falling to Happy's fourth player, Fang Rui. Even so, the fans on Samsara didn't feel satisfied. They felt that it was somewhat of a pity. They really thought that Zhou Zekai was playing well enough to pull off a 1v4. Unfortunately, he ended up losing to Fang Rui.

"He got caught in the trap!"

The Samsara fans all had the same thought. Fang Rui was truly too cunning. Just take a look at the post-fight numbers!

Cloud Piercer had started the fight with 45% of his health, and how much damage did Boundless Sea deal? 13%.

What did this mean? It meant that Cloud Piercer had lost 32% of his health to NPCs.　　

An unfair advantage!

The Samsara fans were furious, choosing to forget about Zhou Zekai's fight with Mo Fan.

In that fight, the post-fight statistics showed that Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer only dealt a total of 23% of Deception's health. The other 77% had been lost to NPCs.

Under similar circumstances, players would always take advantage of what they could. It was just that in the Zhou Zekai vs Mo Fan match, the situation allowed for Zhou Zekai to more easily suppress his opponent.

In the Fang Rui versus Zhou Zekai match, what Fang Rui needed to do was far more complicated. As a result, even though the outcome was the same, it seemed much more difficult for Fang Rui to achieve. It was hard not to have a different impression of the fight. Fans would always be in defense of their idols. For Samsara's fans, it was almost to the point of shedding tears for his grievances.

But after seeing Zhou Zekai walk out from the player booth, everyone immediately stood up and applauded crazily.

Even though it was too bad that it wasn't a 1v4, it was still a 1v3. It was still an unprecedented achievement in the finals. Another brushstroke was added to Zhou Zekai's name in the history books.

Zhou Zekai didn't look to talk, but he wasn't like Mo Fan, who would completely ignore everyone else. As the fans cheered his name, he waved his hands towards them as he walked down from the stage.　

The players on Samsara also stood up and applauded to welcome their captain back. They were tired of praising him at this point and actually started complaining.

"You're so fierce, what's there left for us to do?"

"So you can take care of the team competition by yourself, right?"

"Haha." Zhou Zekai just laughed, but he didn't say anything. Everyone stopped joking around and quickly began discussing who to send for the next fight.

"My turn!" Lu Boyuan volunteered to go up. In the previous team competition, he and Du Ming had tried to pincer Fang Rui in an alleyway, but Du Ming ended up being the one trapped there. At that time, he could only watch helplessly as his friend was killed. He had already been holding it in by then. Later on in the team competition, he and Fang Minghua had been stalled by Fang Rui alone for an unbelievable amount of time.

Fang Minghua was a healer, who needed to be protected by him. But let alone push away Fang Rui, he hadn't even been able to get Fang Minghua's Laughing Song to escape.

He had lost badly to Su Mucheng in the previous group arena too. Lu Boyuan knew that he had been a huge reason for Samsara's defeat last game.

During these two days, Lu Boyuan would often think about his time in Season 8. That season's final had been the pinnacle of his professional career. Through his incredible plays, he helped Samsara take down Blue Rain to win the team their first championship trophy. After that final, Lu Boyuan's spot as a top player and an All-Star had been established.

But now?

His Chaotic Cloudy Mountains had even better stats than before. At that time, when speaking of Glory's number one Grappler, it wasn't him, but Tiny Herb's Flying Drops. Later on, in order to help strengthen his Chaotic Cloudy Mountains, the team purchased the famous Flying Drops and dismantled him for his equipment...　

Lu Boyuan's character had gotten stronger, more famous, but why was he playing worse?

Why?

Was it because his desire for victory wasn't as great as before?

Was it because he had gotten complacent after winning two championships?

No, definitely not!

He wanted more championship victories, more Glory. How could just two be enough?

Lu Boyuan burned with fighting spirit. Seeing Fang Rui on stage, his thirst for battle was stronger than ever.

He wasn't the only one who wanted to go up.

Du Ming had been playing spectacularly last game, but he ended up losing to Fang Rui in the group arena. The team competition had been even more frustrating. Seeing Fang Rui on stage, he wanted revenge. Plus, after beating Fang Rui, Happy's next player should be that person, no?

Thinking of this, Du Ming started getting impatient. Lu Boyuan had just said that he wanted to go, when Du Ming interrupted: "My turn, my turn."

"My turn!" Lu Boyuan glared at Du Ming.

"Me me me!" Du Ming ignored him. Who played next wouldn't be decided by just the two of them. He wasn't going to bicker with Lu Boyuan. Du Ming looked eagerly towards his captain, vice-captain, and even Fang Minghua. The people with the most authority on the team was their captain and vice-captain, of course, but number three wasn't the talented Sun Xiang nor their other All-Star, Lu Boyuan, but Fang Minghua. Although he was the least famous among Samsara's main roster, he was the most senior member in Samsara.

He had started in Season 4, a part of the Golden Generation.

That season had too many astonishingly talented rookies, overshadowing many other excellent rookies.

Fang Minghua had been one of the "nobodies" of Season 4. He had joined Samsara and became a part of the main roster. In the blink of an eye, seven years had passed. The radiance of the geniuses of the Golden Generation shined brighter than ever, Huang Shaotian, Yu Wenzhou, Zhang Xinjie, Chu Yunxiu, Su Mucheng, Li Xuan.... who hadn't heard of them? Yet for all their fame, who among those in that generation had the most championships wins, the greatest glory of them all?

Within these seven years, the Season 4 players who had won the most championships as main roster players weren't Huang Shaotian, or Zhang Xinjie, or Chu Yunxiu.

It was Li Yihui. It was Fang Minghua.

Li Yihui had been considered a member of the Golden Generation, an All-Star player, winning two championships together with Tiny Herb. But he ended up being the first among the Golden Generation to fall. After transferring to Team 301, he completely lost his luster. Within two seasons, he quickly became one of the forgotten.

But Fang Minghua wasn't a member of the Golden Generation. He had been a "mediocre rookie" in Season 4, but he was the one who got the last laugh. As the healer, he won two consecutive championships in Season 8 and Season 9. He was on his way towards the team's and his third championship win.

He wasn't as famous as those in the Golden Generation, but as Samsara's healer for seven years, his seniority in the team wasn't low. Because apart from just being there for seven years, his contributions towards Samsara were well-received.

He had been the one to strongly recommend Zhou Zekai to Team Samsara. He had believed that Zhou Zekai was a player who could not be let go no matter the cost. At that time, Samsara's Sharpshooter was their captain, Zhang Yiwei, and he wasn't nearly as confident in Zhou Zekai's potential. It was under Fang Minghua's relentless insistence that Samsara made the decision to take Zhou Zekai. There were even rumors that his firm stance made Samsara's captain Zhang Yiwei extremely displeased with him. However, Zhou Zekai soon proved that Fang Minghua's opinion hadn't been an overstatement.

In Season 6, when Fang Minghua recommended Jiang Botao, the team highly valued his opinion. That winter transfer season, they decisively purchased Jiang Botao. And once again, Fang Minghua had found another incredible player for Samsara.

This "mediocre rookie" of Season 4 had helped the team wholeheartedly. He had seniority. He had contributed much to the team through great efforts, but he never showed off. He wasn't the captain. He wasn't the vice-captain. But no one on Samsara would ever disregard his opinions.

And he had always done his utmost from beginning to end. He hadn't changed these seven years. Even if he offended the captain and the core player, he would never give up on his viewpoint. If he had a recommendation, he would never hide it.

"I think Lu Boyuan should go!" Fang Minghua said.

Chapter 1663 - 3, Three Percent

Fang Rui sat in the player booth, quietly waiting for his next opponent.

I won!

And it was against Zhou Zekai. He had ended Zhou Zekai’s win streak. To many, Fang Rui had already done something worthy of pride.

But Fang Rui wasn’t satisfied.

Zhou Zekai? So what? Did beating him mean that they had won the finals? No. Not only did it not guarantee them the championship trophy, it didn’t even guarantee them the group arena.

To Fang Rui, Zhou Zekai was just Samsara’s second player in the group arena. Yes, he was formidable and difficult to defeat, but more importantly, after him was Samsara’s third player. If he beat him, it would only be another small step towards victory. There were even more obstacles that needed to be passed!

What was there to be happy about? He was still far from being happy or proud!

Next!

His goal was to beat the next one. After that, it would be the next next one, and then the next next next one.

His thirst for victory would never falter. It was only by constantly beating the next person would he be able to stand on the final podium.

So who’s next! Come!

The next one came.

Samsara’s third player was Lu Boyuan.

In the end, Samsara went with Fang Minghua’s recommendation. All of Team Samsara trusted him deeply. This didn’t mean that he held the most authority on the team, or that he was taking advantage of his contributions to the team. It was the exact opposite. Everyone respected that he never made a display of these two points. He was someone who always judged the matter as it stood, using reasoning to persuade others.

Lu Boyuan had his wish fulfilled. He had been overjoyed at having the opportunity to go on stage, but he quickly calmed himself down. By the time he made it to the player booth and loaded into the game, he had let reason take over him.

The match officially began.

One side was a Qi Master, the other side was a Grappler. This was a battle between two Fighters.

Lu Boyuan’s Grappler, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain, came in full of energy. As for Fang Rui’s Qi Master, Boundless Sea? Even though he had won against Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer, he had lost 47% of his health left. He still had 53% left.

After all, Boundless Sea had been under pressure from the NPCs the entire time. It was impossible for him not to have lost any health in the process, yet he had won under these conditions. It was true that it was intentional, but it still made everyone look at him with a whole new level of respect. If they had been the ones playing, would they have been able to do it?

However, for this match, it didn’t look like Fang Rui planned on doing the same thing. After the match began, his Boundless Sea charged out.

Beat his opponent, and then move onto the next one!

Fang Rui only had this one thought. He knew clearly that he wouldn’t be able to do much more in today’s decisive game.

Even though he had only been against someone with 45% of his health left in the previous fight, it had exhausted him.

The strategy that he had chosen had increased the weight of the burden on him. Whether it was his character’s health or his own energy, the chaotic battle that he had placed himself in was much more exhausting than a normal one. His condition hadn’t been great to begin with either.

He felt the fatigue. He could feel his focus slipping, but he persisted. He had beaten Zhou Zekai, and now, he was going to beat his next opponent.

Because he knew that this would be his last fight this season. How far he could go would be how far he went. Today, he probably wouldn’t be able to fully recover. He probably wouldn’t be able to help the team in the more important team competition coming up.

Fang Rui was unsatisfied, extremely unsatisfied.

He was Happy’s highest paid player with Happy’s strongest character. He would never forget that. But when the team needed him the most, in their most crucial game of the season, he couldn’t help?

Fang Rui hated this feeling. He truly, truly loathed it.

But he couldn’t be rash.

He didn’t think about trying to persevere for the team competition.

Because from the start, he had known exactly how much he would be able to contribute in today’s match. He had originally planned on saving his energy in the group arena, and coming out in the more important team competition. But right now, he could no longer play at 100% for the team competition. He was afraid that he would instead become the team’s burden.

As a result, all that remained was the present, the group arena. How much he would be able to contribute would be how much he contributed. This here would be his everything.

The two characters met in the middle of the canyon.

Lu Boyuan was eager to battle. Fang Rui didn’t delay because he knew that his condition wouldn’t get any better with just a few seconds of rest. He wanted to do everything he could while he still had the ability to.

Forward!

Boundless Sea continued forward, but Chaotic Cloudy Mountain didn’t cower either.

The two sides grew nearer and nearer. As a Qi Master, he could have started attacking a while ago, but he didn’t.

He wasn’t planning on engaging in close combat, was he?

Of the four Fighter classes, Qi Masters were the weakest at close combat. On the other hand, Strikers and Grapplers held the top ranks among all the classes in Glory.

Fang Rui couldn’t possibly think about fighting up close. What was he scheming?

Everyone was thinking the same thing, including Lu Boyaun. A player like Fang Rui didn’t feel trustworthy. What you saw on the surface was always fake.

Lu Boyuan didn’t even dare to blink. He stared intently at the approaching enemy.

Roll!

Boundless Sea suddenly rolled.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountains hadn’t attacked. He wasn’t close enough, yet Boundless Sea looked as if he were dodging frantically.

The scheme is coming!

Everyone thought, including Lu Boyuan.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain immediately made a move. He jumped to the side. Who cared what Boundless Sea was scheming? Moving unpredictably would always be safe.

But Boundless Sea didn’t do anything. The roll just seemed to be a normal roll.

Lu Boyuan kept up his guard. Wasn’t it normal to see Fang Rui do something puzzling? He couldn’t be careless for even a second.

But he still had to try to take the initiative.

Lu Boyuan kept his guard up, while Chaotic Cloudy Mountain approached. Grapplers had to get up close to attack.

Boundless Sea rolled again. This time, it wasn’t forward, or to the left, or to the right, but backwards.

The broadcast and the stadium screens immediately zoomed in on Boundless Sea. Everyone thought that Fang Rui was definitely scheming something just like the last roll.

There hadn’t been anything last time.

But this time, Fang Rui didn’t let them down.

During his roll, Boundless Sea sneakily rubbed his palms together. Lu Boyuan couldn’t see it, but the spectators watching carefully could.

Everyone suddenly felt a moment of “I know what’s going to happen next”.

But even if they knew, it wouldn’t be of any use.

A Qi Blade flew out. Boundless Sea kept rolling, changing directions slightly.

How devious!

The spectators who noticed Boundless Sea’s sneaky Qi Blade immediately knew what Boundless Sea’s goal was.

His Qi Blade hadn’t been aimed towards Chaotic Cloudy Mountain, but with Boundless Sea changing direction, if Lu Boyuan followed along and chased after him, the Qi Blade would be perfect.

The Qi Blade and Boundless Sea’s change of direction had been linked together closely. The angle was even more dirty. If Lu Boyuan was watching his movements carefully, if Lu Boyuan kept up with his tempo and adjusted accordingly, the Qi Blade would be very very very easy to overlook.

So.

Was focusing too hard, reacting too fast, a mistake against Fang Rui?

Unfortunately for Lu Boyuan, he commited this “mistake.”

He had been eager to fight but he maintained his calm. He also made sure to be attentive and to react fast. He was playing incredibly well.

But that resulted in him getting hit.

Qi Blade!

He only noticed it when the attack landed. A mark from the Qi Blade appeared on Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s body.

Everyone felt sorry for Lu Boyuan. Qi Blade had a knockback. Lu Boyuan’s rhythm was interrupted, and the reason was because he was playing too well…

But everyone soon realized that Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s rhythm hadn’t been disrupted by the attack. The step he had been taking was the step he took.

Oh…

Everyone realized what it was.

Reinforced Iron Bones!

Lu Boyuan had already activated Reinforced Iron Bones. When the replay from his perspective was shown, it turned out that he indeed hadn’t seen that Qi Blade. Lu Boyuan had reacted too fast and adjusted too quickly. However, he had activated Reinforced Iron Bones earlier. He seemed to have predicted that he would definitely fall for Fang Rui’s dirty trick and get hit.

Hit me all you want, but don’t think that’ll stop my advance.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain marched forward resolutely. The Samsara crowd erupted with wild applause.

“3”

At this moment, the number “3” popped up in the public chat. The sender was Boundless Sea, Fang Rui.

3? What did that mean?

Everyone stared blankly at the number.

Was he intentionally making things mysterious again?

Ignore it! Kill him!!!

The crowd once again erupted into shouts.

It was 3%…

In the stadium, at a remote and inconspicuous corner, which wasn’t even considered a seat, there was a person standing there, watching the match. He saw through what the “3” meant. If someone looked back to see who he was, they would probably recognize him instantly. It was Lin Jingyan, who had announced his retirement after the semifinals.

Team Wind Howl’s Lin Jingyan, Team Tyranny’s Lin Jingyan, it didn’t matter what team he was on, or if he was retired, he was the person who understood Fang Rui the best.

3.

It was 3%. The damage that the Qi Blade had dealt was 3%.

Fang Rui was keeping track of his damage dealt. He was using this method to record how much he contributed to today’s match.

Chapter 1664 - It Ends Here

Roll, jump, crawl...

Fang Rui was like a fish in the water, moving around freely no matter how shameful it looked. Lu Boyuan's Chaotic Cloudy Mountain stepped forward with Reinforced Iron Bones active, but in the end, Fang Rui was able to escape. And after seeing that Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had activated Reinforced Iron Bones, he took advantage of it to throw out two skills without any concealment.

Reinforced Iron Bones was valuable for its Super Armor buff, and Super Armor was valuable for allowing the user to ignore incoming enemy attacks. If you dodged and hid yourself while using Reinforced Iron Bones, then you were wasting the Super Armor.

5.　

6.

More numbers appeared in the public chat from Fang Rui.

No one had thought anything of the previous "3", but after seeing this "5" and "6", people were finally beginning to catch on.

"Is he counting how much damage he's dealing?"

"How dirty!"

Everyone sighed. This time, even the pro players thought that Fang Rui was using his dirtiness to engage in a psychological battle: listing out every damage he dealt to increase the mental pressure on his opponent.　

It obviously wasn't wrong to think this, and it was indeed something Fang Rui would do. But today, it wasn't actually his intention. He was simply using it as a way to remind himself, to keep himself focused.　　

Soon afterwards, two more attacks landed on Chaotic Cloudy Mountain. The number jumped to 9. His attacks weren't anything special. He was taking advantage of the fact that Lu Boyuan wouldn't give up on trying to take the initiative with Reinforced Iron Bones activated.

If you want to give up, I'll help you give up. But if you don't, then sorry, I won't keep you company.

Five attacks had dealt 9%. But Lu Boyuan's Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had closed the distance considerably. Fang Rui wasn't greedy. He immediately stopped attacking and focused on running away.

Suddenly, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain flickered, closing the distance at an extraordinary speed.

Cloud Body!

Many of the viewers immediately thought of this movement skill. It was the Striker's movement skill, Cloud Body, and the skill that Lu Boyuan had placed on his weapon.

The skill placed on a pro player's weapon wasn't easy to predict. Since there was no way to guard against it, its first usage in a match would always be extremely effective.

Relying on this surprise move, the bit of distance between them was instantly closed. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's two hands reached out to grab Boundless Sea.

In the previous moment, Boundless Sea had been focused on escaping. In the next moment, he suddenly turned around and threw out a palm.

The attack was too fast, too close. It couldn't be dodged, but Lu Boyuan didn't care too much. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain still had Reinforced Iron Bones active. That sort of instinctive attack wouldn't be able to stop him.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's two hands went for the grab, when his body suddenly lifted into the air.

Qigong Blast!

It had just seemed to be an instinctive counterattack, but it turned out to be the Qi Master's Level 70 skill, Qigong Blast. The qi surged through Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's body and wreaked havoc inside. The leather armor on him seemed like it was about to split apart from the outward pressure.

A Level 70 skill couldn't be used so easily. Fang Rui had planned this ahead of time. He had pretended to run away, but in actuality, he had been waiting for Chaotic Cloudy Mountain to come. He didn't care if Chaotic Cloudy Mountain used a movement skill like Cloud Body. No matter what happened, Lu Boyuan would want to get close to him as fast as possible. This point would never be wrong.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was hit.

However, even Qigong Blast couldn't break through Super Armor. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was able to get a hold of Boundless Sea in the end.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain lifted Boundless Sea up and tossed him into the air, the low-level skill Fling. The grabs had begun. However, at the same time, his Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's health slid down by a large chunk. Reinforced Iron Bones only increased the user's physical defense. However, Qi Master attacks dealt magic damage. The defense buff from Reinforced Iron Bones was useless.

18.

Boundless Sea had been tossed into the air, but Fang Rui was still counting. The damage from this Level 70 skill dealt more damage than the previous five attacks combined.

However, the one with the initiative was Lu Boyuan.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain threw Boundless Sea around like a doll. At the same time, he also reported his damage numbers in the public chat.

3, 6, 11, 15.

Four skills, four numbers. Grappler skills were powerful. These four skills dealt nearly as much damage as a Qi Master's five attacks plus a Level 70 skill. He wasn't done yet either.　

Spiralling Whirlwind!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain ended his Grappler combi with a Level 70 skill. Due to the high grab priority, Fang Rui had no way to escape it. Boundless Sea spun in the air as he crashed to the ground with a boom that echoed through the canyon.　

25!!

Lu Boyuan reported another number. This was the total damage dealt from a single combo, far more than the 18% that Boundless Sea had bitterly built up.

This was a Grappler.

Due to the high priority of grabs, if a Grappler could get a single attack to land, the opponent would find it nearly impossible to escape. Grapplers never had long combos, but each attack was extremely powerful. No other class had this sort of consistency in their combos.

After the final hit, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain jumped away.

Fang Rui had seen through Lu Boyuan's intentions and racked up damage, even getting in a Level 70 attack. But so what?

In the end, he hadn't been able to control the situation. After the fierce Grappler combo, Lu Boyuan was the one who had the advantage. Lu Boyuan had hit back, taking out 25% of Boundless Sea's health. If Fang Rui had been trying to put pressure on his opponent by reporting the damage that he dealt, then it had the opposite effect. With such a powerful counterattack from Lu Boyuan, the one feeling the pressure would be Fang Rui.

The dirty method backfired. For the Samsara fans, it was a joyous scene. Pan Lin and Li Yibo also praised Lu Boyuan's counterattack. The spectating pro players all felt that compared to the 25% health lost, the pressure from this counterattack was even more terrifying.

Boundless Sea started rolling around on the ground again. He didn't stand up. He just continued to roll.　　

Fang Rui had started his annoying and unsightly movements again.

Qi Bullet!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain easily dodged it.　

Cloud Pushing Palm...

Cloud Splitting Palm...

Skills poured out. Fang Rui was practically playing the cooldown game, using all sorts of weak, low-level skills. These skills had low cooldowns and fast start-ups. With so many attacks being thrown out, it indeed wasn't easy to defend against.

But so what if it was hard to defend against?

A Qi Bullet hit Chaotic Cloudy Mountain. The qi exploded, but his momentum wasn't impacted at all. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain continued to search for an opportunity to get close to Boundless Sea.

19.　

Another number in the public chat.

After a long struggle, Fang Rui was able to get in a single Qi Bullet, but it had practically zero effect on the battle, dealing only 1%.

But Fang Rui recorded it anyways.

Even with this 1%, he had only dealt a total of 19%, still not enough to catch up to Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's 25%. However, Fang Rui didn't seem to have noticed the 25% he took. He was still carefully keeping track of his damage.

21.

After some more back and forth, he finally got another two percent.

He didn't feel any pressure from Lu Boyuan's counterattack. The only thing on his mind was his own numbers. Even when Lu Boyuan had typed out 3, 6, 11, 15, 25 during the Grappler combo, Fang Rui was only looking at the 18. The number that Lu Boyuan had surpassed in one combo.

19, 21...

Fang Rui carefully and patiently increased this number. There was nothing else on his mind.

24, 28...　　

25 had been passed, but the thought never crossed Fang Rui's mind because he hadn't even seen the 25.

31...　　

Another successful hit.

The stadium was silent.　　

In everyone's eyes, the attacks from Fang Rui couldn't be considered as an offensive play. One attack would just be one attack.

This sort of mindless fighting was too amateurish in the eyes of the pro players. But this amateurish fighting was actually frustrating Lu Boyuan. For Lu Boyuan, he couldn't read Fang Rui. Lu Boyuan's intuition and experience couldn't be used against this sort of strategy.

Fang Rui's playing was pure and simple.

Tactics? Schemes? Psychological warfare? All of these things had been tossed out by him because he didn't have the energy to think about any of it.

After 31, 32.

Another 1% damage. Fang Rui counted it.　　

It was a strategy with no thought to it, and it felt deeply oppressive. Lu Boyuan's Chaotic Cloudy Mountain chased after Boundless Sea fiercely, but he just couldn't grab him. All of a sudden, Boundless Sea would nick him with a tiny poke.

Everyone was staring intently at Chaotic Cloudy Mountain' two hands, waiting for them to grab Boundless Sea, but that moment never happened. Finally, the NPCs on the two ends spawned and began charging towards each other!

None of the two characters were the focus of the NPCs, but it was hard not to be implicated in their battle.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain and Boundless Sea were dodging the NPC attacks, but as they dodged, they would constantly be looking for openings to attack.

35!

Amidst the chaos, Fang Rui was able to land an attack.

The chaos also increased the number of variables being changed. In the end, Lu Boyuan was able to find an opening.

"29!!!"

He typed out the total damage dealt after this blow, but this time, because of interference from the NPCs, he wasn't able to continue the combo.　

Boundless Sea was thrown to the ground, not crashing into any NPCs. Lu Boyuan had done this on purpose. The two had been entangled in the battle between the NPCs for a while. Each of them had gotten in a blow on the other, but neither of them had aggroed the NPCs.

From this perspective, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had the advantage. Grappler attacks had to be done at point blank range. It was practically impossible for him to accidentally hit an NPC. Boundless Sea was different, though. Qi Masters had quite a few mid-ranged attacks. His situation was very similar to Zhou Zekai's situation last round. Fang Rui wanted to attack Lu Boyuan, but he also didn't want to hit an NPC. Fighting from a distance was harder than fighting up close, and compared to Chaotic Cloudy Mountain, Boundless Sea was fighting from a distance.

Even so, Fang Rui was still proactive. Boundless Sea weaved in and out through the NPC crowd, searching for an opportunity. Lu Boyuan thought that he had the upper hand. He had even been afraid that Fang Rui would run away, although that never happened. Fang Rui's Boundless Sea was firmly locked onto him.

39!

Lu Boyuan made a careless mistake, and was hit by another attack from Boundless Sea. A new number appeared.

Does he want to count up to 100?　

It was still far from 100, but Lu Boyuan was certain. How could he know that 100 wasn't Fang Rui's goal? Fang Rui didn't have a fixed goal. The more the better.

41.

45.

47.

50.

50! Half his health!

Not a single attack made anyone feel like Fang Rui had the upper hand, but even so, he had already taken out half of Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's health. As for Lu Boyuan? After his powerful 25% counterattack, he was only able to get in one more 4% attack.

I'm being toyed with by Fang Rui again?

Lu Boyuan couldn't keep himself calm. In the end, he was a rather emotional player. When he was playing well, he could make explosive plays one after the other. But when he tilted, his playing would likely falter.

In today's match, he had strengthened his resolve. When he came on stage, he carefully sorted out this resolve, so he wouldn't be impulsive.

He had suppressed his emotions. He needed to be rational, calm. But Fang Rui's annoying strategy had truly made him lose his temper.

His emotions were in an awful state. He just wanted to vent, to explode with anger.

And when Fang Rui counted to 50, his base line was finally shattered.

Unable to endure it any longer, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain suddenly made a move.

Spiralling Whirlwind!

The Level 70 skill made its appearance again, but this time, Boundless Sea wasn't in his grasp. His hands grabbed nothing but air. The centripetal force generated from this attack would suck in nearby enemies, but Boundless Sea was a bit too far. With a roll, Boundless Sea escaped.

Lu Boyuan didn't stop, launching a group of NPCs into the air.　

Boom.　

Like a meteor, he crashed to the ground, spinning like a tornado. All the nearby NPCs were dragged into the whirlwind, falling down like raindrops.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had provoked the NPCs on both sides. Suddenly, all sorts of attacks were thrown towards him.　　

The attacks were aimed at Chaotic Cloudy Mountain, but they wouldn't purposefully avoid Boundless Sea.　　

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain dashed towards Boundless Sea.　　

Previously, he had to be careful to avoid the NPCs. This time, he wasn't going to avoid them anymore. Lu Boyuan was going to sweep aside any NPCs in his way.

Pa!

A Qi Bullet exploded.　

51.

Fang Rui counted again.　

Lu Boyuan threw all caution to the wind. As Chaotic Cloudy Mountain charged forward, he tossed every nearby NPC towards Boundless Sea. Fling, Spinning Throw, Back Throw... for a moment, he had turned into a long-ranged attacker. The NPCs nearby were his ammunition.

Boundless Sea ran. The incoming NPCs were blocked by other NPCs. Lu Boyuan had made things even more chaotic.

54.

Fang Rui was still calm, using every opportunity he saw to get in a hit.　

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain didn't waver.

Reinforced Iron Bones. He had activated it again. This time, he was really planning on just barging through everything in his path.　

A nearby NPC swung his sword at Chaotic Cloudy Mountain.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain didn't dodge. He leapt into the air.

Aerial Twist!

His two legs latched onto the NPC's neck. With a twist, the NPC was thrown into the air. Before the NPC landed, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain let go, and then latched onto another NPC's neck.

Circle Sweep Kick!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain held onto the NPC with one leg, and then twisted.

Boundless Sea suddenly appeared in front of him. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had used two NPCs as bridges to close the gap between himself and Boundless Sea.

Pa!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's head was whacked. Qi burst forth, Flash Burst!

But it couldn't break apart Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's Super Armor.

His health dropped, but Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had grabbed onto Boundless Sea.

Super Armor. He had Super Armor, and Boundless Sea still had 22% health. Amidst this chaos, Boundless Sea wasn't able to completely avoid any injuries.

22%!

No matter what, I have to take down that last 22%!

The qi burst out from Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's head as Boundless Sea was flung into the air.　　

He quickly looked around him.

The NPCs were attacking him non-stop, but with Reinforced Iron Bones active, he only feared CC skills that could break Super Armor.　

There were none!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain jumped, his health dropping rapidly.　　

There was NPC damage mixed in with that Flash Burst. But he didn't dodge any of the attacks. He reached out and grabbed the airborne Boundless Sea.

Fatal Air Drop!

Boundless Sea crashed to the ground.　　

But just two attacks wasn't enough to take out 22%.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain dropped down as Boundless Sea was thrown ruthlessly to the ground. After touching the ground, Boundless Sea bounced back into the air from the powerful impact.

At this moment, his character was no longer in a grabbed state, so Fang Rui quickly acted.

He couldn't move while in the air. All he could do was have Boundless Sea attack his opponent.

How much health does he have left?

Because Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was still taking damage from the NPC attacks, Fang Rui wasn't certain.　　

Spiral Qi Kill!

As Boundless Sea bounced into the air, he frantically sent out an attack.

A whirlwind of qi twisted towards the falling Chaotic Cloudy Mountain.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain didn't dodge. He couldn't dodge because he was also in the air.

He reached out with his hands and grabbed Boundless Sea.

Overhead Toss!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain twisted his arms and threw Boundless Sea back to the ground.　　

He fell, and Boundless Sea fell. But when he stood up, Boundless Sea was flat on the ground.

It wasn't over yet. Boundless Sea still had 2% of his health left. After his first grab onto Boundless Sea, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain remained close.

Overhead Toss into Ground Toss...

Boundless Sea was lifted into the air and then thrown to the ground.

Boundless Sea's health dropped to zero. Fang Rui was still staring at Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's health bar.

The moment Boundless Sea's health fell to zero, victory was decided, and Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's health was locked into place.

Fang Rui could finally see it clearly.

84.

84%.　

Keep going!　　

Fang Rui was still tapping his keyboard and moving his mouse, but he discovered that Boundless Sea could no longer be controlled. His screen was strange - it had turned gray.

Fang Rui stared blankly.

84%. So it ends here?

Chapter 1665 - For Victory

Won?

Lost?

The two players onstage were somewhat dazed.

Lu Boyuan had been extremely smug when he came up to battle, but the battle had unfolded vastly different from his expectations. He never thought that he would experience this kind of battle before. He won. He had finally cleaned out Boundless Sea’s 22% health. But his instincts still half-expected Boundless Sea to flip up in the next instant and scurry into the mass of NPCs, landing a skill upon Chaotic Cloudy Mountain in the next second out of nowhere.

He was still completely on alert. It wasn’t until GLORY flashed on his screen, until his camera view was changing, displaying his Chaotic Cloudy Mountain going through the various victory poses.

This was a moment that would normally inspire pride in any player. But right now, Lu Boyuan wasn’t feeling any of that. Even he couldn’t describe his current mood. He only stared at the screen, watching his Chaotic Cloudy Mountain finish the victory poses. The screen then exited the battle, and the wait for the next player began.

He won.

Next player.

Only now did Lu Boyuan suddenly have this kind of feeling. Only now did he suddenly feel like this victory was real.

Next player!

Lu Boyuan knew that he should already be paying attention to the transition to the next match, but his brain couldn’t stop. His mind was still flashing with the scenes from the match that had just ended. Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea seemed to be rolling once again…

Of course, Boundless Sea could no longer perform any rolls. Fang Rui stared at that grayed out world displayed after his character died for several seconds before finally standing up.

He walked out of the competitor booth. The stadium seemed very quiet. He looked at the large display screen: Lu Boyuan won, Fang Rui lost.

In the end, he’d still lost.

Fang Rui lowered his head and quietly walked offstage.

The stadium was quiet, and he was very quiet as well. This was unlike his usual self. Normally, he would be inflated with pride after victory, and after a loss he would adopt a “wise person reflecting a thousand times can still make a mistake” attitude.

What’s more, his performance today couldn’t be considered a loss at all. He had fallen to Lu Boyuan in the end, but before this, he had defeated Zhou Zekai, fiercely killed Samsara’s unstoppable momentum. The significance of this one victory was already extraordinary, and then afterwards, he had used 53% of Boundless Sea’s health to wipe away 84% of Lu Boyuan’s.

Even though there wasn’t much worth analyzing in this process, everyone saw one thing clearly: perseverance, perseverance toward victory.

Fang Rui, this dirty player, chased victory without ever looking back. This match he played might not have been pretty, it might not have been nice to look at, but this perseverance and pursuit reached people’s hearts.

Unfortunately, his perseverance was stopped by Lu Boyuan’s sudden explosiveness. Everyone felt the same as Lu Boyuan in his competitor booth, they still hadn’t recovered, their heads were still filled with the images of Boundless Sea rolling and weaving through the crowd of NPCs. It wasn’t pretty, but it left a deep impression.

In this silence, Fang Rui walked back to Happy’s player area. Everyone swarmed up to him, and he bravely forced out a smile. He in fact wanted to show off and act cool like he normally did, but after walking all the way back here, he suddenly felt like he didn’t even have the spirit to be dirty anymore.

Fang Rui sat back down in his seat, stretched his legs, stretched his arms. Chen Guo handed him a towel, and he leaned against the back of his chair and placed it over his face.

It was over…

It really felt like his competitive state had left him.

He had already done everything that he could. So why did he still feel so unsatisfied?

What “work hard and you’ll have no regrets”? Words like that were just to fool people, weren’t they? He still wanted to keep working hard. The team round hadn’t even been played yet!

The towel was cold, but Fang Rui felt like his covered eyes were burning hot.

Ding ding ding…

Suddenly he heard the alert of a text message. Fang Rui could tell that it was his phone. He truly was in no mood to check, but his teammates were right there, and ultimately, he didn’t want everyone to realize that he was acting strange. He wasn’t going to be able to play the team competition, but being unable to play, and not being sent to play, the difference between these things was still quite great.

As Fang Rui wiped the towel over his face, his other hand picked up his phone.

“The match isn’t over yet, and neither are you.”

Lin Jingyan.

This guy…

Fang Rui was stunned. He didn’t immediately look for Lin Jingyan, because he knew that even though this guy had already retired, he wouldn’t let Glory leave his line of sight so easily. No matter in what corner of the world he was now, he would be watching this match for sure.

But, that was all.

Because he had truly said goodbye to this all. Because for him, all of this was truly over.

Fang Rui had no reason to talk about anything being “over”!

Because the match was still ongoing, and his own professional career was still ongoing.

Fang Rui turned his head and watched Tang Rou walk onstage. This was already Happy’s final player, and Samsara, including the still-alive Lu Boyuan, still had three players left.

“Looks like we have to 1v3,” Fang Rui muttered.

“Yes, that’s the only way,” Ye Xiu said gravely, his arms folded.

1v3. Logically, a pro player could never expect a 1v3. They couldn’t set a 1v3 as a requirement for victory.

But right now, Happy’s players held this conviction. They didn’t hide their expectation in front of Tang Rou, because they knew that this woman would never be held back by pressure. Of Happy’s remaining players, if they had to choose one person who they thought could complete a 1v3, it would be her.

As she stepped onto the stage, Tang Rou breathed deeply.

1v3?

The reason she had been criticized harshly this entire season was related to this.

She was a bit embarrassed of how rash she had been initially, but no matter what, the greater the difficulty, the more she wanted to conquer it. This was the core of her character. 1v3 was a challenge that she always wanted to complete, but the team’s victory always came first. And right now, the team’s victory and whether or not she could complete a 1v3 were intrinsically tied together. This overlap lifted Tang Rou’s battle spirit even more.

Seventh round of the group arena. Happy’s fifth player Tang Rou against Samsara’s third player Lu Boyuan.

The match began.

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist immediately charged forward.

This had always been her style, and Lu Boyuan’s Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was only at 16% health right now, so there was even less reason for her to hesitate or stall.

By now, Lu Boyuan had finally walked out of previous battle.

Tang Rou, Soft Mist.

He saw the player he was about to face. This wasn’t a meeting that deserved surprise. After the four previous players, leaving Tang Rou to anchor was an arrangement within expectations.

And Tang Rou’s style was very clear. She came onstage not just to knock down the opponent before her, but the one after, and the one after, her goal would forever be to kill all.

1v3. This was the crazy promise she had once made, and because she had failed it, her name was dragged through the mud.

And now, she was faced with a situation where victory required her to complete a 1v3.

She must be very excited!

Lu Boyuan could think of this point.

Because he and the rest of the pro players could tell, this girl aimed for a 1v3 not to prove how strong she was, but because she simply enjoyed this kind of challenge. That was only the regular season, and there were only three players in the group arena, so a 1v3 was the most that could be done. If the regular season group arena had five players, no one would find it strange if this girl shouted a 1v5.

Many people thought there was something wrong in her head, yet many others felt that this was an honest courage.

1v3, 1v5, these were viewed as difficult, nigh impossible. But every pro player had dreamed or imagine of completing such a thing.

But they would only think about it, they wouldn’t hold any serious hopes toward it. Yet Tang Rou treated this as a challenge, and worked hard to try and fulfill it.

However, right now, she was fighting for her team’s victory, a higher and more responsible goal. It wasn’t like before, where she had been fighting for a careless promise.

1v3!

In this moment, Tang Rou didn’t think at all about that previous promise. All she thought of was victory!

For victory, Soft Mist charged forward.

Chapter 1666 - Don’t Cry, Lu Boyuan

16%.

Lu Boyuan looked at the health remaining on Chaotic Cloudy Mountain.

There wasn't much health left, but he couldn't retreat. He knew what target Tang Rou was charging toward, and he was determined to strike at her head-on.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain rushed forth. At the center of the canyon, the two characters met. Tang Rou's style was always to charge without hesitation, and her common starting move was the powerful attack Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

Lu Boyuan had memorized all of this, and as soon as Soft Mist appeared in his view, he was already bracing himself. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain no longer traveled in a straight line, and instead began to advance in an unpredictable roundabout way, to prevent Soft Mist from breaking through with a single Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

It seemed like Tang Rou didn't care about that much. Soft Mist's movement was as straight as ever, but her camera view was tracking Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's nonstop movement, keeping him in the center of her field of view.

He had chosen this kind of roundabout movement for two reasons. One was to prevent Tang Rou from using her normal method of Dragon Breaks the Ranks, and the other was that this was a common method of closing in on the opponent.

Compared to Gunners and other Mages, Battle Mages and Grapplers were both close-range attackers. But comparing a Battle Mage and a Grappler, there was still a difference in their attack ranges.

The attack range of a Grappler was basically the length of a character's arms, within two units of distance. As for Battle Mages? Their attack range included not only the length of their arms but the length of their weapon. With that, their attack range could reach a max of five or even six units. So to Grapplers, Battle Mages were also long-range attackers. Breaking through that six-unit range to get to two units, completing the close-in, was a difficult problem to solve.

Grappler's skills tended to focus on pure damage. Not including the skills of the other Fighter classes, there was basically no way to restrict, control, or distract the opponent. Movement was the most realistic way.

Today, Lu Boyuan had chosen to put the skill Cloud Body on Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's weapon. It strengthened his movement ability.

The two characters moved closer and closer, gradually nearing a distance of ten units.

Tang Rou had held back on Dragon Breaks the Ranks. Right now, with just a few more steps, she could directly initiate attack.

Lu Boyuan suddenly changed the rhythm of Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's movement. Originally, he had been moving around 70% vertically and 30% horizontally. But with a sharp turn, his horizontal movement suddenly changed to 80%, and his vertical advance was only at 20%.

Instantly, the speed at which the two characters were approaching slowed down. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain, using a large horizontal movement, was swiftly moving to flank Soft Mist.

Ordinary gamers might not have been able to detect much, but in the eyes of the pros, this was an extremely old and clever way of using a rhythm change to create a time disparity.

Once Tang Rou had gotten accustomed to the approach speed of the opponent, if the opponent suddenly changed speed and direction, her reaction would be slowed by a half a beat or a beat.

When close-range classes fought, they needed to take the initiative. One beat or half a beat, that was enough to separate who was faster and who was slower.

Lu Boyuan seized the initiative!

The angle of attack chosen after changing the rhythm was also chosen very well. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain cut into Soft Mist's attack range, but Tang Rou's field of view couldn't keep up. She hastily spun, but she was too slow, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was right next to her, but she couldn't catch him in her sights. She was only off by that half-beat.

Take the lead first!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was already reaching a hand toward Soft Mist.

But a streak of red light suddenly swept across his waist!

Tyrant's Destruction!

Soft Mist's sight hadn't arrived, but her attack had.

Just when Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was about to grab Soft Mist, he was sent flying by this Tyrant's Destruction.

Slow by half a beat?

Yes, she was slow.

But this half-beat slow wasn't because Tang Rou's reaction was slow. It wasn't because she had fallen into the trap laid by Lu Boyuan's sudden change in rhythm.

She was slow by half a beat because she hadn't used her vision to chase Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's movement. She had instead opted to directly control Soft Mist to use an attack.

The control and launch of a Tyrant's Destruction would always be a bit slower than turning one's camera.

This was where the delay had come from.

But in the end, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was sent flying.

Falling Flower Palm!

Soft Mist slid and forced a palm out, toward the flying Chaotic Cloudy Mountain. With a boom, the palm hit, sending Chaotic Cloudy Mountain flying out even faster, toward the canyon wall behind him. After the Falling Flower Palm hit, the Fire Chaser it generated shot toward him and exploded against him, swallowing him in a burst of red fire.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain took even more damage. Soft Mist's arms were already wreathed in the strength buff granted by the Fire Chaser, and Soft Mist charged forward, Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Dancing Fire Flowing Flame was instantly in front of Chaotic Cloudy Mountain. Soft Mist didn't reduce her momentum. Forward, continue forward.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's back finally slammed against the canyon wall, sending a boom echoing through the canyon. It was clear how forceful the blow had been. But his path didn't stop there – his body actually continued to sink into the mountain wall, leaving a hole into the stone.

Dancing Fire Flowing Flame had already completely penetrated Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's body. Right now, she was extremely close to the other character, at a distance of only one unit. For a Grappler, this was the optimal attack distance.

But Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's arms were stuck on both sides of his body, he had no way of lifting them. No matter how fast Lu Boyuan's hand speed was, no matter how high his technique, no matter how strong his willpower, no matter how great his determination, he couldn't.

His health reached zero. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain died.

Tyrant's Destruction, Falling Flower Palm, Fire Chaser, Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

Four attacks surpassed the 16% damage needed to end the life of Lu Boyuan's Chaotic Cloudy Mountain.

Victory was decided. The winner, Happy's Tang Rou.

The stadium hadn't even reacted yet. In the broadcast, Pan Lin and Li Yibo's analysis of Lu Boyuan's clever rhythm change came to an abrupt stop.

What more was there to analyze? Lu Boyuan's Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was already dead. Victory was already announced.

No one had really expected Lu Boyuan to win with Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's remaining 16% health, but this loss was a bit too quick and neat, wasn't it?

The stadium was quiet for a while, until finally, the cheers and applause of Happy's fans rose up from a corner of the stadium.

Samsara's fans seemed to be at a loss. They didn't know how they should respond to the cheers of the opposing fans. Tang Rou's clean victory had left them speechless.

Happy's cheers resounded in Samsara's stadium for quite a while before finally being suppressed by the random noisemakers of Samsara's fans. They could only take advantage of their numbers, because right now, they didn't have any unified slogan to shout. They couldn't stand up together and yell "don't cry Lu Boyuan," right?

Chapter 1667 - Who's Better

Lu Boyuan came down from the stage.

His performance today couldn’t be considered terrible, but it wasn’t great either. All he did was beat Fang Rui, who only had 53% of his health left. His match against Tang Rou was no different than getting instant killed.

Samsara still had the lead, though. The Samsara fans weren’t angry at him. There was still applause, encouragement for his efforts.

This couldn’t cover up the fact that Lu Boyuan’s condition wasn’t at its peak.

He had played poorly in the previous game. In today’s game, he had been brimming with resolve, but his performance was much worse than he had expected.

What’s going on?

Lu Boyuan felt like he had lost direction. He couldn’t seem to get into the right mentality.

He walked back to his seat quietly. Facing the comforting from his teammates, he could only squeeze out a smile.

The match continued. Du Ming was all ready to go. Before he went onto the stage, he couldn’t help but glance at the players on Happy’s side. Of course, he didn’t see the person he was looking for.

Because she was on stage!

Du Ming was getting excited. He had been waiting for this opportunity for a long time, and today, it had finally come.

Du Ming hadn’t forgotten his previous exchange with Tang Rou. It had been a very short one, though, so there wasn’t much to recall.

In that exchange, he had been distracted, thinking about other things. On the other hand, Tang Rou had been completely focused on the match, demolishing him.

Du Ming felt extremely ashamed.

He had let down the team, and let down such a rare opportunity.

That was why he had been hoping for a second chance. He had to have another try. He had to focus on the match, and complete a brilliant conversation by winning.

Du Ming walked onto the stage and into the player booth.

The eighth round of the group arena began. Samsara’s Du Ming versus Happy’s Tang Rou.

The map loaded. The characters loaded.

Charge!

Soft Mist, Moon Luring Frost.

The two players didn’t hesitate and immediately rushed forward. Soon, the two would meet at the center of the canyon.

Neither of them paused to take a rest. The two were both charging towards each other.

Sword raised, spear out, clash!

The sound of their weapons colliding echoed through the canyon. The two started their attack at practically the same time. Then, both of them adjusted their attacks. In the end, when their weapons collided, it became one of them attacking, while the other parrying.

The second, third, and fourth attacks followed!

Both players were playing fast. It was an intense confrontation as soon as the fighting began.

“He’s playing well.”

On Samsara’s side, everyone was paying attention to Du Ming’s performance. They were very pleased with his playing.

“His dream’s come true. How could he not be playing well?” Fang Minghua laughed.

Everyone nodded their heads. Du Ming was playing exceptionally well this finals. It was clearly related to their opponents being Team Happy.

This time, Du Ming wasn’t as distracted as last time. He had turned these distractions into motivation. As a result, he was always able to perform at his best. That was why Samsara was at ease sending him out onto the stage.

And now, he was fighting Tang Rou on stage once again. He didn’t think about their encounter the last time, or the time before that, or the first time.

In his eyes, there was only the match in front of him. In his heart, there was only victory.

He became extremely focused. It was perhaps the most focused he’d ever been in his entire professional career.

Openings that he usually wouldn’t be able to see were clear as day to Du Ming right now.

He saw the tiniest of openings and took it.

Downwind Sword Slash!

The sharp sword wind came out of the blue. A split suddenly appeared in the tight battle. Tang Rou could only have Soft Mist hastily raise her spear to parry with a normal attack, but it couldn’t resist the powerful force from Downwind Sword Slash. Her spear, Dancing Fire Flowing Flame, was knocked aside. Soft Mist was already retreating, but she couldn’t escape from the sword slash!

Blood flew into the air, splashing onto the sword light.

Tang Rou did the best she could to defend against the attack and reduce the damage she took.

But the previous equilibrium had been broken. Sword light flashed, Triple Slash!

Moon Luring Frost suddenly appeared by Soft Mist’s side. This was only the second slash from Triple Slash.

“Amazing!” The expert Blade Master, Huang Shaotian, couldn’t help but give a shout of praise. The attack, distance, angle, and timing, all of it had been perfect. It was impossible to dodge this attack. It didn’t matter how fast Tang Rou reacted, it couldn’t be done.

Another injury was added. Du Ming had the initiative. Sword light flashed, mercilessly flying towards Soft Mist.

The Samsara fans were excited. The previous gloom had been swept away. Du Ming looked as unstoppable as Zhou Zekai!

They began waving their arms and shouting, cheering for Du Ming.

“One wave kill!!!”

They shouted. It would be the greatest response to Lu Boyuan getting dismantled last round.

But…

“One wave…”

By the second word of the second shout, they had to stop.

Soft Mist pointed her spear towards the sky. With a Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart, she stopped Moon Luring Frost’s advance.

Even the pro players were dumbstruck. They discovered that they could no longer predict who would win this match. No one knew what the two on stage could do. They were both playing well beyond themselves. Du Ming was playing incredibly well, but Tang Rou was playing even better. She had been suppressed by Du Ming’s offense, yet just when everyone was wondering how she would be able to get out, she used one attack to turn things around, and start her counterattack.

This wasn’t normal.

This wasn’t something that could be explained through logic.

The stadium screens showed a replay of the Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart, but even the pro players furrowed their brows in thought. How was she able to pull off the attack? How was she able to achieve the outcome she got?

The match wouldn’t stop because they were thinking. Now, it was Tang Rou’s turn to be on the offensive, and Du Ming’s turn to defend. Du Ming had the upper hand before, but in an instant, Tang Rou took it from him.

Du Ming didn’t panic. He calmly observed the situation.

His offensive had been cut off. No worries! Just get it back!

Du Ming’s thoughts were simple but determined. At this moment, he wasn’t thinking of anything else. Even though he was playing well because of Tang Rou, he wasn’t distracted by her. All of his attention was on how to win this battle.

Facing the fiery assault from Soft Mist’s Dancing Fire Flowing Flame, Moon Luring Frost fought back with his Lingering Ice, a clash between fire and ice.

He was only defending, but he would always strike at the most critical time, like a fireman staving off a fire.

He was waiting for an opening.

He didn’t know when the opening would come, but he knew that it would come eventually.

Formless Phantom Blade!

His sword, Lingering Ice, suddenly split apart. Du Ming’s patience was finally about to be rewarded. He seized an opening, and used the Level 70 Formless Phantom Blade.

Sword light weaved into a net, enshrouding Soft Mist.

Her offense was suddenly put to an abrupt stop.

But Soft Mist didn’t retreat!

If her offense had been broken, then just start another one.

Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike!

Soft Mist also used a high-level skill. Her spear blurred into countless afterimages. Tang Rou focused the attacks towards a single direction to clash with Moon Luring Frost’s Formlesse Phantom Blade.

The sounds of collisions rang endlessly.

Under the inconceivable microing by the two players, neither side was able to gain the upper hand.

But the experts had noticed that this balance wouldn’t last forever.

Because there would be a final hit!

Formless Phantom Blade had a final strike. It was the skill’s most powerful strike, dealing high damage and having high priority, knocking the target flying back. On the other hand, Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike didn’t have such a tyrannical effect.

Because of this final strike, Formless Phantom Blade’s attack priority would reach a height that Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike couldn’t contest with. Moreover, Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike would end before Formless Phantom Blade dealt its final blow.

Who won this clash depended on how the two sides managed this final strike, and this moment was about to arrive!

Chapter 1668 - All Set-Up

Red and blue light clashed again and again. Just watching the flashing colors gave the viewers goosebumps. For a moment, the normal gamers didn’t know where to look. They simply watched in awe with their jaws wide open.

It’s here!

The experts knew where the key lay. Just when the collision between skills was about to end, all of them grew nervous and put their full attention toward the battle.

5, 4, 3, 2…

They had started counting down. The last collision between weapons was about to occur. Next would be the final strike. It had been a stalemate the entire time, but this next strike would end it.

She missed her parry?

But no one had thought that before the decisive strike, Tang Rou would slip up. Her Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike had failed to parry the Formless Phantom Blade’s sword slash. Blue light invaded her territory, and blood blossomed into the air.

Hit!

The second to last Formless Phantom Blade hit Soft Mist. Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike was interrupted. The red light glowing from Dancing Fire Flowing Flames dimmed.

The final slash, the strongest hit!

The sword light gave off its most resplendent light, flying towards Soft Mist’s head…

No blood. No knockback. The sword light was still as brilliant as ever. The sword light was still flying. Shock filled the faces of the ones who noticed what had happened.

The final slash, the strongest hit had missed?

Yes, the sword light missed. Soft Mist had retreated during this short window. She had actually ran away. She had always been fierce and domineering, but suddenly, it was as if someone else were playing. This sort of play had Fang Rui’s signature written all over it.

But in the next instant.

In the next moment, the next second, Soft Mist straightened back up and charged forward!

Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost was stuck in the end lag from Formless Phantom Blade. There was no way for him to resist…

How did things turn out like this?

The experts were no longer thinking about the ongoing battle. They couldn’t understand what had just happened. If you could escape one of Formless Phantom Blade’s strikes by taking the previous one, then the skill would be too flawed.

However, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had done it, and by taking the second to last hit, she dodged the final one. Then, the ending lag from the Formless Phantom Blade left the opponent with a huge opening.

The stadium screen immediately began showing a replay, starting from when the two skills clashed.

Once, twice…

The pro players could start to see the reason.

“Watch Soft Mist’s movements.”

“Her parries weren’t just to defend, but to guide…”

“Pay attention to the last one”

“The parry that she missed left an opening exactly where Tang Rou wanted him to attack.”

“Yes, taking the hit helped her get to the right position for the next one…”

“She had been setting it up bit by bit, and Du Ming didn’t notice it at all.”

“Not just Du Ming, did any of us catch it?”

Silence. From rookies to Gods, the ones who caught on the fastest were only able to catch it on the replay.

“Finally, she used the sort of micro-control that Fang Rui specializes in to dodge the final strike…”

“After that, counterattack…”

Yes, counterattack.

While the pro players were analyzing this play, Tang Rou had already started swinging her spear. Fang Rui’s dirty style had only appeared for an instant, then, it was back to her usual fierceness.

Due to being in a stunned state from the skill, Moon Luring Frost was in an even harder-to-break combo.

Du Ming didn’t understand why his Formless Phantom Blade’s final strike didn’t land. He didn’t have the time or resources to carefully analyze a replay like the pro players had done.

He needed to worry about the present. How could he get Moon Luring Frost out of Soft Mist’s combo, or find an opportunity to counterattack?

But Tang Rou wouldn’t give him any opportunities. She quickly reached the end of her combo. The combo had been so short that it felt rather wasteful.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

Battle magic transformed into a dragon and flew into the air. Moon Luring Frost was still under Soft Mist’s control, and couldn’t dodge this attack.

However, Du Ming let out a sigh of relief.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky was similar to Formless Phantom Blade. It had a long ending animation, so it couldn’t be comboed into anything. As for false combos, that depended on the situation. Moon Luring Frost was sent flying as one would expect. Du Ming didn’t see her setting-up any follow-ups.

Boom!

The Rising Dragon Soars the Sky ended, and the battle magic exploded. The glimmering light enshrouded Moon Luring Frost.

Soft Mist was stuck in the skill’s ending animation, but after Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost was hit by the attack, he wouldn’t be able to move immediately. The explosive battle magic still rippled with power.

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist finished retracting her spear and immediately attacked again.

Raise spear, charge!

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

That’s it?

Du Ming was somewhat surprised. Moon Luring Frost had already recovered. Because of the distance, dodging this Dragon Breaks the Ranks wouldn’t be difficult. Tang Rou’s impulsive usage of the skill would give him an opportunity to counterattack. Although Dragon Breaks the Ranks didn’t have a notable ending lag, if she missed, it was still quite a big opening.

There was no time to think. Du Ming had Moon Luring Frost dodge the attack. Although it wouldn’t be difficult, that was only from a pro player’s perspective. For a normal player, Tang Rou’s sudden Dragon Breaks the Ranks wouldn’t be so easy to react to.

Opportunity only came once.

Move to the side, counterattack!

Du Ming’s intentions were clear. After figuring out the timing, he made his move.

Move to the side, unsheath sword, and swing, all in one breath.

He turned and unsheathed his sword, but he unexpectedly wasn’t able to move to the side.

He looked to the side. In front of his eyes was a giant wall. A wall that was very very close to him. As a result, he wasn’t able to fully swing his sword. The sword light was blocked by the wall.

Du Ming stared blankly.

He had missed the timing. Soft Mist had arrived.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Her spear, Dancing Fire Flowing Flame, struck Moon Luring Frost. Du Ming felt himself getting pushed on both sides. His viewpoint began getting smaller and smaller.

A scene suddenly floated into Du Ming’s mind.

In the previous round, Lu Boyuan’s Chaotic Cloudy Mountains had been pinned to the wall by the Dragon Breaks the Ranks and was killed.

A hole the size of a person had remained in the wall. In the group arena, damage to the map would remain.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky had sent him into this hole. The exploding battle magic interfered with his sight, and pushed him even deeper.

At this moment, Dragon Breaks the Ranks…

Moon Luring Frost was sent even deeper. He was trapped inside the hole.

Left, right, retreat, jump?

He couldn’t.

There was only one direction: forward.

And forward was Soft Mist…

Chapter 1669 - The Boos of the Home Stadium

After the Rising Dragon Soars the Sky sent Moon Luring Frost flying, the audience could already see where he would be blasted. Du Ming, who was in the middle of the battle, was perhaps the last person to realize the situation. However, even though ordinary gamers could see it, they didn’t react so quickly. The pros were different – as soon as they saw the direction in which Moon Luring Frost was flying, they were caught off-guard for only a moment before quickly realizing that this was intentional.

What came next confirmed their hypotheses.

A pit that initially didn’t seem that deep. Alone, that wasn’t enough to limit a character’s movements. If Du Ming had detected it from the very beginning, if he had chosen to move in a more diagonal direction, he would have had enough time to get out of the pit and dodge the Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

But unfortunately, he hadn’t paid attention to this detail. He took the opportunity to counterattack by moving horizontally, but then he was impeded by that shallow indentation in the mountain wall.

With that one obstacle, the opportunity was lost. It was too late to make any other response.

The Dragon Breaks the Ranks into Rising Dragon Soars the Sky pushed Moon Luring Frost even further into the wall. Now, it was no longer an obstacle of one moment. Now, Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost was stuck in the pit for good.

Move, there was only one direction.

Attack, there was also only one direction.

And this one direction wasn’t even available to every attack. For example, Downwind Sword Slash, even though it was a straight-line forward attack, Moon Luring Frost was stuck firmly into the pit, and didn’t have the space to perform the starting motions for this skill. Naturally, the skill couldn’t be used.

“Du Ming lost.”

In this moment, everyone was confident in making such a judgment.

No freedom to move, no freedom to use skills, he couldn’t even jump. Soft Mist blocked the entrance, and Dancing Fire Flowing Flame was already stabbing inward. Skills? Were they even needed? Even if Tang Rou controlled Soft Mist to only use ordinary attacks, Du Ming had no way of controlling Moon Luring Frost to dodge. In a situation where he couldn’t move, parrying the attacks became imagination. Soft Mist’s attacks landed with 100% accuracy, which only made Du Ming even more at a loss as to what to do. In this situation where attacks were landing upon him nonstop, even if he had hundreds or thousands of skills that could instantly allow him to move outside of the hole, he wouldn’t be able to use them.

Just like that, he fell…

Du Ming lost even more helplessly than Mo Fan had in the fourth battle, where he’d been unable to land a single hit on Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer.

Mo Fan, at least, had had space to move. He could at least demonstrate attempts, even if they hadn’t succeeded in the end.

But Du Ming?

Even his right to attempt was stolen away. He was stuck in this hole, stabbed by Soft Mist again and again, all the way until he died. It was pathetic to the extreme.

Winner, Happy’s Tang Rou!

The system dutifully announced the result. The Happy fans were thrilled, jumping and shouting in the stadium. The Samsara fans were dumbstruck. When Zhou Zekai had completed his 1v3, they’d thought that victory was already theirs, that Happy was done for. But now, Happy had actually catching back up to them. Tang Rou’s Soft Mist still had 73% health left to face Samsara’s final player. Under these conditions, the final outcome of this group arena couldn’t be predicted.

How did this happen?

The Samsara fans were still stuck in a daze.

When Zhou Zekai, with a Cloud Piercer that was almost at half health, accomplished a 1v3 to reach Happy’s second-to-last character and player, everyone felt that this was a gap that couldn’t be closed.

And then, had it ever felt like Happy was catching up? There hadn’t been that feeling, it seemed like. Everyone was waiting for the result to be finalized. But then, the situation had suddenly become what it was right now. Suddenly, Samsara’s insurmountable lead had shrunk to only this much, 100% against 73%.

The audience couldn’t restrain themselves. This was the deciding match of the finals, the time in which the team needed the most support and encouragement, and yet at this moment, Team Samsara heard the sound of booing.

Glory’s demonic home stadium.

The place where Team Samsara was invincible. Then, last match, Happy had destroyed Samsara’s home game win streak. And this match, Happy caused Team Samsara to hear the sound of booing in their own home stadium.

Not long before this, the stadium had still been filled with the excitement of winning the championship. The mood had swung from one extreme to the other; it was clear how greatly the fans’ spirits had fallen.

On the sidelines, Lu Boyuan was sitting on pins and needles. When Du Ming walked out of the competitor booth and felt this atmosphere, he was also somewhat hesitant and frightened.

The performance of their first player Sun Xiang had been fine. Zhou Zekai had played flawlessly, and he was the one who had ignited the excitement of winning the championship. But after him, Lu Boyuan, Du Ming, Samsara’s decline from prosperity had occurred on their heads.

Zhou Zekai had been eliminated by Fang Rui, but in that battle, Cloud Piercer had lost less health than Boundless Sea. But then it was Lu Boyuan, and then Du Ming. Now the two of them had both lost, yet the two of them combined had been unable to kill off a single whole life on Happy’s side.

The audience was in no mood to reflect upon the process. Just this outcome was intolerable.

In such an important match, the rare scene of the home fans booing the home team actually appeared.

Samsara’s fans were upset because they had held too high hopes for their team. But the pro players? Their stance was more neutral, but in comparison, they felt that it was more interesting for the black horse Happy to overthrow the two-time champions Samsara.

Happy had gone from being left far behind in the dust to suddenly catching up like this. Even the more logical watchers among them felt that this was extremely exciting, and they wanted to see if the situation would become even more interesting.

Would this be a 1v3?

At last, it was time for those standing on Happy’s side to hold this kind of hope. Zhou Zekai had completed a 1v3 against Happy, and now it was Tang Rou’s turn to return that 1v3 to Samsara, a 1v3 that would decide the final outcome of the group arena. Was there anything more wonderful than this?

“1v3!!!”

Happy’s fans were already shouting in the stadium. This angered the Samsara fans even more, and their boos became louder. They hoped that the team would quickly wake up. Originally, it was their side’s 1v3 that had created such a beautiful lead, and now their opponents were yelling about a 1v3. How humiliating was that!

Amidst the away fans’ shouts of a 1v3 and the home fans’ dissatisfied boos, Samsara’s vice-captain Jiang Botao stood up. Under this pressure from both sides, he walked onstage.

The boos suddenly quieted down, proving how popular Jiang Botao was in the hearts of Samsara fans. He’d been voted into the top ten and even the top five All-Stars for the past two years, which absolutely required a large number of supporters.

Samsara’s fans were extremely upset with the situation, but the two players who’d put them in this situation had already lost and left the stage. Right now, it was their vice-captain stepping forward, so many Samsara’s fans’ hopes were once again lifted, and the booing quieted down.

Even so, the amount of pressure that Jiang Botao felt wouldn’t decrease at all. He knew very clearly that even though the booing sounds were quieter, that was because their final hopes were on his shoulders now. If he also could not give a satisfactory result, then the boos that he would suffer when he came offstage would surge even more than they had just earlier.

This battle, he couldn’t mess up!

It wasn’t just the mood of the fans, but the morale of their team as well. If they experienced this kind of blow, then they would be at a great disadvantage entering the team round. He had to figure out a way to stabilize the overall situation.

Jiang Botao came onstage. His movements were neither too fast nor too slow. He walked over to report to the judge, and then entered his competitor booth. It was all carried out in an unhurried, orderly fashion. He was adjusting his own mood, letting himself be as calm as possible, not letting himself worry.

Character loaded, map loaded. The ninth battle of the group arena, the deciding battle, began. Happy’s Tang Rou, character Soft Mist, 73% health; Samsara’s Jiang Botao, character Empty Waves, 100% health.

Soft Mist charged forth.

It was just like last battle, like last last battle. Without thought, extremely decisive.

This was Tang Rou’s style. She had always been like this.

But now, no one would think of Tang Rou as so simple ever again. In the battle that had just ended, despite being in an extraordinarily brave state, Du Ming had ended up losing in such a pathetic way, not by control, nor by technique, but by calculation.

And these calculations had been done without any change to her normal behavior, so much so that before the situation happened, no one had realized.

Those who would play against Tang Rou now knew to be more prepared. The pro players in the audience gave themselves a word of warning for potential future meetings with this Best Rookie.

Chapter 1670 - A Calm and Unhurried Opening

Others were thinking of the future, but Jiang Botao had to face the present.

The match began. Tang Rou’s Soft Mist rushed out. As for Jiang Botao? His playing was the same as his walk to the stage, neither slow nor fast. His Spellblade, Empty Waves, marched ahead comfortably.

The center of the map still had numerous holes left behind by Chaotic Cloudy Mountain and Moon Luring Frost. At the start, everyone had been discussing whether Jiang Botao would be thrown into the holes as well. But when they saw Jiang Botao’s unhurried pace, the discussion ended. With the difference in speed between Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves and Tang Rou’s Soft Mist, the two sides wouldn’t be meeting in the center.

But then again, Tang Rou could just wait at the center of the map for Jiang Botao to arrive, no?

Not long after these guesses were made, Soft Mist continued right past the center of the map.

As a result, the two met on the half of the map closer to Samsara’s spawn point.

Soft Mist didn’t stop and continued forward.

This was how Tang Rou always played, but after seeing her performance today, it was hard not to give her playstyle another thought.

As for Jiang Botao?

Would Jiang Botao think differently and play more carefully?

No one knew. All they saw was his Empty Waves lift his sword.

Earth Wave Slash!

Spellblades had mid-ranged attacks, so it was common to see them attack first against close-ranged enemies. Earth Wave Slash was the Spellblade’s lowest level Spellblade skill. Even though its damage wasn’t high, it was quick and possessed high priority.

Jiang Botao’s opening move was nothing out of the ordinary. It was an opening that Spellblades used 80% of the time.

Calm and unhurried!

The battle had begun. Jiang Botao’s performance could be described with these three words.

Was this the playstyle he was going to use in today’s match?

Playstyle. When this word fell onto Jiang Botao, most people would furrow their brows in uncertainty.

He was an All-Star player, the vice-captain of a championship team. He had a stellar reputation in the pro circle and was very popular amongst the playerbase. However, no one could say what exactly his playstyle was. Even Samsara themselves weren’t sure. When they first discovered Jiang Botao’s talent in tactics and strategies, they had thought of elevating him to the level of a Master Tactician, but unfortunately, he wasn’t able to shine bright enough and the matter was left inconclusive.

Jiang Botao didn’t have a distinct playstyle.

But after a long time, people started to gradually realize that this was perhaps his true style.

His ability to adapt was extraordinary. He could use any playstyle he wanted to battle. He was always the team’s most sturdy pillar.

This was why he was able to synergize perfectly with Zhou Zekai and Samsara.

The Glue, Jack of All Trades, Timely Rain, Tinker…

Jiang Botao had started in Season 6. It hadn’t even been 5 years, and he had countless nicknames. From this, it could be seen how difficult it was to pinpoint his playstyle. But through these numerous nicknames, it was also able to show his strengths.

There was one common aspect with all these nicknames. All of them described Jiang Botao through a team perspective. As for his individual prowess, even today, it seemed to be a difficult question.

Everyone only knew that he was skilled, that he wasn’t easy to deal with. Anyone who played against him had to be on guard. He could play aggressive. He could play dirty. He could play a mental battle. He could do what seemed to be illogical choices…

But no matter what, you couldn’t relax even a single moment. A single moment of carelessness could result in you losing.

Jiang Botao made this ordinary opening move, making it hard to predict what he would do next because there were simply too many possibilities.

This was precisely his aim. He wanted to create a situation filled with possibilities, so he could calmly observe Tang Rou and find a way to win. Even though Samsara needed him to reestablish their morale, he couldn’t act rashly.

Because in his view, different opponents needed to be played against differently, and Tang Rou definitely wasn’t someone he could fight against with brute force.

Jiang Botao was waiting for Tang Rou to act. That Earth Wave Slash seemed to be bait for Tang Rou to attack.

His sword had already come out. Next was to wait to see how Tang Rou would react.

Even though he had seen a few peculiarities from Tang Rou’s previous fight, he was pretty certain that Tang Rou would meet force with force.

Jiang Botao guessed correctly. Soft Mist moved to the side a bit without wasting any movements, just barely dodging the Earth Wave Slash. Then, she raised her spear, Dancing Fire Flowing Flames, and accelerated!

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Tang Rou went with her usual opening move, charging forward the instant she dodged the Earth Wave Slash.

Her timing was good, but all of it was within Jiang Botao’s calculations. He had been ready for all of the possible reactions to his Earth Wave Slash bait. Dragon Breaks the Ranks had been the most likely possibility, and Jiang Botao was on guard against it.

Dodge!

Empty Waves rolled to the side twice.

Because just one roll wouldn’t be enough! With Tang Rou’s reaction speed, she would have enough time to change the direction of her Dragon Breaks the Ranks to cover a target that only rolled once.

Jiang Botao’s deduction was correct once again. As expected, as soon as Tang Rou saw him roll, she immediately adjusted. Soft Mist leaned to the side, altering the direction of the Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

Empty Waves noticed it and did the second roll.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks had missed, and the instant Empty Waves got up from the roll, he swung his shortsword, Divine Chains.

Wave Wheel Slasher!

A grab attack that broke through Super Armor. Even against the powerful Dragon Breaks the Ranks, Wave Wheel Slasher out prioritized it.

The attack, the timing, the angle, all of it had been incomparably cunning.

Would it hit though?

Jiang Botao wondered. From his calculations, there was around a 50% chance he would fail. It depended on Tang Rou’s condition this fight.

Tang Rou’s condition today was outstanding, but she had already gone through two fights. Perhaps she couldn’t keep up her focus, or perhaps she was too excited, or perhaps she was thinking too much about making a comeback.

Countless factors could decide whether she reacted fast enough.

Would it hit?

The sword light flew through the air.

It missed!

Soft Mist had cancelled the Dragon Breaks the Ranks at the last moment, giving her time to leap to the side, dodging the Wave Wheel Slasher.

She dodged it.

Jiang Botao was a bit regretful, but with how well Tang Rou was playing today, this outcome had been more likely.

Jiang Botao wouldn’t linger on this for too long because he had already thought that Tang Rou would likely counterattack the moment she dodged.

What would she counterattack with?

Dancing Fire Flowing Flames whistled through the air, two streaks of red flickered.

Oh, it’s Double Stab.

Empty Waves calmly raised his sword, Guard!

Chapter 1671 - Counterattack Timing

Ding ding!

Empty Waves knocked aside the two spear shadows.

Double Stab as a counterattack. Jiang Botao wasn’t surprised in the slightest. He had been ready for this sort of attack.

While using “Guard”, Jiang Botao had Empty Waves step back. Sure enough, after the Double Stab, Soft Mist stabbed again.

With Tang Rou’s skill, stabbing four times during her jump wouldn’t be a problem for her. Since she had started with Double Stab, there would definitely be another two following.

After Empty Waves stepped back, Jiang Botao had more room to maneuver. Seeing that the stab was just a normal attack, he had Empty Waves swing his sword and parry the strike.

Soft Mist landed on the ground.

She didn’t follow with a Dragon Tooth after the normal attack. Tang Rou had seen Empty Waves block her attacks in succession, letting her know that anything further would likely be blocked as well.

Falling Flower Palm!

As soon as she landed on the ground, she launched a new attack. Falling Flower Palm could be charged, and could also be used while sliding on the ground. The distance between Empty Waves and Soft Mist was perfect for a slide.

Empty Waves retreated again, taking another step back. Tang Rou’s follow-up had been within his calculations as well.

Boom!

The magic shockwave from Falling Flower Palm hit nothing but air. Empty Waves was very very close to Soft Mist, but he was still just a bit too far.

Empty Waves swung his sword.

The distance was too close. Although Wave Slashes were instant-cast spells, its start-up was slower than close-ranged skills. As a result, Jiang Botao chose to use a normal attack instead.

Normal attacks dealt little damage and had weak priority, but if they landed, they would still hinder the opponent’s movements. Tang Rou couldn’t completely ignore the attack. Soft Mist swayed to the right, dodging the slash. At the same time, she thrust her spear.

Tyrant’s Destruction?

Jiang Botao saw Soft Mist sway to the right and immediately thought of this skill. After moving to the right, whether it was her posture or her angle of attack, both were perfect for a Tyrant’s Destruction.

Sure enough, Dancing Fire Flowing Flames tore through the air, Tyrant’s Destruction!

Empty Waves jumped back to dodge the Tyrant’s Destruction. This time, the distance between them was enough for a Wave Slash.

Divine Chains slashed out.

Ice Wave Slash!

Ice crystals formed wherever the blade passed through, sweeping across the ground.

Empty Waves had attacked, but Soft Mist was in a good position after the Tyrant’s Destruction, giving her enough time to react.

Dodge! Attack!

Empty Waves’ offense was quickly put to a stop, and in the blink of an eye, Tang Rou held the initiative again.

The Samsara fans let out sighs of regret. The way things were going worried them.

However, through glances with each other, the pro players had a different opinion.

It was true that Tang Rou held the initiative, but that was from an attack and defense perspective. In terms of the flow of the match, then that might not be the case. Tang Rou was on the offensive, but it mainly because Jiang Botao was letting her.

It had only been a few exchanges since Tang Rou’s opening with Dragon Breaks the Ranks. If Jiang Botao had wanted to seize the initiative, there were at least two opportunities for him to do so.

However, Jiang Botao had only counterattacked after dodging Dragon Breaks the Ranks and Tyrant’s Destruction. The other two times he could have counterattacked, he hadn’t.

Was it because Jiang Botao hadn’t noticed these two other opportunities?

It didn’t seem like it because neither of those two opportunities had been hard to see. Most of the normal players had noticed them.

In that case, why did Jiang Botao choose to give up on these opportunities? The pro players didn’t understand at first, but after seeing Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves try to counterattack after dodging the Tyrant’s Destruction, they had a rough idea of Jiang Botao’s strategy.

He wanted to make things simple. He didn’t want anything too complicated.

Just take those two opportunities that he gave up on. If he had succeeded, he would have been the one on the offensive, but if he had failed?

For those two opportunities, Tang Rou had too many options available to her. There was no way for him to take them all into consideration.

As for the two opportunities that he did take, he had completely read what Tang Rou would do and easily dealt with whatever she responded with.

This was Jiang Botao’s general strategy for this match.

Make things simple, so his opponent only had a few choices, and then take control.

Only a few exchanges had happened. Jiang Botao had spent most of his efforts on thinking. The Ice Wave Slash had missed, and when Tang Rou’s Soft Mist started her offense again, Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves retreated.

Dragon Tooth or Circle Swing? Or maybe even Draconic Crusher.

Jiang Botao thought of Tang Rou’s possible choices.

Dragon Tooth!

The more that he saw Tang Rou stay within his predictions, the calmer Jiang Botao became. He wasn’t at all worried like the fans outside were.

Dragon Tooth missed!

Okay, next is Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart.

Sure enough, Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart.

Miss again!

Dragon Rises from the Sea? Or Cloud Whirling Windstorm?

Oh, Dragon Rises from the Sea.

Dodge!

Soft Mist attacked several times, and each time, Empty Waves retreated.

The fight looked completely one-sided. The moment a potential counterattack from Empty Waves appeared, Soft Mist instantly crushed any chances of it happening.

But even the ordinary viewers had started to notice that even though it looked like Jiang Botao was losing, the one who should be worried probably wasn’t Jiang Botao. Tang Rou had been on the offensive for quite a while now, yet Jiang Botao’s defense looked to be unbreakable. It was as if didn’t see any of her attacks as a threat. Soft Mist had attacked for so long, but had only taken out 7% of Empty Waves’ health. She was still very far from wiping away the lead that he held!

It’s about time for him to counterattack.

The pro players who understood Jiang Botao’s plans took another step ahead of the normal viewers. Jiang Botao was playing this fight very intelligently. He understood clearly that Tang Rou wasn’t an opponent he could deal with through brute force. Facing her fierce offense, no one could be completely confident. Tang Rou was playing incredible today as well. Even the slightest slip-up, and she would punish you heavily for it.

As a result, Jiang Botao was using defense as his offense. From the start, he had been guiding Tang Rou’s attacks. All of her attacks had been within Jiang Botao’s predictions. Not only did it make it easy for him to defend, it was a mental test for Tang Rou as well. Having completely seen through her, Jiang Botao knew when exactly his counterattack would be most destructive.

It was about time.

The pro players all thought the same. Through Jiang Botao’s control, Tang Rou’s mix-ups were becoming less and less varied. At this point, her attack pattern was practically linear. What attack she would do next was something everyone could shout at.

Falling Flower Palm?

Everyone guessed.

Boom! Soft Mist used Falling Flower Palm.

Draconic Crusher?

Sure enough, Dancing Fire Flowing Flames pressed down, Draconic Crusher.

He can counterattack whenever. Everyone thought. His opponent could be read like a book. Making a counterattack was no different than children’s play, no? Right now, it was just a matter of when the counterattack would be the most harmful to Tang Rou.

Dragon Tooth!

The crowd shouted out Soft Mist’s next attack, which Empty Waves dodged.

Counterattack!

Quite a few people shouted inwardly. They felt like a counterattack now would be quite good.

But Jiang Botao didn’t seem to be satisfied with it. Empty Waves rolled backwards, dodging the following Circle Swing.

How greedy!

Everyone thought to themselves. He wasn’t even going to take that? Was Jiang Botao really going to wait until an opportunity where he could kill her in one combo?

Circle Swing was dodged. Dancing Fire Flowing Flames leapt into the air, Sky Strike.

Empty Waves leapt back, while also putting up his Divine Chains in front of him just in case.

The weapons clashed. A Light Chaser formed behind Soft Mist and short directly towards Empty Waves.

The distance was too close. The Chaser was too fast. This time, Jiang Botao couldn’t dodge the attack, and was hit with a face full of sparks.

“Hahahaha!” The pro players laughed out loud.

“Jiang Botao is being too careful!” Someone said.

“If he hadn’t put up his sword, there wouldn’t have been a Chaser. He just gave her a free hit.”

“Yeah, and it’s a Light element one. It’ll increase her attack speed.”

Some of the pro players remarked in this way, but some of the others had a change in expression at this moment.

Had the parry been unnecessary?

The stadium screen coincidentally showed a replay of this scene to show the Light Chaser hitting Empty Waves again, but the pro players were more interested in how the Chaser was formed.

Sky Strike…

The distance… the parry wasn’t necessary!

Everyone thought to themselves. The Dancing Fire Flowing Flames quietly inched forward a bit as it arced upwards.

Quite a few people blinked their eyes, confirming that they hadn’t misjudged.

Yes… Dancing Fire Flowing Flames had inched forward. This Sky Strike wasn’t the same. Tang Rou had intentionally left some room for her to change things up a bit.

Because when facing a Battle Mage, it was best to avoid parrying or blocking the five low-level Battle Mage skills. If the skills hit, Chasers would be formed. Blocking and parrying were considered as hits.

Tang Rou had used this common knowledge to her advantage. She had intentionally made it so that it didn’t seem like her attack needed to be parried, but just as the attack was made, she suddenly changed the trajectory…

It wasn’t as simple as it sounded. It required very precise inputs to make these sudden changes.

The Light Chaser hit, and Soft Mist continued to attack. Even though Empty Waves was able to dodge her attacks, he was clearly having a harder time than before.

Still not counterattacking?

Someone was still thinking.

But a portion of people were now thinking: could he still counterattack?

The mix-up from the Sky Strike hadn’t been accidental, but was this the only time she had made this mix-up?

Whether it was the broadcast or the live stadium replay, none of them would rewind too far back. The pro players had only noticed the problem with this Sky Strike. They had no way to go back right now and check if she had done it before too.

Could it be that… Jiang Botao had not counterattacked, not because he was waiting for the right moment, but because he was actually being suppressed?

This… from when did this start?

Chapter 1672 - : Top Rookie

When did it start?

Jiang Botao was also asking the same question. He had been leading Tang Rou around, controlling the pace of the match. He had always felt like his strategy had been successful. Everything was in his grasp. He could read every mix-up that came at him. Not once did any of Tang Rou’s actions fall outside of his predictions.

He had planned in advance, waiting patiently for an opportunity. He hoped to finish the match decisively with an overwhelming counterattack. This sort of finish would be more reliable, and it would improve the team’s morale. Two birds with one stone.

However, the opportunity never came. Jiang Botao couldn’t help but admire Tang Rou. On this grand stage, in the decisive game three of the finals, she was attacking and attacking but with no success, yet she didn’t become impatient and persevered. Let alone a rookie, even an experienced player might not have such strong mental toughness.

She persevered. Jiang Botao didn’t back down either. Keeping this same pace would be favorable for him in the long-run. The flow and tempo of the match was completely within his grasp. All he needed was one reliable opportunity, whether that was a mistake on her part or a slight lapse in concentration, just one was enough.

But there was none…

The previous Dragon Tooth, Circle Swing, and then Sky Strike, Jiang Botao predicted them all. After the Dragon Tooth, many people felt like he could counterattack, but Jiang Botao hadn’t.

It hadn’t been because he felt like the opportunity wasn’t good enough, but rather in his eyes, he hadn’t seen an opportunity.

At that moment, he felt a shock go through his heart.

Dragon Tooth into Circle Swing, it had been a quick follow-up. If he had counterattacked after the Dragon Tooth, he would have been caught by the Circle Swing. As a result, he couldn’t counterattack, and could only dodge.

Dragon Tooth and Circle Swing had been both easily evaded by Jiang Botao. Then, Sky Strike…

As expected!

Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves hadn’t stopped to take a rest. After rolling away from the Circle Swing, he had jumped to avoid the following Sky Strike.

If he didn’t need to parry, he wouldn’t. This sort of common Battle Mage knowledge wasn’t something he would overlook.

But at that moment, Soft Mist’s spear had suddenly extended forward.

Had he seen that wrong?

Jiang Botao didn’t know if he had seen it wrong but he wasn’t going to take the risk. He had parried, giving Tang Rou a Light Chaser. But compared to getting knocked into the air by Sky Strike, he definitely preferred the former.

Thus, he had put up his sword Divine Chains.

His question was answered.

Soft Mist’s Dancing Fire Flowing Flames struck Empty Waves’ Divine Chains. The Light Chaser shot out. Even if Jiang Botao had wanted to dodge, Chasers had auto-targeting!

The Chaser hit, and Soft Mist’s attack speed increased. Her offense continued.

The single Chaser hitting hadn’t been enough to give Tang Rou much of an opportunity to injure his opponent. The normal players didn’t think too much of it. After all, she had been on the offensive the entire time. It wasn’t possible for Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves to take absolutely zero damage. Even though he had dodged most of the attacks, he had still lost 7% over the course of the battle so far.

However, the pro players knew that this time was different.

Because this time, Jiang Botao had lost his calm. He didn’t have the same foresight as before. The parry had been in haste, meaning it had been outside of his expectations.

The tempo was no longer in his control. The flow of the battle was no longer completely dictated by him.

Pu!

Not long after the Chaser hit, Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves was suddenly hit again. Even though it was just a normal attack with low damage, the pro players were no longer looking at the numbers. Jiang Botao’s control over the fight was slipping.

Had Jiang Botao not been able to think of this normal stab?

No, impossible.

The attack had been obvious. Even a normal player understood that this follow-up would be next.

He knew, but he couldn’t avoid it.

It wasn’t just a slight shock through Jiang Botao’s heart, but rather a deep sense of danger.

It wasn’t any sort of crazy mix-up, nor was it anything new. This was a change done through force by relying on one’s reaction speed and technique. This was what it meant to have talent. And right now, Tang Rou was putting her talent on display. She wasn’t just recklessly erupting with hand speed, but meticulously manipulating the details to create changes.

“Incredible…”

No one knew who said it.

No one responded, but everyone knew that this praise wasn’t towards Jiang Botao, but Tang Rou.

At this moment, everyone realized that Happy’s rookie could no longer be seen as a rookie. This rookie had probably already established herself among the top players of Glory.

Compared to the top rookies each season: Season 2’s Blossoms and Blood, Season 3’s Wang Jiexi, Season 4’s Golden Generation, Season 5’s Zhou Zekai… during their debut season, all of them had already reached the level of Gods. However, as the competition got fiercer, and the Alliance grew, the luster of the top rookies seemed to decline with each season. After Season 6, only Sun Xiang had been given the title as one of the Gods after his rookie debut in Season 7. As for the ones after?

Season 8’s Best Rookie, Zhao Yuzhe? He wasn’t even an All-Star!

Season 9’s Best Rookie, Lu Hanwen? He had attracted a lot of attention because of his age. The mental fortitude and maturity at his age won much praise. Everyone was certain that he would have a glorious future, but no one thought that he was at the level of the Gods yet.

As for Tang Rou?

When comparing these rookies, everyone suddenly realized that Tang Rou’s situation was similar to Lu Hanwen’s, but also different.

Lu Hanwen had been given some lenience because of his age. Everyone’s expectations for him were naturally lower.

As for Tang Rou? Because of the 1v3 fiasco, a whole bunch of people cursed her the entire season. Everyone’s expectations for her were very harsh. If she didn’t do a 1v3, then all sorts of criticism and ridicule were thrown at her.

But 1v3… what sort of criteria was that? Using a 1v3 as a criteria wasn’t just harsh but deliberately making things difficult for her.

If people had looked at her performance over the entire season without bias, then the Alliance giving her the title of Best Rookie should have been indisputable.

High ambitions, strong mental fortitude, frightening talent, and constantly improving in Glory knowledge and technique…

Of the many traits that Tang Rou possessed, the only flaw that she had was her age.

Tang Rou wasn’t too young of a player at 23 years old. In the early years of the pro scene, many players this age would choose to retire. In the current scene, her age was where her skill and experience should be at its peak. As for how long this peak period lasted, it depended on the person. On average, there would usually be a decline after one or two years.

…

But for Tang Rou, this was her first season. Her skill was still increasing, but her age wouldn’t be able to carry her to the peak…

Truly a pity.

Everyone thought to themselves.

But a part from pity, there was also a bit of… joy.

After all, she was an enemy. Even though it wasn’t the manliest of thoughts, who cared if you were born at the wrong time? Those retired top players during Ye Qiu’s reign probably all had thoughts of “if only there was no Ye Qiu”.

At this moment, Tang Rou had unexpectedly given them thoughts of running away.

Everyone wanted to run, but Jiang Botao couldn’t.

He can’t hold on!

When everyone’s focus went back to the match, they saw Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves continuing to retreat in defeat. His previous retreat had been out of free will. He had been guiding Tang Rou along. But his current retreat was out of helplessness. He didn’t have a second choice.

I can’t keep retreating any longer!

Jiang Botao was clear about this point. If this continued, Empty Waves would lose too much health. An explosive counterattack might not be enough to win. Right now, he needed to be unyielding. He needed to fight against Tang Rou blow for blow.

There should be an opportunity to do so, no?

Jiang Botao observed and thought.

He had been giving in to her offense the entire time. Tang Rou should have formed a certain mindset by now. If he suddenly rushed forward, even if he couldn’t make it an explosive counterattack, it should at least mess up her rhythm.

Tyrant’s Destruction!

Soft Mist’s Dancing Fire Flowing Flames swept outwards again. Jiang Botao had also finished formulating his plan.

Now.

He had to do it now. Too much thinking and too much preparation would actually make it easier for Tang Rou to be on guard. He needed to move suddenly and unexpectedly. He needed to create an opportunity when it wasn’t one.

Empty Waves jumped forward as if he were planning on crashing straight into Tyrant’s Destruction, but when he jumped, Empty Waves curled up his legs so that Soft Mist’s spear would be beneath him.

Just this isn’t enough!

Jiang Botao knew it clearly. He had experienced Tang Rou’s speed from a close distance. Although it looked like he had already dodged Tyrant’s Destruction, Tang Rou could definitely adjust in time.

But he wasn’t afraid because Empty Waves had made his move. Jiang Botao wasn’t looking for a breakthrough with this attack. He just wanted to shake things up, make a trade. For him, the trade would be favorable for him.

Unyielding!

Jiang Boyao showed that he could be unyielding too.

Tang Rou didn’t retreat. She obviously wouldn’t. As long as she was still fighting, there was no such thing as retreat.

Sword light flashed, magic waves jumped, Empty Waves’ Wave Wheel Slasher arrived.

As for Tyrant’s Destruction?

Tyrant’s Destruction seemed to have stopped, but there was no change. Soft Mist raised her other hand. Magic quickly began to flow around her.

Not good!

Jiang Botao realized what it was. His heart burned with worry. He just hoped that his attack would reach in time. But in the end, the magic waves surged, locking in place an afterimage…

Teleport.

The bonus skill on her weapon.

A Battle Mage choosing Teleport wasn’t anything surprising. Sung Xiang often chose this skill. Jiang Botao hadn’t overlooked this possibility, but he just didn’t think she could Teleport at this distance. The attack was already upon her, and she actually used Teleport?

This confidence and bravery exceeded his imagination. It seemed more likely that the Teleport wouldn’t go through in time, but Tang Rou wasn’t afraid of the outcome. What she showed was her determination to win even if the Wave Wheel Slasher had hit!

Only by having this determination would she be so decisive during these moments, and it was only by being decisive was she able to successfully dodge the Wave Wheel Slasher with Teleport.

Soft Mist instantly vanished from Jiang Botao’s sight.

Behind…

Jiang Botao immediately guessed. However, Empty Waves was in the air. He immediately cancelled the skill and used Falling Light Blade to try alter his fall, but he was too late…

Dancing Fire Flowing Flames struck his waist, Circle Swing!

Empty Waves was thrown back, but he didn’t slam into the ground. Tang Rou had thrown aside the Circle Swing’s damage, using it just to get Empty Waves closer.

The skill was cancelled, and Empty Waves regained his mobility. Jiang Botao reacted quickly, using Falling Light Blade again.

But what welcomed was him… Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike!

Afterimages of Dancing Fire Flowing Flame appeared all around him. Tang Rou didn’t think about where he would dodge to. She used this skill to block all of Jiang Botao’s options.

Falling Light Blade immediately collapsed in front of Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike. Empty Waves was instantly skewered countless times.

Empty Waves was knocked back, and Soft Mist chased after him, attacking as she moved to deal as much damage as possible with Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike.

She wasn’t done yet…

Dragon Tooth!

After the Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike, she followed with a Dragon Tooth.

Hit, stun, there was no need to ask whether the next attack would hit.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Tang Rou followed with a high-level skill. Soft Mist wielded Dancing Fire Flowing Flames, pressing against Empty Waves. Forward, forward, forward, there was only forward!

With unstoppable momentum, Empty Waves was pushed far back.

Jiang Botao was waiting, waiting for the instant the skill ended…

Boom!

Dragon Breaks the Ranks reached its end, the condensed magic burst apart in the air, creating an explosion.

Empty Waves flew back from the shockwave, but he didn’t miss this opportunity to attack.

Light Wave Slash!

The fastest wave slash instantly formed, slicing towards Soft Mist.

Jiang Botao reacted extremely fast, his timing was on point.

But Tang Rou didn’t lose out. After Dragon Breaks the Ranks ended, Soft Mist jumped back and pointed with her spear.

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart!

Dancing Fire Flowing Flames passed through the Light Wave Slash. One was physical, while the other magic. The two skills collided, neither interfering with each other.

Pu! Pu!

Soft Mist was hit by the Light Wave Slash, leaving a sword mark on her leather armor.

Empty Waves wasn’t able to dodge the pursuit of Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart. The magic pierced through his back.

Soft Mist stumbled, but quickly steadied herself.

Empty Waves had been hit by the Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart while in the air, and was sent flying back.

Land, roll, he immediately steadied himself, but the scene to his left and right made Jiang Botao feel a little strange.

In front of Empty Waves was a wooden sign.

He was looking at the back of the wooden sign. It was very rough, and there was nothing there.

What he couldn’t see was the front of the wooden sign, the three words: Death to Intruders!

Chapter 1673 - Good Thing There’s No More

There were no words on the back of the crude wooden sign, but Jiang Botao already realized what this was.

He had actually retreated for so long, for so far. And now, he had taken one step inside. Could he still leave?

Empty Waves didn’t immediately die. It was like Wei Chen had predicted. The design of this map did not include “insta-kill.”

Previously, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea had taken one step into the forbidden zone, causing the NPCs to appear and attack him.

And Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves had actually let his entire body enter the forbidden zone.

In just one second, the NPCs appeared.

In just one second, Empty Waves was surrounded.

In just one second, the back of the wooden sign vanished from Jiang Botao’s sight, because sword slashes and all sorts of attacks now blocked his view.

The situation was very bad, but Jiang Botao didn’t plan to give up so easily. One second for the NPCs to appear and attack; one second was enough for a skilled pro player to make many judgments and complete many controls.

Nebula Wave Slash!

At the same time as the NPCs attacked, Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves was also already attacking, without holding anything back.

Surrounded on all sides, that was the perfect time to use the powerful Nebula Wave Slash, that both attacked and defended.

The wave energy swirled, expanded, enveloped, hit!

With Empty Waves at the center, a half-sphere steadily grew.

In the system statistics, Empty Waves’ combo count was leaping like crazy. In this moment, unleashing such a powerful attack, who knew how many targets he’d struck simultaneously.

It was very satisfying, very cool.

But no one could smile.

Even though he’d used this powerful attack, Jiang Botao had only managed to prevent Empty Waves from getting trapped in the encirclement of NPCs. But now? Now, he still had to continue to struggle with these NPCs. This one powerful attack couldn’t completely clean them up.

Moreover, there was still Tang Rou.

Correct, Tang Rou was still there.

One second, the NPCs appeared, the NPCs attacked.

One second, Jiang Botao controlled Empty Waves to use Nebula Wave Slash, breaking the encirclement.

One second, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist charged forward…

Stop and watch?

No, not at all.

If not for sending Empty Waves flying with an attack earlier, which put some distance between them, she might have beaten the NPCs to attack him now.

In the end, Soft Mist’s attack was only late by this one second.

Nebula Wave Slash still hadn’t ended. The wave energy was still rippling along Empty Waves’ short sword.

A red silhouette suddenly appeared above him.

No retreating, no dodging, Soft Mist charged forth, Shattering the Lands, a Level 75 Battle Mage skill, shaking against Empty Waves’ Nebula Wave Slash!

Boom!

Soft Mist was like a scarlet comet piercing through the nebula. She couldn’t help but take some damage, but the Shattering the Lands continued forth.

Jiang Botao had no way to dodge, and Empty Waves had nowhere to dodge.

Shattering the Lands, the magic energy barreled forth, hitting Empty Waves and carrying the NPCs.

Tang Rou didn’t care about all that. She let everyone witness her plan. But in this moment, what everyone saw was her letting everything out, from top to bottom, so much so that Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves seemed like a dead man.

Empty Waves wasn’t a dead man, but he wasn’t far from it now.

When attacking by defending, Soft Mist had whittled away some of his health. Then after losing the initiative, many of Soft Mist’s attacks had landed upon him. And now, fallen into the forbidden zone, he faced the focused fire of the NPCs, and then Soft Mist’s powerful attack that ignored all else.

Too difficult…

Blasted by Shattering the Lands, Empty Waves staggered, and his control of Nebula Wave Slash slipped. The NPCs didn’t care whether they lived or died, they didn’t know where the flaw was in Jiang Botao’s control of Nebula Wave Slash was. They ignored everything else and simply attacked in the most convenient way, and instantly there were countless attacks crashing in.

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist was included as well. The Shattering the Lands had drawn the aggro of some of the NPCs, but she was as focused and determined as before as she continued to turn Empty Waves into a dead man.

Helpless…

Jiang Botao didn’t give up, but Empty Waves’ health was gone. Just like that, it was used up. Originally, he could have fought his way out of the crowd, circled around, perhaps even taken advantage of the NPCs like Fang Rui had.

However, Tang Rou’s attack was only late by one second.

And this one second wasn’t because she hesitated, but because Soft Mist needed this one second to reach him.

Tang Rou’s resolve extinguished Jiang Botao’s last hope.

One second, they were close; yet one second had decided who lived and who died.

Soft Mist lived, Empty Waves died…

The stadium was silent.

Tang Rou won? Happy won? This was a… 1v3?

After Fang Rui’s diligent chase and Tang Rou’s returned 1v3, the huge advantage that Zhou Zekai had won for Samsara with his 1v3 was erased just like that? Happy had made their comeback?

Before this round, the fact that Happy had closed the gap was already enough to cause the upset Samsara fans to boo their home team. And now, not only had the gap shrunk, they had lost. They’d had such a big advantage, such a big lead, and then Fang Rui, Tang Rou, two of Happy’s players had completed a reversal?

Samsara’s fans were beyond upset, they were upset to the extreme.

At this moment, a line of text suddenly appeared in the chat.

“Ah, no more opponents, I still have a lot of health…”

Soft Mist was going through the victory poses with the air of triumph. But behind her, Tang Rou was actually sighing, regretful. 1v3 still wasn’t enough, did she still want to fight another for a 1v4?

How arrogant, how presumptuous!

But seeing how much health Soft Mist had remaining, Samsara’s fans felt that they couldn’t do anything.

Soft Mist still had 52% health left, a little over half.

Against Lu Boyuan, perfect win.

Against Du Ming, used 27% health.

Against Jiang Botao, used 21% health.

Not only had Tang Rou completed a 1v3, it was an extremely good 1v3. Killing 3 characters had required less than half her health. It wasn’t any exaggeration to call this one-sided.

And the opponents she’d faced were strong. Du Ming’s fame might have been a little smaller, but he was still part of Samsara’s main, championship roster. Jiang Botao and Lu Boyuan didn’t need to be talked about, these were All-Star level players.

And then, a mere rookie – even if she was the Best Rookie – using less than half health, had defeated all three of them?

This was an even stronger showing than Zhou Zekai. After Zhou Zekai completed his 1v3, Cloud Piercer had 45% health remaining, less than half. At that time, the whole stadium had been cheering for a 1v4…

So now, for Tang Rou with a character at 52% health to sigh about not having the chance for a 1v4, was it excessive at all?

The Samsara fans were extremely depressed!

Finally, Happy’s fans came back to their senses. 1v3, Tang Rou had actually done it. In the group arena of the finals, she’d made a comeback against the championship team Samsara!

In just one moment, some people were laughing so hard they started to cry.

The image of Samsara’s stadium cheering for a 1v4 after Zhou Zekai’s 1v3 was still vivid in their minds! And now, seeing Tang Rou’s sigh, they felt that it was extremely appropriate.

Thus, Happy’s fans quickly began to shout in answer: “Good thing there’s no more!”

It was common for fans in the stadium to spit trash talk at each other. Samsara’s fans understood this kind of mockery.

They’d lost the battle, that was fact. They couldn’t find anything to retort.

Their players weren’t making a good showing! So, when the group arena officially ended and the two teams left the stage, Samsara’s fans weren’t polite. Boos!

Last round, Jiang Botao’s outstanding performance had led the crowd to sing, but this time, they were extremely upset, seething with anger. The booing was non-negotiable.

They’d had such a huge lead, yet the opponent had caught up, and ultimately they’d been beaten by a rookie completing a 1v3. It was frankly a disgrace.

What were the players doing? Had they gotten too proud and complacent after their lead?

The crowd booed like crazy, not just to vent their frustration, but also to send a reminder to the team, to make their players wake up.

They couldn’t continue like this in the upcoming team competition.

During the rest period between the group arena and the team competition, the stadium never quieted down. After the huge ups and downs of the group arena, both Happy and Samsara chose to return to their prep rooms to rest.

Both player areas were empty, yet the booing didn’t stop.

And after seeing high point after high point during this group arena, the pro players watching had also gotten excited, and could no longer watch from a purely rational perspective.

“I’d place a bet, if Samsara really could send up one more person, Tang Rou would have actually gotten a 1v4!” Huang Shaotian’s excitement right now was rather evident.

“Samsara’s morale has definitely suffered a heavy blow. Their adjustment during this intermission is especially important.” Xiao Shiqin liked to make general observations.

“Even Samsara’s fans can’t take it anymore.” Zhang Jiale felt the atmosphere of the stadium. He was fairly sensitive to the mood of fans.

“This is the first time I’ve heard Samsara get booed here,” sighed Yang Cong, who’d been competing in the pro circle for seven years now.

“Same for all of us,” said a number of people.

“Honestly speaking, do you guys think Samsara was playing poorly?” Chu Yunxiu suddenly said.

“Sun Xiang was pretty good, Zhou Zekai doesn’t need to be mentioned.” There was no debate about these two players that Tang Hao named.

And after these two?

“Lu Boyuan’s condition wasn’t very good,” said Han Wenqing.

“Du Ming’s condition wasn’t too bad, though,” Wang Jiexi nodded.

“Jiang Botao’s plan was fairly clear, and the execution was also quite good, but unfortunately…” Yu Wenzhou trailed off.

“Unfortunately, Tang Rou’s performance was better!” After the three major captains commented, Zhang Xinjie finished the sentence that Yu Wenzhou had left unspoken.

Yes, that was how it was.

Whoever played better would win. The principle was just that simple.

Competitions really were decided by one side doing well and the other doing worse and losing. One side does well, yet the other side does better, this kind of helplessness was the main theme on the battlefield.

The pro players didn’t really agree with the boos of the stadium, but there was nothing to be done. Tang Rou had played a 1v3. That performance was just too sharp, too powerful, too domineering. Even though Du Ming and Jiang Botao had been in good condition, they could only pale in comparison.

How would the two teams play the team competition?

Right now, everyone was already thinking about the team battle that would decide the final victor. The map for the team competition had already been randomly chosen. Because the two teams had both returned to their prep rooms to rest, when the map info was broadcast to the stadium, it was simultaneously sent to the prep rooms of the two teams.

Chapter 1674 - The Team Roster to Sprint for the Championship

Abandoned Capital in the Heavens.

When the audience saw the information about the final team battle map, Happy and Samsara got the information at the same time in their respective prep rooms.

The digital display screen, the holographic projection, the televised broadcast, and the small screens in the two teams’ prep rooms, they all simultaneously presented an overview of this map.

Everyone was shocked!

In the holographic projection, what appeared onstage was a circular island peacefully floating in midair, bathed in starlight.

The pro players immediately began discussing what they saw.

“Insta-kill map?”

This was the first thing they thought.

A so-called insta-kill map referred to a map that had areas where a character’s health would instantly drop to zero. In the “Inevitable Confrontation” map of the group arena just earlier, both ends of the map had had an “intruders die” area, which made it seem like an insta-kill map. However, because those “intruders die” areas didn’t directly kill the characters, but rather relied on the NPCs attacking them, this meant that the players could still defend themselves. Therefore, “Inevitable Confrontation” couldn’t be considered an insta-kill map.

On the other hand, this Abandoned Capital in the Heavens map was floating in the air. If a character reached the edge of this map, they would fall off. This could be an insta-kill mechanism.

The final battle would take place on an insta-kill map?

The pro players all discussed amongst themselves.

The more important a match, the more a team would tend to be conservative and cautious. Unexpected things tended to happen on insta-kill maps, so if a team had the choice, they would tend not to select an insta-kill map for an important match. Everyone hoped to achieve victory through their own strength and hard work, rather than be suppressed by this kind of unexpectedness.

Yet now, the final battle of the playoffs was taking place on an insta-kill map?

Just as everyone was talking about this, they suddenly saw a veil of light expanding above the island, eventually enveloping the entire map. Next, a simple explanation appeared, and the first sentence ended the pro players’ discussion.

This was not an insta-kill map. The shroud of light would protect characters from falling off of the island.

The pro players instantly starting booing.

Couldn’t have said that earlier! Made everyone discuss for nothing.

The camera zoomed in, beginning to display the features of this map.

A bleak and desolate expanse of ruins appeared before everyone’s eyes. Two structures that looked like Aztec pyramids were the most preserved features of these ruins. A quiet river flowed behind the two structures, and on the other side was a tranquil stretch of forest. Bathed in starlight, the tree trunks, leaves, the shades of gray all seemed to be tinted a faint blue.

In front of the two structures, trees were also growing out of the city ruins, quietly erasing the remnants of this ancient city.

As the various pro players saw this map, they automatically began drawing up strategies and how they would play, based on their team’s style and class roster. And Happy and Samsara, after seeing this map, began to formally decide their roster for the team battle.

The atmosphere in Samsara’s prep room had been oppressive this whole time. After being overtaken by the opponent performing that kind of 1v3, their morale would take a blow, no matter how strong or solid their confidence was. Right now, everyone was fairly depressed.

At times like these, someone needed to say something. But Samsara’s captain was Zhou Zekai, who’d had a flawless performance in the group arena. Forcing him to say something now would just be too hard on him.

Vice-captain Jiang Botao was usually the one who led the motivational words and such before a match, but in the group arena just now, he had been the anchor who was unable to stop Tang Rou from playing a 1v3 and completing Happy’s comeback. He was part of the reason for damaging Samsara’s morale, so if he said something now, the effect probably wouldn’t be very good. Jiang Botao clearly understood this point, and so he didn’t say anything either.

So, when they returned to their prep room, the first to open their mouth was actually Sun Xiang.

“Everyone, get your spirits up! It’s only one point, all we need to do is win it back in the team competition,” Sun Xiang said.

These were the words, this was the logic, everyone nodded after hearing it, but after that… there was no after that.

Everyone heard Sun Xiang’s words, and they tried to snap out of it, but ultimately this depression in their hearts couldn’t be dispelled.

At that moment, the map that they would be using for the team competition was announced.

“Let’s look at the map first,” Fang Minghua said.

The prep room quieted down. Everyone watched the map introduction.

Very soon, the introduction finished.

Abandoned Capital in the Heavens, it floated in midair, very close to the stars, but the contents of this map weren’t especially new or unique. It was just another environment that they weren’t too familiar with.

But faced with this unfamiliar environment, they still needed some strategy and planning. Before that, they needed to decide on their roster, so that their plans could be specific.

Everyone realized what was about to happen next. Samsara’s reserve players, even though they knew that it was extremely unlikely that they would be appearing in this finals match, still couldn’t help but hold a sliver of hope in their hearts.

Who would be fighting in the final match?

Fang Minghua finally spoke once again: “Boyuan, your condition today isn’t too good.”

Lu Boyuan was startled.

He knew what Fang Minghua meant by these words, and he was saddened. Of course, he didn’t want to lose the chance to appear in the final battle, but he knew that Fang Minghua spoke the truth. Last match he hadn’t been in good condition, and during the two days’ rest he was in deep sorrow as he made up his mind to play well today. Yet, it hadn’t played out the way he’d hoped.

The team hadn’t immediately given up on him when they’d seen his subpar condition. They gave him time to adjust. But now, in the team battle that would determine the final victory, this truly wasn’t the time to place a bet on whether he could settle back into his normal condition.

“Yes…” Lu Boyuan was saddened, but he wasn’t surprised. He couldn’t let his subpar condition continue to drag down the team. He accepted Fang Minghua’s judgment, and he would respect the decision that was coming.

Fang Minghua discussed with Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao for a few moments, and finally this decision was announced.

“Then, Boyuan, you can take a break during the team battle!” Ultimately, it was Jiang Botao, as vice-captain, who made the announcement.

“Understood.” Lu Boyuan nodded. He was unhappy, but the team’s victory was the most important. Individual feelings had to be set aside for now.

“Team competition, Wu Qi, you’ll replace Boyuan in the starting lineup,” Jiang Botao announced.

“Alright.” Wu Qi nodded.

Before Sun Xiang had joined, Lu Boyuan, Wu Qi, and Du Ming were all part of Samsara’s main roster. After Sun Xiang had joined and firmly taken up one spot, there were only two spots left for the three of them.

Lu Boyuan was an All-Star, somewhat more famous than the other two, so his spot was naturally a bit more stable. Thus, Wu Qi and Du Ming entered into rotation.

Last match, Wu Qi hadn’t played. This time, now that Lu Boyuan’s condition wasn’t good, this player who’d also been a main part of their consecutive championship roster finally had the chance to play in the final battle. Even though his popularity was a bit lower than Lu Boyuan’s, within the team, everyone had the same trust in him as they did for every other player.

“Play well!” Lu Boyuan was the first to go up, patting Wu Qi’s arm.

“I will.” Wu Qi nodded. He didn’t seem very outwardly excited.

At this moment, Du Ming’s heart was beating very rapidly.

Wu Qi’s spot was confirmed, and Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, Sun Xiang, Fang Minghua, the spots of these four players were very set. Then for the final spot, would he be playing?

Even though Du Ming frequently appeared in the starting roster, his position wasn’t stable. Even Lu Boyuan had been switched off, which instantly caused him to worry. After all, he had been 1v3’d in the group arena…

“Du Ming.”

But just as he was worrying, he suddenly heard his name called. Du Ming immediately stood up.

“Team competition, you’ll be sixth player.”

“Ah? Oh!” Du Ming was overjoyed. But he was considerate of Lu Boyuan, who’d just been switched off, so all he did was quietly clench his fist.

After that, it was basically a formality to announce Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, Sun Xiang, and Fang Minghua. No one would think that these players would sit on the bench for such a critical match, unless they were in really bad condition.

“Then, let us six players chase that one point!” Fang Minghua said, after the roster was finalized.

No fierce speeches, no light humor. But in the very normal process of studying the map and deciding the roster, the mood of the Samsara players gradually returned to normal. When the roster was finalized and they announced they were going to win this point, everyone’s spirits were jolted.

For the championship. Everyone was very clear on what they’d been chasing all this time.

Did it need to be said?

No.

All they needed was to walk onstage, and win.

They’d done this kind of thing once, twice, three times, many many times. In these past three years, they were the team that best understood how to win.

“Let’s go!” In the end, the silent captain Zhou Zekai only said these two words. In this aspect, he really couldn’t be considered a satisfactory captain. But after saying these two words, he walked at the very front, leading all of Samsara’s players, those who would be playing and those who wouldn’t be. Together, they walked that player passageway that was neither long nor short, returning to the main stadium area.

Booing?

There was no more booing.

The booing had been to express their dissatisfaction with their earlier condition. And now, as Samsara walked toward the moments that would decide their final victory, what they needed was encouragement, and so what the fans gave them was encouragement.

Applause and cheers greeted Team Samsara’s players.

And not long after them, Happy’s players also returned to the main stadium area.

It wouldn’t be long until the final team battle began. Everyone was paying attention to the player areas, guessing at the team rosters.

The judge appeared, and called for the two teams’ players. In each of the two player areas, six players stood up.

Samsara: Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, Sun Xiang, Wu Qi, Du Ming, Fang Minghua.

Applause. No matter who from Samsara was playing, the Samsara fans in the audience would give nothing but support and well-wishes.

And Happy? They also already had six people walking toward the stage.

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Tang Rou, Qiao Yifan, Bao Rongxing, An Wenyi.

Chapter 1675 - We Will

When Samsara’s six players went onstage, everyone instantly noticed that their roster lacked Lu Boyuan, but no one was too surprised. After all, everyone had seen that he wasn’t doing too well, and so it wasn’t unexpected that he would remain sitting in the player area.

But on Happy’s side, when the six players came out without Fang Rui, everyone was shocked. Even Samsara’s fans were confused as to why Happy didn’t send Fang Rui up.

After all, in recent matches, Fang Rui’s performance had been too eye-catching. Last match, MVP, just that was enough to prove this. And today, in the group arena, even though Tang Rou had been the one to complete the comeback with her 1v3, the sound of comeback had begun with Fang Rui.

Who had been the one to ultimately take down Zhou Zekai, who’d just completed a 1v3 and whose character was still at 45%? Fang Rui!

And who had been the one to knock away most of Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s health? Also Fang Rui.

Such an outstanding performance, yet he wasn’t playing in the final battle?

Discussion began in the audience, and those who paid attention to news after matches immediately remembered the press conference of last match. They’d asked about Fang Rui, and Ye Xiu had indeed said, Fang Rui had worn himself out, and it was uncertain if he’d be able to play in the final match.

Most people had treated this as a misleading smoke bomb. Especially when Fang Rui did finally appear in the group arena, many people who remembered this started discussing it again.

But now, Fang Rui was still sitting in the player area. As Happy’s players began their final sprint toward the championship, this player on their team with the highest salary and the strongest character was watching from the sidelines.

Watching the backs of those six as they walked onstage, Fang Rui was also saddened. But he knew clearly that now wasn’t the time to challenge his own spirit and stamina. He would be better off trusting his own teammates. Happy’s players were all outstanding. Who said that they couldn’t do this without him?

“This excellent chance to shine, I leave it to you youngsters!” After returning to the prep room, this was what Fang Rui grandly announced.

He couldn’t see it himself, but from the worry revealed in the eyes of his teammates that couldn’t lie, he knew that he couldn’t hide his condition from them anymore.

“Great, leave it to me!” Steamed Bun said enthusiastically.

Fang Rui was gratified. If everyone could be like Steamed Bun, he thought, this would certainly be a very sweet world.

“Senior, you’ve worked hard.” Qiao Yifan was always rather sincere. He clearly understood the reality of the situation.

Fang Rui patted Qiao Yifan, and his attitude was also very sincere. “Without me, you guys will be the ones working very hard.”

Everyone laughed. But after laughing, they felt that these words, although shameless, were true. Fang Rui’s strength, Boundless Sea’s strength, were stronger than the new players and new accounts of Happy. Without him, the rest of them really would have to work very hard.

“Then we’ll work harder.” Ye Xiu nodded, and began listing names. “Team battle, me, Mucheng, Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi…”

He named four first, and those who’d been named all nodded.

Ye Xiu’s gaze turned to Tang Rou. “Tired after that 1v3?”

“I’m still sunk in regret!” Tang Rou said.

Yes, regret! Those words that Tang Rou had said after that 1v3, almost everyone thought that it was mockery, but in reality, it really was regret, pure and simple. She felt that she could still challenge more players, but unfortunately, because of the match format, there’d been none left for her to fight.

“Alright, you’re about to have five – no, six more opponents,” Ye Xiu said. “Team battle, we five will start, and then, sixth player…”

His gaze swept over. Luo Ji’s heart rate quickened, and it became difficult for him to breathe. Will it be me? The finals? Final battle? Me? I’m nervous! But, I’m excited…

These imaginings were suddenly shoved into the wall by Steamed Bun.

“Move aside, this sort of thing should obviously be left to the eldest brother!” Steamed Bun said.

“Mm, sixth player will be Steamed Bun!” Ye Xiu announced, and then he quickly explained to Luo Ji, “But it’s not because you can’t beat him!”

“I understand…” Luo Ji nodded. And standing in the corner, Mo Fan, who always had an emotionless expression, now showed a flicker of disappointment across his face. But he didn’t step forward to try and argue anything, and only squeezed his hands into fists.

Ye Xiu saw it, and he knew that Mo Fan was very dissatisfied. Of the five people who’d appeared in the group arena, he was the only one who’d accomplished nothing, all because he didn’t know the design of the map and accidentally triggered the ambushing troops. In the end, no matter how hard he tried, he’d still lost completely.

Mo Fan wasn’t in poor condition. If not for that accident, no one knew how that battle would have played out.

But in the end, Ye Xiu still chose not to have Mo Fan appear in the team battle.

Mo Fan didn’t say anything, but Ye Xiu still gave him an explanation. What he said was simply what he’d told him long before, a sentence that was very simple and very ordinary: “For now, you’re still not used to playing in the team battle.”

Mo Fan’s face was still expressionless, like every time Ye Xiu said anything to him. But this time, his fists, which were already clenched, tightened further.

It wasn’t that he hadn’t played in a team battle before. During the regular season, Ye Xiu would still sometimes put him into the team battle. But unfortunately, after this season, although Mo Fan had made breakthroughs in his individual technique, he was still lacking when it came to playing in a team. Perhaps it was because of his natural personality, but even though he understood that team battles required teammates to coordinate, his performance was still extremely mechanical and clumsy.

Not used to it, not suitable for it…

Other people could see it, and Mo Fan himself could feel it even more clearly. Ye Xiu only repeated this point, but it was convincing enough, because that was just the reason.

And then, Wei Chen.

For him, Ye Xiu also had an explanation, but it was only two words.

“You understand,” Ye Xiu said.

“You bastard, don’t you dare lose!” Wei Chen slapped Ye Xiu.

“Every season you were here, I was the champion,” Ye Xiu said.

“Fuck!” Wei Chen’s expression darkened, but it was the truth. During those two seasons, he and Ye Xiu had still been enemies.

“So this time, it should be the same,” Ye Xiu said.

“As long as we win, I’ll be your mascot,” Wei Chen said vehemently.

“Mascot…” Everyone stared at Wei Chen.

“How disgusting, just give me a cigarette!” Ye Xiu said decisively.

Let’s go, the final battle!

Happy walked out of the prep room. And now, Ye Xiu was walking with five others onto this ultimate battlefield.

Once again, standing in this moment.

Ye Xiu felt it was very familiar, and yet at the same time, not.

Cheers, shouts, applause, it was all for the title that was about to be claimed.

Who will be the champions?

“We will!” Samsara’s six players said.

“We will!” Happy’s six players also said.

The battle began.

Chapter 1676 - Came, Left

The battle began, the map loaded, the characters loaded.

The abandoned capital floating in the sky seemed so close to the stars. The entire world seemed to be in only one color, that gray-white suffused with a hint of pale blue. Under this starlight, even the multicolored equipment of the characters who had just loaded in seemed to be layered over with this light.

Soft Mist lifted her spear, One Inch Ash gripped his tachi, and they waited for Ye Xiu's instructions.

Ye Xiu was a seasoned veteran, from the Glory game to the professional stage, there was nothing he hadn't experienced before. But in this moment, he couldn't help but feel emotion swelling in his heart.

From a small Level 1 character in the new server, after two and a half years, he was finally standing here once again. Right now, the two standing in front of him were the ones who had been walking alongside him since that very beginning. Aside from them, there was also Steamed Bun, still waiting in the substitute area, ready to come onstage at any time. And Su Mucheng, who had experienced with him the defeat they'd suffered the last time he was in this moment.

It was this group of people. Two and a half years ago, they were still in the new server of Glory, fighting with the pioneers of the other team guilds for dungeon records.

Today, after two and a half years, they were directly engaged with Glory's top team, striving for that proof of ultimate glory, the championship.

They did it!

Ye Xiu knew that, in this moment, there were certainly countless people who thought this. Starting from a new server, starting from zero, starting over, and at last, reaching the finals. It was simply incredible.

Yes, it was indeed incredible.

But, did that mean that they'd done it? Did this count as success?

Not yet.

The standard dictionary definition of "success" was obtaining the anticipated outcome. Achieving a goal, that was called success. The result they'd anticipated, the goal they wished to achieve, there was only one: winning the championship!

Thus, they were still one step away from success.

"Start!"

Ye Xiu's order came down, and Lord Grim took the first step outward, closely followed by the other four Happy players.

"Start! Is Ye Xiu treating this as running a dungeon or killing a Boss? Still saying 'start'?" In the broadcast, Pan Lin was chuckling, ridiculing Ye Xiu's choice of word.

"Heh, these people here, most of them were players Ye Xiu pulled from in-game!" Li Yibo said. Happy had been playing the Alliance for a year now, and they'd garnered such attention as they fought their way into the finals. They'd accepted a number of interviews by now, and everyone knew a lot about their history. Aside from Su Mucheng and Fang Rui, who had officially transferred, the rest of them, including Blue Rain's former captain Wei Chen, were all people that Ye Xiu had encountered in-game and pulled together to build this Team Happy.

In the beginning, they might have really been like what many ordinary gamers were familiar with, just a group of close friends in-game. But after they'd fought down this road together, this group of close friends was already standing on Glory's highest stage.

Start!

This time, their goal was no longer any dungeon record, or a wild Boss; it was Team Samsara, it was the championship.

Happy's spawn point was on the west, and right now, the five of them were moving eastward in formation. There weren't any clear road signs or markings on the map, but Happy's direction was quite clear; they were headed toward the western Aztec-style pyramid. Once they were close, however, they didn't stop below this pyramid, nor did they climb it. They turned north and circled around to the back of the pyramid.

The back side winked with light. It was impossible to see if the tranquil river was flowing. Happy tested how deep the water ran, but they didn't take the water route. They simply continued east along the back of the pyramid.

From this moment, everyone became even more vigilant. The five characters' views were pointed in five different directions, covering every inch of their surroundings. Theoretically, even if the two teams were moving toward each other at the highest speed, it was still too early for them to meet. Even so, after the experience of last round, where the teams' spawn points were random and not necessarily opposite each other, both Happy and Samsara included this possibility in their calculations, and entered battle condition early.

Soon, Happy's five reached the end of the pyramid's back. The other pyramid that was still intact now entered their sight, and then, they saw the silhouettes of Samsara's five.

Samsara's choice in the beginning of the match was also to first reach the pyramid that was close to them, but afterward, unlike Happy, they hadn't continued to advance. After reaching the pyramid, they began to investigate the surrounding area. Right now, the five characters were all studying, and although they seemed to be scattered, in reality, they maintained a formation that allowed them to coordinate battle at any moment.

When Happy walked out from behind the pyramid and saw Samsara, Samsara also immediately saw Happy. In that moment, both sides stopped moving. They maintained their distance and observed from afar.

The scene was still, but their chats instantly began flying with messages.

Because it was a completely unknown map, they couldn't make any detailed plans based off of the simple introduction given right before the battle. In battles on random maps, there was significantly more communication and direction. Now that the two teams saw each other, Samsara's side instantly began laying out plans, messages flashing out one after another. There was rapid discussion, and a final conclusion. But the players' characters didn't move, not until the messages practically filled the screen. Finally, there was a message: "Go!"

Everyone had read every line of instructions. When the final order came, the five players and the five characters began moving simultaneously.

Long-range, short-range, healer, each of the classes performed their duties and joined together, taking advantage of the special characteristics of the map that they'd observed so far. They swiftly arranged themselves in a satisfactory formation.

And then, on Happy's side, an order was finally issued as well.

"Retreat," said Ye Xiu.

Happy left.

They'd arrived casually from the back of the pyramid, without probing, without spying. The five characters had rushed out as though pressed for time, and stopped as soon as they saw Samsara.

And then Samsara had carefully arranged themselves, making all sorts of preparations for battle, able to advance and attack, able to retreat and defend. They'd taken everything into consideration.

And then Happy retreated.

Samsara had actively prepared everything, but they didn't have an opponent…

"..."

In the channel, Zhou Zekai sent a rare message. It was just a string of ellipses. Even though he didn't speak much in the first place, "reticence" and "speechlessness" were still two very different moods.

"What's Happy doing?" Pan Lin exclaimed. Over on Samsara's side, because of the numerous communications and instructions, even though there were many code-like abbreviations, everyone could still understand the basics. But Happy's side had no communications. Ye Xiu said "start," and they'd set out; Ye Xiu said "retreat," and they'd withdrawn.

"Mm, watch for now," Li Yibo said. It wasn't clear whether "watch for now" referred to Happy's plan, or was directing the audience to simply watch for now…

Right now, the ones who wanted to understand Happy's plan the most was still Samsara. But they didn't make any move. After expressing speechlessness, they immediately resumed their investigation of the area, as though Happy had never appeared.

No clash, just a sighting.

The ordinary gamers were baffled, and the broadcast commentators needed to "watch for now," but the pro players were already beginning to discuss.

"Happy… probably wants to sound out Samsara's mood?" Yu Wenzhou said. Happy's plan, that basically meant Ye Xiu's plan. It wasn't just Pan Lin and Li Yibo, even Yu Wenzhou, a master-level player, didn't dare to speak confidently.

"Samsara seems very steady," Xiao Shiqin said. Things on the psychological level weren't easy to see through. But just from the way that Samsara ignored Happy's baiting-like movement, at least they weren't carelessly led by the nose by Happy.

Then, what next?

Next, the broadcast screen and the live projection were both split in two, so that everyone could clearly see both sides' movements.

Samsara continued to investigate that area, Happy began to move upward along the pyramid from the back side. But Ye Xiu's Lord Grim, after walking about halfway up, suddenly circled around from the back of the pyramid.

Samsara, naturally, was waiting for any movement from this side. As soon as they saw Lord Grim appear, they immediately had preparations.

"Don't panic!" Ye Xiu actually sent a message in the chat.

"I just came to take a look," said Ye Xiu, and then his Lord Grim actually just sat down right there on the eastern slope of that pyramid…

"You guys keep working," Ye Xiu continued.

"Little Zhou, look at 3 o'clock behind you, isn't that platform perfect for some sniping cover?" Ye Xiu actually began to point out things to Samsara.

Chapter 1677 - Hitting the Mountain to Warn the Tiger

Everyone was stunned!

This was the finals, the final battle, the moment that would decide the outcome of a year of hard work!

Unity, tension, seriousness, those should all be expected, but surely they could pass on liveliness?

Yet now, while Samsara was very seriously studying the environment and preparing for battle, what was Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim doing? He was like a hooligan. A hooligan would be squatting at the intersection just next to the school and whistling at the cute girls that passed by; Lord Grim was sitting on the pyramid and throwing all sorts of critical comments at Samsara.

This scene wasn’t right. It wasn’t serious!

But no matter how wrong it was, Ye Xiu was doing just this, and the words were already spoken. This match simply had this kind of style and rhythm. It still had to be watched, and the explanation and analysis still had to be made, no?

And so the broadcast followed what Ye Xiu said, cutting to a close-up shot of the 3 o’clock direction behind Cloud Piercer, particularly that “platform” that Ye Xiu mentioned.

Once this close-up was given, everyone took a look, and those that understood realized that Ye Xiu’s words were completely correct. This location really was a very good sniping point.

“Ah, Little Jiang, your Wave Slash can completely lock that path on your left, did you realize?”

“Wu Qi, that ambush point in the 11 o’clock direction is a pretty good place to hide!”

“Minghua, did you find the best place to heal from? If you found it, then go and stand there, what are you still spinning around for?

“And also, guy using One Autumn Leaf, did you notice the distance between those two broken walls behind One Autumn Leaf? If Evil Annihilation is held horizontally, it can’t pass through that space. Did you guys increase Evil Annihilation’s length? It wouldn’t have been like this before.”

In an instant, one sentence per person. The broadcast couldn’t even keep up switching back and forth between shots, and ultimately just split the screen into multiple sections. These four people who were pointed out by Ye Xiu, each got their own section of the screen…

Everyone immediately realized, just like when he’d been talking to Zhou Zekai, Ye Xiu wasn’t just making things up. The things he’d pointed out about these four players, whether big or small, were all very real issues.

But would the Samsara pros really be incapable of discovering these things themselves? Of course not. After all, they’d been investigating this area for longer than Ye Xiu had. But the thing was, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had just casually sat down on the pyramid and casually said these things, yet every needle he’d sent had drawn blood. This demonstrated his skill. Added on to his bearing, it really felt like he was giving pointers to Samsara.

“Immature!”

“Shameless!”

“Disgusting!”

A few Samsara fans decried Ye Xiu’s actions. It had to be said, trash talk could sometimes attack even the audience.

But those who were at a higher level, especially the pro players, knew that this wasn’t that simple. Ye Xiu’s actions weren’t just to show off from above. He was hitting the mountain to startle the tiger, warning Samsara by saying: be careful, I can see through all of your plans.

And to be able to do this, Ye Xiu had made good use of the map.

The two pyramids on this map could be called the high points, but because they were so large, even a Launcher, the class with the longest attack range, could not effectively use supportive attacks when standing on the very peak. Furthermore, attacks from halfway up the pyramid would be extremely limited. Therefore, the high points of these pyramids could only be used as observation points, not any strategic points.

Thus, Ye Xiu discovered the reconnaissance use of this location, and looking down upon them, he began to analyze Samsara’s deployment. Before anything else, he was attacking Samsara on a psychological level. If Samsara could not restrain themselves and immediately came to attack Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, then they would definitely suffer for it.

Lord Grim didn’t need to be mentioned, and the other four Happy players were already prepared at another side of the pyramid. If Samsara came their way to attack, Happy would have the map advantage.

But when it came to pro players, the chances of that happening were far too small. In this kind of critical battle, Samsara definitely would not take an action like this that would put them at a clear disadvantage.

But Happy still prepared for this possibility. Even though this was such a small chance, they would not pass it up.

Samsara, as expected, was not so hasty. After being criticized by Ye Xiu, they only hesitated for a moment, but afterward, everyone began to carefully discuss in their team chat. Directly charge Lord Grim, sitting halfway up the pyramid? That possibility wasn’t even mentioned.

The match seemed to be locked in a stalemate.

The small chance that Happy had hoped for didn’t happen, and Samsara, having had all their plans and strategies exposed by the opponent, weren’t sure how to continue.

Switch to an area that Happy couldn’t observe? Then what if Happy just didn’t come? Would this battle of this match be triggered by the judge getting involved and forcing the two teams to meet?

Happy was patiently waiting for Samsara’s movements, and Ye Xiu wasn’t idle. He helpfully named another few places on the map for Samsara to use, even some that accounted for strategic coordination between the players.

Samsara was finally no longer silent.

“God Ye has seen through us completely!” Vice-captain Jiang Botao spoke.

“What, like it’s hard?” Ye Xiu said.

“Since you’ve seen through us, why not come give it a try and attack?” Jiang Botao said.

It was a very clear provocation, so clear that it was uninteresting.

“Sure, coming.”

Who would have thought that Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim actually just stood up, and Happy’s other four players immediately appeared on the side of the pyramid and began to charge down.

“Beat them at their own game, make the opponents second-guess.” Watching the match, Tiny Herb’s Wang Jiexi guessed at the intent behind Ye Xiu’s actions.

Such a clear provocation, yet Happy had actually directly accepted it. In Samsara’s shoes, who wouldn’t be second-guessing? Wang Jiexi had the omniscient view, and could see Happy’s team chat, so he knew that Ye Xiu hadn’t given any detailed strategic instructions to Happy. If not for that, he might also be wondering whether Ye Xiu actually had a strategy that could break through their arrangement.

“He definitely doesn’t. If he did, he would have attacked way earlier.”

“Right, and Happy doesn’t have any plans in their team chat. This is a random map, they only just saw this map for a bit from above. Their communication through glances isn’t that incredible, right?”

“Yeah, it’s just a false show of strength, to make Samsara worry.”

“Then after that?”

The pro players were all discussing, and their opinions were essentially the same as Wang Jiexi’s. But after that, they all got stuck on this question.

After that?

Let Samsara second-guess, and then? And then Happy would just charge forth and chaotically fight, without any sort of plan?

That was completely illogical!

This was an advantage of random maps for the audience. Because the teams couldn’t make any secret preparations before the match, more directions were needed during the battle. The strategic plans of the two teams could be completely seen from their team chats.

But right now, Happy had actually had no plans. This was simply too irrational.

What were they trying to do?

Chapter 1678 - Wording

Was it a feint? Or was it a bluff?

There seemed to be only these two possibilities. Which one was it?

The viewers were merely guessing for the fun of it, but for Samsara, the guessing would affect whether they won or lost this match.

As a result, Samsara’s guess was crucial. Everyone was staring intently at Samsara’s team chat, observing the rapid discussion taking place there.

Samsara didn’t hesitate. They didn’t waver because of these possibilities because they didn’t even bother discussing whether it was a feint or a bluff. From the beginning, the direction of Samsara’s discussion was to look for a solution to both possibilities.

Samsara rushed out.

Whether it was a feint or a bluff, Ye Xiu was targeting their understanding of the terrain. Samsara had given up on utilizing the area that they were familiar with. Instead, they chose to leave and welcome Happy directly.

Did Ye Xiu’s words really have that much of a psychological impact on them?

Not necessarily!

But Samsara didn’t lower their guard. It was similar to when Happy had been on top of the pyramid, fully prepared in the unlikely scenario that Samsara would brainlessly charge up the pyramid. In contrast, instead of just being prepared, Samsara wanted to eliminate even the unlikeliest of scenarios.

Because of Ye Xiu’s imposing air, everyone felt like the atmosphere of the match had been ruined. In reality, from these small details and from the way both teams approached this fight, the atmosphere wasn’t ruined at all. It was completely in line with how the finals should be: careful and cautious as if this was their last hope, refusing to let even the slightest possibility go.

Finally, the two teams met.

Samsara charged out from the ruins, while Happy charged down from above the pyramid, losing their height advantage.

The two sides gradually approached, intentionally controlling their pace. Their footsteps were neither too fast nor too slow.

Dancing Rain raised her handcannon. Cloud Piercer raised his dual guns. These two long-ranged classes were about to enter each other’s attack range.

But the first to erupt wasn’t the two long-ranged attackers, but Happy’s team chat.

“An, fall back.”

“Tang, right, go around 3.”

“Qiao, right, follow 2.”

“Su, stay back, go high.”

Four orders in quick succession. Go around three? Follow two? Most of the viewers were confused. A few of the more attentive ones, who paid attention to how teams communicated with each other, could understand the general meaning behind these two phrases.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo, the two commentators, had to be mentioned. Even though the two often made mistakes in their analysis, the two were quite diligent with their work. If they weren’t skilled enough to understand the team’s intentions, then there wasn’t much they could do about it. However, the two had spent time going over things that could be studied like how the team shot callers worded their orders to the team.

Although Happy was a new team, their shotcalling style and wording wasn’t too strange. After all, their shot caller was Ye Xiu, who had led Excellent Era for close to eight years. His same shotcalling habits had been brought over to Happy, so Pan Lin and Li Yibo didn’t need to put in much effort to grasp it again.

Most people were confused by the phrases like “go around three” and “follow two”, but Pan Lin was already yelling in astonishment: “Go around three? Follow two? This map…”

Pan Lin’s astonishment wasn’t towards Ye Xiu’s arrangements but the way he worded his orders. Because from what he understood, the phrases “go around three” and “follow two” were frequently used in their home game matches. In other words, they really only used these phrases in maps that they were familiar with.

The numbers “two” and “three” weren’t coordinates, but rather an agreed upon direction. It was suitable for some maps, while unsuitable for others. But for a random map…

A random map?

Pan Lin blanked. Li Yibo had realized it faster than Pan Lin. He had been trying to piece together his understanding of these two phrases and the map’s terrain, and he soon discovered that the pieces fit together perfectly.

“This terrain…”

“Happy had observed this terrain from up on top of the pyramid,” Li Yibo said.

“But they never communicated anything about it in the team chat!” Pan Lin said.

“Certain agreed upon things don’t need to be communicated…” Li Yibo said.

Changes had begun happening in Happy’s formation. Tang Rou and Qiao Yifan started moving towards the right, while Su Mucheng and An Wenyi had started moving back. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim started moving to the left, leaving the front completely open.

For a moment, Happy’s healer was in Samsara’s direct line of sight. This seemed to be a good opportunity for them to charge right through the middle to him, but Ye Xiu, Tang Rou, and Qiao Yifan were clearly planning on surrounding them.

A pincer?

It looked like one!

But seeing the orders “go around three” and “follow two,” Li Yibo explained that Happy’s intentions were to “separate the enemies!”

A random map has its advantages!

Li Yibo sighed with emotion. His eyes were practically brimming with tears of excitement. If every match had shot callers clearly listing out their team’s every move, then he would never make humiliating mistakes in his analysis. Communication through glances, tacit understanding, Li Yibo hated those deeply.

“Let’s see how Samsara will respond. Right now is indeed a good opportunity for them to directly go for Happy’s healer, but that would only be the case if Happy’s goal is to pincer them. In reality, Happy’s goal is to separate Samsara, as a counter to Samsara’s attempt to charge straight through the middle…” Li Yibo said.

“What will Samsara do… they haven’t said anything in their team chat, but they’re starting to make adjustments too…” Pan Lin shouted, “Cloud Piercer is lined up in the middle, One Autumn Leaf in front, healer at the center, Jiang Botao and Wu Qi behind… Samsara is planning on engaging in a frontal assault!!”

A frontal assault?

The expressions on the spectating pro players were grave.

That was what their formation looked like, but it was too early to tell if that was their plan. Pan Lin elaborated on the positions of each of Samsara’s players, but he didn’t go in order of when they moved into position.

This ordering was crucial. Communication through glances was done starting from one character, creating a butterfly effect where everyone else would react and fall into place. Samsara’s change in formation had started with Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer, and Pan Lin had mentioned him first. By the time he had started discussing this point, Samsara’s formation had been completed. He had just been going in order from front to back. But if you looked more closely, there was a difference in who moved first and who moved later. Zhou Zekai had been the first to move because he was the team’s core. Next was Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves, and then Fang Minghua, Wu Qi, and finally Sun Xiang.

Sun Xiang moving last wasn’t because he was the new player on the team or because he was the most lacking in synergy with the team.

It was actually the opposite. Sun Xiang moving last was precisely the reason for why the ordering mattered.

If Samsara had truly been planning on a full frontal assault, Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf, the team’s spearpoint, should have been the fastest to react to Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer. Because this frontal assault would be led by him. He needed to be the first to act so that the others could respond to his actions accordingly.

But he moved last. The average viewer might not find anything strange about it, but to the pro players, it was suspicious. If Samsara’s intentions were for a frontal assault, then this would be considered a mistake on Sun Xiang’s part for being absent-minded.

However, this wasn’t a mistake!

The steadiness that Samsara displayed in their formation gave the pro players a sense that Sun Xiang’s lateness was to cover up something.

But what was it?

There wouldn’t be a replay for it. For a moment, no one could see through it. They could only wait and see what would happen next.

Samsara continued forward!

It really did look like they planned on charging straight for Happy’s healer.

Happy’s left and right flank had formed and were beginning to converge…

Charge!

A character suddenly rushed out from Samsara’s formation towards Happy’s healer.

One Autumn Leaf?

No, Cloud Piercer!

Samsara’s offense had begun, but the one at the front was Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer!

Chapter 1679 - Interrupt

The sound of a gunshot wasn’t surprising to anyone.

Long-ranged classes almost always made the first attack. However, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer didn’t just attack, he charged forward. In the blink of an eye, Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf was left behind.

What kind of rhythm was this?

Everyone watching was astonished, but their doubts didn’t last long. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer started attacking, and the rest of Team Samsara soon followed.

Did they attack too?

No!

None of the other four players coordinated attacks with Zhou Zekai. The four characters contracted the formation.

One Autumn Leaf, Laughing Song, Cruel Silence, the three of them formed a triangle, protecting the one in the center: Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves.

Empty Waves began casting. Magic started to emanate around his shortsword, Divine Chain, as if it were trying to establish a connection with some sort of power.

Lightning Wave Formation!

The experienced players noticed the sparks of lightning flashing from Divine Chain and its surroundings, and deduced what Empty Waves was casting.

The pro players immediately figured out Samsara’s plans.

It didn’t matter whether Happy was trying to surround or separate them with a pincer. Under the protection of the Spellblade’s Lightning Formation, Samsara would not be in danger. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer became Samsara’s main attacker, while the other four became his support. Samsara wasn’t going to give Happy even the slightest opportunity.

“Can Happy interrupt it?” Pan Lin spoke. He realized where the crucial point lay.

The cameraman quickly switched viewpoints. The focus was first given to Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain. Then, the camera moved towards Empty Waves. Empty Waves’ position was very subtle. It was just outside of Dancing Rain’s range.

The camera turned again to Happy’s other long-ranged character: Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu. Countless people were looking forward to what he would do. He always seemed to be able to do the impossible. Sure enough, Lord Grim started to move. He had originally been hiding in the ruins. Suddenly, with a flicker, he came out from behind a broken wall.

Gunshot!

But no sound could be heard.

Because gunshots had been ringing the entire time. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer had open fired. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim sudden gunshot was perfectly in line with one of Cloud Piercer’s gunshots. The two overlapped, one obscuring the other. The only sign that Lord Grim had fired his gun was a flash of light.

Everything had happened in an instant. The broadcast couldn’t keep up with these changes just by switching between viewpoints.

Fortunately, for the live audience, the stadium’s projection technology allowed them to see a more comprehensive view of the battlefield. It was just that the details needed to be caught by the viewer themselves.

Bang!

A seemingly silent bullet shot out and exploded.

Lightning was still crackling around Empty Waves’ Divine Chains. Lightning began to gather around, creating a net of electricity.

The interrupt failed!

The bullet had been blocked by a jet-black streak of light.

Spear, Evil Annihilation!

The awe-inspiring One Autumn Leaf stood in Ye Xiu’s way, putting a stop to his plans. This wasn’t the first time, but no matter how many times Chen Guo saw this scene, she would always feel uncomfortable.

The gunshot was blocked, and it was no longer possible for Ye Xiu to try again. Lord Grim couldn’t even see Empty Waves anymore from his position.

Move, get to another position…

But the cast time for Lightning Wave Formation wasn’t very long. There wasn’t much Ye Xiu could do in that short window.

There wasn’t anything more Lord Grim could do…

But Happy’s plan was to pincer Samsara from two sides. The left wing had been blocked, but the right wing had only just started.

The two players on the right wing didn’t have long-ranged capabilities. To interrupt Empty Waves, they needed to get close.

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist rushed forward!

“Too impulsive!”

“How crazy!”

The pro players let out sighs. They clearly didn’t agree with Tang Rou’s decision. The other side had four people in a fully defensive formation, yet she wanted to get close and break through it? She was practically sending herself into the tiger’s mouth. Even if she successfully interrupted Empty Waves, what next? Soft Mist would be surrounded by four players. Even if Ye Xiu and Qiao Yifan were close by, Happy would be in a very bad position.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Soft Mist charged forward as if she were unstoppable, bringing her unrelenting momentum from her 1v3 in the group arena.

“Uh, maybe actually?”

Seeing her grandeur, some of the people who felt like Tang Rou had been too impulsive suddenly weren’t sure anymore. They felt like maybe she really could break through Samsara.

Samsara responded as if they were facing a huge threat. They needed to put their all into their defense, but the one who stepped forward to face Soft Mist made everyone surprised.

Laughing Song?

Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song, Samsara’s healer, looked like he was planning on stopping Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

“How is that possible?” Countless people cried out in astonishment. Laughing Song raised his cross, Angel’s Protection, and began casting a spell.

This is…

A white light flew out in front of Laughing Song.

Halo Smash!

A Paladin skill. At max rank, it was an unbreakable shield whether it was magic or physical, no attack could break past it.

But Laughing Song was a Cleric. This Halo Smash was a bonus skill on his weapon, and could only be at rank one. How could a rank one Halo Smash stop Soft Mist’s Dragon Breaks the Ranks?

The pro players quickly calculated in their heads.

Halo Smash. Even at max rank, it would only be able to just barely block the attack. But at rank one? Dragon Breaks the Ranks would be mitigated somewhat, but Laughing Song would certainly take a huge hit.

But then again, looking at his positioning, as long as he could mitigate the blow, Empty Waves would be protected. Soft Mist would no longer be able to interrupt Empty Waves’ cast. Then… there was no then. Her attempt would be done. The cast would be completed. Soft Mist’s Dragon Breaks would be stopped, and she would no longer have any more opportunities.

Samsara was different though. Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence had his dagger ready for when Soft Mist and Laughing Song collided.

Silent Thunder!

This was the name of the dagger in his hands. It kept a low-profile, almost invisible inside Cruel Silence’s sleeves.

“As expected, it won’t work…”

Seeing Samsara’s response, everyone who had thought that maybe Tang Rou could do it suddenly changed their minds.

But to everyone’s surprise, just before Soft Mist’s Dragon Breaks the Ranks collided with Laughing Song’s Halo Smash, Tang Rou cancelled the skill.

Turn, sidestep…

Using the leftover momentum from Dragon Breaks the Ranks, Soft Mist suddenly slid to the side.

Was there an opening there?

The sudden change had astonished everyone. The others on Samsara had to put their attention on Soft Mist.

But Empty Waves wouldn’t be interrupted!

The surrounding electricity suddenly formed a net. Lightning Wave Formation had been set down.

But at the same time, on the ground where the lightning crackled, a flower of darkness quietly unfurled.

Chapter 1680 - Unevenness and Surprise

Phantom Demon! One Inch Ash!

Even though the live audience had the projections in the center of the stadium, giving them a comprehensive overview of the battlefield, many of them had still overlooked Qiao Yifan. No one had expected that from Ye Xiu to Tang Rou, both of them had only been trying to get the enemy’s attention. The one to complete the attack was Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash.

And One Inch Ash’s attack target clearly wasn’t to interrupt, but to trade.

The Lightning Wave Formation that Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves placed down was primarily for defense. It was to stop Happy from getting close to them.

In this sense, Samsara had succeeded. Neither Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim nor Tang Rou’s Soft Mist could get close. After Tang Rou cancelled Dragon Breaks the Ranks, she quickly moved away. Instead of trying to force her way in through another opening like everyone thought she would do, she ran as fast as she could out of the Lightning Wave Formation’s range.

Then, there was Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash. He didn’t get close. He didn’t need to get close. While Ye Xiu and Tang Rou attempted to interrupt Jiang Botao’s cast, he hid himself and quietly began casting his own spell. Whether the interrupt succeeded or failed, Samsara’s attention would be drawn away from him. By the time One Inch Ash appeared, he would be done casting, and it would be too late for Samsara to try and interrupt him.

Dark Boundary!

Darkness descended. The screens of four of Samsara’s players went black as if the power had been cut off.

The crowd went into an uproar.

The battle had just begun. After only a single clash, the kings, Samsara, had suffered a huge loss. There were only five of them on the field, and four of the five had been caught in the Darkness Boundary. It was truly a rare sight.

Samsara had overlooked Qiao Yifan’s existence. This was absolutely a mistake on their part. However, at the same time, Happy’s ingenious ploy had to be given credit as well.

Because of how uneven it felt!

An unevenness in skill between players was a common issue in new teams. Happy was a new team. There was Ye Xiu, one of the greatest players of all time, leading the way. Then, there was Su Mucheng and Fang Rui, two All-Stars. After that, there was just a bunch of rookies. This unevenness was extremely apparent. An Wenyi was considered Happy’s weakness precisely because of this disparity in skill.

However, Happy took advantage of this problem, creating a lot of strategies revolving around it. In this match, they once again utilized it.

Compared to An Wenyi, Qiao Yifan had never been viewed as Happy’s weak point. In fact, he was looked upon quite highly. Many Tiny Herb fans criticized the team for letting of such an outstanding player.

Qiao Yifan shouldn’t have been overlooked. The gap in skill between him and the top players on the team shouldn’t have been so apparent. However, Happy set their own pace, creating this false image.

First, Ye Xu’s Lord Grim charged out. Samsara had to focus their attention on him and answer back.

Next, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist charged out like a fierce tiger. Tang Rou had just achieved a 1v3 against them. Samsara obviously couldn’t relax against her.

The two of them quickly drew in all of Samsara’s attention. In front of their imposing presence, Qiao Yifan seemed to be invisible. It was almost inevitable.

Qiao Yifan didn’t disappoint. He seized this opportunity well. There hadn’t been any communication in Happy’s chat during this time, but each of them seemed to naturally know what to do. The pro players, who paid attention to the details, also noticed that An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands had drawn in the attention of Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain couldn’t be ignored by him either. Not only were An Wenyi and Su Mucheng defending against Zhou Zekai’s one-man assault, they were also taking away his attention. They had lured him to a position, where he wouldn’t be able to see One Inch Ash unless he turned his head back.

It seemed to just be a mistake from Samsara, but how could it be so easy for such a low-level mistake to happen to Samsara?

This was a match between the two top teams in the Alliance. Most of the time, mistakes didn’t just happen. The opposing team made the mistakes happen.

Happy had successfully set up a situation that led to Samsara making a mistake. Now, four of Samsara’s players were blinded.

“Don’t leave anyone out!” Fang Minghua reminded everyone in the team chat. Although the four of them had been blinded, they could still use the team chat.

“Everyone, forward!!” Jiang Botao shouted.

Forward? Which way was forward?

Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer was forward.

It seemed to be a fairly vague order, but everyone on Samsara immediately understood. The ones who hadn’t been facing forward turned around. Despite being blinded, they were pretty close.

Afterwards, move.

No disorder could be seen. The team moved together as one. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves swung his sword again.

Nebula Wave Slash!

He unexpectedly went with this Level 75 skill. It could be considered as quite wasteful just for defense, but wastefulness had its value. Tang Rou had originally been planning on rushing into the Lightning Wave Formation to attack them, but she had no choice but to change her mind. Although Jiang Botao was blinded, he was able to create a powerful barrier around the four of them with Nebula Wave Sword.

However, moving together as one wasn’t exactly the wisest choice to escape from a ghost boundary. This was because the enemy Ghostblade could just set up another ghost boundary wherever they were going towards, catching them in another net.

Samsara did it anyways because they had one person who had not been caught.

Zhou Zekai, Cloud Piercer.

After seeing his teammates’ movements, he immediately started assisting them. His first task was to stop Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash from placing down another ghost boundary.

Turn fire!

The bullets flying towards Little Cold Hands instantly shifted towards One Inch Ash. However, Cloud Piercer couldn’t actually see One Inch Ash from his position. Even so, with the help from his teammates, he could get a rough approximation of One Inch Ash’s location. His attacks might all miss, but they would still seal off the areas where ghost boundaries could be placed.

One step, two steps…

Samsara’s four players stayed together, and it looked like they would soon exit the range of the Darkness Boundary. Zhou Zekai didn’t need to protect them for long.

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain fired artillery shells at him to interfere. Tang Rou’s Soft Mist dashed over. It looked like she wanted to body block Cloud Piercer’s bullets.

Troublesome!

Zhou Zekai immediately had Cloud Piercer move. No matter what, he needed to stop One Inch Ash from placing down another ghost boundary. This moment was crucial!

It’s coming!

One Inch Ash stopped moving. Only a tiny bit of it peeked out. He had a clear view, and he was positioned at the right angle. He had finished casting his ghost boundary. He just needed to set it down. He swung his tachi, and Soft Mist was just about to reach him.

A gunshot. The ghost soul’s power began to spread from One Inch Ash’s blade.

It’s impossible!

The stadium screens and the broadcast showed Cloud Piercer’s perspective. There was no One Inch Ash in his line of sight. Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had covered him completely. This bullet would definitely be blocked.

Pu!

A hit.

Blood spurted into the air from the bullet wound. Tang Rou didn’t feel Soft Mist get hit, but then, the ghost god’s power began to fade from One Inch Ash’s weapon.

It hit?

Qiao Yifan himself couldn’t believe it, but the wound on One Inch Ash was real. The damage wasn’t much, but his ghost boundary had been interrupted.

Where did the bullet come from? Qiao Yifan was puzzled. Tang Rou was clearer than him. The bullet had gotten past Soft Mist, yet Soft Mist and One Inch Ash had been perfectly lined up.

Curve Firing…

The stadium screens put on a slow-motion replay. Cloud Piercer had activated Curve Firing. The curve of the bullet had been extremely small. The extra time that it took for the bullet to curve was short enough that it could still reach One Inch Ash in time. If he had acted slightly slower, One Inch Ash wouldn’t have been interrupted.

Fortune had come!

Even Zhou Zekai couldn’t help but let out a sigh of relief. He had dealt with this predicament.

The final step!

Samsara’s four characters finally rushed out from One Inch Ash’s Darkness Boundary. Their eyes finally saw the light of day, when their screens suddenly turned black again.

What?

In that instant, the four on Samsara were wondering if their computers really had lost power. They had clearly seen the light. How could it have turned dark immediately afterwards? Even if One Inch Ash’s ghost boundary hadn’t been interrupted, it couldn’t have been another Darkness Boundary. He had cooldowns.

Wait, Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash couldn’t use Darkness Boundary again, which meant it had to be…

Ye Xiu! Lord Grim!

Their screens had been dark, so how could they know what Ye Xiu was doing? And by the time Zhou Zekai noticed it, it was too late. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had patched up the gap, placing down his own Darkness Boundary.

Samsara had overlooked another person, and this time, it was Ye Xiu, the person who they should never overlook.

But the pro players could completely understand. No matter how amazing Zhou Zekai was, he was only one person. Happy had put up a nearly impenetrable defense for One Inch Ash. He had miraculously interrupted him with a Curved Firing. There hadn’t been any time for him to look at Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim even if just a glance.

That bastard was simply too shameless. He had added a ghost boundary to his umbrella: Darkness Boundary.

Dual Linking Ghost Boundaries!

The pro players looked towards Team Void’s two Ghostblades. Because this was exactly like Team Void’s signature move, including the unexpectedness of it.

Of Team Void’s Ghostblade Duo, Li Xuan’s Crying Devil was a standard Phantom Demon, primarily using ghost boundaries. On the other hand, Wu Yuce’s Carved Ghost was a hybrid class. What ghost boundaries he used were a mystery in every match.

In the pro scene, Wu Yuce’s Carved Ghost was absolutely the craziest about resetting his skill tree. Every single match, he would reset his skill tree. No one knew which ghost boundaries he would coordinate with Li Xuan in their Dual Linking Ghost Boundaries.

Wasn’t this sort of unexpectedness the same as what Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was giving to Samsara?

Right after exiting a Darkness Boundary, Samsara’s four had entered another Darkness Boundary…

Chapter 1681 - The Response of the Top Pros

In terms of damage taken, Samsara was actually doing quite well. The damage from Darkness Boundary was negligible. It was a prime example of a skill that was effective for its ability to create openings through its crowd control effects.

However, despite being Blinded in Qiao Yifan’s Darkness Boundary, Samsara didn’t take much damage. It wasn’t that Happy wasn’t trying. It was just that they had to respond to Samsara’s answers.

With four characters blinded, most teams would scatter to make it easier to escape from the Darkness Boundary. Even if one or two were focused down by the enemies and delayed, the others would quickly escape and be able to turn around and help their teammates escape.

But this wasn’t what Samsara did.

After being blinded, the four of them moved together as one unit. It seemed like a disaster in the making, but Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves created a beautiful protective barrier for them with Nebula Wave Slash, preventing Happy from reaching them.

They had made mistakes and overlooked certain players on the enemy team, but when it was time for them to take on the necessary burden, they didn’t panic. They maintained the confidence and calm that a championship team should possess. The four on Samsara couldn’t see what was going on around them, but they had their characters turn and move, calmly leaving the Darkness Boundary under the protection of Nebula Wave Slash.

The only one who hadn’t been blinded, Zhou Zekai, had also given them the greatest support possible. Under Su Mucheng’s barrage of artillery fire, he had miraculously interrupted Qiao Yifan’s follow-up ghost boundary.

Unfortunately, Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash wasn’t the only one with Phantom Demon capabilities.

Ye Xiu, Lord Grim.

While Zhou Zekai was completely preoccupied, Ye Xiu was easily able to set up a Darkness Boundary, linking it together with One Inch Ash’s. As soon as the four on Samsara exited the first, they stepped into the second.

The Nebula Wave Slash from Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves didn’t last forever. Providing protection for them until they left the first Darkness Boundary was its limit. Both the Lightning Wave Formation and Nebula Wave Slash were now out of the picture. Darkness surrounded them, and they were no longer protected.

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist was already rushing towards them.

This time, how would Samsara stop Happy’s advance? Zhou Zekai? He was only one person. Happy was attacking from four directions. It was impossible for him to take care of all of them.

Pincer, go around three, follow two, fall back…

These were Happy’s initial arrangements. And at this moment, their characters were shining with brilliance after completing them. It was because of their positioning that Samsara had overlooked an enemy player twice. It was because of their positioning that the number one player, Zhou Zekai, had no way to protect the other four on Samsara.

The other four on Samsara had finally responded though. They had been a bit surprised at first, but they quickly regained their composure. Jiang Botao immediately shouted “Scatter” in the chat.

Samsara had moved together as one previously because of Nebula Wave Slash. The skill had provided them with a protective barrier that enabled them to push forward without worry. Once they left the Darkness Boundary, they would be able to launch a fierce assault towards Happy’s healer. However, they hadn’t expected Dual Linking Ghost Boundaries from Happy. Given their current situation, they had no way to protect everyone all at the same time while blinded. As a result, they could only go with the usual tactic, and scatter.

Everyone on Samsara was a top player. It might be the same tactic, but it was completely different when executed by Team Sasmara.

When normal players scattered, it would be every man for himself. The more that got away, the better.

However, when Samsara scattered, there was logic and order to it. They scattered to minimize the casualties.

The key: the healer!

If all four scattered, who would be the easiest for Happy to focus down? The healer.

No one mentioned it in Samsara’s team chat because no one needed to. Any one of the others could be focused, but if Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song was taken into Happy’s grasps, Samsara would be in an extremely terrible position.

This was the difference between pro players and normal players. Minimizing the damage taken wasn’t necessarily the most optimal goal. Keeping the situation balanced, maintaining intact formation, controlling the tempo, etc. All of these aspects needed to be considered.

The first thing Samsara did was provide support for Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song. This task obviously couldn’t be given to the other three who were blinded. Unless they had another skill similar to Nebula Wave Slash, they wouldn’t be able to protect him from all sides.

The only one who could take the task was Zhou Zekai.

Scatter! Attack!

All of these thoughts, all of these changes happened in a split second.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks! Shining Cut!

Two figures dashed out. One Autumn Leaf and Cruel Silence. Blind didn’t stop them from using skills. Both of them used movement skills. As for which direction they went in? Forward! Both of them went forward.

The order was to scatter, but neither One Autumn Leaf nor Cruel Silence did. The two characters rushed out towards the same direction.

They were running away, but in the process of doing so, they didn’t forget to keep up the pressure on Happy.

Of course, their aim wasn’t the most accurate because of the Blind. The direction that they went in might not have any targets, but even so, they might be able to escape from the Darkness Boundary. Even if they didn’t, they would be one step closer to their objectives.

Dancing Rain, Little Cold Hands.

The two were in this direction, and both were very afraid of an enemy getting close. Sun Xiang and Wu Qi coordinated their escape and rushed forward together. During their escape, they needed to keep up the pressure on Happy. At this moment, there was nothing they could do about Happy’s attacks towards them. However, by doing this, Happy would need to take into consideration how much of a threat Sun Xiang and Wu Qi would be to Su Mucheng and An Wenyi. Would they need to prepare countermeasures against this threat?

This was Samsara’s response.

This was a response befitting a top team.

Their response forced the enemy to answer back. Even if four of them were in a bad position, their reply back was filled with aggression.

At the same time, Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves swung his Divine Chain.

Ice Wave Slash!

Ice crystals swept forward without a target. Empty Waves stepped on the path of ice that he paved, moving in the opposite direction of One Autumn Leaf and Cruel Silence.

This direction, Shattering the Lands!

Tang Rou charged forward, the moment the four Samsara players scattered.

One Autumn Leaf and Cruel Silence dashed out, while Soft Mist used Shattering the Lands.

The two characters had used movement skills, allowing them to escape from Shattering the Land’s range. Unfortunately for Jiang Botao, he was heading straight towards it.

He couldn’t see, but there was one person in Samsara who could.

“Jiang, right 30′ Shattering the Lands” Zhou Zekai warned the moment Soft Mist attacked. His meaning: Jiang Botao, 30 degrees to the right, Shattering the Lands.

If the attack was there, then the character was there.

How to respond? Zhou Zekai didn’t say. He didn’t have the time to give too detailed of a response.’

Empty Waves hadn’t even taken two steps along the icy path that he paved, when Jiang Botao noticed Zhou Zekai’s warning.

Shattering the Lands was an AoE attack. It was 30 degrees to his right and had already come out. Empty Waves had taken two steps in that direction. His chances of avoiding it: zero.

I can’t dodge! I can only attack back!

Empty Waves turned around. He turned right 30 degrees and swung his sword!

Jiang Botao couldn’t see anything, but in his mind, he could see the Shattering the Lands descending.

Light Wave Slash!

The fastest wave slash shot out.

Would it hit?

Jiang Botao didn’t know, so he didn’t stop there. Empty Waves swung his sword again.

Fire Wave Slash!

The strongest of the wave slashes flew out at an angle slightly lower than the previous Light Wave Slash.

Boom!

Shattering the Lands crashed down.

Magic swept the ground. However, at the same time, everyone could see that Soft Mist was engulfed in flames. The Fire Wave Slash had hit.

Chapter 1682 - The Center of Cruelty

Hit!

Fire Wave Slash landed!

Through Zhou Zekai’s concise tip in the team chat and his own intuition, Jiang Botao was able to land Fire Wave Slash on Soft Mist while blinded.

Although his Empty Waves wasn’t able to dodge Shattering the Lands, there was nothing else he could have done. He had been on the back foot, but was able to force a trade, and quite an impressive one too.

Battle magic erupted, raging flames blazed.

The two skills displayed their destructive power. The earthquake triggered by Shattering the Lands sent Empty Waves tumbling. At the same time, the Fire Wave Slash swallowed Soft Mist, sending her crashing to the ground in a blaze of fire.

“Fire hit”

Zhou Zekai confirmed the hit in the team chat. He was telling Jiang Botao that his Fire Wave Slash had hit. It was equivalent to telling Jiang Botao where Soft Mist was.

Jiang Botao understood. His stumbling Empty Waves raised his sword.

The crowd cheered and clapped excitedly at this play, but the pro players were truly stunned.

Not for the Fire Wave Slash, but for the raise of his sword.

Because this time, Empty Waves was bearing the brunt of Shattering the Lands. Battle magic battered him, sending Empty Waves stumbling the entire way through. Empty Waves was still blinded too! Even under these conditions, Jiang Botao was able to keep Empty Waves’ balance and prevent him from falling to the ground. This was incredible enough already, yet he was also able to keep his sense of direction!

Sword raised, gunshot!

Cloud Piercer fired.

Zhou Zekai wasn’t only paying attention to Tang Rou and Jiang Botao. As the only person on Samsara who could see, he needed to keep track of everything taking place on the battlefield.

Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf and Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence launched a sudden assault. To no one’s surprise, Su Mucheng and An Wenyi chose to retreat. They knew that once the two left the Darkness Boundary, it would be disastrous if they got too close. Thus, they might as well take precautions. As they retreated, they also took the opportunity to attack. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain fired mercilessly towards the two blinded characters.

Boom boom boom!

Dancing Rain’s artillery shells bombarded One Autumn Leaf.

Samsara’s fans didn’t think much of it. However, many of Happy’s fans consisted of former Excellent Era fans. This scene made them feel quite uncomfortable.

One Autumn Leaf, Dancing Rain, Best Partners for four consecutive years. To the Excellent Era fans, they were used to seeing Dancing Rain providing cover for One Autumn Leaf, and One Autumn Leaf protecting Dancing Rain from enemies getting close.

But now, Dancing Rain was trying to kill One Autumn Leaf…

This wasn’t the first time, and it wouldn’t be the last.

Perhaps the scene of the two characters fighting together shoulder-to-shoulder might never appear again. But no one knew how long it would take for them to get used to this scene. Maybe it would be like this forever. Whenever Dancing Rain and One Autumn Leaf appeared on the battlefield together, everyone’s first thought would be the two as partners, not enemies.

Enemies…

Every Glory fan who held a deep impression of these partners couldn’t help but repeat these words in their heads. Then, they saw One Autumn Leaf charging towards Dancing Rain, not to protect, but to pressure her. They saw Dancing Rain aiming at One Autumn Leaf, not to provide cover, but to stop his advance.

“I’m sure a lot of you are feeling sad seeing this scene…” Even Pan Lin couldn’t help but comment on something outside of the scope of the match. “But this is one of the cruelties of competition.”

The viewers watched the cruelty happening, and felt for the players on stage.

Gunshot.

A bullet flew from Cloud Piercer’s gun towards Dancing Rain.

Zhou Zekai was pressuring Dancing Rain. It could be considered as an attempt to interrupt this cruelty. However, Su Mucheng was the center of this cruelty, and she needed to persevere and continue for her team. She dodged Cloud Piercer’s attack and continued to bombard One Autumn Leaf with artillery shells.

You really are strong…

Ye Xiu was also on stage. He could see everything as well. He knew that facing One Autumn Leaf was perhaps even more difficult for Su Mucheng. When Ye Xiu saw One Autumn Leaf, he at least knew that he himself wasn’t the one there. But to Su Mucheng, One Autumn Leaf had always standing beside her. He was still standing there, but now, his spear was pointed at her.

One Autumn Leaf might not be a friend anymore, but I still am!

Cloud Piercer fired at Dancing Rain. Empty Waves raised his sword. By relying on his intuition, he was going to attack Soft Mist again. A figure suddenly flickered in front of him without any warning.

Ye Xiu, Lord Grim!

Lord Grim had been wandering around the left side, mainly using long-ranged attacks to strike Samsara’s holes. Suddenly, a shadow clone was left there, his real body cutting to the center of the battle.

Colliding Stab!

Lord Grim made his move. Jiang Botao had no idea what was happening. Zhou Zekai, who was supporting Sun Xiang and Wu Qi, hastily shifted targets in response to this sudden change. Warning Jiang Botao in the team chat would be too late.

Boom!

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella struck the plate armor on Empty Waves.

Empty Waves still swung his Divine Chains, but the gathered magic brushed past Soft Mist’s side.

Jiang Botao felt Empty Waves move. He felt Empty Waves getting hit by an attack.

Who? By what?

Lord Grim pressed his sword against Empty Waves, planning on bringing him away with him using Colliding Stab.

Cloud Piercer’s gunfire arrived, but another person on Happy had arrived as well.

Qiao Yifan. He coordinated together with Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim from the right wing. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had entered the Darkness Boundary, but he didn’t. His One Inch Ash quietly circled around behind Cloud Piercer.

There was only one pair of eyes on Samsara. Zhou Zekai had too many things he needed to take care of. His vision was limited. Happy had intentionally been focusing the main battle in one location, leaving an opening for Qiao Yifan to take advantage of.

Get close, good enough, cast!

The ghost god’s power gathered around his blade. Qiao Yifan was extremely nervous.

Would his attack hit?

He stared intently at Cloud Piercer’s back. He was afraid that Cloud Piercer would suddenly turn around and aim his gun at him.

Cloud Piercer didn’t turn around, but he did suddenly move. As he moved, his dual guns erupted in a blaze of sparks. In an instant, his bullets reached every part of the map.

Rapid Fire! Random Firing!

Zhou Zekai was planning on using this type of burst to cover the entire battlefield by himself!

Chapter 1683 - Happy’s Plans

Cloud Piercer whirled around, bullets flying towards every critical point.

Even under the effects from Random Firing and Rapid Firing, his aim was as precise as ever.

Bullets...

Qiao Yifan didn't even see Cloud Piercer's gun aimed towards him. He just saw him flash by him for an instant, and a bullet was flying towards One Inch Ash.

Just a bit off!

Qiao Yifan was somewhat unwilling to let the opportunity go, but there was nothing he could do. The cast time for ghost boundaries wasn't something that he could control.

Dodge.

He could only dodge. If he didn't dodge, he would be interrupted.　　

But just when he dodged the bullet, he saw another one flying towards him.

Zhou Zekai wasn't only focused on Qiao Yifan. There hadn't been any pauses both times Zhou Zekai faced towards him, but his bullets went for him nonetheless. It wasn't just him, but An Wenyi's Little Cold Hands, Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain, Tang Rou's Soft Mist, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim...

The crowd went wild!　　

This was what they had been hoping for. This was what made Zhou Zekai so captivating. Using godlike inhuman skill to sweep away everything in his path.

Random Firing and Rapid Firing. A normal player would have no way of aiming properly, but Zhou Zekai was able to guide each bullet to wherever he liked.

One Inch Ash's ghost boundary failed.

Sun Xiang and Wu Qi suddenly acquired a powerful shield of bullets. The two finally rushed out from the Dark Boundary, recovering their sight. They immediately set their eyes on Dancing Rain and Little Cold Hands.

The situation had changed. However, there was one part that hadn't.

Ye Xiu's Lord Grim. Although Cloud Piercer's Random Firing and Rapid Firing had shot him full of bullet holes, it didn't stop him from using Colliding Stab!

Zhou Zekai realized that something was wrong. With Cloud Piercer covering every member on Happy, he saw all of Happy's movements clearly.

Su Mucheng and An Wenyi looked like they were retreating. Tang Rou's Soft Mist seemed to be trying to force his way through the rain of bullets to Cloud Piercer's side. Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash was behind him, dodging his bullets, but unable to complete any of his spells. Their movements...

Lord Grim!

They were coordinating with Lord Grim.

In other words, Jiang Botao's Empty Waves was their true target. 　　

Too far!

After realizing this point, Zhou Zekai came to the conclusion that the distance between Empty Waves and Samsara was a problem. It might be a small one, and it was different from the coordinated assault from One Autumn Leaf and Cruel Silence. Samsara hadn't prepared for this change. Lord Grim's Colliding Stab had created it.

Gunfire focused!

The Random and Rapid Firing hadn't ended. Zhou Zekai suddenly focused his efforts onto Lord Grim.　

A single bullet hitting had negligible hit stun. It wasn't enough to interrupt a skill cast, but when multiple bullets chained together in quick succession, the hit stun could no longer be ignored.

Blood splattered into the air. Lord Grim's movements had clearly become slower, and Empty Waves was pulling away from the umbrella sword pressed against his chest. The dense gunfire was forcefully slowing down Colliding Stab, while also dealing quite a bit of damage to him.

This sudden outburst created a new peak in energy from the crowd. The bright red blood was incomparable joy to the Samsara fans.

But it was only for an instant!

The wave of red blood stopped abruptly. Lord Grim was actually able to dodge the bullets.

The viewers, the pro players, all of them felt their eyeballs fall out of their heads.

What sort of inhuman skill was needed to be able to evade such dense and heavy gunfire? The control needed was astonishing, and Lord Grim was moving quite fast too, making it even more inconceivable.

Ye Xiu didn't pause for everyone to ponder over it. After dodging to the side, Lord Grim used another skill.　　

Falling Flower Palm!

A palm flew out, striking Empty Waves and sending him flying backwards.

Empty Waves had finally left the Darkness Boundary. Jiang Botao could see again, but what he saw was his Empty Waves flying away from his team. Before he could get a read on the situation, Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella once again slammed into Empty Waves.

Charge!

Falling Flower Palm wasn't enough. Lord Grim used Charge, evading Cloud Piercer's pursuit, while also pushing Empty Waves even farther away.

Happy's plan was already very clear at this point. Lord Grim was doing whatever he could to bring Empty Waves away, separating him from the rest of Team Samsara.

The normal viewers had yet to catch on. What they saw was Sun Xiang and Wu Qi pressuring Su Mucheng and An Wenyi. What they saw was Zhou Zekai's godlike shooting. What they saw was Fang Minghua's Laughing Song casually walking out from the Darkness Boundary. Jiang Botao's Empty Waves was being pushed back, but in their eyes, it was just a small flaw in the overall situation. Moreover, Happy had paid a significant price to achieve this. Lord Grim had taken quite a bit of damage from Cloud Piercer's burst even with his unbelievably fast evasion.

Even if he dodged, what could he do? The big stadium screen put on a slow motion replay. It was only through this replay did people realize that Lord Grim had used a skill to get away from the rain of bullets. He had used the speed from Shining Cut to escape. But this made Ye Xiu's play even more terrifying. The window that he needed to do it in had been miniscule. It practically wasn't even a window, yet he was actually able to make it?

Everyone sucked in a cold breath of air. Even the average viewer knew how terrifying such a feat was.

To do it just to keep on attacking Empty Waves, was this small flaw really that small?

From Ye Xiu's choices and his determination, quite a few people began to realize that Empty Waves' situation might not be so simple. Everyone began to shift their attention to that end.

Empty Waves, Lord Grim, a speeding bullets.

Zhou Zekai's full attention was directed there. Besides him, no one could immediately step forward to obstruct Happy's plans. Sun Xiang and Wu Qi had used their movement skills to get out of the Darkness Boundary. Then, in order to put pressure on Su Mucheng and An Wenyi, they chased after them. From Empty Waves' position, the two of them were running away from him.

Fang Minghua's Laughing Song, who people thought would be Happy's main target, hadn't really been targeted at all. In the end, Laughing Song took his final step and made it out into the light.

However, the first thing he saw was One Inch Ash's blade, emanating with ghostly light.

Chapter 1684 - The Target to Shoot

Interrupt!

Fang Minghua’s first thought was to interrupt Qiao Yifan’s cast. However, his Laughing Song was a Cleric. He didn’t have any skills that could instantly stop One Inch Ash from completing his spell. One Inch Ash was nearly done with the cast. When the ghost god’s power finished gathering, the Ghost Boundary would be complete.

“Ghost!”

All Fang Minghua could do was warn his teammates. However, Sun Xiang and Wu Qi were both close-ranged characters, and were far away from him. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves was Happy’s main focus. Empty Waves was even farther away. Even if Empty Waves had long-ranged skills, it wouldn’t be enough.

There was only Zhou Zekai and his Cloud Piercer.

Zhou Zekai’s full attention was on assisting Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves. He hoped to stop Happy from reaching their goal. If he could help Jiang Botao win even the slightest opening, Jiang Botao would be able to get out.

But he couldn’t!

Ye Xiu had Lord Grim dodge what attacks he could, and tank what attacks he couldn’t. All so that he could continue with the plan. In short, Zhou Zekai had to keep his focus there. He needed to keep trying. But at this moment, he received Fang Minghua’s warning.

Zhou Zekai was helpless. He could only have Cloud Piercer turn. He had to interrupt Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash. If not, the Ghost Boundary would certainly prevent him from attacking Lord Grim.

Zhou Zekai acted swiftly. Cloud Piercer turned quickly, but no matter how fast he acted, it would still affect his pressure towards Lord Grim.

The Ghost Boundary was interrupted again. This time, let alone Zhou Zekai, even the pro players outside felt like they had swallowed a housefly.

“These Ghost Boundaries are too tricky. Even if they fail, they mess up Zhou Zekai’s rhythm. It’s extremely helpful for Ye Xiu. If it were me, that would be the best I could do as well,” Glory’s number one Phantom Demon, Li Xuan, didn’t hide his admiration for Qiao Yifan. He was giving him praise in all regards.

“Stop sticking gold onto your own face. Have you noticed his positioning?” Chu Yunxiu added.

The pro players immediately paid attention to One Inch Ash’s positioning. Li Xuan continued: “Of course. He’s positioned behind One Autumn Leaf and Cruel Silence. He’s also lined up with Empty Waves and Cloud Piercer, using Cloud Piercer to block Empty Waves’ sight of him. If Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song had stepped out of the Darkness Boundary even a step later, the Ice Boundary would have likely succeeded.”

“What if it were Crying Devil?” Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie suddenly said.

“Ah, that’s the unfortunate part, ” Li Xuan nodded his head. His Crying Devil was the number one Phantom Demon, and all Phantom Demon skills required cast times. As a result, cast speed was a top priority. His Crying Devil was one tier above Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash in terms of stats. If One Inch Ash had been Crying Devil, Fang Minghua’s warning would have been too late.

The pro players only took a few seconds to discuss all this. However, Happy and Samsara hadn’t stopped to wait for them. Numerous changes had happened in these few seconds.

Samsara, who had been on the backfoot the whole time, were in a much better situation than before now that the two Darkness Boundaries had disappeared. Even if none of Samsara’s players had been inside the Darkness Boundaries, it still separated them from each other.

Now that this forbidden zone vanished, Samsara could finally move around freely between the two sides. The first thing that Fang Minghua did was step into the previous forbidden area. In the blink of an eye, only Sun Xiang remained to put pressure on Su Mucheng and An Wenyi. Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence had turned around and was moving towards Empty Waves.

Because of Qiao Yifan’s timely interference, Zhou Zekai wasn’t able to suppress Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. Once Tang Rou’s Soft Mist made her way over, it became impossible for Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer to hold them down alone.

However, the Darkness Boundaries were gone. Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song and Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence rushed over, and in an instant, Samsara splitting apart earlier looked even more beautiful. The separated Empty Waves had been linked back together with the team.

Happy opened the match with two Darkness Boundaries to trap four of Samsara’s players. Their opening was undoubtedly in their favor. However, despite their spectacular start, the outcome wasn’t as great as they would have liked.

They hadn’t been able to deal much damage while their opponents had been trapped by the Darkness Boundary. Their plan to separate Empty Waves seemed like it had failed after the two Darkness Boundaries disappeared.

Had Happy played it badly?

No one thought so.

Starting from their pincer formation, Happy’s tactics had been extremely effective. Every player had performed their task outstandingly.

However, Samsara’s responses weren’t inferior at all. They had been at an extreme disadvantage, yet they had minimized the losses. It was true that they had lost more health, but they didn’t let Happy take control of the battle.

Happy’s crucial Darkness Boundaries had disappeared. Samsara began to actively take back the initiative.

Zhou Zekai had been a huge reason that Samsara was able to keep things together during this period of time. Without his existence, without his strength, who knew how badly the situation would have spiralled out of control.

Cloud Piercer’s Rapid Firing was still active. However, the Random Firing skill duration had come to an end, reducing his firepower significantly. Samsara had finally stabilized the situation though. The next act was now beginning.

But to everyone’s surprise, Zhou Zekai used Dual Load, instantly refreshing Cloud Piercer’s Random Firing.

He’s going to keep it up?

Everyone was astonished.

The opening confrontation had been intense. Even though Happy wasn’t able to establish an overwhelming lead, they were winning right now. Samsara’s players were rather scattered about right now. It wasn’t the best time to counterattack. Samsara didn’t even have an immediate target to focus on.

In any case, Zhou Zekai had already started. Bullets rained down again on the battlefield, except this time, Zhou Zekai no longer took care of everyone. He was unexpectedly aiming mainly towards Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash. As he fired, he even started moving towards One Inch Ash. Qiao Yifan was clearly Zhou Zekai’s target.

There was Ye Xiu, who had beaten him in the 1v1. There was the All-Star support, Su Mucheng. There was the Best Rookie, Tang Rou, who had just 1v3ed Samsara in the group arena. However, Zhou Zekai’s target was actually Qiao Yifan.

Qiao Yifan hastily had One Inch Ash dodge and retreat, but Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer wasn’t letting up. When everyone looked again, at this rate, the two would be separated from the rest of their teams.

“Could it be… BOX-1?” Blue Rain’s captain, Yu Wenzhou, said doubtfully.

Chapter 1685 - True BOX-1

Yu Wenzhou wasn’t certain. As one of Glory’s four Master Tacticians, there was no way he wouldn’t recognize a common tactic when he saw one. It was just that Zhou Zekai’s focus towards Qiao Yifan didn’t seem to fit the goals of a BOX-1.

The purpose of a BOX-1 was to shut out the opposing team’s most important player. Everyone recognized Qiao Yifan’s capabilities. Happy’s advantageous opening had required his Darkness Boundary. Ye Xiu separating Jiang Botao from the rest of Samsara had been thanks to Qiao Yifan’s interference towards Zhou Zekai. He had been a crucial component in Happy’s plans.

But was Qiao Yifan’s importance to Happy greater than Zhou Zekai’s importance to Samsara?

In a BOX-1, the core player rarely carried it out because you would lose your own most important player. It wouldn’t be an effective play. If it were core versus core, then it was sort of understandable. But with Zhou Zekai carrying out the BOX-1, didn’t it seem like Samsara was the one losing out?

Yu Wenzhou glanced towards Xiao Shiqin. Xiao Shiqin glanced towards Zhang Xinjie. The three Master Tacticians all looked at each other. In the end, no one was able to give a reason.

But this was the way the match was going. Cloud Piercer chased after One Inch Ash. With Random Firing and Rapid Firing, Cloud Piercer had been able to cover all five players on the enemy team. Now, his focus was entirely on one target. Qiao Yifan had no way of fighting back. His only option was to run for his life.

One ran, one chased. Qiao Yifan obviously didn’t want to lose contact with his team, but with Zhou Zekai chasing closely after him, just being able to dodge attacks was impressive enough already. How could he have the time to pick where he wanted to go?

“Is Zhou Zekai planning on taking advantage of his class?” Xiao Shiqin suddenly thought of something and said.

What was the advantage that Sharpshooters had? As pro players, the answer was practically instinctive. Combined with the present situation, everyone instantly understood that Xiao Shiqin must be talking about their range. Because Cloud Piercer was a long-ranged attacker, while he chased away Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash, he could still provide support to his other teammates. In other words, his BOX-1 wasn’t only to separate an important component in the opposing team’s tactics, he was relying on his class’s advantages to continue coordinating with his own team.

Xiao Shiqin also played a Gunner, so he figured it out a bit faster than Yu Wenzhou, Zhang Xinjie, and the other players. When everyone realized what he was saying and looked back at the match, they felt like that really was the answer. Once Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was pushed far enough away, Cloud Piercer suddenly turned around and fired a few shots at Lord Grim and Soft Mist.

For now, Zhou Zekai wasn’t Samsara’s core, but he could still help the rest of his team. His attacks towards Lord Grim and Soft Mist hadn’t been random. He was perfectly in sync with his team’s tempo.

With Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence arrival and the assistance from Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer, Jiang Botao was finally able to find an opportunity.

Empty Waves used Earth Wave Slash. Mid-swing, he changed directions, turning it into a Wave Wheel Slasher so that he could threaten both Lord Grim and Soft Mist. Although neither of the attacks landed, he was able to create an opening for himself.

Retreat!

Empty Waves immediately retreated. Lord Grim and Soft Mist were too close to him to the extent that even after Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence joined in, Jiang Botao still felt like he was in trouble. Spellblades needed enough space to fully utilize their strengths. Although Wave Slashes were instant cast skills, their start-up animation was slow compared to most other close-ranged skills. It was easy for Spellblades to get overwhelmed at very close distances.

After taking a step back, his situation became much better. For a top player like Jiang Botao, a distance of one step was like the difference between heaven and earth.

Light Wave Slash!

Empty Waves swung his sword as he retreated, using the Spellblade’s fastest attack. Before, there hadn’t been enough time for the attack to start up. But with a bit of distance between them, the attack would come out, and it would be too late for the other side to dodge.

Light flashed.

Saying that the attack arrived in the blink of an eye would be an insult to the speed of the attack. A distance of one step was practically non-existent. As soon as Empty Waves swung his sword, the attack landed.

This wasn’t something that you could react to unless you had predicted it. As a result, Jiang Botao didn’t attack Lord Grim. In his eyes, Ye Xiu was more likely to predict it, so he went for Tang Rou instead.

Sure enough, Tang Rou wasn’t able to dodge it.

But just because she wasn’t able to dodge it didn’t mean that she hadn’t done anything. Tang Rou had reacted. After dodging Empty Waves’ Earth Wave Slash and seeing Empty Waves retreat, she had reacted. It was just that her reaction wasn’t to dodge Empty Waves’ following attack, but to immediately give chase.

Soft Mist took a step forward. She stabbed with her spear, and the sword light arrived.

Hit!

The Light Wave Slash left a bloody mark on Soft Mist. As for Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves? He had been hit by Soft Mist’s spear and thrown into the air.

Circle Swing!

It didn’t matter which attack hit first. In any case, neither of them was able to interrupt the other. Soft Mist was hit by Light Wave Slash, and Empty Waves was hit by Circle Swing.

Tang Rou’s control over the skill wasn’t affected. Empty Waves, who had just gotten away, was thrown back in the blink of an eye.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim quickly followed. He wasn’t in a hurry to attack. He positioned himself so that Empty Waves was pincered by Lord Grim and Soft Mist.

Wu Qi, who had been ready to rescue Jiang Botao, missed. Just like Jiang Botao, he hadn’t been ready for Tang Rou’s sudden attack. Cruel Silence was very close to Empty Waves, but Lord Grim and Soft Mist were closer. Not only that, the two had Empty Waves pincered. Wu Qi couldn’t directly charge in.

Suddenly, a gunshot!

Cloud Piercer’s attack came again, forcing Ye Xiu and Tang Rou turn their attention towards it. If the two dodged Cloud Piercer’s attack, they would give up their positioning. Empty Waves was getting back onto his feet right when Cloud Piercer attacked. And with Ye Xiu and Tang Rou distracted for a moment, Empty Waves was able to get back up.

“Sure enough!”

The pro players were certain now. Zhou Zekai was doing what they thought. Not only was he pinning down Qiao Yifan, he was also using his range to provide support to his team at crucial moments.

Jiang Botao had Empty Waves get up. Wu Qi didn’t miss this opportunity for Cruel Silence to attack. Along with Cloud Piercer’s support, the two on Samsara quickly switched positions. Empty Waves was finally protected behind Cruel Silence.

As a result, Samsara was able to relieve the pressure on Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves. Ye Xiu and Tang Rou originally had a firm grasp of the situation. However, Zhou Zekai’s interference had broken it.

“Rather than saying it’s a BOX-1, it feels more like a Star Tactic,” Xiao Shiqin said. Everyone nodded their heads.

“The true BOX-1 is on the other side,” Zhang Xinjie suddenly said.

Zhang Xinjie emphasized details. When he saw Zhou Zekai supporting Jiang Botao and Wu Qi again and again, he immediately realized that something wasn’t right. Ye Xiu and Tang Rou weren’t receiving any help at all.

This was truly strange. Happy had one of Glory’s best supports, Su Mucheng. Her synergy with Ye Xiu, and her synergy with Battle Mages were second to none. Her support towards Ye Xiu and Tang Rou should be excellent.

Yet where did she go?

Everyone had been focused on the battle taking place on one side, but Zhang Xinjie had started paying attention to the other battle long ago.

Su Mucheng was being forced back by Sun Xiang.

But Zhang Xinjie wasn’t someone who would jump to a conclusion, so he spent more time looking at the battle taking place there. Now, he was completely certain. This was the place where the true BOX-1 was being carried out.

Sun Xiang versus Su Mucheng.

One Autumn Leaf versus Dancing Rain.

BOX-1.

Chapter 1686 - The Weakest One

Happy’s in a bad situation!

Seeing the BOX-1 that Sun Xiang executed against Su Mucheng, the pro players came to a unified conclusion.

A random map required many strategies to adapt to variable conditions, but facing an unchanging opponent, a few general strategic directions could still be established beforehand.

Just like how Happy’s plan to target Jiang Botao had been revealed earlier, the current situation showed Samsara’s general intent when facing Happy.

First, there was Ye Xiu. Last round, Samsara had tried a 3v1, but Ye Xiu had managed to hold out for a long time. So, this time, they didn’t try to focus fire on Ye Xiu to take care of him quickly.

Tang Rou, after completing a turnaround for Happy with her 1v3 in the group arena just now, had dealt a great blow to Samsara’s morale. However, after the team round began, Samsara didn’t seem to hold any fierce grudge against her or her Soft Mist. They simply fought her normally.

Against Qiao Yifan, Samsara sent their core player Zhou Zekai to personally restrict him. This seemed more like an on-the-spot arrangement. On one side, he restricted Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash; on the other side, he still gave powerful support to his own team. Zhou Zekai made thorough use of his class’s specialty to attack in two directions at once.

And Sun Xiang’s BOX-1 against Su Mucheng, this seemed like a strategy that had been planned beforehand. Samsara’s line of thought in this match had been to take Su Mucheng, this master of support and coordination, out of the battle.

However, Samsara’s strategy wasn’t limited to just this. Right now, there was still another player on the battlefield.

An Wenyi, Happy’s healer, the Cleric Little Cold Hands, was standing on the battlefield unscathed.

The battle had already unfolded, but when Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf and Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence charged toward his Little Cold Hands and Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain, he had already felt that something was off.

He was the healer, someone who would always be an important target of attack. When these two had approached, he hurriedly retreated, seeking Su Mucheng’s cover.

But very quickly, he realized something. Whether Sun Xiang or Wu Qi, these two characters seemed to be entirely focused on attacking Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain.

He healed from the side, he used a few of the Cleric’s controlling techniques from the side, but those two people were simply on guard against his interference, nothing more. Their full attention was on Su Mucheng.

If not for these two pincering her, how could Su Mucheng have been pinned down so easily? It was because of Wu Qi’s help that Sun Xiang had been able to successfully establish a BOX-1 against Su Mucheng. And at that moment, Wu Qi had run back to help Jiang Botao without a glance back.

An Wenyi had already been feeling that something was wrong. At this, his fingertips grew cold.

He saw Samsara’s strategy. Including Samsara’s attitude toward him.

All this time, because he had been viewed as Happy’s weak point, he had often become the opponents’ target of attack during the team round. Happy had performed many strategies to take advantage of this.

But today, in this battle that would determine to whom the championship would belong, An Wenyi suddenly discovered that he was disregarded…

An Wenyi was always calm and logical, but this time, his emotional state suffered a blow. View him as the weak point, he accepted it. He admitted that his skill was insufficient, even among the batch of rookies in Happy, let alone the pro circle as a whole.

But now, Samsara’s attitude wasn’t just treating him as the weak point. They were completely and wholly ignoring him. When Sun Xiang and Wu Qi’s characters closed in, they came only toward Su Mucheng, without sparing him half a glance. Right now, his Little Cold Hands was only standing there. He had no protection of any sort, but Samsara had no intention of attacking him.

This attitude was simply expressing: his existence didn’t matter. His Cleric simply could not affect the final outcome of this battle.

Were they looking down on him?

Or… was this really the only value he had?

When he’d been treated as the weak point, he could still draw the opponents’ attacks, and from there become the center of a trap for the opponent.

But now, in the eyes of the mighty Samsara, was he really nothing?

An Wenyi’s hands were cold, and his heart grew cold as well. He knew his shortcomings, he knew that he might not have any talent, but he hadn’t given up, he had kept working hard. Even when he was the weak point known to all, he had used his identity as the weak point to contribute to the team.

He appeared calm only because he was logical, only because he clearly recognized his own ability and limits. He did not resign himself to this fate. He had been working hard all this time so that he would no longer be viewed as the weak point.

And so, he’d had a few shining performances, not as the bait or the trap, but as a Cleric. He had even earned the recognition and praise of his idol, Glory’s number one Cleric Zhang Xinjie. This let An Wenyi felt that his hard work hadn’t been for nothing. Perhaps he was no longer the weak point, perhaps he would soon be able to shine.

But now, that didn’t seem to be the case.

In the eyes of Samsara, this strongest team in the Alliance, he wasn’t even considered the weak point. He was no more than a worthless piece of trash…

No one could know the sheer loss in An Wenyi’s heart right now.

He had been working hard all this time, but in the end, was the difference between him and everyone else really still so large? Had his so-called improvement been no more than wishful thinking? In reality, was he still that most useless one?

“Something’s wrong with Happy’s healer.” Once again, it was Zhang Xinjie, who would observe every detail on the battlefield, who noticed first.

Right now, neither Samsara’s Fang Minghua nor Happy’s An Wenyi had encountered any harassment. But it was for different reasons – Happy was currently unable to spare any hands to target the healer, while Samsara was purposely ignoring Happy’s healer. All of the pro players could see this quite clearly.

“It seems like… he doesn’t know what he should do?” Thunderclap’s Xiao Shiqin said, after observing Little Cold Hands’ actions.

“All this time, he’s struggled to survive under high pressure. Today, now that Samsara’s ignoring him, does he not know what to do?” Tiny Herb’s Wang Jiexi tried to figure out An Wenyi’s current mood.

None of them correctly guessed An Wenyi’s mood, because these god-level players had never met this kind of treatment before. The weak point, the flaw, the dead-last, these descriptions had never been associated with them. Those who could feel that distress in An Wenyi’s heart right now were only those who had experienced what he had – those who’d been ignored, who’d been treated coldly, who hadn’t been valued.

Wind Howl’s Tang Hao was smiling bitterly. This disregard from Samsara put him in a particularly bad mood.

Blue Rain’s Captain Yu Wenzhou also sighed, and said: “He’s suffered a psychological blow.”

A psychological blow?

Many of them exchanged glances. It was inevitable that Happy would be somewhat lacking on technique or strategy. But psychologically, on this team, the old and the young, the strong and the weak, they were all demons. When had they ever revealed any kind of psychological problems?

“Samsara’s given An Wenyi a fatal blow…” Yu Wenzhou said.

“What do you mean?” A number of people asked.

“Denied his worth once and for all,” said Yu Wenzhou.

Denied An Wenyi’s worth once and for all?

Everyone’s gazes returned to the battlefield, as the situation on the battlefield grew more and more intense. Happy had already been at a disadvantage, and the performance of their healer was currently unusually clumsy. This kind of performance was the so-called “pig teammate,” more terrible than a godly opponent.

“There is a problem, and it can only be mental,” many people said, nodding.

An Wenyi’s skill wasn’t anything special, but in this kind of situation where there was no interference, his judgment and accurate grasp of timing combined with the high intelligence and high crit stats of Little Cold Hands should be enough to serve as Happy’s most solid backing. But now, it seemed as though he’d lost his mind, that he had no idea what the thought process of a battle should be.

A psychological problem was always a big problem.

Especially for those who always seemed to be very psychologically strong, who never had any problems. As soon as a problem did appear, then it would be even more difficult to deal with.

An Wenyi lacked self-confidence because he was too logical. He logically recognized that his strength still wasn’t enough, and that he therefore shouldn’t have self-confidence. Carefully, bit by bit, he’d built up his confidence. But now in this battle, the final battle, the battle that would determine everything, Samsara’s total disregard shattered the confidence that he had so carefully raised. It destroyed all of those hopes he’d had for himself, hopes that had been born with such difficulty.

By now, he had no idea how to continue, he needed to help…

“Hey!”

At this moment, a message appeared in Team Happy’s chat.

“Hurry and heal!” It was Ye Xiu speaking. It looked like he was just reminding An Wenyi to keep up with the tempo.

“Don’t think too much. It’s true, you’re not very exceptional.” Who would have thought that Ye Xiu would suddenly send another sentence? This kind of sentence, appearing at a moment like this? In the eyes of any pro player, this was practically cooperating with the psychological knives that Samsara was throwing.

“This guy is insane!”

“Is this considered curing poison with poison?”

Everyone was shouting.

“But…” A transition appeared.

“Even if you’re a piece of straw, when you’re tied to a deluxe mitten crab, then you have the worth of that crab!”

Everyone was stunned.

These words seemed to have some philosophy to them. It was just that this metaphor… it seemed a bit self-inflating. What the mitten crab in the metaphor referred to couldn’t be clearer. This guy, he was simply too shameless. Did he know how to be humble?

But when An Wenyi saw these words, he too was taken aback.

That was right… No matter how worthless he was, he had a group of beautiful teammates at his side! Relying upon their light, even if he could reflect only a little bit of it, he would be bright enough that he couldn’t be ignored, right?

My skill isn’t as good as your healer’s, and my control of the situation definitely cannot compare to that of your experienced and thoughtful Fang Minghua.

But even if what I can do is only one-tenth of what your Fang Minghua can, even if you think it’s a negligible, insignificant ten percent, what if our Happy only needs that ten percent?

No need for doubt, no need for confusion. He only needed to do all that he could do, and the rest of it, he would leave to his teammates! What was he thinking about? Had he gotten too used to being treated as the weak point? Did he think that he was the core that the opponent needed to take care of?

That had never been the case!

He had always been no more than the weakest player in Happy. That had always been the case.

The fortunate thing was, he had a group of amazing teammates.

Chapter 1687 - The Weakling's Counterattack

No matter how bad I am, I’m Happy’s healer!

An Wenyi regained his calm, regained his reason. He quickly observed the present situation.

Things weren’t going well for Happy. Everyone on the team had been separated. Even Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain, with her ultra long-range, had lost contact with the team.

Which side needed the most help?

An Wenyi immediately examined each of the battles taking place.

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain was pinned down by Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf. Even if he tried to help, a Launcher would have a hard time forcefully breaking past a Battle Mage.

What about Ye Xiu and Tang Rou?

It was a 2v2 against Jiang Botao and Wu Qi. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves had escaped from their grasps. Wu Qi had joined up with him, and now, the two sides were going back and forth. For a moment, neither side seemed to be able to gain the upper hand. However, behind Jiang Botao and Wu Qi was Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song, who was providing support to them. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer would also help from time to time. In the long-term, it seemed like he would be needed there.

However, An Wenyi didn’t immediately go over to help. He turned towards Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash.

Although Su Mucheng was pinned down by Sun Xiang, the one in the worst shape was actually Qiao Yifan.

Qiao Yifan had no way to use any of his skills. Ghost boundaries had cast times. Without any place to hide, any attempts to place down a ghost boundary would be interrupted. Zhou Zekai wouldn’t let him out of his sight. With Random Firing and Rapid Firing active, the previous wave of attacks had sent One Inch Ash fleeing like a mouse. The duration of those two skills had ended, but Zhou Zekai was still keeping Qiao Yifan in check. Any time One Inch Ash tried to swing his sword, a bullet would fly his way.

Qiao Yifan was helpless. He could only keep moving, while searching for an opening or a place for him to hide. However, Zhou Zekai never let up. If One Inch Ash moved, he would move too. Utilizing the Sharpshooter’s range, Cloud Piercer had an exceptional radius of defense. Against many classes, this defense would appear somewhat lacking, but for a spell-based class like a Phantom Demon, it was more than enough.

Qiao Yifan needs help!

Seeing One Inch Ash struggling to break free from Cloud Piercer’s pursuit, An Wenyi reached a conclusion.

As a result, An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands started moving.

“What is he thinking?”

The pro players had seen Ye Xiu’s words to An Wenyi, but they didn’t know how much help those words would be to An Wenyi. When they saw Little Cold Hands suddenly start moving, they had no idea what he was thinking. It didn’t seem like he was trying to reach a place where he could cast spells.

“He’s…”

As Little Cold Hands approached his target, everyone started to see.

Cloud Piercer!

An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands was actually charging straight towards Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer.

“What is he thinking?!” Everyone was dumbfounded.

Wasn’t this upside-down? The weakling that Samsara had chosen to ignore was actually running towards Samsara’s greatest, most dazzling player? Had he gone insane?

“Is he planning on giving up his life to block the bullets?” someone guessed. An Wenyi had done this many times in previous matches. The other teams would regard their healer as the target that needed the most protection. On the other hand, Happy would sometimes throw their healer out to the wolves to act as a meat shield.

“What’s wrong with that? The healer’s job is to protect the team!” Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie said.

True!

Protect the team. Everyone understood the healer’s responsibility, but was this sort of method really that effective? Zhou Zekai just needed to turn his attention to him for a second to stop him, no?

An Wenyi obviously understood this reality. This was also why he chose to charge directly towards Cloud Piercer.

Ignoring me?

Fine!

I’m going to run at you, so keep on ignoring me!

An Wenyi thought to himself. He wasn’t sulking though. It was a logical decision. He was certain that by doing this, he would lure away Zhou Zekai’s attention. Switch targets to him? Stop him from approaching? All of those could happen, but An Wenyi believed firmly that if Zhou Zekai had Cloud Piercer aim his guns at him, Qiao Yifan, Ye Xiu, and Tang Rou would definitely seize this window of opportunity to do something.

This was the way he survived in Happy. This was the way he survived in the pro scene. If it was just his healing, then there was only so much he could contribute. He needed to do other things to make up for his lack of skill, such as using his own character’s health.

The crowd began letting out cries of surprise.

Happy’s weakest member was actually running straight into the jaws of Samsara’s strongest, and he was a healer too.

What is he thinking?

Is he trying to kill himself?

The viewers had begun to notice, and so had the players on the battlefield.

“This guy…” Fang Minghua was a healer, and he needed to keep his eyes and ears open at all times. As a result, he was the first to notice An Wenyi’s surprising movements. At first, he thought that An Wenyi was acting like a child throwing a tantrum. Seeing how Samsara was ignoring him, An Wenyi was using this sort of method to force Samsara to pay attention to him.

But when he looked closer, he saw how steadily Little Cold Hands was moving. He saw how Little Cold Hands would look around from time to time. It made him realize that this definitely wasn’t him acting like a child. An Wenyi had made this decision in an attempt to turn the situation around.

What is he planning?

Little Cold Hands hadn’t done anything yet, but Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash suddenly acted.

Move!

He had been moving constantly, but after taking these two steps, when Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer adjusted his aim, a figure suddenly appeared in front of him.

Little Cold Hands?

Zhou Zekai ignored him. It was just a Cleric. Even if he got closer, he was no threat.

Step to the side!

Cloud Piercer stepped to the side, opening his vision again, and fired.

Bang!

A bullet flew out. Little Cold Hands also followed and stepped to the side.

Too slow…

Zhou Zekai saw Little Cold Hands and figured out An Wenyi’s intentions, but he knew what An Wenyi’s weakness was. He knew that his reaction speed and technique were lacking. As a result, if he moved and then attacked, An Wenyi wouldn’t be able to keep up.

Sure enough.

When Little Cold Hands moved to the side, the bullet had already been fired and it went right past him.

But there was no One Inch Ash in Zhou Zekai’s line of sight.

Move to the side again.

Zhou Zekai found a new angle and attacked again. An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands followed along again, but nothing changed. His reaction speed wasn’t fast enough to keep up.

However, Zhou Zekai was frowning.

Even though An Wenyi failed to block his attack, even though Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash still wasn’t able to place down a ghost boundary, An Wenyi was still an additional burden for Zhou Zekai, requiring him to put in extra effort. It was as if there was a moving obstacle between Cloud Piercer and One Inch Ash now. Zhou Zekai had no choice but to expend more energy to avoid this obstacle.

Switch targets and kill Little Cold Hands.

That was what most people were thinking he should do. However, if he did that, his attention would mainly be focused on Little Cold Hands. Qiao Yifan would likely seize this opportunity to escape.

Things weren’t so simple… if someone else could keep Qiao Yifan pinned down, then it wouldn’t take him long to get rid of that pesky Cleric!

But there was no one…

Because he had forced Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash away from everyone else. He was the only one nearby that could keep him under control.

This separation had originally been his advantage, but right now, it was being used against him.

Once you ride a tiger, it’s hard to get off, and the one who put him in this situation was Happy’s weakest member, the one Samsara had decided to ignore.

An Wenyi, Little Cold Hands…

Regardless, this situation could not continue. He had to get rid of him, even if it meant giving Qiao Yifan an opening. There was nothing else he could do.

Just when Zhou Zekai was about to act, a figure suddenly slammed into Little Cold Hands from the side.

Laughing Song?

Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song, Samsara’s Cleric, had unexpectedly brandished his cross and charged straight into Little Cold Hands.

Was this a… fight between Clerics?

Everyone was dumbfounded. What sort of match was this? What was going on with these two teams’ healers?

One of them ran straight towards the jaws of the enemy, while the other ran over to swing his cross…

Was that really the only way?

The viewers were a bit puzzled. This was supposed to be a match of the highest level, so why was it looking like a match of the lowest level?

Zhou Zekai let out a sigh of relief.

Fang Minghua had noticed his predicament, seeing that Zhou Zekai was having trouble because of Little Cold Hands.

Take over and pin down Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash? Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song wasn’t capable of doing that, but he could contend against Little Cold Hands. Both of them were Clerics, who didn’t have much combat capabilities. But if it was a 1v1, Fang Minghua felt like he should have the upper hand against An Wenyi, no?

Thus, in the finals that represented the highest level of pro play, the strange scene of two Clerics whacking each other appeared.

No skills were used. It was just the two of them swinging their crosses, using normal attacks to beat each other up.

It wasn’t that Clerics didn’t have crowd control skills. It was just that with An Wenyi’s determination and caution, Fang Minghua felt like this was the most reliable method.

Chapter 1688 - Heroic Leap

How did it turn into two Clerics beating each other up?

This scene could occasionally be seen in the game, usually when players were bored, but it was unheard of in pro play. There were times when healers were forced to fight, but those were out of helplessness, for self-defense. However, this was likely the first time a Cleric had intentionally rushed in to attack another Cleric.

When a cross swung, there would be a sound effect as well. This sound seemed incredibly unfamiliar to everyone’s ears.

Laughing Song, Little Cold Hands. The two Clerics traded blows. The two characters happened to be male and female, an almost tragic sight to witness, like a family fight in the streets.

Who studied how to fight at close combat as a Cleric? Even Fang Minghua, who was an experienced player, hadn’t. An Wenyi didn’t need to be said. Although he had been scouted from the game, with his rational mind, he never participated in something as boring as a Cleric brawl, let alone studied it.

Pipipi! Papapa!

The crosses flashed with white light, weaving back and forth, occasionally colliding. A rain of white light poured down, pelting the two Clerics. However, their health barely moved. They were Clerics. How much attack power could they have?

Fang Minghua was starting to feel a bit of regret. He was regretting how he had used Charge to get close.

Charge was a Knight skill. Because it was a pre-advancement Priest skill, he could also learn it. Using it to attack wasn’t something a Cleric wanted to use it for, after all, it was an effective skill for movement and escaping. And because of this, no Priest class would let go of this skill.

It had become a habit for Fang Minghua. He had needed to get to An Wenyi quickly, so he had instinctively used the skill. Now that he and An Wenyi were fighting, he realized how useful Charge would have been now.

I’m not experienced enough!

Fang Minghua didn’t have any experience closing in on an opponent and attacking.

But just when he remembered Charge, he suddenly realized: not good!

Laughing Song had used Charge, but what about Little Cold Hands?

He hadn’t seen Little Cold Hands use it.

Just when he had this thought, he immediately saw Little Cold Hands pause, Charge!

Bang!

Little Cold Hands lowered his head, ready to ram into Laughing Song. The cross looked completely useless in his hands. Although it was clearly an attack skill, it looked like he was making a fool of himself.

But no matter how stupid it looked, it was a Charge, and one at a very close distance to the target.

Laughing Song was suddenly sent flying, but Little Cold Hands didn’t stop. He was unexpectedly chasing after Laughing Song.

Had he gotten addicted to the thrill of close combat?

No!

That wasn’t the reason.

Little Cold Hands had his Charge off cooldown the entire time, but An Wenyi didn’t immediately use it. He had been waiting for an opportunity.

Finding the right timing was An Wenyi’s specialty. Even if Fang Minghua had been ready for it since the start, stopping Little Cold Hands from using it wouldn’t have been so easy.

Laughing Song was sent flying.

Little Cold Hands rushed out.

His direction, Cloud Piercer!

An Wenyi hadn’t forgotten his original intention. He hadn’t come here to fight the enemy Cleric. He had come to interfere with Zhou Zekai. He had come to create opportunities for his team. He had come to turn things around so that the team could win!

Fang Minghua had relieved the pressure from Zhou Zekai, allowing him to continue controlling the battlefield. Zhou Zekai had wanted to provide some assistance to Fang Minghua, but before the appropriate opportunity came, Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song shot towards his Cloud Piercer like a bullet.

It had been too sudden. Zhou Zekai hastily had Cloud Piercer dodge to the side, but then, he saw Little Cold Hands following close behind, rushing towards him with Charge.

“Ah!”

At this instant, countless people shrieked.

An Wenyi, Little Cold Hands, this flimsy Cleric had unexpectedly attacked Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer? That bastard! It’d probably be the greatest achievement in his career!

But, no!

Zhou Zekai’s reaction speed was incomparably quick. His hand speed was even quicker. He had been getting out of Laughing Song’s way when he suddenly noticed Little Cold Hands. At that point, Little Cold Hands had practically reached him already, yet he had actually been able to react in time.

Bang bang bang bang!

Cloud Piercer fired his dual guns, using the recoil to increase his speed. In the end, he was able to avoid the Charge.

How close!

Zhou Zekai felt a cold sweat dripping down his back. If the Charge had hit him, his tempo would have been disrupted. Now… it was still fine. Even though it would be a bit troublesome, he could still keep things in control.

While he had been dodging, he had looked around, particularly at Qiao Yifan’s side. Sure enough, Qiao Yifan had seized this opportunity to start casting a ghost boundary. Cloud Piercer had only barely dodged the attack from Little Cold Hands. His balance wasn’t the best, but Zhou Zekai was confident. Even in this situation, he could accurately hit One Inch Ash in the chest.

Aim!

He lifted his gun. Cloud Piercer readied the trigger, when a shadow suddenly descended from the sky. In this shadow’s hands was a white light, dim and insignificant. Yet at this moment, this white light was invincible!

Heroic Leap!

An Wenyi saw that his Charge would miss, so he cancelled it and turned around, Heroic Leap!

An Wenyi knew that his reaction speed was slow. He knew that his hands weren’t quick. But at this instant, he put everything he had to be as fast as possible. He was pushing himself to his limits. He didn’t even know if what he was doing was accurate, or if he would hit his opponent.

Heroic Leap.

This was the skill that An Wenyi had placed on Little Cold Hands’ weapon. The skill name was mighty, but An Wenyi knew that the purpose of this skill wasn’t its might. It was similar to Charge. It was supposed to give Little Cold Hands another escape tool.

However, right now, he wasn’t running away. He wasn’t trying to survive. His Little Cold Hands swung his cross, using Heroic Leap to smash into Cloud Piercer, smash into Glory’s number one player, smash that being high above him. If he could hit him, it would probably be his greatest achievement.

An Wenyi didn’t object at all to this point.

This moment was indeed the greatest highlight of his career.

Heroic Leap!

Little Cold Hands jumped up. Little Cold Hands fell. The feeble light knocked down Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer, this existence at Glory’s summit.

At this moment, Little Cold Hands had Cloud Piercer beneath his feet.

Chapter 1689 - A Change in Situation

“What is this? What just happened?”

Everyone watching the match suddenly heard a hoarse shout from Pan Lin. It sounded like he wanted to crawl out and grab the audience’s neck to get to the bottom of this matter.

Even so, no one felt like he had lost his composure, because they were all going crazy just like him.

A Cleric knocking down a Sharpshooter. More importantly, the Sharpshooter was Cloud Piercer, controlled by Zhou Zekai, Glory’s number one player in recent years. Even if that was just context, it was a powerful scene, placing him in the spotlight.

Everyone knew that even if An Wenyi wasn’t a great player, even if he was considered one of the worst among Happy’s rookies, what he had contributed today would be remembered for years. This scene was similar to Tyranny’s Assassin, Cold Seasons, from many years ago. He wasn’t a particularly well-known player, but his shattering Life-Risking Strike against One Autumn Leaf in the finals became the most breathtaking moment that year.

An Wenyi’s attack wasn’t anything special, but his Little Cold Hands was a Cleric! A Cleric knocking down Glory’s number one player. This was more than enough for this moment to be written into the annals of Glory.

Although to be accurate, Cloud Piercer hadn’t been knocked down. After all, Heroic Leap wasn’t a skill with a forced knockdown. Zhou Zekai hadn’t been able to avoid the attack in time, but it wasn’t hard for him to Quick Recover and avoid crashing into the ground.

But whether or not he really did get knocked down wasn’t important. With Quick Recover, Cloud Piercer would roll and then get up. In everyone’s eyes, Cloud Piercer rolling on the ground was no different than Little Cold Hands sending him tumbling with a Heroic Leap.

Apart from the staunch Samsara supporters, this moment made everyone’s blood boil with excitement.

But not Zhou Zekai.

Many people might think of this as humiliating to him, but he had no such thoughts. No matter how weak An Wenyi was, he was an opponent. It was just that from his skill level and his class, he should have been someone easy to deal with. But this time, this opponent had made the right decision at the right time. In that instant, he hadn’t been weak at all.

But it was only for an instant.

Zhou Zekai still didn’t think An Wenyi was much of a threat. Even when Little Cold Hands had hit him with Heroic Leap, what he had cared more about was interrupting One Inch Ash.

I need to hurry and interrupt him again.

This was the more urgent matter in Zhou Zekai’s mind.

Roll, find the target, aim…

Before Cloud Piercer even got up, Zhou Zekai had started preparing for his next attack.

But he was too late.

On the battlefield, only an instant was needed to make a difference. From start to finish, An Wenyi hadn’t been able to gain the upper hand on Zhou Zekai, but in that instant, he had won. He had won his team an opportunity.

Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash had already walked to the necessary position and had started casting a ghost boundary. If Cloud Piercer had been able to get off his shot previously, he would have been able to interrupt One Inch Ash. But it was too late to try now.

The spell was complete. The ghostly power gathered around One Inch Ash’s blade, Snow Stripe. By the time the gunshot rang, One Inch Ash had already swung his sword.

Even though the others on Samsara had their own battles to take care of, they would pay attention to the changes going on in the battlefield from time to time. Seeing that Cloud Piercer wasn’t able to interrupt One Inch Ash in time, they knew that a ghost boundary would be completed soon. Jiang Botao and Wu Qi began to retreat in haste.

“Haha, it’s a feint!” Outside of the match, Li Xuan laughed. In that instant, Li Xuan was able to tell that One Inch Ash had hidden a little trick when he placed down the ghost boundary. Only someone like Li Xuan, Glory’s number one Phantom Demon, could have noticed it.

Sure enough, the moment the tip of the blade reached the bottom of its arc, it suddenly turned.

Dense ghostly energy filled with a chilly frost blossomed like a pale blue flower.

Ice Boundary!

In the center was One Autumn Leaf!

At the final moment, Qiao Yifan, who had originally been pointing towards Empty Waves and Cruel Silence, turned towards One Autumn Leaf.

It wasn’t that Sun Xiang hadn’t noticed that Qiao Yifan was setting down a ghost boundary. It was just that Qiao Yifan’s feint hadn’t been so easy to see through. Only Li Xuan had been able to.

When he saw the direction of the Ice Boundary, as well as Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves and Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence retreating, Sun Xiang more or less disregarded it. By the time Qiao Yifan made the change, it was too late for him to react in time.

The biting cold instantly slowed One Autumn Leaf. Not being directly turned into an ice cube was already quite lucky.

Pu!

One Inch Ash was struck by the bullet. In order to placed down the Ice Boundary, there was no way Qiao Yifan could have dodged it. Cloud Piercer had only been just a little bit too late. It looked as if it had hit One Inch Ash before the ghost boundary had been set down.

Blood spurt out from the wound, but it was meaningless. An Wenyi had created an opening for Qiao Yifan, and Qiao Yifan had used it to alter the flow of the match.

Dancing Rain rushed out!

Sun Xiang wanted to stop her, but One Autumn Leaf was now too slow to catch up to her.

Boom boom boom!

Glory’s number one support started firing artillery shells around the battlefield. She was finally doing what she was best at, supporting.

Artillery shells flew towards Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves and Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence. The flames from the explosions flashed in front of their eyes.

When One Inch Ash turned his blade, the two realized that they had been tricked.

The two hastily tried to get back, but the players on Happy weren’t wooden trees. The two of them had given up their position to avoid the ghost boundary, so Happy immediately had someone occupy it.

Tang Rou, Soft Mist!

A Battle Mage fighting up close, while a Launcher supported from afar?

A familiar combo. Many people’s thoughts immediately returned to those former days. Even though the duo hadn’t been able to win the championships, the two were the greatest partners in all of Glory.

But now, One Autumn Leaf had become Dancing Rain’s enemy. The one playing the Battle Mage was different. As for Su Mucheng’s former partner, Ye Xiu?

He was Happy’s true lead, and Happy’s true core.

No one dared to overlook him, whether it was the enemy players or the viewers watching. Even when the rising stars of Happy shined again and again, those familiar with Ye Xiu would always pay attention to his each and every move.

If there were no opportunities, he could create opportunities for himself. An Wenyi had helped Happy win the team an opening. Would Ye Xiu keep biding his time? Would Ye Xiu not do anything?

Of course not!

Tang Rou had been left to deal with Jiang Botao and Wu Qi alone. At this moment, Ye Xiu turned fire!

Gunshots rang continuously.

Zhou Zekai hadn’t been able to interrupt Qiao Yifan in time. When he saw Qiao Yifan’s feint muddle Jiang Botao’s and Wu Qi’s tempo, he realized that the previous situation could no longer continue.

With One Autumn Leaf trapped in the Ice Boundary, the BOX-1 would certainly fail.

The situation had changed, which meant that he needed to hurry and adjust. He needed to find a new breakthrough point. As a result, Zhou Zekai set his sights on a target close to him.

An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands.

Ultimately, he was Happy’s healer. No matter how amazing he had been previously, a Cleric was someone who the team needed to protect. Who knew how many strategies had been devised over the years to get to the enemy healer.

Right now, Happy’s healer was standing right near Cloud Piercer without anyone to protect him.

Let alone the fact that Zhou Zekai’s Sharpshooter could even fight evenly against Ye Xiu’s unspecialized in close combat, even if he couldn’t, a Cleric should lose to a Sharpshooter anyways.

At that moment, he fired again, this time, towards Little Cold Hands.

Gunshot, blood. The white robe on Little Cold Hands was dyed red. Others might think that this was a form of revenge from Zhou Zekai, but in reality, it wasn’t.

The enemy healer had gifted himself over, so why shouldn’t he attack him? It was the rational thing to do.

Chapter 1690 - The Warrior Shining Like a Shooting Star

Whoever controlled the enemy healer, controlled the battle.

These words were a common saying in Glory. The team competition revolved around attacking and defending the healer. Compared to fighting for wild bosses in the game, even more strategic and tactical complexities were involved. The difficulty of wild bosses was mainly due to the sheer number of players involved. However, on the pro stage, everything needed to be far more precise.

In this team competition, both sides had taken unconventional routes. Happy chose to target Jiang Botao's Empty Waves. They didn't seem to show any particular attention towards Fang Minghua's Laughing Song. As for Samsara? Their attack towards Happy's healer wasn't tactical; it was psychological. For a time, their method had been effective. However, An Wenyi was quickly brought back by Ye Xiu. Then, he violated everything a healer should do, and brought Happy back from a disadvantage.

However, the price he paid was completely exposing himself to Zhou Zekai and Cloud Piercer's dual guns.

With the enemy healer sitting right there out in the open, Zhou Zekai didn't mind changing the team's original strategy of ignoring him to killing him. Strategy and tactics had to be adjusted according to the circumstances.

An Wenyi had predicted this outcome when he took the risk. He obviously tried to run, but Zhou Zekai didn't give him a chance. Once Cloud Piercer failed to interrupt One Inch Ash, he immediately shifted his attention to An Wenyi's Little Cold Hands.

As he attacked Little Cold Hands, he didn't forget to be wary of One Inch Ash behind him. At the same time, he also checked how the rest of his team was doing.

Tang Rou's Soft Mist rushed forward, ready for a 1v2. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim pulled away and turned around.

He's coming!

Zhou Zekai saw everything clearly. He had predicted that Happy wasn't going to give up on their healer so easily. From the looks of it, the rescue would be coming from Happy's strongest force.

If Ye Xiu's Lord Grim got close to him, not only would Little Cold Hands be saved, his control over One Inch Ash would drop drastically. By then, Lord Grim and One Inch Ash would form a team, and he would be the one in a predicament.

Fortunately, while Happy had sent aid for Little Cold Hands, Samsara didn't leave Zhou Zekai alone to fend for himself.

Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf had been slowed by the Ice Boundary, but he was able to leave the Ice Boundary in the end. Because of Zhou Zekai's interference, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash wasn't able to set up any other ghost boundaries.　　

After walking out from the Ice Boundary, One Autumn Leaf's movements were back to normal. However, it was no longer possible for him to continue shutting down Dancing Rain. Much of the success for the BOX-1 was because of Wu Qi's help. The two of them had teamed together to quickly shut down Su Mucheng.

Now, Wu Qi was no longer there to help. With just Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf alone, it wasn't easy for him to seal off Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain. Su Mucheng was very experienced with these sorts of situations. Sending just one player alone to deal with her would likely end up with Su Mucheng kiting, while she continued to support the rest of the team.

Sun Xiang knew how challenging it would be to face Su Mucheng, and given the present situation, he couldn't waste any more time.

Charge!

This time, One Autumn Leaf didn't target his former partner, but rather his former owner.

Ye Xiu, Lord Grim!

Sun Xiang wanted to stop Ye Xiu from interfering with Zhou Zekai. If he could stall long enough for Zhou Zekai to finish off Happy's healer, victory was theirs.

But Lord Grim turned around and switched targets!

Lord Grim had been rushing to Little Cold Hands' aid. But as soon as he saw One Autumn Leaf running towards him, he immediately gave up on his original plan and ran away towards a different direction.

Swish swish...

Two movement skills came out in quick succession. Countless peoples' eyes were still on the afterimages left behind by Lord Grim. However, for Fang Minghua, in front of him was the real Lord Grim.　　

Laughing Song had previously gone to fight against Little Cold Hands, but he had been sent flying by Little Cold Hands' Charge.

By the time he steadied himself, Little Cold Hands had sent Cloud Piercer tumbling along the ground. But similar to Zhou Zekai, Fang Minghua didn't let this scene cloud his judgement. He also didn't feel much threat from Little Cold Hands. The attack had indeed been impactful, though. The entire flow of the match could potentially reset.

What came after was as he expected. Starting from when Cloud Piercer failed to interrupt One Inch Ash's Ice Boundary, the situation changed. Su Mucheng was finally able to escape from the BOX-1. Jiang Botao and Wu Qi had their tempos disrupted from One Inch Ash's feint.

But... the key to the match is still in our hands!

Fang Minghua had also noticed Little Cold Hands. That attack had helped Happy change the situation, but at the same time, he was now a lamb in a tiger's den.

Whoever controlled the enemy healer, controlled the battle!

Fang Minghua trusted that Zhou Zekai wouldn't forget such a critical point in the heat of the moment. Even though he was at the top of Glory, he would never forget about the fundamentals.

Zhou Zekai didn't let him down. His reaction was even faster than he had hoped. He only fired at One Inch Ash once before focusing on Little Cold Hands. Fang Minghua could see that Little Cold Hands' back was already dyed with blood.

This is how it should be.

Fang Minghua felt much calmer. He immediately began doing what he was supposed to do. But then, he saw Lord Grim.　　

Lord Grim had originally rushed over to Little Cold Hands' aid, but when One Autumn Leaf also rushed over to intercept him, he suddenly changed directions.

Fang Minghua faintly realized something as Laughing Song began to run. But Lord Grim was too quick. In the blink of an eye, Lord Grim sealed off his escape route.

So that was his true aim!

Fang Minghua felt a shudder in his heart. Rescue Little Cold Hands? No! Ye Xiu's goal had been him from the very beginning. Little Cold Hands was bait to lure away Zhou Zekai and Sun Xiang.　　

Who did Laughing Song have to protect him?　

No one.

Jiang Botao, Wu Qi, Sun Xiang, none of them could help him. The only one who could help was Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer.　　

However, Little Cold Hands was stuck by his side. He couldn't contend against Cloud Piercer, but by sticking to his side, even just sticking his hands out and waving them around would be a form of interference.　　

This is... a trade?

Fang Minghua discovered that An Wenyi had already given up on himself. He had no plans on surviving.

He had barely healed anyone. Instead, he used this simple and crude method to cling onto Cloud Piercer. 　

Happy's weakest to stop Samsara's strongest? Was that Happy's strategy? Was this Tian Ji's horse race?

Then, by using the opportunity that An Wenyi opened up, Happy would attack Laughing Song, and both healers would be eliminated?

Fang Minghua knew that Happy was more than willing to trade healers. He wasn't being conceited. He was no doubt superior to An Wenyi as a healer. He had this confidence. In fact, every pro healer would have this confidence.

That was why Samsara had intentionally ignored An Wenyi, because even if An Wenyi was given free reign, he wouldn't do better than Fang Minghua. In Samsara's eyes, there was no risk to doing this.

How could they have expected An Wenyi to not be a healer when he was given free reign? He unexpectedly became an attacker, an extraordinarily weak attacker. Samsara ignoring him suddenly became his stage to shine.　　

Unfortunately, his attack was like a shooting star. In just a flash, it faded away. But in the end, he was able to change the situation. Then, Happy seemed to no longer have any use for him. Happy was clear that in a battle of healers, An Wenyi would lose to Fang Minghua.

As a result, they abandoned him to trade for Fang Minghua.

Today, Little Cold Hands' identity as a healer was a bait.

He shone brilliantly for an instant before fading away, and by doing this, he was going to drag down Samsara's healer with him?

I won't let you have your way!

Fang Minghua had Laughing Song retreat to get as much distance between himself and Lord Grim. His teammates had noticed what was going on. They would certainly try and help him. They knew that this trade wasn't worth it. It wasn't just the difference in value between healers. Without Fang Minghua, Samsara had no healer. However, without An Wenyi, Happy still had Ye Xiu and his Lord Grim!

Lord Grim's healing capabilities weren't great, and as the team's main attacker, Ye Xiu couldn't sacrifice too many of his offensive stats to strength Lord Grim's healing. He might not be a great healer, but he could heal at crucial moments, which could potentially save a life. In terms of technique, while every pro healer could dare to say that they were better than An Wenyi, no would dare to say they were better than Ye Xiu.

Stall and wait for help.

This was Fang Minghua's plan. He had a skill ready to be used as Lord Grim closed in...

Fang Minghua could feel his palms sweat. He knew Ye Xiu's terror, which meant that he was even more careful with how he timed this skill.　　

Angel's Might!

A Paladin skill, a forced knockback that ignored Super Armor. Fang Minghua wanted to rely on this skill to win more time for his steam, but he needed to get the timing right. He was afraid that if he used it too early, it might not be effective, or Lord Grim might interrupt him.

He stared closely at Lord Grim. Lord Grim and started attacking him from afar. Fang Minghua tried his best to dodge as he endured and waited.

It's time! Now!

Angel's Might!

It was only level one, but in an instant, the divine protection flashed around Laughing Song and quickly spread.

But Lord Grim vanished.

There was no shadow clone. It wasn't Shadow Clone Technique. There was no trace of magic. It wasn't Teleport... even if he used those movement skills, he might not be able to escape. Those were displacement skills, but Angel's Might was an AoE, no?

Where did he go?

Fang Minghua felt a chill. He suddenly realized a possibility.　　

In the center of the spreading light, Lord Grim tunneled through the earth from beneath Laughing Song.

Ninjutsu - Underground Tunneling Technique!

Chapter 1691 - Flexibility

Peng!

Laughing Song’s neck was split open. Lord Grim had given a solid cut. But no matter how bad it looked, since this was a level one skill, its damage wasn’t high. The purpose of the skill wasn’t the damage, though. Lord Grim had used the underground effect to avoid Angel’s Might, allowing him to close the distance on Laughing Song.

Not good!

Fang Minghua immediately thought. In reality, Laughing Song was still quite healthy, and although the enemy ace had closed in on him, it wasn’t a fatal situation. His team could still rescue him.

Fang Minghua understood this reasoning, but he couldn’t control the sense of crisis rising in his heart. It was as if Lord Grim had given Laughing Song a fatal blow.

This was pressure.

Even if he had won two championships, when Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim got close, Fang Minghua could still feel the stifling pressure bearing down on him.

He wanted to hurry and get away. He wanted to hurry and find a way to get to his team. He hastily looked around, but his eyes were already facing the sky.

Lord Grim quickly followed with another attack. After Underground Tunneling Technique was a knock-up skill, launching Laughing Song into the air.

This didn’t mean that Fang Minghua had to give up on his original plans. He could still observe the surroundings and make decisions while in the air! Fang Minghua hastily adjusted his view, but as soon as he turned, the ground was now rapidly retreating away along with the sword pressed against Laughing Song’s stomach.

Colliding Stab!

Before Laughing Song was fully airborne, Lord Grim attacked. By doing this, with Laughing Song’s feet off the ground, the knockback from Colliding Stab would be at its fastest and its farthest.

Where is he taking me?

Fang Minghua quickly thought. The damage from Colliding Stab wasn’t significant. It was also rarely used as part of a combo. It had two main uses. Its first use was as a movement skill. The second use was to displace the opponent. In a team competition, its second usage was more commonly seen. When focusing on a certain target, you always wanted to bring the target to an appropriate location.

Including the Underground Tunneling Technique, Lord Grim had only used a total of two skills before coming out with Colliding Stab. Along with the fact that was still in the air, it definitely seemed like Ye Xiu was taking him somewhere.

Is Happy planning on focusing me?

Fang Minghua felt that it seemed unlikely. From what he remembered, Happy didn’t have anyone nearby who could get to him. Unless they planned on forcing their way over?

So that’s their plan!

Fang Minghua couldn’t help but look around again. He quickly noticed another figure coming into view.

From afar, Dancing Rain had thrown a burning beacon onto him. The mushroom cloud from the Heat-Seeking Missile instantly engulfed him, but during this process, Lord Grim took care of him very dearly. He didn’t let Laughing Song get sent flying away from the shockwave.

But honestly, Fang Minghua didn’t want Ye Xiu’s concern for him. He could understand Su Mucheng providing support with an attack over here, but soon after the dense smoke dispersed, a red shadow flickered in front of him.

Soft Mist?

With help from Su Mucheng, Tang Rou had been fighting against Jiang Botao and Wu Qi, yet in the blink of an eye, she had reached Laughing Song. This was an aggression without regard for anything else!

But because of this, Fang Minghua wasn’t as flustered as before.

Happy’s sudden shift in targets was rather crude. Happy had directly left Jiang Botao and Wu Qi open. The two of them weren’t outside bystanders. They would quickly be in pursuit. The balance wasn’t so easily grasped.

Just when he was thinking this, he saw Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves and Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence close behind Soft Mist, not giving an inch to her.

But soon afterwards, the distance between them suddenly widened.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Soft Mist suddenly used this high-level skill. Laughing Song was still airborne, and Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was still taking care of him. There was no way he could dodge this attack. Suddenly, he was sent flying into the air again.

Soft Mist instantly closed in onto Laughing Song. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim followed close behind with a Shining Cut.

They wanted to avoid Samsara’s rescue team.

Fang Minghua saw through it, but wasn’t that being too naive?

Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves had fewer movement options, so the distance between them widened by quite a bit. But Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence was an Assassin, the best out of all 24 classes in terms of mobility. He immediately went in pursuit with a Shining Cut. Then, he activated Swift Movements and sprinted. It wouldn’t take long for him to catch up.

Laughing Song could completely survive until then. After all, Happy was mainly trying to move him away. Their DPS wasn’t nearly as high as it could be.

Right when Soft Mist’s Dragon Breaks the Ranks ended, Laughing Song was picked up by Lord Grim.

Fling!

Laughing Song was thrown out.

What…

Fang Minghua was puzzled. Then, he saw magic ripple outwards from Soft Mist. Then, she blinked away.

Teleport!

Soft Mist teleported to where Laughing Song would fall and then followed with an attack.

Cruel Silence, who was just about to catch up, was suddenly thrown behind, let alone Jiang Botao who was even farther away. He was even farther away than Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf.

This… isn’t good!

Fang Minghua was startled by Ye Xiu’s and Tang Rou’s practiced coordination. This meant that the two weren’t doing this on the spur of the moment. Happy had practiced this tactic before.

This was a set-up!

Anyone with a bit of experience would understand. Oftentimes, pre-planned set-ups couldn’t keep up with the constant changes of a match, but if this sort of set-up was able to be implemented smoothly, the other side would always have the upper hand. From the coordination between Ye Xiu and Tang Rou and the interference towards the pursuers from Su Mucheng, he could see hints of it.

Happy wasn’t recklessly charging at him. They were planning on moving him around until he died!

As soon as he thought of this, he looked at the two characters carrying out this task.

Lord Grim didn’t need to be mentioned. With so many movement skills at his disposal, his unspecialized sat comfortably as king in terms of mobility.

As for Soft Mist? He could see the buff from the Neutral Chasers around her legs, drastically increasing her movement speed. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf had been left in the dust because he didn’t have the buff from Neutral Chasers.

Bad! Happy’s tactic was bad news for them!

Chapter 1692 - A Gun Can Miss

Fang Minghua sensed Happy’s intentions, and he knew that the situation was not looking good. He was very clear about the mobility of Samsara’s characters. Normally speaking, Assassins, Battle Mages, and Sharpshooters were relatively mobile. His Laughing Song and Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves were only slightly worse.

However, right now, Laughing Song didn’t need to move on his own. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim and Tang Rou’s Soft Mist were helping him move using blow-away and knockback skills. Laughing Song’s current movement speed was even faster than his sprinting.

Su Mucheng helped block the pursuers and would even coordinate with Ye Xiu and Tang Rou from time to time. Together, the three of them formed a beautiful combo.

Battle Mage and Launcher?

Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng, Best Partners?

All of these were a part of this well-coordinated play. On Samsara’s side, even with Swift Movements activated, Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence could only keep up with them. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf had no Neutral Chasers to buff him, and clearly lagged behind. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves didn’t even need to be said. He had been left in the dust. His situation looked rather embarrassing.

“How bold!!” The pro players discussed spiritedly. Happy was clearly doing something beyond their expectations.

In the finals, especially the deciding match, everyone would always be particularly careful. That was where the saying “anticipated match, boring game” came from.

But the play that Happy was making? This was an extremely risky play. While attacking Laughing Song, they had to carry him along faster than Samsara could, and Samsara wasn’t slow at all. The coordination needed was extraordinarily difficult. There were too many factors needed to be taken into consideration. Even the slightest slip-up would end in failure.

Happy’s healer, Little Cold Hands, was being blown up by Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer, and Happy wasn’t giving their healer even the slightest bit of help. If they made a mistake and Samsara caught up, it would be impossible for them to save Little Cold Hands. Little Cold Hands had lost half his health already. If Samsara was willing to focus him without regard for anything else, they could finish off Little Cold Hands in the blink of an eye.

Failure meant death!

Happy was determined to carry out this healer trade. They were walking on a tightrope, not leaving themselves any path of retreat. A single misstep, and they would fall into a bottomless abyss!

Compared to their brilliant teamwork, the pro players admired Happy’s bravery more.

The other problem was that a majority of their efforts needed to be put into moving Laughing Song, so even though Ye Xiu and Tang Rou were both dealing damage, their DPS was mediocre. They couldn’t compare to Zhou Zekai’s explosive DPS towards Little Cold Hands.

Zhou Zekai felt a bit more at ease because of this, but he didn’t stop paying attention to that side. Seeing that the other three on Samsara weren’t able to catch up to Happy’s side, Zhou Zekai had decided to give them a helping hand. He could see how difficult it was for Happy to execute this play. The slightest interference might be able to break it apart.

His Cloud Piercer wasn’t faster than Cruel Silence or One Autumn Leaf, but he was a long-ranged attackers. He could attack Ye Xiu and Tang Rou from his current position.

He made his decision. Cloud Piercer suddenly stepped back and moved to the side. Then, he lifted his guns.

Bang! Gunshot, a figure, blood!

Little Cold Hands suddenly moved to the side too, positioning himself in front of the guns.

Knee Strike!

Cloud Piercer lifted his knee. He wasn’t in a hurry to keep Little Cold Hands under control. Even a single bullet might be enough to break open the situation on that side. He only needed a tiny opening, and during this tiny opening, what could a Cleric do to him?

An Wenyi obviously couldn’t do anything to him. He only had one thought on his mind: I have to stop Zhou Zekai from providing support no matter what.

His Little Cold Hands had no combat ability. His little tricks might work against Samsara’s healer, but it was nothing in front of Zhou Zekai. The only thing he could use was Little Cold Hands’ body. He could use his life to block Cloud Piercer’s bullets.

An Wenyi was certain that he had never been this focused in his entire life. His Little Cold Hands had been taking a beating the entire time, but as soon as Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer moved aside to shoot towards that side, he immediately did all he could to stop him.

Sometimes, he could do it. Sometimes, he couldn’t.

But he knew how crucial this moment was. He couldn’t fail this time.

Little Cold Hands threw himself towards Cloud Piercer’s guns.

But what followed soon after was a Knee Strike.

An Wenyi saw it very clearly.

Little Cold Hands jumped back.

The Knee Strike missed!

But with this dodge, a small opening was left behind.

Cloud Piercer raised his guns and fired twice.

Little Cold Hands jumped up!

An Wenyi had Little Cold Hands jump towards Cloud Piercer’s head to block his vision.

The only thing that Zhou Zekai could see was a blood-soaked Cleric’s robe.

Blind firing?

Zhou Zekai had the ability to do so, but the problem was that he needed to aim at a very fast moving target. Even if he had a clear view of his target, he would need to predict where the target would move ahead of time. It wouldn’t have been easy. But now that he was blinded, it was too difficult even for Zhou Zekai.

Even so, he still fired his guns.

The bullets loaded and fired. He had to at least try.

The gunshot startled An Wenyi, but he didn’t dare look back. What if it missed? He had to keep going!

But at this moment, Cloud Piercer jumped up, and his Little Cold Hands was currently falling. There was a difference in timing, and this time, let alone Zhou Zekai’s line of sight, even Cloud Piercer’s two guns were above him.

There’s nothing I can do…

An Wenyi could only watch. He had no way to stop Cloud Piercer from attacking.

Damn it…

An Wenyi hated himself for being so useless.

Gunshot…

The airborne Cloud Piercer fired two shots in quick succession. But then, An Wenyi saw Ye Xiu type in chat: “Keep it up!”

Ah?

This time, An Wenyi couldn’t help but look back.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was using Charge to move ahead. His umbrella was in its shield form, a Priest weapon, so it didn’t affect his usage of Charge. As a result, he saw Lord Grim’s umbrella facing the side, blocking Cloud Piercer’s shots.

“Don’t get careless! Just because he’s fired his gun doesn’t mean that we’ll definitely be hit!” Ye Xiu continued.

“Also, Little Zhou, wasn’t your attack a bit too careless?”

As he said this, the canopy of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella folded. The umbrella ribs retracted, exposing the muzzle of a gun.

Gunshot!

Ye Xiu had fired back at Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer.

Chapter 1693 - Dual Guns Erupt

Block, counterattack, and taunt in the chat.

Ye Xiu’s response seemed so casual. An Wenyi was so moved he almost cried.

This was his teammate, a teammate that couldn’t be more reliable. He might not have been able to stop Zhou Zekai from attacking, but his teammates weren’t going to be done in so easily. His teammates were all far stronger than him. It was precisely because he had such amazing teammates that his reckless interference was especially meaningful.

I have to keep going! An Wenyi grit his teeth.

But at this moment, a bullet flew over over. Finally, it wasn’t Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer harassing others, but someone harassing him.

The speed of the bullet wasn’t fast, which let Zhou Zekai know that this was a Stun Bullet.

It moved slowly and had low damage, but its secondary effect was frightening. The attack had to be avoided. However, Cloud Piercer was currently airborne, making it much more difficult for him to dodge. Zhou Zekai looked at the direction of the bullet. Then, Cloud Piercer fired rapidly towards the ground, using Aerial Gun to force Cloud Piercer to the side. The Stun Bullet brushed past him just like that.

But…

Pu!

The sound of a bullet hitting flesh could be heard clearly.

How?

Zhou Zekai was startled. He saw it clearly. Cloud Piercer should have been outside of the bullet’s trajectory. But what hit Cloud Piercer was unmistakably a Stun Bullet.

Behind…

Zhou Zekai realized what had happened.

But Cloud Piercer was stunned now. There was nothing he could do as he fell from the skies.

Dancing Rain!

Countless people only realized it after the replay. When Ye Xiu counterattacked, Su Mucheng coordinated with him, and fired a Stun Bullet from behind Cloud Piercer.

The two of them timed it perfectly. The Stun Bullets were fired at the exact same time. Even a godly Sharpshooter like Zhou Zekai hadn’t noticed that two bullets had been fired at that moment. As for the others on Samsara, they had been waiting for Zhou Zekai to create an opportunity for them to rescue Laughing Song. How could they have known Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng would work together to attack Zhou Zekai? Even now, they were still lamenting that the attempt to block Ye Xiu had failed. They were still hoping for Zhou Zekai to try again, and hadn’t noticed that a Stun Bullet had hit Cloud Piercer.

An Wenyi didn’t know either. All he saw was Cloud Piercer dodging Lord Grim’s Stun Bullet.

I can’t only rely on my teammates. I have to work even harder!

An Wenyi strengthened his resolve, but immediately afterwards, he noticed that Cloud Piercer was stunned!

Stunned!

An Wenyi’s mind worked quickly. He didn’t understand how, but Cloud Piercer was stunned.

The Stun Bullet hit?

An Wenyi was puzzled. He had clearly seen the bullet miss. How did he get hit? Ye Xiu… how did he pull that off?

An Wenyi was thinking too much, but he knew that he had to seize this opening. He had been working as a meat shield the entire time, but now, there was an opportunity for him to attack back.

Little Cold Hands was covered in blood, yet the light of her holy cross shone as pure and bright as ever.

Hypnosis?

An Wenyi wanted to use this skill the most. However, although Hypnosis had a powerful CC effect, it had a long cast time. The stun duration wasn’t enough for Little Cold Hands to complete Hypnosis.

The next best thing was Sacred Fire.

Five seconds of reduced damage, and three seconds of Silence. Sharpshooters utilized their normal attacks far more than other classes, so being silenced wasn’t as terrifying for them. However, it would still greatly reduce his combat strength. More importantly, Clerics didn’t have any better CC skills available.

No matter how great Zhou Zekai was, he couldn’t cleanse the Stun. He could only watch as Little Cold Hands summoned a Sacred Fire.

The spell was cast, and holy fire engulfed Cloud Piercer. It wasn’t until these flames blazed that the others on Samsara realized that something had happened to Zhou Zekai. Everyone turned to look, and saw Little Cold Hands lighting Cloud Piercer on fire…

At that distance, a Cleric without any protection was actually able to land Sacred Fire on Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer?

Stunned?

Frozen?

Hypnotized?

Dizzy?

In any case, the others on Samsara could ascertain that Cloud Piercer had definitely suffered some immobilizing effect.

Help him?

The thought popped into everyone’s minds, but it was quickly thrown aside.

No matter what status he was affected by, it wouldn’t last long. Zhou Zekai was only facing a Cleric, who posed no threat to him. Cloud Piercer was also a long-ranged attacker. Even if An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands ran away during this time, he wouldn’t be able to escape from Cloud Piercer’s attack range.

There’s no need to help him.

Everyone came to the same conclusion. However, they had to face the effects of Zhou Zekai temporarily gone.

An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands didn’t run away because he knew that he couldn’t. The key was Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash. He had been pinned down by Zhou Zekai the entire time. The Heroic Leap from An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands had helped him win a small opening, but that had only happened once. Afterwards, as Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer attacked Little Cold Hands, he also took care of Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash, preventing him from setting up any ghost boundaries. An Wenyi obviously wanted to protect him, but close combat was never a Cleric’s specialty in the first place. When Zhou Zekai truly focused on him, there was only so much he could do. When he blocked the bullet for Ye Xiu and Tang Rou, he had gotten lucky.

One Inch Ash?

Samsara’s players shifted their attention to One Inch Ash. But soon afterwards, they discovered that One Inch Ash had disappeared!

To the side of the lofty pyramid were the remains of an ancient city. Destroyed walls and pillars were scattered throughout the ruins. When Cloud Piercer had been hit by the Stun Bullet, Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash had taken the opportunity to hide who knew where.

Zhou Zekai hadn’t noticed.

No one on Samsara had noticed.

Even An Wenyi hadn’t noticed.

Many of the spectators hadn’t noticed Su Mucheng’s Stun Bullet until the replay, but Qiao Yifan had noticed it.

Because he was always paying attention to the entire battlefield. He was always observing each and every teammate and opponent.

The simultaneous Stun Bullets from Lord Grim and Dancing Rain.

Apart from Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng themselves, he was the only player on the battlefield to have noticed their teamwork.

It’ll hit!

Qiao Yifan determined at that moment.

Should he place down a ghost boundary to further suppress Cloud Piercer?

He quickly dispelled the thought.

Because Qiao Yifan didn’t have any ghost boundaries available that would suppress Cloud Piercer effectively.

Darkness Boundary and Ice Boundary were on cooldown.

Ash Boundary, Silence Boundary wouldn’t be effective on Cloud Piercer. It would be somewhat of a waste of an opportunity.

As for Flame Boundary, which dealt damage, and Plague Boundary, which changed the opponent’s stats, those were even more meaningless.

In the end, Qiao Yifan chose to move away.

Using this opportunity, One Inch Ash escaped from Cloud Piercer’s firing range.

Little Cold Hands and Cloud Piercer were too close, so the stun duration wasn’t long enough for Little Cold Hands to run away. However, Qiao Yifan had been trying to run away from Zhou Zekai for a long time and was farther away from him. Now that such a huge opening had appeared, escaping would be easy.

Cloud Piercer’s bullet didn’t chase after him. In fact, none of the other Samsara players had looked towards One Inch Ash.

Qiao Yifan’s heart was beating like crazy. He knew that he had to take advantage of this opportunity no matter what.

He contacted Ye Xiu in the chat, and the two had a brief conversation.

One Inch Ash carefully hid himself behind a crumbling wall. His Silver weapon, Snow Stripe, started to glow

Chapter 1694 - Phantom Demon’s Obstruction

Boom boom boom...

Lord Grim and Soft Mist sent Laughing Song hurtling away. As they pushed him along, they attacked Laughing Song whenever they could. The skillful coordination between the two of them made even their teammate, Qiao Yifan, sigh in admiration. At the same time, he also noticed that Lord Grim had set it up so that Laughing Song wouldn't be able to see One Inch Ash.

"Is that also considered Vanishing Step?" Qiao Yifan thought to himself. He didn't forget to be diligent with his observations. Whether it was an ally or an enemy, he would do his best to find things that he could improve upon from them. From Lord Grim's attacks towards Laughing Song, Qiao Yifan could see hints of Vanishing Step. Usually, Vanishing Step was performed by moving into their dead angles. In this case, Ye Xiu was using Lord Grim's attacks to adjust Laughing Song's positioning, placing One Inch Ash inside Laughing Song's dead angles.

"The principle's the same, but it looks even harder than Vanishing Step," Qiao Yifan believed. Using attacks to control someone else's character was definitely much more difficult than controlling your own character.　

Now, it's my turn!

Qiao Yifan wouldn't forget to keep learning even inside a match, but he wouldn't forget about his mission either. Seeing Lord Grim and Soft Mist moving Laughing Song along, his One Inch Ash immediately began casting as if he had received an order.

The ghostly power flowed along his blade like water. Suddenly, it dripped down, and sunk into the ground, spreading outwards.　

Outside of the ruins, Wu Qi's Cruel Silence was still the fastest among Samsara. Even though Samsara had noticed that Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash had suddenly vanished, rescuing Laughing Song was necessary. For now, they could only stay in pursuit, while being wary of their surroundings.

Nineteen steps away!

Wu Qi was keeping track of the distance. The distance between Cruel Silence and Laughing Song wasn't steady. Sometimes, the distance would widen. Sometimes, the distance would shrink. After all, the two sides weren't simply running. Ye Xiu and Tang Rou had to coordinate together, and Wu Qi needed to avoid Su Mucheng's interference.

Sure enough, not marking Su Mucheng had a huge impact. Samsara could feel it deeply. If not for Dancing Rain's interference, they might have been able to catch up to Lord Grim and Soft Mist by now.

However, the situation couldn't be considered too terrible.　　

Wu Qi was confident. With him in close pursuit, Lord Grim and Soft Mist could only attack on occasion. Laughing Song would still be able to survive for a long time.

During this time, would the two on Happy be able to keep this up without making a single mistake?

Zhou Zekai's previous long-ranged assistance had failed, but that didn't mean it would stop there. Suppose the worst case: An Wenyi's Little Cold Hands was able to prevent him from providing support every single time. In that case, Zhou Zekai could simply focus on killing Little Cold Hands, and then help them. There was more than enough time.

There was also Su Mucheng's interference. Samsara was preparing to restrict her. Jiang Botao's Empty Waves was slower than the others. He was being left farther and farther behind, so it was pointless for him to continue chasing. He might as well turn around and go for Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain.

The others hadn't noticed the Stun Bullet from Su Mucheng onto Cloud Piercer, but Zhou Zekai had. He told his team, and the team felt like a BOX-1 on Su Mucheng was necessary. They shouldn't be giving her free rein.

However, Samsara hadn't expected Happy to make such a bold play. Moreover, Ye Xiu's methods were rather risky, which was why they all charged over there. If they had known this would end up being a competition in speed and that Happy had specifically practiced for this, they would have split up the work long ago. For example, Jiang Botao's Empty Waves was a Spellblade, who wasn't suited for a race.

They had promptly made the necessary adjustments. It couldn't be said that their reaction was slow, so they weren't feeling too frantic at the moment. The only problem was Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash.

That guy had suddenly disappeared. Fore Samsara, he was a huge worry. Phantom Demons had immense crowd control. If they were suddenly caught in one of his ghost boundaries, it would be devastating.　　

Even though they were worried, Samsara didn't slow down. The only thing that they could do was give chase.

Since they weren't clear about One Inch Ash's situation, worrying about him too much would only distract them. Samsara was quite resolved about this point.　　

Wu Qi's Cruel Silence carried on the glorious speed of an Assassin, moving swiftly like an arrow. With a flicker, he appeared into Qiao Yifan's line of sight.

Suddenly, he slowed down.

What's going on?

Wu Qi was startled for a moment, but he quickly realized what had happened. The earth beneath Cruel Silence's feet looked as if it had been dyed with black ink. His every moment suddenly seemed heavy.

Ash Boundary increased the weight of the affected characters, reducing their movement speed. The effects had spread onto Cruel Silence.

The distance between Cruel Silence and Laughing Song suddenly widened. Cruel Silence could only trudge his way through slowly. He turned his head, and saw One Inch Ash hiding behind the wall.

Wu Qi sent a message, telling his team of One Inch Ash's position.　　

However, it would take him some time before he walked out of the Ash Boundary. Jiang Botao's Empty Waves was charging towards Dancing Rain. Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer was no longer stunned, but he couldn't see One Inch Ash from his position. It would be hard for him to cover him.

There was only Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf left.　　

One Autumn Leaf had also been caught by the Ash Boundary. However, he had been slightly behind Cruel Silence, who was at the very center of it. That meant that he would be able to exit the Ash Boundary much sooner.

Right now, they needed to keep close to Lord Grim and Soft Mist, which meant that they had to keep pushing forward. However, if he wanted to leave this Ash Boundary, he would need to fall back.

One Autumn Leaf moved back. He had no other choice.

Cruel Silence slowly moved forward as he waited for a skill to come off cooldown. 　

Shining Cut!

With this movement skill, Cruel Silence would be able to quickly get out of the Ash Boundary.

But then, he saw the ghost god's power gathering around One Inch Ash's tachi, Snow Stripe.

This...

A deathly silence descended.　　

The Shining Cut that had just gone off cooldown was suddenly sealed.

Silence Boundary. All skills were silenced while inside of it.

Weighed down by Ash Boundary and silenced by Silence Boundary, Cruel Silence could only slowly walk forward.

Even though One Autumn Leaf had escaped, if he wanted to push forward, he would need to go around the ghost boundary. 　

Lord Grim and Soft Mist were getting farther and farther away, but he would need to go around the ghost boundary while also being careful of One Inch Ash. Sun Xiang was feeling particularly annoyed.

But right now, he was facing an even more difficult choice.　　

Should he continue chasing after Lord Grim and Soft Mist, or should he go after One Inch Ash?

He wasn't the only one thinking this question. Outside of the match, the pro players were also in a fervent discussion.

One Autumn Leaf was very far from Lord Grim and Soft Mist. If he continued to give chase, would he be able to catch up? Lord Grim and Soft Mist had no way escaped outside of Cloud Piercer's attack range. If Zhou Zekai wanted to provide support to his side, he would need to give up on Little Cold Hands. However, giving up on Little Cold Hands was risky. Little Cold Hands didn't have much health left. If he gave up on him, and Laughing Song wasn't rescued in the end, it would be like losing an army after having given away the bride. It looked like Zhou Zekai was clearly prioritizing killing Little Cold Hands. Without his support and at this distance, would giving chase do anything?

But if he didn't give chase... the other side would be completely free. They could stop and focus on attacking. It would be a 2v1, and it wouldn't be long before Laughing Song was killed. A healer for healer trade would be Samsara's loss. That was certain.

Both options were unfavorable for Samsara...

"But what if he could kill One Inch Ash here?" someone suddenly said.

Both sides would kill the other side's healer, but Samsara would also take down One Inch Ash. That would be a 1v2 trade, and that was undoubtedly a trade that Samsara would take.

"But that would be quite difficult, no?" Li Xuan said. He had the right of speech on anything related to Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash. As the number one Phantom Demon, he knew what Qiao Yifan should do next.

"I know it." Seeing Qiao Yifan's response, Li Xuan nodded his head.

One Inch Ash walked out.

His position was already exposed. There was no point in hiding behind the wall anymore, so he walked out from behind the wall. Not just Wu Qi, but Sun Xiang also knew exactly where he was.

However, One Inch Ash was standing inside his ghost boundary.

Ghost boundaries weren't just to control and restrict the enemy. Ghost boundaries such as Sword Boundary could also buff the Strength and Intelligence of allies. At the same time, the ghost boundaries that debuffed the enemy could also be considered a form of protection for allies as well, no?

Countless players, especially the close-ranged ones, loathed ghost boundaries. The more extreme ones even considered ghost boundaries as a BUG.　　

Because if the Ghostblade stepped into his own ghost boundary, how were the close-ranged classes supposed to fight him?

How?

Fight the Ghostblade while being unable to see inside a Darkness Boundary? Or while slowed in an Ash Boundary? Or while unable to use skills in a Silence Boundary?　

It was impossible!

That was why Sun Xiang could only look at him hatefully. It wasn't that close-ranged classes had no methods to deal with ghost boundary. However, these methods were slow and required time. But what Samsara lacked the most was time. While he slowly contended with Qiao Yifan, Ye Xiu and Tang Rou would kill off Laughing Song in the blink of an eye and then come back to help Qiao Yifan.

"If Jiang Botao were still there..." Wang Jiexi said.　

Jiang Botao's Empty Waves was a Spellblade. Spellblade attacks weren't long-ranged, but mid-ranged. But since he didn't need to get close, he didn't need to slowly contend with a Ghostblade. Moreover, with another player's fighting strength, Samsara would be able to kill One Inch Ash much faster if they focused him. They could decisively give up on Laughing Song, and go for a 2 for 1 trade.

But unfortunately, Jiang Botao wasn't there.

Chapter 1695 - A Glimmering Technique

Was it a problem with Samsara’s arrangements?

After Pan Lin and Li Yibo analyzed the present situation, most of the viewers thought so. If Jiang Botao were there, the situation would be much better. However, Jiang Botao wasn’t there. If that wasn’t a problem with their arrangements, then what was it?

But the pro players disagreed.

Saying that it was an issue with Samsara’s arrangements was like giving advice in hindsight. At that time, Samsara’s decision to send away Jiang Botao had been correct. On the other hand, their decision to ignore Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain at the start and have everyone go rescue Fang Minghua was questionable.

At this moment, because of Jiang Botao’s absence, Qiao Yifan posed an enormous problem for Samsara. Then again, if Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves had been there, Qiao Yifan probably wouldn’t have made the same play.

Instead of saying that it was a problem with Samsara’s arrangements, it would be better to say it was a timely decision from Qiao Yifan. Through his astute observations of the overall battle, he was able to create a new situation that looked as if it stemmed from an error on Samsara’s part.

“An outstanding team player,” the pro players praised. Every single time this happened, it was a form of torture to Tiny Herb. The profound stares from everyone said everything. No matter how calm they may be, they couldn’t help but feel a bit uncomfortable.

Samsara had no time to admire Qiao Yifan’s incredible play. For them, this incredible play meant huge trouble for them.

Lord Grim and Soft Mist, should they chase them or not?

It was a difficult decision. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf circled around the ghost boundary.

Chase!

Sun Xiang saw it. After he and Wu Qi were blocked by Qiao Yifan, he saw Ye Xiu and Tang Rou slow down, waiting to see what he and Wu Qi did before taking the next step. If Samsara turned on One Inch Ash, those two would probably stop completely and focus on killing Laughing Song as fast as possible.

Samsara didn’t wish to see this happen. Whether or not they could catch up wasn’t important, they would at least be putting pressure on them. That way, Happy had to keep moving Laughing Song along, and perhaps those two might make a mistake.

Chase, he had to give chase. If the two of them couldn’t, then at least one of them should.

Sun Xiang understood this point, and immediately sent a message to Wu Qi through the team chat. The two split up. Qiao Yifan was left to Wu Qi, while Sun Xiang had One Autumn Leaf circle around to continue giving chase.

Suddenly, sword light flashed. Moonlight Slash into Full Moonlight Slash, the classic Ghostblade combo appeared in front of One Autumn Leaf. Sun Xiang wasn’t looking for trouble, but Qiao Yifan was. Postured like a Sword Demon, a Phantom Demon attacked.

How could Qiao Yifan, who excelled at reading the big picture, not recognize the severity of the situation? Little Cold Hands’ death was certain. Whether Ye Xiu and Tang Rou could finish off Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song was crucial. For this to happen, blocking Sun Xiang and Wu Qi from getting to them was essential. Qiao Yifan couldn’t let them through no matter what. Unfortunately, One Inch Ash’s CC skills were on cooldown. No matter how much damage Flame Boundary dealt, or how much defense Plague Boundary lowered, it wouldn’t stop the other side from getting through.

Out of choices, Qiao Yifan could only have One Inch Ash take the fight to One Autumn Leaf.

Sun Xiang’s reaction was quick. One Autumn Leaf sidestepped twice, evading One Inch Ash’s attacks. One Inch Ash was extremely close to him. Sun Xiang really wanted to beat him up with his Evil Annihilation. He suddenly had an idea, and quickly typed in the chat: switch!

Having Wu Qi, who was trapped in a ghost boundary, deal with Qiao Yifan wasn’t as easy as it sounded. Affected by both Ash Boundary and Silence Boundary, Cruel Silence’s combat prowess was extremely weak. In an actual 1v1 against One Inch Ash, he would certainly be on the losing side. He might even be completely dominated. Close-ranged classes claiming ghost boundaries as “BUGs” wasn’t without its reasoning.

But right now, Qiao Yifan was ignoring Wu Qi, instead going for Sun Xiang. If One Inch Ash were pinned down by One Autumn Leaf, then when Cruel Silence left the two ghost boundaries, it wouldn’t be too big of a delay considering an Assassin’s speed.

So, switch!

Sun Xiang was ecstatic seeing this opportunity appear. It seemed like the attentive Qiao Yifan had made a mistake because of his heavy responsibilities.

Tyrant’s Destruction!

The moment he typed out “switch,” One Autumn Leaf unleashed a Tyrant’s Destruction to push One Inch Ash farther away from his ghost boundaries. Without ghost boundaries, a Phantom Demon would be at a huge disadvantage in close combat. A Phantom Demon’s essential tools, ghost boundaries, required cast times, but how could there be any time for them to cast anything in close combat? As for their remaining attacks, those would low-level Elementalist and Battle Mage skills. However, these skills were mainly reserved for survival, not actual combat.

But Qiao Yifan’s reaction was unexpectedly fast as well. When the Tyrant’s Destruction swung his way, One Inch Ash leapt backwards and then moved to the side. His rhythm was light and brisk. His movement gave people a sense of familiarity, but it seemed rather strange on One Inch Ash.

“What’s this?” The number one Phantom Demon, Li Xuan, blurted out. He was incomparably familiar with Phantom Demons, but his first thought was that his movements seemed strange.

The experienced pro players had the same feeling, but for a moment, they couldn’t quite pinpoint why. After this next step, One Inch Ash stepped to the side again.

“Overlapping Sidesteps,” someone shouted. When this name was said, everyone immediately understood where this sense of deja vu came from.

Overlapping Sidesteps wasn’t a rarely-seen technique. In fact, it was a very common one. However, because many classes had their own unique playstyles, many classes had their own unique techniques.

Overlapping Sidesteps was one such technique. It was a very basic movement technique. It was done by using small steps at a fast pace to circle around the opponent’s side or back to complete a back attack.

Back attacks dealt extra damage, which was a mechanic common to all classes. However, there was one particular class, which had additional bonuses for back attacks.

Assassins!

The Assassin class advancement skill “Assassination Arts”, buffed the damage from back attacks even further. Assassins were inherently fast and nimble, so players tried to go for back attacks whenever possible. Any class could perform Overlapping Sidesteps. It was just that Assassins made the best use of the technique. As a result, Assassins were usually the best at this movement technique.

One Inch Ash obviously wasn’t an Assassin. A few close-ranged classes would sometimes use it, but Ghostblades, particularly Phantom Demons, seemed to have no relation with this technique. But at this moment, One Inch Ash was using it, making the people watching feel like it was an unfamiliar sight. However, the distinct characteristics of the technique could clearly be seen. It didn’t look like he was doing it on a whim. Only a practiced and skilled Assassin had this level of mastery.

Why would a Ghostblade, a Phantom Demon, have practiced an Assassin’s technique to this extent? To the point that he could even execute it so smoothly at such a critical moment?

Many people felt puzzled, but those with an understanding of Qiao Yifan’s background, especially the Tiny Herb players, didn’t find it particularly strange. When Qiao Yifan had been a part of Tiny Herb, the team had him play an Assassin. It was a class that he had bitterly practiced with in the pro scene for half a year.

He had switched classes to a Phantom Demon, but he hadn’t abandoned the techniques that he had practiced as an Assassin. He had worked hard to learn those Assassin techniques. Even though his new class wasn’t suited for them, he felt like keeping them under his belt could never be a bad thing. After all, he had a teammate who was proficient with all classes, and Qiao Yifan had seen him use techniques from numerous classes, transforming the rotten into the miraculous. He didn’t have the talent to be proficient in all classes, but everything he had already practiced was a weapon. There would be a day, a moment, where it would be useful. Even a single time would be enough for it all to be worth it.

And this moment had come.

Overlapping Sidesteps!

A very ordinary technique that many Assassins were extremely familiar with. This technique was used to get to the side or behind an opponent as fast as possible, but this didn’t mean that the opponent would be unable to move. Against an opponent of Sun Xiang’s calibre, a two-step Overlapping Sidesteps was something that he could keep up with. What’s more, these Overlapping Sidesteps were being done by a Phantom Demon, not an Assassin.

No one could have expected a Phantom Demon to use Overlapping Sidesteps, let alone have such mastery over it. It was as if he were an actual Assassin.

When Sung Xian realized this and reacted, One Inch Ash completed his third step.

Three steps, three small steps, and One Inch Ash circled around from One Autumn Leaf’s front to his side. Only then did Sun Xiang react. Only then did One Autumn Leaf move. But One Inch Ash had already made his move.

Lunge!

A low-level Blade Master skill, an extremely fast stab.

It was too fast. It was impossible to dodge. One Autumn Leaf was hit.

The damage from the skill wasn’t high, but the skill had a knockback effect.

Sun Xiang’s expression changed. He realized what this knockback meant.

To One Autumn Leaf’s side was the Ash and Silence Boundary.

Chapter 1696 - First Death

Weight increased, skills sealed.

Chase after Lord Grim and Soft Mist under the effects of both Ash Boundary and Silence Boundary? Kill Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash? Don’t even bother thinking about these possibilities. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf had been pushed into the overlapping ghost boundaries.

Ghost boundary effects usually only lasted a few seconds, but on the pro stage, a few seconds was more than enough to alter the course of the match.

Lord Grim and Soft Mist immediately stopped their high-speed movement, instead switching into kill mode. The two characters poured out their attacks and skills. Laughing Song’s health plummeted as if someone had turned on the tap.

Sun Xiang and Wu Qi could only watch quietly.

They were the closest to Laughing Song, but these ghost boundaries made them feel as if they were the farthest away.

Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves had already started suppressing Dancing Rain. It wasn’t possible for him to switch targets and worry about others. No matter the development, suppressing Su Mucheng would always be an important win condition. Samsara had indeed been too hasty before. Suppressing Su Mucheng should have been a task carried out at all times.

There was also Zhou Zekai.

Whenever the team was in a stalemate, at a disadvantage, or in an uncertain situation, Zhou Zekai would always stand out, using his powerful presence to lead Samsara out, turning the tides and putting them on the road to victory. It was almost to be expected.

As a result, countless eyes looked towards Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer.

The Samsara fans hoped for another miracle from Zhou Zekai.

Happy’s players would never relax their guard against this top player. Among them, there was one pair of eyes that was practically glued to Cloud Piercer. His gaze never went anywhere else.

An Wenyi.

He didn’t know that Qiao Yifan had sealed off Samsara’s two pursuers with his ghost boundaries.

He didn’t know that Ye Xiu and Tang Rou had stopped to hurry and kill Laughing Song.

He didn’t know that Su Mucheng was fighting against Jiang Botao, trying to find an opportunity to help her teammates.

He didn’t even know how much health Little Cold Hands had left, nor did he look at Cloud Piercer’s health. The only thing he paid attention to was Cloud Piercer’s movements and his two guns.

Left? Right? Retreat? Jump?

An Wenyi stared at the movements of the guns. His Little Cold Hands reacted accordingly. In the pro scene, he was seen as a clear weakness of Happy’s, but at this moment, he was keeping watch over the best of the best in Glory.

Based on what?

An Wenyi didn’t know. Or perhaps it was just his conviction. His conviction to stop Zhou Zekai from escaping. His conviction to win.

To be the champion!

The Glory Alliance’s champion.

One year ago, two years ago, An Wenyi could only dream of those words. He had just been another player among the hundreds of millions who played Glory. He had been a Cleric, who admired Glory’s number one player, Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie, and supported Tyranny as a result. That was why he had joined Tyranny’s in-game guild, becoming one of the regular healers among Tyrannical Ambition’s teams.

For the vast majority of players, being a regular in a Club guild was considered being among the top players in Glory. But in Tyrannical Ambition, he wasn’t even good enough to be one of the elites. The guild’s elite team would usually be personally led by the guild leader. For him, the elite team had already been unreachable.

But in less than two years, he stood on the pro stage, fighting against players who had formerly been on a different plane of existence. He shook hands and greeted his idol, Zhang Xinjie. And now he was in the finals, fighting for the championship title.

So what if he was Happy weak point? If he could win the championship, nothing else mattered.

Fight and hold him down!

An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands was a like a piece of sesame soft candy. He was tangled around Cloud Piercer, blocking off his guns and his vision.

Keep going! Keep going!

He had forgotten everything. The only thing remaining in his heart was his conviction. Even when Little Cold Hands was down to his last drop of life, he didn’t hesitate. He wasn’t looking at anything else. His final struggle was the same as any other moment. Determined and resolute, he had to block Cloud Piercer no matter what.

Bang!

This was the last gunshot that An Wenyi heard. Then, the sky and earth went spinning. He saw Cloud Piercer sweep past him in a flash.

I can’t let him through!

An Wenyi thought to himself. He had Little Cold Hands reach out with his hands to grab onto the corner of Cloud Piercer’s windbreaker.

Got him!

When Little Cold Hands’ fingers touched Cloud Piercer’s windbreaker, An Wenyi’s heart burst with joy. Had he successfully stopped Zhou Zekai again?

But in the next second, the windbreaker vanished from his view. Only his hand was left, still stretched forward.

The world turned gray.

It’s over…

Little Cold Hands fell, becoming the first death this match. For An Wenyi, the finals was over. His season was over. He no longer had control over the outcome, but everything he had done still remained. However, he still had one lingering regret in his heart: that windbreaker, why wasn’t I able to grab onto it?

Happy’s healer was dead!

Usually, this news would make the opposing team overjoyed. Even if Happy’s healer was Happy’s weakness, a healer was a healer, an irreplaceable asset in the team competition. Whoever controlled the enemy healer, controlled the match. Then, what if you killed the enemy healer? That was practically an early proclamation of victory.

However, apart from some sparse applause from Samsara’s fans, no one was excited at this scene. No one felt like the world was theirs when Happy’s healer died because everyone knew that just killing Happy’s healer didn’t count for anything. Whether Samsara could rescue their own healer was the important question.

Cloud Piercer rushed over like an arrow. Laughing Song had been brought outside of his attack range by Lord Grim and Soft Mist because An Wenyi’s crazed struggle against him had made it so that he was unable to get closer.

“I wonder if a new method to deal with Zhou Zekai has been found,” Li Yibo joked around, but he didn’t get any responses from Pan Lin. He was completely absorbed into the match. An Wenyi’s stupid yet smart play, the tenacity and spirit that he showed wasn’t something Pan Lin could laugh about.

A new method?

It was just a joke. Everyone felt that what they had just witnessed was inconceivable, and something inconceivable often couldn’t be replicated. Even An Wenyi himself wouldn’t be able to repeat his performance today. Before today, he had probably never thought that he could do something like this. Even after this match, when he looked back, he himself would find it unbelievable.

A new method?

Only something with reason and context could be called a method. This sort of unconventional miracle couldn’t be considered a “method”.

Now, the miracle had faded away. Samsara’s Zhou Zekai had finally regained his freedom. This was also someone brought miracles to Samsara again and again. What would he do for Samsara next?

One step, two steps, three steps…

Cloud Piercer quickly gave chase. There was no one to stop him. Even though Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain fired a few artillery shells at him, she wasn’t able to sustain it. Jiang Botao marking her was already paying off. She couldn’t do as she pleased anymore. She needed to first deal with Empty Waves’ attacks before she could do anything.

They’re in firing range!

Lord Grim and Soft Mist were finally in Cloud Piercer’s range. During this time, Ye Xiu and Tang Rou hadn’t chosen to escape. They had lost control over Zhou Zekai. They could only hurry and try to finish off Laughing Song.

Bullets flew out, and in the blink of an eye, a rain of bullets swept towards them. The two continued to attack as they brought Laughing Song over behind a crumbling wall for some cover.

But the cover only lasted a short while.

The wall was short and small. In just a few steps, Cloud Piercer had vision of them again.

One Autumn Leaf and Cruel Silence had finally left the Ash Boundary and Silence Boundary. Even though Qiao Yifan had enshrouded them with more ghost boundaries, these new ones didn’t have powerful CC effects. As a result, the two didn’t hesitate to force their way through them.

It looks like this is all I can do. Seeing Laughing Song’s remaining health, Qiao Yifan triggered his final move.

Ghost Feast!

The chained ghost boundaries erupted, and because the ghost boundaries weren’t completely overlapping, the ghost god’s power enveloped an enormous area. At the same time, even though the Ghost Feast covered a huge area, its damage and effects weren’t as high.

Sun Xiang and Wu Qi weren’t scared by it. The two used skills to overcome the effects of Ghost Feast, and rushed out towards Laughing Song.

Laughing Song didn’t have much health left, but there was still time!

Cloud Piercer’s long-ranged attacks weren’t able to completely interrupt Lord Grim’s and Soft Mist’s attacks, but they were able to influence their offense somewhat, lowering their DPS. Happy wouldn’t be able to kill Laughing Song before they arrived.

It’s Samsara’s win!

As long as Samsara rescued Laughing Song.

At this moment, too too many people had this thought. Happy’s wandering assault had completely suppressed Laughing Song, but the DPS was too low. Even though Zhou Zekai was the only one attacking Little Cold Hands, without anyone interfering, he could completely focus on offense.

Too slow. Happy had run fast, but their damage output was too low.

Sigh… those with hope for Happy had already begun sighing. But just when Cloud Piercer moved into a new angle to attack, Zhou Zekai stared blankly.

He had realized something. They had overlooked something once again.

Happy’s healer was the first to die. Thus, Happy’s sixth player would be the first to switch in at the support zone below the pyramid.

Steamed Bun Invasion.

Chapter 1697 - Simple Detail

It was a bit too late for Lord Grim and Soft Mist to kill Laughing Song, but now, with Steamed Bun Invasion?

Ordinary viewers might have noticed how severe the problem was, but the pro players already couldn’t help but begin to applaud. Because they knew that this was definitely within Happy’s calculations.

They couldn’t fault Samsara for overlooking this, because they had only noticed anything when Steamed Bun Invasion had entered from the support zone and joined in on attacking Laughing Song. It was only because they were in the audience and had the omniscient view that they saw Steamed Bun Invasion sooner and recognized the problem faster.

And on Samsara’s side, even now, Zhou Zekai was the only one who had seen Steamed Bun Invasion, and only he had recognized this problem. Sun Xiang and Wu Qi’s views were blocked just perfectly, so they hadn’t yet seen the sixth player Steamed Bun Invasion, and they hadn’t realized that Happy had been running this whole time not just to avoid their pursuers and escape Cloud Piercer’s firing range, but also to place the final attack location right next to the support zone.

As soon as they began executing this exchange, Happy had realized that Little Cold Hands would definitely die before Laughing Song, so they had made preparations long before.

Happy had seen a little further. By the time Samsara realized the problem, it was already too late.

“Ash!”

In Samsara’s chat, a message from Zhou Zekai suddenly appeared.

Zhou Zekai was extremely decisive. As soon as he realized the problem, he swiftly let go.

It was too late to save Laughing Song.

This was the conclusion he made, and so Cloud Piercer turned fire, suddenly attacking One Inch Ash.

Sun Xiang and Wu Qi were stunned. The two of them had still been desperately making their way their as fast as they could. Zhou Zekai’s message, Zhou Zekai’s intent, they instantly understood, but why?

Even now, the two of them still hadn’t realized that this was close to the support area. They hadn’t realized the problem that because Happy’s healer died first, their sixth player would appear and increase their DPS.

But right now, there was no time for them to hesitate, or ask an extra question.

Turn fire!

Instantly, these two firmly carried out their captain’s directions. On the battlefield, the players were mostly left to rely on their own judgment and initiative, but when there was a clear instruction or intent, cooperation came first. As for whether or not the players could instantly grasp the intent of an instruction, that depended on the tacit understanding between team members.

Sun Xiang and Wu Qi hadn’t seen Steamed Bun Invasion, so they didn’t understand the full situation. But the two cooperated with Zhou Zekai with unquestioning resolve.

One Autumn Leaf, Cruel Silence, the two characters suddenly spun around, swiftly charging toward One Inch Ash.

Qiao Yifan was startled. He had still been calculating which of One Inch Ash’s ghost boundaries were off cooldown so he could go sneak attack a few more of Samsara’s players, when all of a sudden, three of his opponents were suddenly charging toward him without warning.

Qiao Yifan’s situational awareness was excellent, he was cautious and attentive, but ultimately he still lacked battle experience. Samsara’s swift and decisive response caught him off-guard.

Cloud Piercer’s gunfire came toward One Inch Ash first, and One Autumn Leaf and Cruel Silence were converging upon him. Even though these two still didn’t understand the reason for turning their fire, their execution was clean and precise. When they switched their target, the first thing they did was cut off the path that One Inch Ash could have used to get support from Lord Grim, Soft Mist, and the others.

They wanted to force One Inch Ash into a corner. Qiao Yifan could see this, and he didn’t want to tangle with them. One Inch Ash turned tail and ran.

With Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer marking him, his One Inch Ash had no chance to cast any ghost boundaries. Moreover, when he’d been slowing down One Autumn Leaf and Cruel Silence earlier, One Inch Ash had been setting ghost boundaries one after another without any rhythm. Right now, many of them were still on cooldown!

“They’re on me!”

While Qiao Yifan had One Inch Ash to flee, he was also swiftly alerting everyone in Happy: Samsara was coming for him.

And the escaping Qiao Yifan wasn’t simply running way in any random path. There was no way he could race against three people. Besides, movement speed wasn’t a Ghostblade’s strength. One Inch Ash leapt forward, tumbling over a fallen stone pillar, and after that he didn’t stand up again. Hiding behind it, he frantically crept along.

Borrowing this cover, he could avoid at least some of the damage from Cloud Piercer’s fire for now. Qiao Yifan knew that he couldn’t escape completely. All he needed to do was stall, to hold on for as long as he could, until his own side could come help him.

The cover of the stone pillar also blocked his field of view, so Qiao Yifan couldn’t see the situation of his pursuers. However, some distance away, he could see the struggle between Su Mucheng and Jiang Botao.

If he crept closer, he could achieve a bit of support from Su Mucheng’s firepower!

Qiao Yifan saw very clearly that, right now, Su Mucheng might be the only one who could extend a hand of support.

But at this moment, Qiao Yifan heard a gunshot.

Different types of guns fired shots with different sound effects. Guns of the same type would sound more similar, but the differences between a rifle, a revolver, and a handcannon were simply too different.

The sound of this shot clearly had a lot of strength behind it, and there was no series of rapid sounds after it. This was very clearly characteristic of a rifle shot’s sound.

A rifle…

Right now, the only one on the battlefield with that type of gun was the gun form of Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

Ye Xiu was currently closing in on Laughing Song, Lord Grim didn’t have a reason to use firing attacks. So, was this shot meant to support him?

Qiao Yifan was indeed very attentive to detail. After hearing just this one shot, his mind considered many things. And on Su Mucheng’s end, he noticed that her Dancing Rain was currently moving toward his own position. But it wasn’t clear that it was to support him. It seemed more like she was simply making a strategic supporting movement.

Qiao Yifan didn’t act rashly. He continued along his chosen path. Only when One Inch Ash was furiously running did he hurriedly swivel his view to look back.

And so, he saw Lord Grim.

He thought that the others couldn’t come support him so quickly, but when he saw Lord Grim’s position, he realized that Lord Grim wasn’t just firing that one shot when he found the spare time. Lord Grim was actually charging straight out, chasing after the tails of those three Samsara players.

This is…

Qiao Yifan was stunned, but he quickly realized.

Stupid! How was he so stupid?

The reason why it would have been inconvenient for Ye Xiu and the others to come rescue him was because they had to focus fire to kill Laughing Song as fast as possible before Samsara could save him. But now, Samsara’s three had clearly changed their target. They were no longer trying to rescue their healer. With that, of course, killing off Laughing Song was no longer a pressing matter. Controlling and killing a Cleric, one person was enough for that. So, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim quickly broke away to leap at Samsara’s tails, without any delay.

As expected of a God!

Even though Qiao Yifan had been playing with Ye Xiu for over two years now, his feelings of worship had never faded. Just now, for example, the logic was as simple as adding one plus one, but under the intense conditions of battle, to be able to recognize and react so quickly, that definitely wasn’t as simple as one plus one.

At least, Qiao Yifan hadn’t thought of it, and Samsara had overlooked it too, no?

In the audience, the pro players were still praising Zhou Zekai’s decision to turn fire as unusually decisive! They were just like Qiao Yifan. In that moment, their minds hadn’t made the connection. But then, they saw Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim rushing forth ferociously. After everyone was stunned for a moment, they too all realized what was going on, and they were filled with mixed emotions. It was such a simple logic, how come they had all overlooked it?

The pro players all exchanged glances, and no one spoke.

But at that moment, just as it seemed that Cloud Piercer was closing in on One Inch Ash with single-minded focus, just as it seemed that he was going to seize him in his grasp, Cloud Piercer suddenly made a 180-degree turn. He lifted his dual revolvers, and they spat fire.

Turned fire!

Cloud Piercer actually turned fire once again, moving quickly at the same time. He actually threw One Inch Ash aside again, and charged back toward Laughing Song.

This is…

The audience was once again dumbfounded.

Had Samsara really overlooked such a simple logic? Perhaps some people would, but Zhou Zekai hadn’t. He had been using this simple principle to lure Happy into lessening their offense against Laughing Song, and then, using the range advantage of his Cloud Piercer, he turned fire yet again and break the offense that Happy had mounted against Laughing Song.

A small advance and retreat, a link that everyone had overlooked, yet Ye Xiu and Zhou Zekai had set up so many schemes here.

“Perhaps these two really are on another level…” said honored guest Li Yibo in the broadcast. This was an extremely simple detail, but the real story lay within this simple detail.

Zhou Zekai controlled Cloud Piercer to charge in that direction. His long-range control was limited, but Fang Minghua wasn’t dead. If Zhou Zekai’s offense could allow him to seize the slightest opening, he would work as hard as he could to persist. But even so, Zhou Zekai wasn’t completely confident. Ideally, Happy would have only left one person to continue attacking Laughing Song. Judging from Happy’s bold and wild style today, he felt that that possibility was quite likely.

But although Happy was quite unrestrained when they were going wild, when Zhou Zekai hoped for them to go wild, to his surprise, Happy had in fact restrained themselves.

Perhaps they had seen through his intention? Zhou Zekai thought. After all, the other side had realized that they could loosen up and send an attacker away. With Ye Xiu’s knowledge and shrewdness, it was very likely that they had also prepared to defend against this strategy of baiting the tiger away from the mountain.

But if they had recognized this possibility of bait, and still sent out an attacker anyway, then it had to be said that Happy really was quite daring.

But to go wild like this all the time, there had to be some price to pay, no?

Cloud Piercer charged forth, his gunfire quick and biting. Zhou Zekai had thought very deeply, but he didn’t waver on his decision. He didn’t have a good handle on this situation, but he still firmly believed that this was worth an attempt. He believed in himself, and he believed in Fang Minghua.

Our healer is still here!

Chapter 1698 - Steamed Bun’s Sand Toss

Opening!

Fang Minghua had been searching for an opening the entire time, but this one was by far the closest to him yet.

Cloud Piercer’s bullets rained down. Fang Minghua could practically see the bullets flying past Laughing Song’s eyes. Happy wouldn’t retreat. Even if they had to take damage, they had to kill Laughing Song.

But under Cloud Piercer’s firepower, how could it be so easy to just tank the damage?

Reinforced Iron Bones!

The newly subbed in Steamed Bun was quick-witted. The moment Zhou Zekai attacked, his Steamed Bun Invasion activated Reinforced Iron Bones. With Super Armor, his rhythm wouldn’t be broken no matter how dense the rain of bullets. At worst, he would take more damage.

The breakthrough point would have to be Soft Mist.

Fang Minghua began paying more attention to Soft Mist’s side. He watched Laughing Song’s health carefully. Every second felt like a year.

This was a match point. If Samsara could successfully rescue Laughing Song, Samsara would almost certainly win. The countless Samsara fans among the crowd stood up from their seats. Whether or not their team could lock in the win gripped their hearts.

Closer, closer!

They prayed in their hearts. Because they could see that at this distance, Cloud Piercer’s offense wasn’t threatening enough. A bit closer… a bit closer and his gunfire would be more dense, and he would be able to rely on chaining together his attacks to fully suppress Soft Mist’s attacks. Or perhaps because she tried too hard to dodge, her rhythm would get messed up, and Fang Minghua would be able to find an opportunity to rescue himself.

Advance! This was the conviction in Zhou Zekai’s heart.

Opening! This was what Fang Minghua hoped for. He would never give up until the end.

Tang Rou began feeling the pressure.

Steamed Bun immediately activated Reinforced Iron Bones. He wasn’t feeling any pressure on his end, but that also meant that he was pushing it all onto Tang Rou. Zhou Zekai obviously wasn’t going to waste his time trying to stop a Super Armored character.

“Maybe Bao Rongxing shouldn’t have activated Reinforced Iron Bones,” Pan Lin said.

“Maybe… but even if he hadn’t, it wouldn’t have stopped Zhou Zekai from focusing on a single target,” Li Yibo said.

“That’s true,” Pan Lin nodded his head.

“Maybe Bao Rongxing should try and protect Tang Rou!” Li Yibo said.

“Her protection’s already arrived,” Pan Lin said.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim rushed towards Cloud Piercer, firing at him.

Zhou Zekai obviously saw him, but he had the same mentality as Tang Rou and Steamed Bun right now. Offense was his number one priority. He would only deal with the attacks that would interfere with his offense.

Hurry!

There wasn’t much time left. Once Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim got close to him, Zhou Zekai was certain that everything would end there. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim sticking onto him was far more threatening than An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands.

He moved away, doing what he could to delay Lord Grim. He open fired. This was the final sprint. There was only one chance left.

Rapid Firing, Random Firing, Berserk Firing…

At this moment, Cloud Piercer activated every buff he had. Zhou Zekai didn’t hold back, pushing his firepower to its peak.

Success or failure would be decided here, Gatling Gun!

Cloud Piercer suddenly stood his ground. He stopped firing with his dual guns, instead pulling out a heavy machine gun. Under the various Sharpshooter buffs, the bullets from Gatling Gun were practically connected as they flew out like a ray of light.

Tang Rou immediately recognized that she had to dodge no matter what. If the laser-like rain of bullets landed, she would likely be knocked back.

Soft Mist dodged. The Gatling Gun followed her. As the gun turned, the bullets were like an orderly flight of steps, creating an arc.

The arc forced Soft Mist to move in one direction. An opening finally appeared in front of Laughing Song.

Opening!

The opening that he had been waiting for who knew how long had come.

At this moment, Fang Minghua’s attention was entirely on Steamed Bun Invasion. He knew that the only one who could attack and stop him was Steamed Bun Invasion. He didn’t have the ability to fight against Steamed Bun Invasion, but he could avoid him. He had to avoid him.

Charge!

Laughing Song charged towards that opening. However, his gaze was locked firmly onto Steamed Bun Invasion.

Steamed Bun Invasion swung his fist as if it were a conditioned reflex. He sent a punch to intercept the fleeing Laughing Song.

But no matter how fast his reaction speed was, it was just an ordinary punch, so ordinary that Fang Minghua nearly laughed.

How easy!

Fang Minghua quickly acted. Laughing Song leaned slightly to the side as he rushed forward. Steamed Bun Invasion missed.

Fang Minghua obviously didn’t think that it was over just because he had dodged this single punch. But with how easy it had been to avoid Steamed Bun Invasion’s first attempt, he suddenly felt like he could see another opening on Steamed Bun Invasion.

After one opening, another one followed. Fang Minghua surged with excitement. His fingers suddenly felt even lighter and nimbler than before. Laughing Song raised his cross, ready to cast an instant Holy Cure on himself. His situation before had been so dire that he hadn’t even been able to cast an instant-cast skill.

Holy light gathered around his cross. Just before it shone onto Laughing Song, Steamed Bun Invasion’s ordinary fist suddenly opened wide, releasing a handful of sand.

Sand Toss?

The holy light extinguished.

Fang Minghua couldn’t describe what he was feeling with words. That punch was a Sand Toss? You can Sand Toss like that? If it’s Sand Toss, then throw it earlier? Why would you clench your fists so tightly? If the hand holding the sand hit me, what would that have done?

Sand Toss. Fang Minghua suddenly had countless questions about this common Brawler skill. Laughing Song had already been hit by the sudden Sand Toss. Fang Minghua hadn’t been able to react to it in time.

His screen turned dark.

A max-leveled Sand Toss had a 100% chance to Blind if it hit the face. The effect lasted eight seconds.

The countless Samsara fans closed their eyes. Eight seconds of Blind. Laughing Song had no chance of escaping anymore. Zhou Zekai had created an opening for him, but Fang Minghua could only rely on himself to take it. However, with eight seconds of Blind, there was no hope left for Fang Minghua.

“What the fuck? He can’t even dodge a Sand Toss?” Countless players cursed.

The pro players were speechless.

This Sand Toss… what should they say! It felt like a joke. It could be considered a cheese, a cheap play by a normal player.

But Steamed Bun had brought this cheese to the highest stage on Glory, extinguishing Fang Minghua’s last hopes.

“Unlucky!!!”

Everyone could sympathize with Fang Minghua. Now that everyone had seen it, everyone felt like they could easily deal with it. Against this delayed Sand Toss, you could dodge or interrupt it, easy as pie.

But Fang Minghua was the first to be cheesed. When he saw that punch, the thought of it being a Sand Toss probably hadn’t even crossed his mind, and because of that, what should have been child’s play ended his life.

Apart from sympathy, the pro players could only give him their sympathy. Pan Lin and Li Yibo didn’t know what to say. It was such an important match point, and it was resolved through a little trick? This decisive match was filled with all sorts of weirdness.

But in the end, Fang Minghua’s time was over. Praying for Zhou Zekai to pull off another miracle was hopeless. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had reached Cloud Piercer. With Lord Grim’s mobility, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer had no way to kite him. The two began an intense duel.

Not long afterwards, Samsara’s Laughing Song died. For both teams, the first to die was the healer.

Everyone had faith in the words: whoever controlled the enemy healer, controlled the match. Now that both healers were dead, who knew what direction the match would move towards. At least, it would still be a 5v5.

However, many of the viewers felt somewhat strange when they saw the names of Happy’s characters. Coincidentally, all of these people happened to be players from the tenth server.

Lord Grim? Soft Mist? One Inch Ash? Steamed Bun Invasion? Only Dancing Rain was slightly off. But the others, wasn’t this the team in the tenth server that had set countless dungeon records?

Chapter 1699 - What a Brawler

Today, the tenth server players were no longer noobs. Many of them had reached the Heavenly Domain, and begun their higher-level journey there.

But whether they’d gone to the Heavenly Domain or remained in the tenth server, any gamer who had experienced that pioneering period in the tenth server could never forget the dungeon record war at that time. Even if every server would experience a period like that, even if most people were only bystanders, no new server’s dungeon records had ever been so thoroughly dominated by the same people. The records they achieved seemed to symbolize eternity.

And now, the names that had left these records appeared in the ultimate battle of the finals. Neat and orderly, just like the original, a team with no healer, only DPS.

Dancing Rain, Cleansing Mist, the names of these two accounts weren’t the same. But they were the same class, the names used the same characters. By now, everyone had basically guessed that the Cleansing Mist of that time had been used by the person currently playing Dancing Rain, Su Mucheng.

For a pro player to go for a normal server’s dungeon record, many people would suspect them of bullying normal players. If this had been exposed at that time, Su Mucheng probably would have suffered all sorts of condemnation. But now, the situation was different. Everyone had witnessed Happy as this team grew, step by step. The dungeoning team that had swept those records, that had been their earliest form. Now, they stood upon Glory’s highest stage.

The players who had started in the tenth server, who had been only noobs back then, were thoroughly moved. They had never experienced any Glory history before the tenth server. They had only heard about the past, they had never really been deeply affected by it, because it was at a distance. But Happy had risen suddenly from their tenth server, to stand on Glory’s ultimate battlefield. In their eyes, this team was a symbol of their era. This was a new team, who, in the middle of their era, had grown up with them, and burst forth.

In this moment, countless tenth server players were blazing with passion. With Team Happy, they could truly feel immersed in this moment. Never before had a team left such a clear and heavy mark upon a server – never before, never until now.

This is our era, this is our symbol!

Tenth server!

Many gamers who had come from the tenth server suddenly erupted with this cheer, confusing many other players. This kind of immersion, this kind of significance of a symbol – without experiencing it themselves, they could never understand.

Even in the live audience, Samsara’s home stadium, a commotion rose up. Of course, a number of Samsara fans had come from the tenth server as well.

However, although the sight of these names may have caused memories to resurface, these gamers would not change sides because of this.

The match continued. A list of characters could not kill an opponent.

Ye Xiu and Zhou Zekai were fighting, and it was hard to tell who had the upper hand.

Su Mucheng and Jiang Botao were circling, although Dancing Rain was clearly moving closer to Lord Grim’s side, trying to establish a connection.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun had finally taken care of Laughing Song, and the two of them were swiftly rushing toward Lord Grim.

Happy’s next target was Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer?

That seemed to be the case. Happy was not a team that could be predicted through common principles, and it wasn’t like they hadn’t focused the opponent’s core before. In that team battle against Tiny Herb in the regular season, they had focused and killed Wang Jiexi’s Vaccaria, which had become a textbook example of this strategy.

And in conditions where both sides no longer had a healer, attacking the absolute core of the “one-man team” Samsara, Zhou Zekai, was simply following a logical train of thought. In the Tiny Herb match, when they’d focused Wang Jiexi’s Vaccaria, even trading two for one was worth it.

However, Samsara immediately detected this clear intention.

This confrontation between Zhou Zekai and Ye Xiu right now was no less intense than their 1v1 had been last round. On one side, bullets flew; on the other, a weapon shifted between a thousand forms. But when he saw more of Happy’s players running toward him, Zhou Zekai knew this couldn’t continue.

Cloud Piercer began to fight while falling back.

If only talking about movement speed, no character could keep up with Lord Grim. But when a sharpshooter used Aerial Fire to move, the technique came with a natural protection of firepower. If the opponent wanted to give chase, they had to defend against the bullets that came their way.

Neither side had a healer anymore. Decisions like blindly tanking damage now had to be weighed carefully. But Ye Xiu completely ignored this fact about the present situation. Lord Grim opened his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, Charge!

Lifting a shield only decreased the damage, it didn’t completely negate it. Such a move still meant that he was tanking the damage to attack.

But Ye Xiu had other reasons for doing this. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun were just about to arrive, so at this moment, it was of course crucial that he stick to Cloud Piercer so that they had a beautiful 3v1 situation. Even if Cloud Piercer didn’t die, any amount of damage was helpful. Right now, the situation was that there were no healers. His Lord Grim would sacrifice some blood now to see more blood spill from Cloud Piercer later.

The Charge instantly closed the distance between the two characters. Even Zhou Zekai himself knew that there was no way his Cloud Piercer could shake off Lord Grim in the span of a few steps. When the Charge activated, he was already controlling Cloud Piercer to change directions.

Sidestep!

Cloud Piercer stepped to the side, letting Lord Grim’s Charge go past him. The skill allowed the user to move very fast, but because it was so fast, it was difficult to adjust or control the movement.

But Ye Xiu was no ordinary person. When he saw Cloud Piercer dodging, he immediately cancelled the Charge. Against his own inertia, Lord Grim twisted his body to change directions. However, Zhou Zekai had also predicted that he might be able to make this kind of response, and his character was already backing even further away. He wanted to use these kinds of nonstop direction changes to shake off Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim.

This match had seen a Cleric brawl, it had seen the cheap trick of Steamed Bun Invasion tossing a handful of sand. It had been almost embarrassing for the audience to watch. But when they saw the direct confrontation between Ye Xiu and Zhou Zekai, this level, this skill, this technique demonstrated was just going up and up.

Changing directions to get away, it was a very foundational technique. But when it came to Ye Xiu and Zhou Zekai, with the speed and frequency of these changes, not to mention the feints thrown in, it was almost too much for the eye to see. On the pro players’ side, the seniors of the various teams all treated this as teaching material for their rookies to watch and learn. At the same time, their hearts were trembling as well.

Zhou Zekai didn’t manage to have Cloud Piercer shake off Lord Grim, but Ye Xiu hadn’t been able to let Lord Grim get a solid control of Cloud Piercer. But reaching this point was already extremely difficult. For a Sharpshooter to be tangled with Lord Grim to this extent and still avoid being at a disadvantage, perhaps only Zhou Zekai could pull that off. And for someone to struggle with Cloud Piercer like this without letting him slip away, aside from Ye Xiu there weren’t very many who could.

But overall, if this situation continued, it was Zhou Zekai who would be at a disadvantage. As long as Ye Xiu could pin down Cloud Piercer like this, he was achieving his goal. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun’s characters were growing closer and closer. A Brawler had mid-range attack skills, and Steamed Bun Invasion was already preparing his move. Most people had no way of guessing what attack this guy would use. If you thought too deeply, you would end up like Fang Minghua. If your thoughts were too shallow, then, well! Steamed Bun’s skill was right there, he could use any number of high-level techniques.

Brick!

In the end, when Steamed Bun Invasion stepped within attack range, in his hand was still his favorite, Brick.

The Brick flew, but the distance was a bit far. While Cloud Piercer was struggling with Lord Grim, he lifted his guns – bang bang, and that Brick was shattered in midair.

“Whoa, you’ve got some skill!” Steamed Bun’s strange words immediately arrived. In all of Glory, everyone knew that Zhou Zekai very much had some skill. Truly, everyone found Steamed Bun’s shocked tone incomprehensible.

“Boss I’m coming, watch me!” Steamed Bun was still shouting. With this tone, it really seemed as though there were some powerful attack in the making. But if you wanted to say that this was him giving a signal to coordinate with Ye Xiu, that didn’t seem too right. A signal for cooperation, it wouldn’t come with such a grandiose announcement in the public chat.

And so, Steamed Bun Invasion attacked again.

Molotov Cocktail!

Another flying projectile, what use was that?

The high-level pro players could no longer take any of Steamed Bun’s crude actions seriously. The Brick had been shattered by Zhou Zekai’s fire in midair, what could this Molotov Cocktail do? What’s more, even if Zhou Zekai didn’t manage to shoot it down, then if it hit, it would just cause some AoE burn damage. Cloud Piercer would just lose some health, that was all. It wouldn’t help control the opponent at all!

Every class type had a subclass that excelled in control.

For the Swordsman class, that was the Ghostblade. For the Gunner, the Spitfire; the Mage, Witch; the Nightwalker, Warlock; the Priest, Exorcist. And among the Fighter classes, the Grappler’s so-called control revolved around the strong priority of that class’s grab skills, which would simply bind the opponent. If talking about the true meaning of “control,” the one at the front of the Fighters was still the Brawler class.

Right now, Happy just needed to control Cloud Piercer. But then, Steamed Bun Invasion came in with a Brick, which was too far and posed no threat. And then, a Molotov Cocktail, which, even if it hit the opponent, would pose no threat of control.

“What kind of bullshit is this.” Among the pro players, Tang Hao could barely stay seated. He felt that this kind of Brawler level was embarrassing to the Brawler class as a whole. Even though Steamed Bun had played a big role in killing Laughing Song, the skill he’d displayed then was nothing impressive. Everyone sympathized with Laughing Song; no one praised Steamed Bun for being exceptional.

And now, in such a critical moment, Ye Xiu was working so hard to keep Zhou Zekai from escaping! Steamed Bun Invasion had mid-range attack options, he could start supporting early, but these two attacks didn’t give Zhou Zekai any difficulty at all.

“Get a brain, won’t you!!” Tang Hao couldn’t help but begin shouting.

Chapter 1700 - Red-Black Clash

The players laughed up their sleeves.

Tang Hao was a rather haughty person. Let alone a rookie, he even looked down on many of the famous pro players. Steamed Bun had triggered him. It was as if he were Happy’s coach. Seeing Steamed Bun’s performance turned his expression unsightly.

Steamed Bun Invasion’s “brainless” Molotov Cocktail ended up just like what everyone had expected. It was barely an inconvenience for Zhou Zekai. However, without a healer, health became much more precious, so Zhou Zekai didn’t let the Molotov Cocktail hit him. Cloud Piercer raised his guns. This time, he didn’t even need two shots. He sniped the Molotov Cocktail from the air with just one shot.

Boom!

The Molotov Cocktail shattered and burst into an enormous fireball. The fire spread outwards.

Zhou Zekai’s expression turned pale. Even though it was only for an instant, he clearly felt that the instant the fireball spread outwards, Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion had been enveloped by it.

This was a form of cover!

Zhou Zekai reacted swiftly, immediately realizing that he had been a bit careless. But that was also in part because of how sloppy Steamed Bun’s Molotov Cocktail was. No one had expected this sloppiness to have such a huge effect. The Molotov Cocktail provided large-scale cover for Happy.

At this moment, there was no time for Zhou Zekai to think about too many things. He tanked Lord Grim’s attack, while moving to the side. He was repositioning himself to find a new angle of attack, and to avoid Steamed Bun’s and Tang Rou’s potential follow-ups.

They’re here!

Zhou Zekai was mainly looking in Soft Mist’s and Steamed Bun’s direction. Sure enough, the blazing fireball was split apart in the center by a flash of red.

Soft Mist, Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

That was close!

It was a good thing Zhou Zekai reacted quick enough, predicting what might happen next. If not, Cloud Piercer wouldn’t have been able to dodge Soft Mist’s Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

Soft Mist closed the distance in an instant. Ye Xiu had coordinated with Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, making sure that Lord Grim wouldn’t obstruct Soft Mist’s Dragon Breaks the Ranks. Unfortunately, Zhou Zekai had reacted too fast, preemptively dodging it.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks missed!

After all, with that type of cover, neither side could see each other. Tang Rou immediately rushed out with Dragon Breaks the Ranks, but she didn’t know that Zhou Zekai had moved away. By the time Soft Mist pierced through the fireball, it was too late for her to adjust her attack.

Cancel!

Tang Rou didn’t feel bad about wasting the skill. She cancelled Dragon Breaks the Ranks. However, the momentum brought by the skill wasn’t small. Cancelling wasn’t the same as finishing the move. There wasn’t as much control over her movements. As a result, Soft Mist continued to be pushed forward. Tang Rou had Soft Mist forcefully turn. Her sliding feet pressed a hole into the ground.

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart!

Another high-level skill! Even when facing Zhou Zekai, Tang Rou didn’t back down. In the blink of an eye, her Soft Mist switched places with Lord Grim, taking the role as the main attacker. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim moved to her side, becoming her support.

Not good!

When the pro players saw Ye Xiu and Tang Rou switch positions, they knew that the two of them together would be extremely difficult to defend against. No matter how capable Zhou Zekai was, Cloud Piercer was still a Sharpshooter. A 1v2 in close quarters wasn’t just a difficult situation, but a dangerous situation. What’s more, Steamed Bun Invasion had also charged through the fireball. His hands were waving around in the air. Who knew what ridiculous play he would pull off next.

Everyone’s attention was focused on this side. Everyone was wondering whether Happy would be able to kill Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer. The other parts of the battle didn’t seem as important. Soft Mist’s Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart was just about to pierce into Cloud Piercer. Cloud Piercer was trying to dodge, but no one knew if he would be able to. Suddenly, a black shadow flickered between the two.

Hua!

Two spears, one red, one black, clashed. The unstoppable Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart was knocked askew by the collision. The collision had been created by an attack with even higher priority than Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart. It was the attack that Soft Mist had just used.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

One Autumn Leaf!

Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf suddenly returned. He hadn’t targeted anyone with Dragon Breaks the Ranks. Instead, he put himself between two characters to protect Cloud Piercer.

Tyrant’s Destruction!

One Autumn Leaf knocked aside Soft Mist’s spear. Then, he cancelled Dragon Breaks the Ranks, and followed with Tyrant’s Destruction. He was planning on sweeping aside both Soft Mist and Lord Grim.

Tang Rou refused to back down. She cancelled her Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart, and followed with a Tyrant’s Destruction of her own.

The two spears collided again. The same skill against the same skill. With both skills maxed, their damage and priority were the same. The winner of the clash would be decided by the character’s stats.

For Soft Mist, apart from Dancing Fire Flowing Flames, she had other Silver equipment that Happy had scrambled together. Soft Mist’s stats wouldn’t lose to most other Battle Mages in the pro scene, but compared to the Battle God, One Autumn Leaf, there was still a clear disparity. The two skills collided, and Soft Mist clearly lost. Not only did One Autumn Leaf’s Evil Annihilation stop the momentum from Soft Mist’s Dancing Fire Flowing Flames, it continued along its original trajectory.

Even so, the power of One Autumn Leaf’s attack was reduced significantly. Whether it was speed or damage, the skill was no longer a threat.

But One Autumn Leaf had the upper hand. If he switched moves, his would come out before Soft Mist’s.

Sky Strike!

Evil Annihilation suddenly swung upwards. The Tyrant’s Destruction changed into Sky Strike. The slow spear suddenly accelerated.

Soft Mist’s Dancing Fire Flowing Flames had been knocked aside. It wouldn’t be easy for her to block this Sky Strike from her position. This was obviously why Sun Xiang had chosen to switch to Sky Strike. The average viewer wouldn’t be able to understand this tiny detail.

Even if the Sky Strike wouldn’t be easy to parry, Tang Rou still didn’t back down. She struck back with a Sky Strike of her own. This time, there wouldn’t be a collision. It would be a trade.

It was a trade, but one came before the other. One Autumn Leaf’s was faster. Once Soft Mist was launched into the air, it was hard to say if her Sky Strike would reach One Autumn Leaf. Tang Rou wasn’t sure either, but she continued onwards.

Bang!

She hadn’t parried, but the sound of a parry could be heard. Soft Mist’s Sky Strike swept forward, but One Autumn Leaf’s Sky Strike had been blocked by Lord Grim’s Dragon Tooth from the side. Tang Rou didn’t back down, not only because of her confidence in herself, but her confidence in Ye Xiu. She trusted that Ye Xiu would help her when she needed it.

One Autumn Leaf’s Sky Strike was blocked. It was too late for him to dodge Soft Mist’s Sky Strike. After being hit by Dancing Fire Flowing Flames, he was launched into the air.

But Tang Rou had Ye Xiu, and Sun Xiang had Zhou Zekai. After being protected by One Autumn Leaf, Cloud Piercer didn’t immediately run off. As soon as One Autumn Leaf was launched into the air, a figure appeared behind him. Cloud Piercer had a long sniper rifle aimed steady.

Thunder Snipe!

Zhou Zekai had Cloud Piercer take out this powerful skill. The long sniper rifle was aimed right at Soft Mist’s head.

The sparks flying out from the muzzle of the gun seemed to stick to Soft Mist. At this distance, it was impossible for Soft Mist to dodge the Thunder Snipe. Blood burst from Soft Mist’s head.

A huge loss!

The spectators all thought the same. Both sides had gone back and forth. Even though Soft Mist had successfully knocked One Autumn Leaf into the air, the damage from Thunder Snipe was on an entirely different level. What’s worse was that One Autumn Leaf was in the perfect position to be attacked, but with the Thunder Snipe, there was no possibility of Soft Mist following up. The knockback from Thunder Snipe was massive. Soft Mist was still stumbling back.

Ye Xiu was still there.

But Lord Grim didn’t have any attacks that could match Thunder Snipe’s damage. The damage from that one snipe wasn’t something that he could regain with a single attack.

Sword Draw!

Cold light flickered, a blade unsheathed. Lord Grim attacked both Cloud Piercer and One Autumn Leaf, while also protecting Soft Mist. It was the best he could do.

One Autumn Leaf couldn’t dodge while in the air. The Sword Draw was fast too. He had no time to parry it either. He could only take the hit. However, Zhou Zekai had predicted that Ye Xiu would respond in some way. After successfully landing Thunder Snipe, he retreated. It was almost as if Lord Grim and Cloud Piercer were in sync. The Sword Draw was dodged cleanly.

Cloud Piercer retreated. Close combat against close-ranged classes was very unfavorable for a Sharpshooter. Zhou Zekai took this opportunity to pull apart from Happy’s characters. As he retreated, he continued to attack and protect One Autumn Leaf. At the same time, their sixth player, Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost, had finally arrived, and was about to enter the fray.

But he was still a bit far from this side of the battle.

“I’m here!” Steamed Bun typed into the chat. This was a common habit amongst in-game players. Once Steamed Bun became a pro player, he didn’t throw this habit away. In the competitive scene, others might be using the chat to wage psychological warfare on the opponents. On the other hand, Steamed Bun used the chat to say meaningless nonsense.

Okay, you’re here. So what?

Many of the viewers replied back inwardly.

Chapter 1701 - Unspoken Understanding

Steamed Bun Invasion charged forth.

What attack would he execute? Everyone was rather curious and eager to see what he would do, all turning their attention to him. Even Sun Xiang didn’t dare let his guard down. Steamed Bun’s skill level was very volatile, hard to gauge or comment on, but it wasn’t someone anyone should ignore. Currently, One Autumn Leaf was airborne, but being airborne wasn’t the same as being stunned. He could still attack and move to an extent.

He was getting closer… and closer…

Steamed Bun Invasion lunged forwards with his fists raised, yet, under the eyes of the watching crowd, he didn’t strike.

What was he waiting for?

Everyone wondered to themselves, watching as Steamed Bun Invasion rushed closer and then… Street Riot!

What the fuck!

Everyone cursed in their hearts.

What was he waiting for? He was waiting to close the distance! A powerful skill unleashed just like that, in your face, with no cover or prep. He just ran up to his target and used it.

The pro players were completely speechless. How… low-level, how… noobish! However, this was exactly what the players of Samsara had not been watching out for. They focused on Steamed Bun Invasion, wary of his next move, yet he didn’t make a move. He just ran and ran and then when he got close, he used a powerful skill.

A low-level move, yet on this high-end stage, it had become a feint that managed to trick everyone. No one would’ve guessed that Steamed Bun Invasion’s movements were so simple and straightforward, actually just running up and unleashing a powerful skill.

What an embarrassment…

All the pro players held their heads in their hands. It was they who had let such a player appear on this ultimate, final stage! It was their fault for not managing to eliminate him in an earlier round.

“When up against this guy, you can’t face him with the same state of mind you would have in a normal match,” someone was saying. Steamed Bun had played quite a few matches this season, and there were many of pro players that had the experience of facing him. His unpredictability was something known and tested.

However, not using the usual state of mind you’d have towards matches was an easy thing to say, but if not your usual state, then what state should you use? Steamed Bun’s strange thought processes weren’t something you could deal with by finding the right state. If you treated him as a noob, then that would be a mistake you’d definitely regret making. But if you treated him like a pro player… just look now, he managed to get the advantage through a distinctly non-pro action. This guy switched freely between playing like a noob and like a pro. There really wasn’t anyone who could keep up with his rhythm.

“Follow your own rhythm, don’t focus too much on his actions.”

“Isolate him.”

“Mark him.”

“Pincer.”

The pro players were all talking amidst themselves, as though how to deal with Steamed Bun’s weirdness were an academic discussion topic.

Steamed Bun wasn’t exactly a top-tier player, but he also wasn’t someone easy to deal with either. Many had fallen to his unpredictability. Though his instability might negatively affect his team, in a life and death match like this, they couldn’t place their bets on an unknown. What if he was hiding a secret weapon or something just for this match? It wasn’t like that hadn’t happened before.

The pro players had yet to come up with a conclusion from their discussion. Meanwhile, Steamed Bun Invasion’s Street Riot was taking the spotlight on the field. All sorts of low to mid level Brawler skills being unleashed in a mindless torrent. From the rate at which he was dishing out attacks, it was clear that his technical skill was nothing to laugh at.

Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer could still pull away and avoid it, but Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf wasn’t so fortunate. Originally, being airborne wouldn’t have been much trouble for One Autumn Leaf. He had kept his focus on what Steamed Bun was going to try when he ran over, yet the other didn’t do anything. When One Autumn Leaf finally landed, quick recovering and about to get up and continue fighting, Steamed Bun Invasion’s powerful skill was launched.

Bricks, Sand, Inject Poison, Paralysis Needle…

All sorts of skills and items came raining down on One Autumn Leaf, with punches and kicks interweaved between. A level 70 skill wasn’t easy to deal with, and Sun Xiang was rapidly beaten back. After One Autumn Leaf’s quick recovery, he didn’t manage to actually get up, rolling on the ground to try and dodge the assault.

Zhou Zekai, having pulled his Cloud Piercer out of the way, looked back and realized that his evasive maneuvers had been a little too excessive! Steamed Bun had been completely locked on to One Autumn Leaf, and Street Riot’s skills were all directed at him. Not a single one came for Cloud Piercer.

However… if Cloud Piercer had been in his original position, then that might’ve been a different matter.

Zhou Zekai knew to look at things from different sides, and didn’t underestimate Steamed Bun’s decision. No matter if it was a coincidence or chance, he would treat it as it if it were intended.

However, he wasn’t able to support Sun Xiang at the moment. As soon as his Cloud Piercer stepped back, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim immediately darted in, cutting him off from One Autumn Leaf. Then Lord Grim closed in, attacked, not giving him an opening to come to Sun Xiang’s aid.

By now, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had managed to recover from the impact of that snipe. She threw herself back into the fray without hesitation, charging at One Autumn Leaf.

For a moment, the players of both teams were paired up in one on one fights, without any cooperation happening. It seemed to have no tactical elements. However, from what the players were attempting to do, it was possible to find tactical intent. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain kept trying to edge over to this side. She clearly didn’t want to continue dueling Jiang Botao one on one,. She hoped to play on her strengths, using her abilities to support the entire team in combat.

Jiang Botao, responsible for marking her, felt a little helpless. Empty Waves’ attacks weren’t able to lock Dancing Rain down completely. It wasn’t to say that Jiang Botao’s mechanics or ability wasn’t good enough, it was a limit of the class he played. Spellblades did high single target damage, but it was hard to chain skills. So against him, Dancing Rain still had room to maneuver. All Jiang Botao could do was to try his best to stop Su Mucheng from reuniting with her teammates, but he couldn’t lock her down completely so she was still managing to slowing edge over.

The cannon swung around; Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain had finally entered the range at which she could provide support. Immediately, she sent a missile over to help Tang Rou and Steamed Bun’s offensive, making things even harder for Sun Xiang, who was fighting one against two.

One against three, huh?

Dancing Rain’s offensive support cannonfire was a nightmare for Sun Xiang. He wasn’t having a good time against his current two opponents. One was fierce and fearless, the other unpredictable and strange. The two had completely different styles, and didn’t even attack with the same rhythm. They were basically ignoring each other as they fought. Even so, it wasn’t easy for Sun Xiang to deal with. The two weren’t consciously attempting to synchronize and act cooperatively, but they seemed to have a kind of unspoken understanding between them. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun had started from zero and gotten here fighting and growing side by side. They had never purposefully tried to develop any sort of tacit understanding and cooperation. It had formed naturally. It was something even they themselves probably couldn’t describe or explain: why did they have such habits in combat? It was because they were used to having each other present when fighting. Their understanding and tacit teamwork was all completely subconscious.

If even they didn’t realize it, then how would their opponents be able to see it? So it seemed like the two weren’t cooperating at all, yet they were just extremely hard to deal with.

“This duo is a rather… strange one…” The pro players started thoughtfully discussing amongst themselves again as if the doors to a new land had opened for them. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, a duo that seemed to have no method or organization to their teamwork, yet there was a strange, indescribable feeling there. For a moment, none of them knew how to explain it.

“Usually, for a team offensive, you would try to mess up their rhythm, thus reducing their combative ability. However, from the very beginning, they never had a shared rhythm to their actions,” Wang Jiexi said, primarily aiming to share his observations to his Tiny Herb teammates.

“That’s why Sun Xiang can’t find an opening right…?” Yet that when Blue Rain’s Huang Shaotian butt in.

“Not at the moment, but who knows what will happen?” Wang Jiexi said. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun’s teamwork was vague, uncertain, so he wasn’t sure if they would be able to keep Sun Xiang suppressed, or if Sun Xiang would soon find an opening. However, currently, it seemed like Sun Xiang no longer needed to find any opening. Samsara’s sixth player, Du Ming’s Moon-Luring Frost had arrived.

Triple Slash!

Moon-Luring Frost charged in, slashing thrice with his blade, once at Soft Mist, once at Steamed Bun Invasion, and with the last, he changed directions.

Moon-Luring Frost left!

The first two slashes of Triple Slash seemed like he was just harassing them as he passed by while the last one had Soft Mist, who had turned to attack him, striking air.

Dancing Rain!

Moon-Luring Frost ended up charging in her direction, standing in the way of her cannonfire.

Su Mucheng rapidly regained her supportive maneuvers, but Samsara wasn’t willing to let her do as she wished. Though Jiang Botao’s marking was effective to some degree, it was still limited and full of openings due to his class. If they wanted to properly lock Su Mucheng down, then they would have to do as they were doing before and have a melee class close in and keep her occupied.

This was the reason why Du Ming only spent a moment helping Sun Xiang. However, he did pull off a successful feint. The two attacks from Triple Slash had everyone thinking he was about to fight at Sun Xiang’s side. However, no one had expected him to dart away as Tang Rou went to deal with him.

He’s coming at me!

Du Ming’s true intentions were exposed and Su Mucheng immediately prepared herself. However, while Happy only just found out about Du Ming’s intentions, Samsara had already discussed it. Jiang Botao had already made preparations. The skills that Empty Waves was saving were suddenly unleashed in a torrent.

Why did Spellblades have a hard time chaining their attacks? On one hand, their skills weren’t as fast to activate as close-ranged classes’ skills were. Another point was that their skills had relatively longer cooldowns. It wasn’t impossible to unleash a rapid barrage of skills, but after you were done, all the skills would be on cooldown, and how would they defend against their enemy’s counterattack then?

However, Jiang Botao didn’t care about that at this moment. He used this wave of skills to try and lock down Dancing Rain’s movements, giving Moon-Luring Frost a chance to close in.

Under each team’s tactical efforts, the two sides finally launched into a much more tactically minded face off. Lord Grim and Cloud Piercer’s battle was also slowly inching closer to the center of the action, preparing to welcome even more complex variation into the battle.

However, in another area of the map, the ongoings seemed to have no relation to this area.

Wu Qi, Qiao Yifan.

These two were currently locked in a one on one fight, but it had been a long time since the broadcast had paid them any attention.

Chapter 1702 - Changing the Standard Method

"Jiang Botao's Empty Waves suddenly exploded, firing a series of attacks toward Dancing Rain! Du Ming seized this chance, Cruel Silence is currently flying toward Dancing Rain… Ah… Ye Xiu's Lord Grim is moving in this direction, but he probably can't block this. Steamed Bun Invasion ambushed… uh, it counts as an ambush, probably? But it was dodged!"

Charged with surging passion, commentator Pan Lin described these complex battles that were just about to intertwine together. As for the other area of this battlefield, it wasn't that the broadcasters didn't notice it, but compared to this area, the scene that those two players brought wasn't thrilling enough.

Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf turned to help Zhou Zekai, but before this, he had already cooperated with Wu Qi to establish the route over there. It was like how when the battle first began, the two of them had pincered Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain. This time, the two of them used basically the same method to deal with Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash.

But because Zhou Zekai's situation was more dire, this time, the two of them didn't manage to carry out their plan to the fullest. Sun Xiang had One Autumn Leaf turn away sooner, leaving Qiao Yifan to Wu Qi alone. At this time, Wu Qi's Cruel Silence still hadn't completely closed in on One Inch Ash, but he was at least sticking to him very tightly.

By now, One Inch Ash basically had no way to demonstrate his Phantom Ghostblade abilities. Cruel Silence was too close - One Inch Ash had no way of stopping to cast a ghost boundary. Qiao Yifan could only run away, run nonstop. He needed distance. Dark Boundary, Ice Boundary… these ghost boundaries were all already off cooldown, but he had no space to cast them.

But Qiao Yifan didn't panic. He carefully observed everything in front of him now. He knew that in a simple footrace, he definitely wouldn't be able to escape Cruel Silence. He had to use the map somehow.

Fortunately, Phantom Demons did have a few close-range tricks. Qiao Yifan controlled One Inch Ash to fight as he moved, and at the same time he studied his surroundings in all directions, carefully memorizing everything he saw. Gradually, a plan began to form in his mind.

This'll do!

Even though Qiao Yifan wasn't sure if his idea would work, he could only give it a try. Close-range fighting wasn't a Phantom Demon's strong suit. Walking and fighting like this, he had already lost quite some health to Wu Qi's Cruel Silence.

Moonlight Slash!

One Inch Ash suddenly attacked. It seemed sudden, but he was a Phantom Demon, which only had a few slashing skills. Thankfully, they were all low level and had short cooldowns, otherwise he'd have run out of moves long ago. Moonlight Slash, this was a skill that One Inch Ash had used who knew how many times already, so no matter how sudden it was, there wasn't any feeling of newness to Wu Qi. Without even thinking, he was already swiftly responding.

Turn, move!

Cruel Silence's steps were quite large, because Moonlight Slash would become Full Moonlight Slash. This was a fairly standard method. And Full Moonlight Slash would follow the user's controls, usually deflecting toward the direction in which the opponent dodge. So, when dodging Moonlight Slash, one also had to consider the forthcoming Full Moonlight Slash as well, and leave some extra space when dodging. If one tried to use something like Overlapping Sidesteps here, they would definitely be punished.

No, Wu Qi had seen through Qiao Yifan's method, but he didn't have any way to break it. This was the worth of the standard method. In order for it to be called standard, it had been refined hundreds and thousands of times, it was a highly-used technique. These sorts of techniques had gone through enough testing, such that no matter how good or bad their damage was, they at least put the user in a good position. When up against this kind of technique, no tricks could be pulled. Methods to counter it were simply those that had been determined to be the most effective after many tests. For Assassins, this was the large step that Cruel Silence had taken.

But this time, after the sword carved out this Moonlight Slash, the light immediately faded.

No Full Moonlight Slash!

But this couldn't be considered surprising.

This was a standard method, so of course, all of its variations had been studied as well. Moonlight Slash and Full Moonlight Slash were often used consecutively, but that didn't mean that they had to be. However, because of this "often," Moonlight Slash always had to be dodged as though it were two attacks. There was nothing to discuss about that. Even if the opponent didn't plan to chain the attacks, if you really treated the Moonlight Slash as just one attack, then it would be very easy for the opponent to make a last-second adjustment and add on a Full Moonlight Slash.

So, there was no way around it.

Even if you knew that this method could be changed in this way, you could only act after the change appeared.

Earlier, Qiao Yifan had controlled One Inch Ash to use Moonlight Slash three times, all of which had been followed by a Full Moonlight Slash. Very fast, very steady. The solid foundational strikes meant that Wu Qi didn't dare get overconfident, so his performance was also very steady. So this time, the fourth time, Cruel Silence took a large step again, still dodging the Moonlight Slash as though it were two attacks. But this time, there was only Moonlight, no Full.

What kind of change would this cause?

This was hard to say. After this, there were many options that could be taken. But one point was worth noting. Why was it so common to go from Moonlight Slash to Full Moonlight Slash in the first place? It was because connecting these two skills revealed no openings. It was the best guarantee of safety. But when Moonlight Slash was used on its own, this skill seemed a bit frail. Without a Full Moonlight Slash, if the opponent reacted quickly enough, if he seized the opening to attack, then the Phantom Demon would be in a bad spot.

Wu Qi's reaction was very fast. As soon as he saw the blade stop, he knew that Qiao Yifan was changing things this time. Even though he had experienced the standard method three times just earlier, Wu Qi was not stuck in his ways of thinking.

Shining Cut!

As though he had been prepared for this long before, Cruel Silence rushed forward.

With such an instantaneous reaction, there was no need to worry about whether Qiao Yifan had purposely controlled One Inch Ash to delay his attack. With such a fast reaction, even if Qiao Yifan had added this delay in his chained slashes on purpose, this delay had already become an opening.

Ding!

The sound of the collision rang out.

One Inch Ash's tachi Snow Stripe successfully blocked Cruel Silence's Shining Cut that had carried both man and dagger.

Guard!

Qiao Yifan controlled One Inch Ash to use a sudden Guard, blocking the Shining Cut that swiftly came at him. Clearly, he had been prepared for this.

Not good!

This feeling suddenly floated up in Wu Qi's mind. The standard method of Moonlight Slash to Full Moonlight Slash, he had been prepared for; changing it so that Moonlight Slash was no longer followed by Full, he instantly changed as well, as fast as he could. But the opponent had been prepared for his immediate offensive. Clearly, Qiao Yifan had predicted this, he knew that Wu Qi would launch a fast attack in response to his change.

Guard.

Their weapons clashed, but the sound rang for only a moment. In this moment, the two characters had gotten extremely close. On the screen, Wu Qi could see their crossed weapons, and the somewhat gloomy face of his opponent One Inch Ash.

But very soon, that face pulled away from him. The Guard blocked his attack, so Cruel Silence came to a stop, but his One Inch Ash used the Guard to slide backward.

This was the priority that the system dealt, Wu Qi had no way to interfere with that. But this moment was very short. In the next moment, he was already moving to his next attack.

As the Shadow Follows!

Raise speed, forcibly follow the target.

After recovering, Cruel Silence immediately activated this skill. Behind him stretched a chain of shadows, but in front of him, two lines of crossed swordlight flashed out, as though solidified, waiting for Cruel Silence to crash into them.

Gore Cross!

As the Shadow Follows could not go through an attack. Changing direction and circling around was possible, but this Gore Cross was too close, it had come too quickly, it was too late for him to change direction.

He could only cancel the skill!

In the end, Cruel Silence forcibly came to a halt, stopping himself in front of the Gore Cross. Having to change direction again, start up again, give chase again, who knew how much this had slowed him down. But Qiao Yifan evidently wasn't done. As One Inch Ash seized the chance to slip away, he also sent an Earthquake Sword toward him.

All of this, the televised broadcast hadn't shown. But the live audience had the projection, and countless screens above were showing all part of the battle. If the audience wanted to see something, there was no delay at all. Among Samsara's audience, there would of course be Wu Qi fans, and right now, they watched as Qiao Yifan used all of these techniques to trap Cruel Silence in place. Even they felt aggrieved.

In just these few moments of effort, One Inch Ash had slipped away behind an unidentifiable structure that was half-sunk into the ground.

Now, Wu Qi didn't dare let Cruel Silence chase right after him. One Inch Ash had left his line of sight. The next moves would depend entirely on position. Distance was no longer the one indicator of advantage in this situation.

Jump up?

Circle to the front?

Two choices dangled in front of Wu Qi.

Chapter 1703 - Return of the Phantom Demon

When he had other options available, he would always choose one of the other options, instead of directly chasing after an easier ambush.

Jump!

Time didn’t permit Wu Qi to think too much. He quickly made his decision. Even though circling around to the front was the most dependable way to ambush the enemy side, if the enemies left his sights for too long, he would have to guess when to attack. While he circled around to the front, it wasn’t like the enemies couldn’t change their minds and retreat.

Air Jump!

Air Jump was an Assassin-only skill, allowing the character to make a second jump in the air. Jumping over the wall and onto the roof wasn’t a problem, but when Cruel Silence leapt into the air and looked down from above, Wu Qi was stunned.

This building didn’t have a roof.

Wu Qi hastily swung Cruel Silence’s dagger. This sort of movement would affect his character’s trajectory in the air, but it wouldn’t have as large of an effect compared to say, the recoil from a gunshot. Cruel Silence struggled in the air, but in the end, he wasn’t able to land onto that tiny foothold at the top of the wall, and instead jumped right over it.

Of course, he wouldn’t take any fall damage. However, since he had gone up, he had to come down, which meant a bit of extra time.

With this bit of delay, perhaps the other side would now have a ghost boundary waiting for him.

Wu Qi sighed. He didn’t stop moving though. As soon as Cruel Silence landed, he jumped up again.

Cruel Silence was now inside the building. He could see where all the footholds were located now. Air Jump was a passive skill. It didn’t have a cooldown, so Cruel Silence jumped again onto a foothold above.

Again!

He didn’t rush out or continue forward. He simply jumped in place.

His previous mistake had been because of his lack of understanding with this random map, but it could also be said that Wu Qi hadn’t thought his actions through. After Wu Qi made the mistake, he immediately became more cautious. He didn’t have Cruel Silence directly jump down. He didn’t have Cruel Silence approach the edge either. He was afraid that if took one too many steps, he would step right into One Inch Ash’s ghost boundary.

Now that he was up above, Wu Qi could see One Inch Ash below him.

Sure enough, One Inch Ash was casting a spell. Right when he jumped and looked down, One Inch Ash finished his cast. The ghost god’s power emanated from One Inch Ash’s Snow Stripe and flowed down…

Wu Qi was glad that he hadn’t taken that step. However, when he saw the ghost boundary forming, Wu Qi felt that it was a bit strange.

If the ghost boundary had been set up to ambush him, wasn’t the placement of the ghost boundary a bit too off?

Yes, too off.

The spectating pro players had noticed it as well.

“Because his goal isn’t to attack,” Li Xuan said.

With this in mind, the players who thought that it was “off” immediately understood.

Yes, the goal wasn’t to attack.

This ghost boundary wasn’t to ambush Cruel Silence. This ghost boundary was defensive.

Qiao Yifan also noticed Cruel Silence, looking down from above. But he had finished casting his ghost boundary. It couldn’t be interrupted anymore. He let out a sigh of relief. After setting down this ghost boundary, he ignored Cruel Silence, and had One Inch Ash leave.

Wu Qi obviously wanted to give chase, but just when he was about to go do so, he suddenly realized how disgusting One Inch Ash’s placement of the ghost boundary was.

One Inch Ash wasn’t far from Cruel Silence, but with this ghost boundary, it suddenly felt like he was looking at him from far away. If he wanted to chase after him, he would need to circle around the ghost boundary. Compared to this, the crumbling rooftop was cute.

Even so, Wu Qi didn’t hesitate. Cruel Silence continued to chase after One Inch Ash. He circled around the ghost boundary, and could only watch as One Inch Ash widened the distance between them. However, he didn’t stop.

Then, One Inch Ash began casting another ghost boundary.

The spectating pro players realized what Qiao Yifan was planning.

He was very calm. He didn’t forget himself because his previous play had given him a bit of an advantage. Even though he had a good opportunity to counterattack Wu Qi, he had chosen not to because his goal was clear.

He wanted to get back to the rest of his team.

Phantom Demons were most effective in group fights. Control the opponents, buff allies. Team battles were where Phantom Demons best put their abilities to use. His value to the team was worth much more than his individual battle strength.

That was why even though he had the opportunity, he had no intentions of fighting with Wu Qi. He was using this opportunity to hurry and reconvene with his team.

That was why the ghost boundary that he placed down wasn’t to attack, but to defend, to protect.

Of course, if Wu Qi had ignored the ghost boundary and had Cruel Silence step right into it, Qiao Yifan would obviously give him a quick beating before leaving. Evidently, Wu Qi wasn’t that stupid.

Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence circled around the ghost boundary. Samsara’s fans were hoping for him to perform some sort of miracle act and break apart the ghost boundary set down by Qiao Yifan. But he didn’t. Wu Qi seemed to be cooperating with Qiao Yifan’s goals. From start to finish, he wasn’t able to close the distance.

Utilizing the terrain and his ghost boundaries, Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was able to smoothly reconvene with his team.

The pro players applauded.

Qiao Yifan’s utilization of the terrain and his class abilities were certainly worthy of praise, but the pro players were more appreciative of his clear-headed recognition of his role in the team. He was able to keep his calm, and remember what value he brought to the team as a whole. He had done everything in order to return and play his role as a support to the entire team.

For a young player like him, this was truly a rare trait.

As the pro players clapped, they couldn’t help but turn their heads to look at the expressions of Tiny Herb’s players.

Everyone on Tiny Herb looked a bit uncomfortable. Qiao Yifan’s eye-catching performance made them feel as if they were pandas trapped in a zoo. Right now, they could only look towards their captain because their captain was always calm and composed.

But this time, they discovered that Wang Jiexi’s expression wasn’t very calm and composed. In fact, he looked rather serious.

Even their captain was beginning to regret letting Qiao Yifan go? The Tiny Herb members looked at one another, especially at Zhou Yebai, their team’s Ghostblade player. He had originally been the person who cared most about this issue, but Wang Jiexi had dispelled those doubts earlier. But when he saw Wang Jiexi’s expression now, his heart sank.

“Captain,” Xu Bin whispered to Wang Jiexi. He had joined Tiny Herb after Qiao Yifan left, so he didn’t have the same thoughts as the others on Tiny Herb. However, he could tell that Qiao Yifan’s outstanding performance was making the team uncomfortable. Before, Wang Jiexi was unaffected, so these negative emotions didn’t have as much of an impact on the team. But now, even Wang Jiexi looked to be disturbed. Who knew how much of an impact this would have on the team, especially on Zhou Yebai. The pressure on him must be enormous.

“Pay attention to the match,” Wang Jiexi said.

The match?

Everyone on Tiny Herb was stunned.

It turned out that their captain hadn’t been concerned with Qiao Yifan, but rather something in the match?

The situation had become somewhat chaotic.

Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves had sent out wave slash after wave slash earlier, intending to create an opportunity for Du Ming to close in on Dancing Rain.

Samsara was providing cover for their ally, but it wasn’t like Happy didn’t have anyone helping Su Mucheng.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim turned fire in an attempt to intercept Du Ming. Even though Du Ming was able to avoid Lord Grim’s attacks, Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly threw a Brick at him for some inexplicable reason.

Yes, for some inexplicable reason!

Anyone could see that Steamed Bun Invasion had been completely focused on attacking One Autumn Leaf. If he had planned on turning away and providing help to that side, why would he do it from so far away? If he had done so earlier, he could have coordinated with Ye Xiu, and the two of them would have likely been able to stop Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost.

But he hadn’t.

Just when everyone thought that nothing was going to happen, a Brick suddenly flew his way.

Du Ming really hadn’t been paying attention.

Fortunately, he wasn’t alone. Someone else on Samsara noticed the Brick and warned him.

Warning, react, move.

In the end, Du Ming was able to avoid the Brick. Seeing how much time Du Ming had to react to Steamed Bun’s attack, it could be seen just how little of a threat that Brick had been.

But the entirety of Samsara had been given a fright.

Pretend you were taking a higher-level math exam. All of the problems you encountered so far had been extremely difficult. Suddenly, an addition and subtraction problem was thrown at you to solve.

According to common sense, this sort of problem shouldn’t be appearing in the exam, and no one would have prepared for this sort of problem either.

No one was going to be stumped by such a simple problem, but it was enough to make everyone jump in surprise.

After the initial surprise, all you had to do was answer the question. But this was a competitive match. If you didn’t deal with the suprise properly, a Brick might just hit you in the head.

Du Ming hadn’t thought that Steamed Bun would suddenly throw this sort of problem at him because there had been no need! An attack from Steamed Bun Invasion’s position was no threat to him. For you to throw a Brick from there, was it you being a noob? Or did you think I was a noob?

Who knew what Steamed Bun was thinking. In any case, the Brick had been thrown. If it weren’t for Zhou Zekai’s timely warning, who knew what would have happened. The battlefield was quite chaotic at the moment. All sorts of attacks and sounds could be heard. Du Ming may have likely missed the sound of the wind behind him.

This brief fluster was enough to delay him. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim hadn’t been able to catch up at first, but with this delay, he had suddenly closed the distance.

Du Ming had no time to close in on Dancing Rain, or take revenge on Steamed Bun. He had to fight off Lord Grim.

Du Ming was now entangled with Ye Xiu, and it suddenly put Jiang Botao in a bad position. He was throwing out wave slash after wave slash, but then it turned out that Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost wasn’t able to do anything with it. Didn’t that mean he was open right now? Dancing Rain aimed her cannon at him. Luckily, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer helped out just in time to protect Empty Waves.

At this moment, Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash finally returned. A new variable had come into play.

Qiao Yifan’s Phantom Demon, with his powerful crowd control and AoE buffs, was definitely good news for Happy!

Happy’s supporters immediately brightened at this sight.

The spectating pro players thought the same. They knew from experience how valuable a Phantom Demon was in a group battle. Moreover, Qiao Yifan had outstanding map and team awareness. With his addition, Happy was like a tiger with wings.

“Whether Samsara will be able to keep Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash in check will be the deciding factor of this match,” Li Xuan concluded. Of course, this might his bias towards Phantom Demons. At the very least, when he made this remark, quite a few people took exception to it.

“Whether Happy is able to protect One Inch Ash is also crucial,” someone said.

“Isn’t that the same as what I just said!” Li Xuan pointed out. If Samsara needed to keep Qiao Yifan in check, then Happy would want to stop them from achieving that. Wasn’t that obvious?

The two sides reacted extremely quickly. This time, Steamed Bun Invasion did something logical. He suddenly rushed towards Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim seemed to have taken the baton, and retreated towards One Inch Ash.

Cloud Piercer fired his dual guns, one gun to protect Empty Waves, the other to attack One Inch Ash.

Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened. Qiao Yifan had acted as if he knew that someone would protect him. By the time the bullet was fired, he had already been casting a spell.

Not waiting for Samsara to find a new angle of attack to interrupt him, he placed down the ghost boundary.

Sword Boundary! Buff the team’s Strength and Intelligence.

Happy’s combat power immediately soared to new heights, and this was just the beginning. Because of Qiao Yifan’s return, Samsara was already beginning to lose their footing. They needed to keep One Inch Ash in check no matter what.

Chapter 1704 - Assassin

If one side was attacking, then the other side would naturally be defending. At the moment, it was too early to say who held the initiative. However, if Samsara adopted the mindset of “if it’s too hard to deal with, then just avoid it,” they would definitely be the ones on the backfoot. The competitive stage was ruthless. If you gave an inch, the enemies would take a mile. A chain of ghost boundaries coordinated with other attacks might just be enough for Happy to win with a single play.

Team Samsara didn’t plan on running away.

With Sword Boundary in effect, Happy’s overall combat strength soared, but no matter how powerful the buff was, it wouldn’t be enough to overwhelm Samsara. Strength and Intelligence mainly affected their DPS. It had no effect on the tempo. In fact, Samsara had no need to make any adjustments to their original plans.

Continue!

Samsara didn’t cower. The team stepped into the Sword Boundary to battle against Happy.

This decision was quite wise. In the end, the Sword Boundary wasn’t able to win Happy an opening. Samsara had started actively pursuing One Inch Ash. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves suddenly threw aside Dancing Rain, cutting straight towards One Inch Ash.

Waltzing Wave Slash!

A wave slash flew towards One Inch Ash. After Qiao Yifan placed down the Sword Boundary, he didn’t immediately start casting the next. He reckoned that Samsara wouldn’t give him an opportunity to. Sure enough, a Waltzing Wave Slash came flying at him. He couldn’t completely depend on Lord Grim to protect him. Although the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella covered a wide area, it didn’t cover every part of him. Jiang Botao had specifically chosen Waltzing Wave Slash so that his attack could curve around the umbrella shield. If Lord Grim went to block it, an opening would appear for Cloud Piercer.

He couldn’t always rely on his teammates. Oftentimes, he needed to find opportunities to place down ghost boundaries on his own. If he could just stand still, setting up ghost boundary after ghost boundaries, the battle would be too easy.

Roll!

One Inch Ash dodged the Waltzing Wave Slash, while taking a look at his surroundings. Qiao Yifan was observing his opponents, his teammates, and the terrain. Where could he find an opening?

One Inch Ash rushed out.

Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer was the most troublesome opponent for him. Finding cover wouldn’t be a bad idea.

Zhou Zekai immediately saw through Qiao Yifan’s intentions. He fired both his guns at One Inch Ash to stop him.

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain immediately turned on Cloud Piercer. This time, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim didn’t chase after One Inch Ash to provide cover for him. He used a Charge, straight towards Cloud Piercer.

If Happy focused solely on defense, then Happy would be the ones on the backfoot, not Samsara. Ye Xiu understood what he needed to do. He had protected One Inch Ash when he was placing down a Sword Boundary. Now, he had to attack Cloud Piercer, and rid Qiao Yifan of his biggest obstacle.

Zhou Zekai couldn’t let Lord Grim get close to Cloud Piercer. Perhaps his only choice was to back away. Seizing this opportunity to get close to One Inch Ash would undoubtedly be the best case scenario. Unfortunately, Ye Xiu had guessed his thoughts. When Lord Grim rushed over, Zhou Zekai had no choice but to give up on the idea.

He moved laterally with Aerial Gun. Zhou Zekai was trying to get to a different angle so that he could get past Lord Grim. But Ye Xiu was cunning and experienced. He immediately saw through his intentions. Lord Grim stopped and changed directions.

Attack while defending. Defend while attacking.

Ye Xiu had mastered this intricate art. He had once again become teaching material for the seniors of the various teams. Zhou Zekai had to face against this both offensive and defensive rush. For a moment, he had no way to break past him. He couldn’t focus his attention on One Inch Ash either. Qiao Yifan was able to immediately find an opening.

One Inch Ash had found cover. Cloud Piercer’s long range couldn’t be counted on anymore. Jiang Botao reacted quickly. Empty Waves suddenly sent an Earth Wave Slash towards Steamed Bun Invasion.

The distance was a bit far, so the chances that it would hit were rather low. But even so, Steamed Bun had to go out of the way to dodge it.

With this, an opening appeared for Du Ming. He quickly acted. Moon Luring Frost activated Shadow Steps and used Triple Slash to instantly close the distance on Tang Rou’s Soft Mist.

A team battle turning into a bunch of 1v1s? Unless it was intentional such as what Team Wind Howl often did, it would never happen. A sudden switch between players due to a change in circumstances was what should happen.

Samsara had made numerous switches in this short period of time. Du Ming finally had his 1v1 against Tang Rou. Du Ming was excited to face his crush, but he wasn’t going to show any mercy. Which of the five shadows from Shadow Steps was the real one? This sudden switch in opponents caught Tang Rou off guard. She indeed couldn’t figure out which one was real.

If she couldn’t find the real one, then she could only face them all. Running away was the easiest way to handle this situation, but Tang Rou had to be mindful of the overall situation. She understood that Samsara had switched targets continuously all in order to get to Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash. If she chose to run away, she would leave an opening for Samsara to take advantage of. Whether it was Sun Xiang or Du Ming, one of them would break past and reach One Inch Ash.

I can’t back down!

Tang Rou had always been unyielding, and now, she even had a perfectly good reason to be that way.

Cloud Whirling Windstorm!

Soft Mist took a step back as if she were planning on running. But then, with a twist of her wrist, she flicked out a high-level skill. The wind produced from the spinning Dancing Fire Flowing Flames let out a faint red glow. Dancing Fire Flowing Flames was a Fire element spear. If an elemental skill wasn’t used, the attack would automatically be a Fire attack. An enormous cloud of fire suddenly formed and extended outwards.

One Autumn Leaf? The five Moon Luring Frosts? Don’t even think about charging through.

It didn’t matter if Sun Xiang and Du Ming was able to create an opening to break through. With this delay, Samsara’s offense had been severed. This delay gave Qiao Yifan enough time to complete another ghost boundary.

Snow Stripe rose into the air, the ghost god’s power condensing around it. Sure enough, Qiao Yifan seized this opportunity to have One Inch Ash start casting another ghost boundary. He didn’t think it was possible to actually find a completely safe area. Everyone was fighting for an opportunity, and an opportunity had come!

Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer was busy fighting against Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim.

Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves was rather far away. To interrupt him, he would need to get past multiple layers of defense. Being able to guide this relay between targets for Samsara was already impressive.

But in the end, Du Ming and Sun Xiang had been delayed by Tang Rou. Was Samsara really unable to stop another ghost boundary from forming?

No…

While gazing towards the ghost god’s power being summoned, Qiao Yifan suddenly realized that there was still one other player on Samsara.

Where was he?

“Behind!”

Warnings popped up from Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng simultaneously. One Inch Ash was enveloped by a shadow. Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence had jumped right over the barrier protecting One Inch Ash. In the next moment, blood poured out from One Inch Ash’s slit throat.

Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence had been chasing after him the entire time, but in the end, he had been forced to back off. He could only take the long way and circle around the ghost boundaries.

His pursuit wasn’t able to form any sort of threat. Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was able to smoothly reconvene with his team and place down a Sword Boundary. Then, Samsara rushed at him, but under the protection from his teammates, he was able to find another opening.

During this time, what had Wu Qi been doing? What had Cruel Silence been doing?

Qiao Yifan had been paying attention to the overall situation, and he had an impression of Cruel Silence. However, his impression of him was very faint. At that time, Cruel Silence just seemed to be moving, searching for an opportunity to attack, but without any clear plans in mind. Qiao Yifan didn’t see him as a threat, and dismissed him.

But in the blink of an eye.

While everyone else on Samsara was unable to act, Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence suddenly appeared beside One Inch Ash.

What was this feeling?

Qiao Yifan couldn’t describe it. Suddenly, he thought of something. It was when he had been promoted from Tiny Herb’s training camp to the main team, the words that Wang Jiexi had spoken to him when he was handed the Assassin account card.

“Assassins hide in the shadows. The most terrifying Assassins are the ones that look ordinary because of how easy it is to drop your guard against them. Appearing ordinary to the point of being invisible is a truly rare talent.”

Chapter 1705 - Pull One Hair and the Whole Body Moves

The crowd erupted into fervent applause. How could the Samsara fans not be excited seeing Wu Qi suddenly find a killing opportunity? They didn’t look into the details too clearly. Just the outcome alone made them extremely pleased.

The pro players let out expressions of astonishment.

They had spectator views, allowing them to see everything that was happening in the match. Had Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence done anything exceptional?

No.

No one thought so.

They knew that he had been moving around on the battlefield, but their attention had been on Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer, then Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves, then Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost.

Similar to how Qiao Yifan had dismissed him, the spectating pro players had as well.

Wu Qi wasn’t a threat?

The answer to that question was no. The present situation was the best proof. Cruel Silence had gotten behind One Inch Ash, delivering back attack after back attack. He was in the perfect position to deal damage. If he wasn’t a threat, then what was a threat?

Yet no one had noticed the threat.

An unremarkable Assassin was the perfect Assassin.

Was Wu Qi an unremarkable player? No one really thought so. A main roster player in a two-time championship team could never be disregarded. However, compared to the other stars in the roster, Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, Sun Xiang, Lu Boyuan, four All-Stars, Wu Qi paled in comparison even if his popularity wasn’t bad.

He wasn’t an unremarkable player, but when he was put into Samsara’s roster, he became unremarkable.

It wasn’t that he hadn’t been a threat before, but rather that the pressure put on by the others on Samsara covered his threat.

He wasn’t as proactive as the others, but he never went out of his way to hide his tracks. He found the perfect balance, making his Cruel Silence appear invisible in this intense battle.

Then, he made his move!

From the start, Happy’s healer hadn’t really undertaken any actual healer work. Whatever health was lost on Happy’s side was lost forever. Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash had been focused by Zhou Zekai for a lengthy period of time. As a result, he had lost quite a bit of health. Now that Wu Qi had successfully closed in, mercilessly stabbing him in the back, his health instantly dropped below 50%.

Qiao Yifan recalled Wang Jiexi’s words. Wu Qi seemed to possess the rare talent his former senior had sought. He was certain that he hadn’t ignored Wu Qi. He really had taken note of his Cruel Silence, but… he hadn’t noticed Cruel Silence’s threat. Or perhaps the threat hadn’t caught his attention. He had felt like the others on Samsara had been a higher priority.

Was this the sort of Assassin player that Tiny Herb had hoped he would become?

Qiao Yifan didn’t know the answer, but he didn’t feel too regretful over it. He had fully transitioned into a Phantom Demon, and the class suited him perfectly. For him, Assassins were of the past. He hadn’t given up on the things that he had learned as an Assassin, but that didn’t mean he had any intentions of going back.

Perhaps he really had missed an opportunity at Tiny Herb, but he didn’t feel upset over the past. It only made him treasure the present even more.

It hadn’t been easy getting to where he was now, and he was very happy with what he had. He needed to do everything he could to protect all of this.

One Inch Ash rolled and jumped.

Turn, stop, sprint…

Qiao Yifan did everything he could to escape, but Wu Qi was like a maggot feeding on a corpse, refusing to let him go.

Tang Rou was closest to Qiao Yifan.

She had just forced away Sun Xiang and Du Ming to create an opening for Qiao Yifan, but in the blink of an eye, the situation flipped. She was now being suppressed by the two on Samsara. She wanted to help One Inch Ash, but for now, she wouldn’t be able to.

Switch!

Du Ming and Sun Xiang switched positions. Sun Xiang wanted Du Ming to deal with Tang Rou, while his One Autumn Leaf turned to pincer One Inch Ash so that they could kill him sooner.

Tang Rou was already gloomy being suppressed by the two on Samsara, how could she let them do as they pleased so easily?

Downwind Sword Slash, ignore!

Her Dancing Fire Flowing Flame swung towards One Autumn Leaf. Soft Mist took Moon Luring Frost’s blow, but she wasn’t going to let One Autumn Leaf get past her.

One Autumn Leaf was forced back. However, Soft Mist stumbled and fell from the Downwind Sword Slash. Du Ming clearly hadn’t expected Tang Rou to ignore his attack, so his follow-up came a bit slow.

Tang Rou let the follow-up hit her, allowing the attack to push her towards One Inch Ash.

I don’t think so!

For Samsara, letting Wu Qi fight against Qiao Yifan 1v1 was fine. Wu Qi had the upper hand. Going over to help him wasn’t necessary. Stopping Happy from rescuing Qiao Yifan was a much higher priority.

Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike!

One Autumn Leaf dashed forward. His Evil Annihilation moved like a blur, the angle of attack cutting off Soft Mist’s path.

Boom boom boom!

Cannonfire sounded. The long-ranged support from Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain had arrived. However, there were simply too many places that needed her help. Qiao Yifan was in a dire situation, and because Tang Rou was in a hurry to rescue Qiao Yifan, their formation was thrown into disarray.

This was what the phrase “pull one hair and the whole body moves” meant. In the team competition, a single player falling into a passive position could cause the whole team to fall into a passive position. Keeping the balance steady during these situations required experience. Tang Rou was clearly lacking in this area. Her reaction to the change in situation had been poor. She panicked and tried to force her way through, immediately putting herself into a bad position.

Su Mucheng’s support clearly showed her richer experience.

She didn’t focus on the center of the issue, on One Inch Ash’s side. Instead, she focused on helping Tang Rou.

If she could help Tang Rou find an opening, Tang Rou would naturally be able to rescue Qiao Yifan. Moreover, while Sun Xiang and Du Ming blocked Tang Rou, they formed a clear defensive line. Not just Tang Rou, but if Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun wanted to rescue Qiao Yifan, they would need to break past this defensive line. Su Mucheng had chosen to focus this area because it would be valuable to everyone on the team.

She hadn’t completely ignored Qiao Yifan’s predicament either. While she focused supporting Soft Mist, she snuck in attacks at Cruel Silence to try disrupt Wu Qi’s rhythm and create an opening for Qiao Yifan.

Explosions erupted continuously, but even though Launcher attacks were fierce, their crowd control was lacking. Tough and unyielding weren’t traits unique to Tang Rou. Samsara’s Du Ming showed that he could be unyielding as well.

Formless Phantom Blade!

Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost released the Level 70 Blade Master skill. Intersecting sword light intercepted the roaring artillery fire.

Chapter 1706 - Matter of Life and Death

Parrying against a long-ranged Gunner class character?

For normal players, this was unimaginable. Even if it happened, it was mostly due to luck rather than skill. But at the pro level, there were a decent number of players who could achieve it. Still, this happened only on occasion, and it was usually just parrying one or two shots.

Du Ming wanted to use a high-level skill to directly face the heavy artillery fire of a Launcher?

Astounded. Everyone was astounded. Today’s match was a rollercoaster everywhere you looked. And now, it was finally Du Ming’s turn to show his magic…

It was impossible to parry a Sharpshooter’s hurricane-like flurry of shots regardless of skill. You were limited by your attack speed.

However, a Launcher’s attacks wouldn’t be as dense as a Sharpshooter’s, thus making it possible for Du Ming to try this. However, even though Launchers were slower, every one of their attacks carried more power and AoE.

The explosions instantly enveloped Moon Luring Frost. But the explosions stopped there.

These explosions were meant to be centered around Soft Mist. But now, Moon Luring Frost became the center.

Moon Luring Frost’s health was dropping, but the explosions weren’t able to get past him.

The attacks were intercepted!

No matter how surprising this was, it was reality. In exchange for his health, Moon Luring Frost did not fall, or get sent flying. Du Ming was extremely precise at judging the trajectory of the incoming attacks.

Du Ming was sacrificing his health, but by doing so, he maintained the advantage that Samsara currently held. He was trading his health for One Inch Ash’s health. Compared to One Inch Ash, the health loss from parrying Dancing Rain’s attacks was far lower than the health loss from repeatedly getting stabbed in the back by Cruel Silence.

Readjust. Change the approach, or change the attacks?

Everyone who put themselves in Su Mucheng’s shoes asked themselves this question. Pan Lin and Li Yibo of the broadcast team were currently rambling away at a list of Launcher attacks that couldn’t be parried.

Like Laser Rifle, or Satellite Beam…

These two commentators were incomparably confident when talking hypotheticals. They spouted these skills like they had them written on the back of their hands.

But Su Mucheng did not make any adjustments. Dancing Rain continued to push forward, increasing her offense and keeping up the pressure on Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost.

Du Ming can be unyielding, but she could also be unyielding!

Many people were speechless. Today, both teams seemed extremely stubborn. They were like a bickering couple!

It could be called stubbornness, but to say they were bickering was a bit shallow.

The pace of this match had already been set. It didn’t matter if it was Samsara, the team fighting for their third championship win, or Happy, the astonishing new team, both teams refused to give in. They even traded off their healers first, the roles typically viewed as the core of a team.

Both teams were fighting tooth and nail, fighting for the initiative. At times like these, success depended on the side that was more adamant in carrying out their plans.

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain forcefully attacked, while Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost forcefully defended. Su Mucheng had the initiative while Du Ming had to be reactive.

But if she changed her tactics due to Du Ming’s defense, she would be the reactive one.

Being flexible isn’t a bad thing. Oftentimes, it’s necessary to adapt in a match. But this depended on the situation. Su Mucheng had no choice but to stick to her original plan, because Samsara was applying too much pressure. With the tempo that Samsara had established with their fierce counterattack, Su Mucheng had no space to be flexible; no time to be indecisive and try a new approach.

She must remain firm. She would remain firm.

Du Ming, you dare to get in my way? Then I’ll send you on your way to death!

How long could he keep up parrying? There was a reason people usually didn’t parry against Gunners. It was too risky and too difficult. Du Ming attempted it only because the situation called for it; if he was in a 1v1 against a Launcher, he definitely wouldn’t charge in headfirst, and try to slice apart the missiles coming his way.

Seeing that Su Mucheng wasn’t letting up, those who were pondering Su Mucheng’s situation had now turned their heads to scrutinize Du Ming’s situation.

Du Ming was also in a difficult position.

He was being stubborn to try and scare Su Mucheng off by creating a troublesome situation for her. He wanted her to reassess and change her approach. However, Su Mucheng stood her ground and welcomed the troublesome situation. This put Du Ming on the spot: should he retreat or not?

Everyone was closely linked to each other. If he retreated, the cannonfire would reach Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf, which would then allow Tang Rou’s Soft Mist an opportunity to break free. In turn, she would be able to attack Cruel Silence, allowing Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash an opportunity to escape.

The final ring of the chain was as such: a matter of life and death for One Inch Ash. And this chain currently involved every character on the battlefield. Thus, a question was posed to Du Ming, and his answer would cause a whole chain of events to unfold.

Retreat?

Du Ming eliminated this answer.

No one had chosen to retreat in this match. Even An Wenyi, that mediocre healer, dared to harass Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer. Du Ming needed to let Happy know that Samsara also had this kind of determination and courage.

Stand strong!

Flames and smoke from the explosions continued to unfurl. Du Ming had cancelled the Formless Phantom Blade early because he didn’t want the long ending lag from the last strike. Even without the high-level skill, his sword still shone brightly. Every missile fired by Dancing Rain was sliced apart by Moon Luring Frost’s blade.

“Keep it up!!!”

Right now, shouts came from the Samsara fans. Right now, many had already forgotten why Du Ming needed to parry Dancing Rain’s attacks head-on; forgotten what the consequences of his actions were. They were only moved by his actions. Happy had shown this resolution, this stubborn persistence. Now, so would their Samsara!

Keep it up! Just keep it up.

In this moment, even Du Ming had forgotten why he had to do this. He had no time to think about anything else, as he felt the pressure increase under the continuous attacks and growing list of exhausted skills.

Boom!

This sound was heard countless times, and everyone was becoming desensitized to it. But this time, everyone’s hearts jumped. Because this time, Moon Luring Frost was sent flying.

Sure enough, he wasn’t able to keep it up?

Even though they know Du Ming had already performed sufficiently, that he did all he could, that what he had achieved was nothing short of incredible. But this result would inevitably still sadden some.

Couldn’t keep it up?

No!

Not yet.

Moon Luring Frost was blasted away, but sword light flashed out once again.

Sword Draw!

Sword light slashed out and two more explosions were heard. Even though his character was flying away, he still managed to block the following attacks. When he landed, he quickly rolled and used Triple Slash.

Moon Luring Frost’s body was still bent when he shot out.

Boom boom boom, another three explosions. Moon Luring Frost once again dove headfirst into the artillery fire. Once again, he parried Dancing Rain’s attacks.

Applause. Unending applause. Samsara’s fans wanted another way to express their emotions right now, but they could think of any. They could only yell themselves hoarse, clap their hands raw.

No one paid attention to how much health Du Ming sacrificed to keep up this defense. All they knew was that Du Ming had given a very satisfying answer to the conundrum that he had been faced with. He was doing the impossible, and his teammates had to live up to their own expectations too. Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf had a vice grip on Tang Rou’s Soft Mist; Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves also held Steam Bun Invasion back. Ye Xiu was aware of what was happening, but any character being pursued by Cloud Piercer would have a very hard time attempting to do anything else at all.

At the core of the problem, Qiao Yifan had already used everything at his disposal, including the tactics that he learned when he trained as an Assassin player. Everything he tried was of no use. He was facing a real Assassin, one who was more proficient than him. With the rest of Samsara creating the necessary space for him, and with how close he was to his target, he would lose his job if he let One Inch Ash get away.

And Wu Qi did not let him get away. Cruel Silence’s attacks chained together seamlessly, cutting away One Inch Ash’s life.

Chapter 1707 - The Ultimate Support

30%, 22%, 17%, 11%...

One Inch Ash's health continued to drop, falling until near death.

Even though he looked helpless, even though Samsara was blocking the others on Happy perfectly, even though according to common sense, it was over for One Inch Ash, Qiao Yifan didn't give up. Pan Lin and Li Yibo didn't dare declare him dead.

Because Team Happy couldn't be judged according to common sense. They had pulled off too too many surprising feats.

And this time?

One Inch Ash was at red health.

Qiao Yifan wasn't ready to give up, but there was only so much he could do. On the competitive stage, going from heaven to hell only took the blink of an eye. Less than a minute ago, he had beautifully escaped from Wu Qi's Cruel Silence and returned to the team, becoming the key factor in forcing Samsara into a passive position. But now, One Inch Ash was on the verge of death.

Without a healer, there was no room for error. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim could heal, but Qiao Yifan knew that Lord Grim's healing could only be used to let a character survive for one more breath. During a crucial moment of life and death, his healing could potentially be a deciding factor. However, his current situation was different. The enemy side was chasing closely after him. He was losing health but he couldn't retaliate. Surviving for one more breath was pointless. The enemies were right beside him. One more breath was just one more stab. How could that be difficult for Wu Qi to do?

Unless he was able to break free from Cruel Silence, there was no chance. Even if he could, with how little health One Inch Ash had left, he wouldn't live for much longer. Without a healer, Samsara could easily find a way to eliminate a nearly dead character, and Happy wouldn't be able to stop them.

But if he really could break free, it would be an opening for him. Perhaps he could make one last move, using the last of his life to give one final contribution to the team.

Qiao Yifan didn't lose hope. The little remaining health left ignited his little hope. He didn't know if there would be an opening, but if an opening came, he would be ready.

6%...

There was only a sliver of hope left. But when everyone saw Cruel Silence's attack, they fell into despair.

Level 75 skill: Rend!

Wu Qi erased that final sliver of hope. Rend was only a single skill, but everyone knew that Assassins had five Level 75 skills: Rend, Kill, Dodge, Flash, Exterminate. When these five skills were used in sequence, they would deal an enormous amount of additional damage.

One Inch Ash only had 6% of his health left. Was that additional damage necessary? Just two of the five skills would be enough to erase One Inch Ash.

Nevertheless, Wu Qi still began with the first move in the set, Rend. He didn't relax his guard even in these final moments. He was going to extinguish One Inch Ash's life along with what little hope remained.

Rend!

Cruel Silent twisted his body, and a cold light flew from his dagger. Wu Qi checked his surroundings, making sure that there was no danger around him. He also made plans for what he should do after One Inch Ash was dead.

He saw Ye Xiu's Lord Grim trying somewhat desperately to rush back under Cloud Piercer's pursuit.

It's too late for him.

Wu Qi thought to himself. Even a long-ranged attack wouldn't be able to stop him from killing One Inch Ash. Rend, Kill, Dodge, Flash, Exterminate. Only two of the five needed to hit.

But Lord Grim didn't attack Cruel Silence. Lord Grim extended his left hand, making a beckoning gesture with his index finger.

Wu Qi was stunned...

There was a lot of freedom in Glory, but it wasn't to the point where you could move your fingers however you liked. This type of movement was a skill, a Knight skill.

Provoke! The target would be Taunted for three seconds.

"Fuck!" Wu Qi cursed out loud.

Ye Xiu unexpectedly used Provoke at this critical moment.　　

And so, "Rend" took an abrupt turn in midair. This sort of sudden change couldn't be accomplished through inputs from the user. The system needed to force it to happen. Of course, with the distance between the two characters, it wasn't like the dagger would suddenly start flying towards Lord Grim's face, even if Wu Qi really wished that was how it worked.

The "Rend" ended up hitting nothing but air, air in Lord Grim's direction. It was obvious what would happen next.

Then, Cruel Silence began to involuntarily move towards Lord Grim.

Assassination interrupted.

A three second opening. Health remaining, 6%.

Everyone was dumbfounded. When all hope seemed to be lost, a turning point appeared?

Right when Cruel Silence turned his body, One Inch Ash also turned in the same direction. Sword light flashed. A Ghost Slash flew towards Cruel Silence.

Then, cast!　

He didn't run. He didn't hide.

6% health was just too little health. Without a healer, a nearly dead character would actually make it harder for the team because of the need to protect him.

Qiao Yifan didn't plan on having One Inch Ash survive for any longer. He was going to use his final moment to provide one last bit of support for his team. He instantly figured out how he could help Happy for what was to come after his death.

The ghost god's power gathered around his sword at an extremely fast speed. This didn't seem to be a high-level ghost boundary. For his final act, he was going to place down a... Sword Boundary?

Increased Strength and Intelligence for all allies inside the ghost boundary. It was a skill that had no crowd control effects.

Had Qiao Yifan been afraid that there wouldn't be enough time for One Inch Ash to cast a longer spell? Was that why he used his fastest ghost boundary, Sword Boundary?

That was what many people thought, even quite a few of the pro players. After all, the logic was quite sound. After Samsara's Cruel Silence was Taunted away, the others immediately turned on One Inch Ash. They didn't want this Phantom Demon to run amok and give them any more trouble.

One Autumn Leaf charged over.

Cloud Piercer's bullets flew towards One Inch Ash.

Not only did they want to finish off One Inch Ash, they wanted to stop him from casting any ghost boundaries.

But One Inch Ash casted a Sword Boundary, which only took a single breath to complete. The two weren't able to stop him in time.

As a result, it looked like Qiao Yifan had chosen Sword Boundary instead of any other ghost boundary because he was afraid of getting interrupted.

But those at a higher skill level saw things from a different perspective.

One Autumn Leaf and Cloud Piercer were able to react so quickly and smoothly because Happy let them.

As soon as the the two turned towards One Inch Ash, what did Soft Mist and Lord Grim do?　

Soft Mist and Lord Grim also turned!

Their target was Moon Luring Frost, and the Sword Boundary was placed right on top of Moon Luring Frost.

A trade!

That was what many people realized.

Du Ming's Moon Luring Frost had been holding off Dancing Rain's heavy artillery fire. His performance was shocking, but he had taken a considerable amount of damage as a result.

Qiao Yifan's One Autumn Leaf was already on the verge of death. Without a healer, Happy didn't try and protect him too excessively. An opening appeared, and One Inch Ash seized it. Samsara shifted their focus towards One Inch Ash, while Happy shifted their focus towards Moon Luring Frost.

One Inch Ash only had 6% of his health remaining. Even though they didn't know how much health Moon Luring Frost had, he should at least have over half his health.

Could Happy complete this trade? Many people were doubtful.

But soon, everyone took notice of Happy's formation.

Had their intent to trade One Inch Ash for Moon Luring Frost a plan devised in the spur of the moment?

No!　　

Soft Mist and Lord Grim rushed towards him. The two formed a perfect pincer. This play had clearly been premeditated. 　

Dancing Rain had been attacking Moon Luring Frost relentlessly in preparation for this play. If she could get past him, then she could help rescue One Inch Ash. Moon Luring Frost refusing to let up was somewhat surprising, but because of this, Happy was able to come up with the plan to switch focus to Moon Luring Frost.

Qiao Yifan was clear about his team's intentions. As a result, his final act was to provide the most brilliant support he could bring.

The DPS buff from Sword Boundary was only one portion.

He had placed down a ghost boundary that wouldn't be interrupted by the enemy side so that he could buy himself some time. Then, he had One Inch Ash run away.

With only 6% of his health left, he would feel like a burden if his own team tried to protect him. But if his own team left him to die, then his existence became a burden for the enemy team.

Samsara couldn't send out their full support for Du Ming because they needed to split their forces to finish off One Inch Ash...

Chapter 1708 - Reward for Perseverance

The situation was laid bare for Samsara to see. How would they respond?

They had to chase after One Inch Ash. Just because he only had 6% of his health left didn't mean that he was no threat. If they let him go free and he placed down a few ghost boundaries, the situation would take a turn for the worse.

But if they gave chase, how many people did they need to send after him?

One? Two? If they sent too many, what would happen to Moon Luring Frost? They couldn't let Happy complete this trade. A character with 6% health for a character with more than 50%? That trade was too lopsided.

They had no time to carefully analyze the situation. During the small window when One Autumn Leaf and Cloud Piercer shifted their focus to One Inch Ash, Soft Mist and Lord Grim were about to reach Moon Luring Frost.

No matter how fierce Du Ming may be, this time, he didn't dare face them directly. But Happy had made ample preparations for this play. Tang Rou and Ye Xiu sent attacks to help One Inch Ash and to pressure Moon Luring Frost.

The turn onto Moon Luring Frost looked as smooth as butter. In an instant, the two formed a pincer, trapping the retreating Moon Luring Frost.

Mounted Gun!

Satellite Beam!　　

Su Mucheng was as decisive as always. As soon as she saw Ye Xiu and Tang Rou surround Moon Luring Frost, she immediately used her high-level skills, sending out her most powerful attacks. With Ye Xiu and Tang Rou blocking him, where was Du Ming going to escape to? Moon Luring Frost was engulfed by the Satellite Beam.

Against this sort of encirclement, no matter how amazing Du Ming might be playing, there was no way he could escape on his own. He needed help.

The closest to him was Jiang Botao's Empty Waves.

When Cruel Silence had been Taunted away, when Zhou Zekai and Sun Xiang tried to interrupt One Inch Ash, Jiang Botao remained calm and collected. He didn't think that Samsara needed to pursue an almost dead enemy with full force. He stayed at his position and continued what he was doing. And now, Moon Luring Frost was closest to him. Helping him was quite convenient. His wave slashes would easily reach that side of the battle.

But what about the enemy he was facing?

Jiang Botao had been enduring Steamed Bun's harassment for this entire time.

Yes, endure.

To Jiang Botao, this was the word that best described his situation.

In the deciding match of the finals, you needed to be cautious and steady. But Steamed Bun didn't seem to know what these two words meant. He was the same as ever, erratic and impossible to predict. Neither thinking too deeply nor acting too shallowly was appropriate. Samsara had already suffered from making these mistakes.

Steamed Bun was reckless. To Jiang Botao, it was a form of extreme provocation. A few times, Jiang Botao had to restrain himself from fiercely retaliating.

But...

Cautious! Steady!

For the sake of the big picture, he didn't dare be hasty, especially against Steamed Bun. Being careful against him would never be wrong. Keeping him suppressed and preventing him from disturbing the other parts of the battle was Jiang Botao's mission. Otherwise, once this guy went wild, who knew if he would harm them or harm his own team. For this deciding match, Happy put their double-edged sword out on display. Perhaps their intentions were to win by banking on his randomness.

Jiang Botao saw the change in situation. He didn't need to worry too much about how Qiao Yifan's side would be handled. It shouldn't affect him in any way. But he took on the main burden of rescuing Du Ming. How should he deal with Steamed Bun? That guy was too erratic. Even when he fully focused on him, there were holes. At present, Jiang Botao was suppressing him, but if he had to split his attention to help Du Ming, who knew what that guy would do? Steamed Bun's unpredictability was particularly grievous in these kinds of situations.

How should he handle this?

Jiang Botao thought carefully. A shadow suddenly flashed by him.

He was thinking, but Steamed Bun didn't think!

Ye Xiu, Tang Rou, and Su Mucheng. All three of them were focusing Du Ming's Moon Luring Frost. Steamed Bun Invasion wasn't far from Moon Luring Frost, and he immediately joined in with the crowd.

Fuck!

Jiang Botao didn't think that during this moment of distraction, Steamed Bun would slip away. He had yet to figure out how to handle Steamed Bun, when Steamed Bun made the first move.　

Opening!

Jiang Botao saw numerous openings on Steamed Bun Invasion. This simplified matters. Follow after Steamed Bun Invasion!

Ice Wave Slash!

Steamed Bun Invasion stopped fighting with Empty Waves, giving Jiang Botao all the freedom he wanted. Ice crystals swept forward in pursuit of Steamed Bun Invasion, while also spreading towards Lord Grim and Soft Mist.

Powerful Knee Strike!

Steamed Bun also used a skill. Steamed Bun Invasion launched towards Moon Luring Frost with a Powerful Knee Strike.

There was still some distance between the two characters. If this were a 1v1, Du Ming could have easily dodged it. However, right now, he was under attack in three directions from Lord Grim, Soft Mist, and Dancing Rain. There was no room for him to dodge. The knee strike struck the side of Moon Luring Frost's face. Blood splattered across the ground. It was quite gruesome to look at.

Moon Luring Frost stumbled to the side. Ye Xiu and Tang Rou didn't stop him. The two attacked, keeping pace with his stumble. With this displacement, all of them just happened to dodge Empty Waves' Ice Wave Slash.

A coincidence! This had to be a coincidence!

Ye Xiu and Tang Rou moving along with Moon Luring Frost while also dodging made sense, but Steamed Bun using Powerful Knee Strike to neutralize his Ice Wave Slash? Did that guy even have the brain for such a smart play?

Even though Steamed Bun was unpredictable, from what people saw, most of his unexpected plays leaned on the stupider side. Jiang Botao didn't think that he had thought of so many things with his Powerful Knee Strike.

But whether he had done it on blind luck or not, the Ice Wave Slash missed. Steamed Bun Invasion landed on the ground and followed with a Strangle. His movements were smooth and practiced. In the beginning, when he first started clearing dungeons, Ye Xiu had explained to him that using this skill would increase the entire team's DPS. This concept was rooted deeply in his mind. Even in the finals, as soon as he saw that the team was focusing on a single target, Steamed Bun's first thought was to use this skill to help them.

With the attack buff from Sword Boundary and the defense debuff from Strangle, Moon Luring Frost's health instantly fell by 17% from their combined attacks.

This efficiency made Jiang Botao start to panic a bit. Steamed Bun had a high amount of synergy with the others on Happy. His addition brought a frightening increase in their DPS. With just this single move, who would dare say that he would bring trouble to his own team? He was Happy's DPS insurance.

I have to hurry and bring him away!　　

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Tang Rou... all three were important targets. But right now, Jiang Botao's attention was entirely on Steamed Bun. He noticed how much Happy's DPS increased with his addition.

Fire Wave Slash!　

Empty Waves stepped forward and swung his sword.

Spellblades were mediocre in terms of crowd control. Fire Wave Slash had astonishing knockback though. If it hit a target up close, the knockback would send the target flying away. Even if it didn't, it would at least break Steamed Bun Invasion's Strangle. Fire Wave Slash had a fairly large hit box too. This attack could also hit Lord Grim and Soft Mist.

Boom!

Flames burst forth in the blink of an eye, enveloping Steamed Bun Invasion.　

But Steamed Bun Invasion didn't budge.

Reinforced Iron Bones!

Steamed Bun had unexpectedly activated a Super Armor skill, making it impossible for Steamed Bun Invasion's Strangle to be interrupted by ordinary attacks. As for Lord Grim and Soft Mist, Ye Xiu and Tang Rou easily evaded the Fire Wave Slash. All it did was delay them a bit.

Both attacks had failed to be of any use. Samsara's response towards One Inch Ash had also been revealed.

Samsara had given Qiao Yifan quite the focus. Zhou Zekai and Sun Xiang, the Alliance's new Best Partners, were working together to finish off One Inch Ash.　　

Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf closed in, while Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer sealed away One Inch Ash's escape routes. The two wanted to eliminate Qiao Yifan as fast as possible.

Qiao Yifan knew that he wouldn't be able to escape, but he also knew that his current attempt at escaping was a chain, holding back Samsara. If he could last even a second longer, it would be a huge help to his team.

His efforts weren't being wasted at all. Qiao Yifan was glad. Previously, when he had been chased by Cruel Silence, he hadn't given up. He had tried everything he could to survive, carefully observing everything around him, seeing which terrain he could take advantage of.

However, Cruel Silence had stuck to him tightly. Nothing he tried worked. He wasn't able to make anything out of the terrain that he noticed.

But right now, he was being pursued by different enemies for a different purpose. The combined forces of Zhou Zekai and Sun Xiang were much greater than Wu Qi alone. However, One Autumn Leaf was still closing on him. He hadn't reached him yet. Cloud Piercer was long-ranged. Even though their offense was extremely fast, Qiao Yifan's response was even faster than theirs.

Because he hadn't given up when Wu Qi had been chasing him. Because he had always been searching for an opportunity to escape. He hadn't been able to break free from Wu Qi, but what he observed gave him the information he needed to instantly come up with a plan against Samsara's new pursuit.

He used the terrain, turned, rolled...　　

Against the Best Partners on Samsara, the 6% health One Inch Ash was able to survive for 6 seconds.　　

6 seconds sounded like nothing, but it was the reward for Qiao Yifan's previous efforts. Six seconds, One Inch Ash had fallen. Six seconds, Moon Luring Frost was on the brink of death.

Cloud Piercer and One Autumn Leaf turned fire.

Jiang Botao had been trying his hardest the entire time. Wu Qi's Cruel Silence had rushed over as well.

But Steamed Bun Invasion and Lord Grim had activated Reinforced Iron Bones. The six seconds that Qiao Yifan had gained for his team was put to good use.

Moon Luring Frost fell.

Chapter 1709 - Initiative

Trade, another trade.

Before, it was a trade between healers. The fight had been fierce and shocking to watch. This time, the trade was more ordinary. However, what everyone saw was a trade that shouldn’t have happened when Samsara should have had the advantage.

Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash had barely 6% of his health left, while Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost had over 50%. At that time, who would have thought a trade was even possible?

When Wu Qi used a high-level skill as his finishing move, everyone thought that Samsara would be up a player.

But a reversal happened during the next six seconds.

Cruel Silence was Taunted away. One Inch Ash placed down a Sword Boundary and then ran for his life. Cloud Piercer and One Autumn Leaf turned on One Inch Ash, while Lord Grim and Soft Mist turned on Moon Luring Frost.

Happy’s plan to trade players was laid bare, but how many people actually thought that Happy would succeed?

Yet Happy succeeded.

Wasn’t this somewhat similar to that healer trade? An Wenyi’s task had been to stop Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer. Little Cold Hands’ health had plummeted like a faucet turned on. As for Samsara’s Fang Minghua and his Laughing Song? Happy put in an enormous amount of effort, successfully executing a highly difficult coordinated play, to evade Samsara’s rescue attempts and complete the trade. At that time, everyone thought that the chances of Laughing Song getting rescued and Little Cold Hands getting killed was much higher.

Little Cold Hands was the first to be killed, and Samsara had a good chance of rescuing Laughing Song.

But they were only off by a bit.

If that place wasn’t a support zone, if Happy’s Steamed Bun Invasion had been just a bit slower, if Steamed Bun’s crazy Sand Toss hadn’t happened…

If not for those, Laughing Song might not have been killed. However, it had all happened. Laughing Song died, and both sides lost their healer.

Last time, Samsara had been off by just a bit, and this time? The same story!

If Ye Xiu’s Provoke hadn’t been so timely, if Steamed Bun hadn’t turned on Moon Luring Frost so quickly, if there had an opening in Lord Grim’s and Soft Mist’s encirclement, if Qiao Yifan hadn’t stalled for that extra second…

It felt as if Samsara was taking large strides ahead, while Happy was making quick little steps from behind and teetering on the verge of collapse. However, in the end, they were able to follow close behind.

Samsara had the upper hand.

Four of them had been caught in a trap and blinded at the very start, but they were able to make it through that predicament. Samsara had two huge opportunities to take the lead.

Yet everyone felt like Happy was winning.

Because Samsara failed to grasp these two huge opportunities. Despite the challenges, Happy had caught up through quick little steps and successfully clawed their way back.

It was even again, a 4v4.

From the health on both sides, Happy was still a bit behind. They had narrowly escaped two crises. It wasn’t possible to not have paid a price. However, everyone still felt like Happy had the advantage.

Group arena.

Happy had won the group arena with a one point lead. The battle looked even, but in reality, Happy was leading. If they kept trading and trading until both sides perished, the winner would be Happy.

Was this Happy’s strategy? Was this Happy’s plan?

That was what many of the viewers thought because Happy had been extremely decisive with both trades. The sacrificed players were aware of their role, and the other players didn’t hesitate to abandon them.

Then, who would Happy go for next?

Cruel Silence?

Cruel Silence was the closest to the three on Happy that had killed Moon Luring Frost. He was the most convenient target.

Sure enough!

As soon as Moon Luring Frost fell, before his corpse even stopped moving, Happy immediately turned. The three moved to surround Cruel Silence. Attacks flew his way.

Cruel Silence was ripped into shreds.

Shadow Clone Technique!

The one to get attacked was Cruel Silence’s shadow clone. Wu Qi didn’t lack vigilance. As soon as he saw that Moon Luring Frost’s death was certain, he immediately realized who Happy’s next target would be. He had seen Happy’s offensive prowess for himself. Cruel Silence was a feeble Assassin. Wu Qi didn’t dare to fight them. He immediately used Shadow Clone Technique to escape.

How close…

Seeing the Shadow Clone Technique get destroyed in an instant, Wu Qi felt glad. If he had been slightly less careful, if he had tried to run away normally without Shadow Clone Technique, he wouldn’t have been able to escape unharmed.

“Behind”

A warning came from the team chat. Wu Qi saw it, and saw Soft Mist suddenly vanish. Traces of magic were left behind. Lord Grim was broken apart by Cloud Piercer’s bullets.

Teleport!

Shadow Clone Technique!

The two on Happy reacted extraordinarily fast. In the blink of an eye, they chased after Wu Qi.

Behind!

Wu Qi had received the warning. There was no time for him to look back. Cruel Silence immediately jumped forward and rolled! Who knew what was coming at him from behind. However, in front of him, there was Steamed Bun Invasion, holding a Brick in one hand and making a fist with the other. Who knew what he would do. Sure, he could see the Brick in his hand, and he was clearly about to throw it. But what if he suddenly cancelled the Brick and threw a handful of sand at him with the other hand?

Shattering the Lands!

Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf finally arrived. He saw that Cruel Silence was surrounded, and no matter which side he attacked, he wouldn’t be able to completely lift the siege. In that case, he might as well just use a high-level skill. It didn’t matter who he hit. The important part was that Happy had to dodge the AoE from Shattering the Lands. The AoE effect was similar to how enemies would circle around a ghost boundary.

Wu Qi understood tacitly. He immediately adjusted Cruel Silence’s movements to draw close to Shattering the Land’s AoE.

Magic swept the ruins. Sure enough, the three on Happy had to dodge. If they wanted to surround Samsara again, then they wouldn’t only be facing Cruel Silence, but One Autumn Leaf as well.

A single high-level skill broke apart Happy’s encirclement. Samsara took this opportunity to begin their counterattack.

“Bun!” A message in Samsara’s chat.

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain was quite far away. Ye Xiu and Tang Rou were together. Although Steamed Bun’s Steamed Bun Invasion could quickly receive help from either side, he was clearly the easier target. As a result, he became Samsara’s breakthrough point. Jiang Botao confirmed it with everyone to avoid any miscommunication.

But as soon as he sent the message, he saw Steamed Bun Invasion charge towards his Empty Waves.

This guy’s acting reckless again!

Jiang Botao thought to himself. He had Empty Waves take a step forward, but then, he discovered that it wasn’t just Steamed Bun Invasion charging towards him, but Lord Grim and Soft Mist as well.

Happy had set their sights on his Empty Waves as the next target.

Jiang Botao didn’t panic. The situation on both sides was fairly even. Neither side had a clear advantage, so they were both looking for opportunities to take the initiative. He calmly paid attention to their attack routes, while also keeping wary of Dancing Rain’s distance from him. He retracted his step and jumped back, while swinging his sword.

Waltzing Wave Slash!

Wind Wave Slash!

Light Wave Slash!

Three consecutive wave slashes. Light and Wind were the fastest of the wave slashes. The two slashes intertwined together, and instantly caught up to the Waltzing Wave Slash. The two slashes gave off a shining light that covered the radiance from Waltzing Wave Slash. Amidst these two fast attacks was a venomous fang. Jiang Botao’s three wave slashes had been carefully set up. He also knew who this Waltzing Wave Slash would end up flying towards. He already had a follow-up in his mind. Suddenly, a shadow drew near. A triple wave slash play? Too slow!

Lord Grim.

Too decisive, too fast.

Jiang Botao’s careful calculations and precise timing were smashed with brute force, making it all seem superfluous.

He turned simple into complex, while Ye Xiu turned complex into simple. He had set up layers of calculations, while Ye Xiu used just a single word “fast” to pierce through them all.

This time, Jiang Botao panicked. He had thrown out three wave slashes, but he hadn’t expected the other side to act before he did. It suddenly felt like he had no tools left to use. The follow-up he had ready was still on cooldown!

Earthquake Slash!

Helpless, he could only retreat, while immediately using a low-level skill to try and stop Ye Xiu. But Lord Grim simply leaned to the side, moving even faster than his Earth Wave Slash. The Earth Wave Slash missed, and Lord Grim was getting even closer.

Sword Draw!

Jiang Botao wanted to act again, but Lord Grim instantly drew his sword. The sword light collided against Empty Waves’ Divine Chains, interrupting Jiang Botao’s next wave slash.

Collapsing Mountain!

Lord Grim leapt into the air. His Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was like an axe as it descended.

Too hasty!

Jiang Botao was delighted. Lord Grim’s offense was too excessive, giving him an opportunity to react. Empty Waves dodged to the side and raised his Divine Chains into the air again.

Wave Wheel Slasher!

This skill could even break Super Armor. Neutralizing a Collapsing Mountain wouldn’t be a problem. However, the instant the wave wheel formed, Lord Grim suddenly retracted his heroic Collapsing Mountain.

Falling Light Blade! Lord Grim suddenly turned in the air.

A trap!

Jiang Botao immediately realized. The Collapsing Mountain had been bait. Wave Wheel Slasher had extremely high priority, posing a huge wall to an opponent’s offense. Ye Xiu intentionally acted a bit hasty to bait Jiang Botao into using Wave Wheel Slasher. Then, he would avoid it and close in without worry.

Moreover, powerful skills like Wave Wheel Slasher had longer ending lag. For an attacker, this was a huge opening!

Chapter 1710 - Because He Was Close

If there were no opportunities, then create one yourself.

Jiang Botao had realized it, but he was too late. It couldn’t be said that he had been careless. Ye Xiu’s offense looked to be hasty to him, but it had been very subtle. Jiang Botao had noticed the flaw because of his sharp senses. A normal player or even many pro players might not have sensed anything awry with the Collapsing Mountain.

This was one of Jiang Botao’s strengths, but this time, it became his bane. He had noticed this hastiness, but he had been too sensitive.

Jiang Botao didn’t think the Collapsing Mountain into Falling Light Blade was a difficult sequence to execute. Anyone who was familiar with the technique could do it. However, Jiang Botao hadn’t been ready for the subtlety in Lord Grim’s movements, nor did he think his wave slashes could be dodged.

This was a bait specifically targeting him. The bait didn’t target his flaws, but rather his strengths.

If his skill level wasn’t high enough, he would have likely just dodged the Collapsing Mountain like others would. But because he was so skilled, he saw a small flaw in the Collapsing Mountain, and used Wave Wheel Slasher to take advantage of this opening. Unfortunately, it was all a trap that left him open.

Cancel Wave Wheel Slasher!

When Jiang Botao realized that he had fallen for a trap, he immediately cancelled the skill. However, it didn’t matter how fast he was. The ending lag from Wave Wheel Slasher was an opening, and cancelling the skill was an opening too. Lord Grim had already dodged the Wave Wheel Slasher. Whether or not the skill was cancelled was no longer a concern to Ye Xiu because he was fast enough. Lord Grim’s attack was fast enough!

Falling Light Blade fell.

No one knew if Jiang Botao was able to finish cancelling the skill. The shockwave from Falling Light Blade swept by Empty Waves’ feet, launching him into the air.

Sky Strike!

Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into a spear. With a flick, it struck Empty Waves, and sent him even higher into the air.

Slash!

Empty Waves swung his sword. This was how a pro player should react: defend against the enemy’s attacks.

Unfortunately, Lord Grim wasn’t the only one attacking him. Furthermore, Lord Grim wasn’t someone that could be put to a stop with a swing of a sword. Lord Grim dodged the sword slash. At the same time, his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into its gun form. Three Anti-Tank Missiles fired out, keeping Empty Waves tumbling in the air. Steamed Bun Invasion threw out a few mid-ranged attacks as well: Poison Needle, Brick, Molotov Cocktail.

It wasn’t easy to control an airborne character. With the Anti-Tank Missiles keeping him tumbling, Jiang Botao wasn’t able to dodge even a single one of Steamed Bun Invasion’s projectiles.

Falling Light Blade!

In the end, Jiang Botao wasn’t someone easily shaken. After waiting out this wave of attacks, he immediately tried to escape. Empty Waves crashed towards the ground. Suddenly, a wave of sword light flashed by his eyes. A familiar sight.

Wave Wheel Slasher!

The skill, which he had just used and been forced to cancel, was put to use by Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. There was no time for Jiang Botao to react. He was hit!

Empty Waves was held in the air by the rotating waves. At this moment, his teammates, One Autumn Leaf, Cruel Silence, and Cloud Piercer finally arrived.

Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike!

Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf took a stance. The magic bursting forth from his spear, Evil Annihilation, blossomed like a shooting star. The three players on Happy, who were close to Empty Waves, were engulfed by the countless meteor strikes. At the same time, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer activated Rapid Firing. His bullets rained down, complementing the Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike.

The crowd went wild.

While the connoisseur enjoys the artistry, the layman enjoys the show.

Zhou Zekai and Sun Xiang, the newly crowned Best Partners, had worked together multiple times over the course of this match, yet they had never reached this level of “hype.” And this time, the two had put out a beautiful display of teamwork. Everyone could immediately feel the exquisiteness of their coordination. Cheers echoed throughout the stadium. It was as if this play would wipe out the entirety of Team Happy.

Their combined attack was indeed powerful.

There was no flaw in their attack. The three on Happy were forced to retreat.

However, Happy didn’t only have three people. Samsara had given Su Mucheng complete freedom, though it would perhaps more accurate to note that it wasn’t out of choice. Dancing Rain raised her handcannon. An enormous amount of energy began to condense around it.

Hurricane Cannon!

A Level 75 skill, guaranteeing the might of the attack. If the attack dealt little damage, then it would certainly have a powerful effect.

Hurricane Cannon had both. Because of its power, its start-up time was rather troublesome. The energy had to be charged up, similar to how a spell needed to be casted.

But there was no one marking Su Mucheng. If she wanted to charge up energy, then she could do so without any worry!

Bang!

The speed of the whirlwind was terrifying. As soon as it fired from the cannon, the surrounding air was swept aside. In the blink of an eye, the Hurricane Cannon arrived at the net formed by Sun Xiang and Zhou Zekai.

Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike?

Rapid Firing?

Neither of the two could stop the Hurricane Cannon. Anything in its path was twisted into oblivion. Only a few remnants of the Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike was left.

One Autumn Leaf had to retreat. The Hurricane Cannon had been aimed at him. The Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike was unable to stop its advance. If he didn’t retreat, he would be blasted away by the Hurricane Cannon.

The enemy retreats, I advance!

Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike!

Happy really seemed to have their hearts set on taking revenge. Jiang Botao had used Wave Wheel Slasher to fend off Ye Xiu, who then dodged it and retaliated with his own Wave Wheel Slasher. The three on Happy were forced back by Sun Xiang’s Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike. Right after the attack was neutralized, Happy returned with their own Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike.

But everyone had to admit that using Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike as a counterattack was indeed an appropriate move choice. Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence had been protected by One Autumn Leaf’s and Cloud Piercer’s net. That guy was indeed an expert at hiding himself by putting on an unassuming presence. While Zhou Zekai and Sun Xiang attacked, he seemed to be doing nothing. But in reality, he had been waiting quietly for the right moment to burst out.

But this time, the opportunity wasn’t ripe yet, when Dancing Rain blasted everything apart with her Hurricane Cannon. Soft Mist’s Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike complemented the blast with a barrage of spear strikes towards Cruel Silence and One Autumn Leaf.

Retreat. This time, Samsara retreated. Cloud Piercer, who was positioned farther away, was outside of the attack’s range. While Sun Xiang and Wu Qi retreated, Zhou Zekai attacked.

Rapid Firing hadn’t ended yet! Bullets quickly converged, focusing on Soft Mist.

Tang Rou had noticed him adjust his firing angle, and immediately had Soft Mist sway to the side to dodge. As she swayed, her control over the Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike became unsteady, and an opening was exposed.

Chance!

Hiding one’s killing intent and waiting for an opportunity were Wu Qi’s strengths. Even while retreating, he searched for possible openings. The moment he saw one, he immediately grabbed onto it.

Forward!

Shining Cut would be too slow. Wu Qi didn’t hold back, making sure that he seized this opportunity.

Teleporting Stab!

An instant three-unit distance teleport. It was far faster than Shining Cut. However, Cruel Silence was more than three units away from Soft Mist. No matter how fast the skill was, it wouldn’t move him far enough.

Flickering Stab!

Wu Qi was aware of this issue. After Teleporting Stab came Flickering Stab. The three steps became four steps.

Wasteful!

Using Teleporting Stab solely as a movement skill was truly rather wasteful. However, if not for Teleporting Stab, how could he launch such a lightning-fast offense? The two skills were chained together perfectly. It was practically impossible to see the transition between the two skills. The Teleporting Stab seemed to suddenly transform into Flickering Stab.

Did he cancel the skill?

The pro players were in a discussion. If he hadn’t cancelled the skill, the transition couldn’t have been so smooth. But if he hadn’t cancelled, then Wu Qi’s hand speed in that instant must have been astonishing. Who knew how many times he had practiced this dual stab technique.

Such skill, such speed, how could it be dodged? Impossible! There was no time to react!

But right before the strike was completed, Cruel Silence suddenly froze.

Paralysis?

Wu Qi was dumbfounded.

Paralysis Needle?

He saw a swaying Steamed Bun Invasion in his view.

Steamed Bun Invasion had stopped such a fast attack? He had actually noticed it and reacted to it in time?

How?

Wu Qi thought it was impossible. If a reporter interviewed Steamed Bun this question right now, Wu Qi would certainly cough blood at the answer.

Because he was close. Steamed Bun would definitely reply back with this answer.

Yes, because he was close.

This was Steamed Bun’s simplistic way of thinking. He had to join the battle. He had to find a target to attack. He had been evaluating who to attack, and wanted to find one which he would pose the biggest threat to.

The closer he was to the target, the bigger of a threat he would be. Although Brawlers had mid-ranged attacks, their main source of damage was from close-ranged attacks.

So the closest target was the easiest for him to attack.

While he had been looking for a target, Wu Qi discovered an opening, and Cruel Silence charged out!

At that moment, Steamed Bun’s eyes lit up.

Wasn’t Cruel Silence the closest target?

So he immediately attacked.

A Paralysis Needle was thrown.

The thin Paralysis Needle was difficult to notice in the first place. Even if Wu Qi had noticed it, Cruel Silence had been moving extremely fast. It would have been a huge test for Wu Qi’s reaction speed.

There was no need to administer the test though. Wu Qi failed to notice the needle.

It was unexpectedly Steamed Bun who interrupted him. This time, he was swift. This time, he had done something intelligent. This time, he had done something that even Ye Xiu hadn’t been able to do.

That was what Wu Qi believed.

But in reality, it wasn’t a reaction. It was simply because he was the closest.